<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7259">radish root</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:11:39" name="Organic Eprints" id="FW14-e012"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e012-7259-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7259_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:11:41">http://orgprints.org/5644/</link><title>Resistenter Ölrettich zur Regulierung von Wurzelgallennematoden im ökologischen Landbau.</title><description>1.

{Project} Resistenter Ölrettich zur Regulierung von Wurzelgallennematoden im ökologischen Landbau. [Use of resistant fodder radish to control root-knot nematodes in organic farming.] Runs 2002 - 2003. Project Leader(s): Hallmann, Dr. Johannes, Biologische Bundesanstalt für Land- und Forstwirtschaft.

Item not publicly available online.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7259-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7259_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:15:42">http://orgprints.org/5414/</link><title>Safe food production on soils contaminated with organochlorine pesticides.</title><description>2.

{Project} Safe food production: Safe food production on soils contaminated with organochlorine pesticides. [See also Eprint-Nr.: 6276.] Runs 2005 - 2008. Project Leader(s): Wyss, Gabriela and Mäder, Paul, Research Institute of Organic Agriculture (FiBL), CH-5070 Frick.

Item not publicly available online.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7259-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7259_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:19:55">http://orgprints.org/7897/</link><title>Growth of legume and nonlegume catch crops and residual-N effects in spring barley on coarse sand.</title><description>3.

Askegaard, M. and Eriksen, E. (2007) Growth of legume and nonlegume catch crops and residual-N effects in spring barley on coarse sand. J. Plant Nutrition and Soil Science, 170, pp. 733-780.

Restricted access</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7259-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7259_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:23:28">http://orgprints.org/7988/</link><title>High densities of Collembola and mites in organic fields with undersown catch crops.</title><description>4.

Axelsen, J.; Thorup-Kristensen, K.; Askegaard, M. and Krogh, P.H. (2006) High densities of Collembola and mites in organic fields with undersown catch crops. . [Submitted]

Restricted access</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7259-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7259_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:24:51">http://orgprints.org/4296/</link><title>Resistenter Ölrettich zur Regulierung von Wurzelgallennematoden im ökologischen Landbau.</title><description>5.

Biologische Bundesanstalt für Land- und Forstwirtschaft, Institut für Nematologie und Wirbeltierkunde (2003) Resistenter Ölrettich zur Regulierung von Wurzelgallennematoden im ökologischen Landbau. [Use of resistant fodder radish to control root-knot nematodes in organic farming.] Bundesanstalt für Landwirtschaft und Ernährung (BLE), Bonn, Geschäftsstelle Bundesprogramm Ökologischer Landbau.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7259-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7259_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:26:51">http://orgprints.org/1776/</link><title>The effect of catch crops on sulphate leaching and availability of S in the succeeding crop.</title><description>6.

Eriksen, J. and Thorup-Kristensen, K. (2003) The effect of catch crops on sulphate leaching and availability of S in the succeeding crop. In: Davidian, J.C.; Grill, D.; De Kok, L.J.; Stulen, H.; Hawkesford, M.J.; Schnug, E. and Rennenberg, H. (Eds.) Sulfur Transport and Assimilation in Plants: Regulation, Interaction and Signaling. Backhuys Publishers, pp. 205-207.

Restricted access</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7259-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7259_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:28:47">http://orgprints.org/210/</link><title>Forbedring af jordkvaliteten efter jordpakning - er løsning løsningen?</title><description>7.

Grossmann, Cand. agro. Freya (2002) Forbedring af jordkvaliteten efter jordpakning - er løsning løsningen? Thesis, KVL, Sektion for Økologisk Jordbrug. DJVB.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7259-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7259_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:31:02">http://orgprints.org/8958/</link><title>Nachhaltige Wirkung von Ölrettich auf die Abundanzdynamik von Wurzelgallennematoden im ökologischen Landbau.</title><description>8.

Hallmann, Johannes and Rau, Florian (2004) Nachhaltige Wirkung von Ölrettich auf die Abundanzdynamik von Wurzelgallennematoden im ökologischen Landbau. [Sustainable effect of fodder radish to the abundance dynamic of northern root-knot nematode Meloidogyne hapla in organic farming.] Biologische Bundesanstalt für Land- und Forstwirtschaft, Institut für Nematologie und Wirbeltierkunde.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7259-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7259_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:32:31">http://orgprints.org/9488/</link><title>Bekämpfungsstrategien für den Wurzelgallennematoden Meloidogyne hapla im Ökologischen Landbau.</title><description>9.

Hallmann, Johannes; Rau, Florian and Puffert, Markus (2007) Bekämpfungsstrategien für den Wurzelgallennematoden Meloidogyne hapla im Ökologischen Landbau. [Control strategies for the root-knot nematode Meloidogyne hapla in organic farming.] Poster at: Zwischen Tradition und Globalisierung - 9. Wissenschaftstagung Ökologischer Landbau, Universität Hohenheim, Stuttgart, Deutschland, 20.-23.03.2007.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7259-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7259_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:32:57">http://orgprints.org/20308/</link><title>Desempenho do consórcio entre repolho e rabanete com pré-cultivo de crotalária, sob manejo orgânico.</title><description>10.

Oliveira, Fábio Luiz de; Ribas, Rodolfo Gustavo T.; Junqueira, Rodrigo M.; Padovan, Milton P.; Guerra, José Guilherme M.; Almeida, Dejair L. de and Ribeiro, Raul de L.Duarte (2005) Desempenho do consórcio entre repolho e rabanete com pré-cultivo de crotalária, sob manejo orgânico. [Performance of cabbage and radish intercropping under organic management.] Horticultura Brasileira, 23 (2), pp. 184-188.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>