<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7265">grassland plants</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:43:15" name="Organic Eprints" id="FW14-e012"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e012-7265-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7265_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:43:26">http://orgprints.org/3599/</link><title>Naturindholdet i hegn på økologiske og konventionelle bedrifter.</title><description>1.

(2003) Naturindholdet i hegn på økologiske og konventionelle bedrifter. no. 89. Proceedings of 1. Danske Plantekongres 2004, Herning, Januar 2004.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7265-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7265_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:47:08">http://orgprints.org/19606/</link><title>Ecosystem Functions and Services of Biodiversity in Grasslands.</title><description>2.

{Project} EcoServe: Ecosystem Functions and Services of Biodiversity in Grasslands. [Økosystem Funktioner og Services af Biodiversitet i Græsmarker.] Runs 2011 - 2013. Project Leader(s): Eriksen, Jøregen.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7265-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7265_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:49:00">http://orgprints.org/13494/</link><title>Endofytiska svampar i vallgräs.</title><description>3.

{Project} Endofytiska svampar i vallgräs. Runs 0007 - 0009. Project Leader(s): Huss-Danell, Kerstin.

Item not publicly available online.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7265-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7265_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:50:12">http://orgprints.org/11117/</link><title>Gesundheit und Leistungsfähigkeit von Milchkühen im ökologischen Landbau interdisziplinär betrachtet – eine (Interventions-) Studie zu Stoffwechselstörungen und Eutererkrankungen unter Berücksichtigung von Grundfuttererzeugung, Fütterungsmanagement und Tierhaltung (Verbundvorhaben).</title><description>4.

{Project} Gesundheit und Leistungsfähigkeit von Milchkühen im Ökolandbau: Gesundheit und Leistungsfähigkeit von Milchkühen im ökologischen Landbau interdisziplinär betrachtet – eine (Interventions-) Studie zu Stoffwechselstörungen und Eutererkrankungen unter Berücksichtigung von Grundfuttererzeugung, Fütterungsmanagement und Tierhaltung (Verbundvorhaben). [Health and performance of dairy cows in organic farming from an interdisciplinary point of view – an (intervention-) study on metabolic disorders and mastitis with regard to forage production, feeding management and husbandry practices.] Runs 2007 - 2010. Project Leader(s): Barth, Dr. Kerstin, Bundesforschungsanstalt für Landwirtschaft (FAL), D-Westerau.

Item not publicly available online.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7265-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7265_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:51:09">http://orgprints.org/7281/</link><title>Kolbalanser i det ekologiska lantbruket.</title><description>5.

{Project} Kolbalanser i det ekologiska lantbruket. [Carbon balances in organic agriculture.] Runs 2002 - 2004. Project Leader(s): Kätter, Thomas, Swedish University of Agricultural Sciences, SLU.

Item not publicly available online.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7265-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7265_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:52:39">http://orgprints.org/7286/</link><title>Kvantifiering av mineralvittringens bidrag till grödornas kaliumförsörjning på olika typer av jordbruksmark.</title><description>6.

{Project} Kvantifiering av mineralvittringens bidrag till grödornas kaliumförsörjning på olika typer av jordbruksmark. [Cycling of plant nutrients, quantification of the contribution of mineral weathering to the supply of potassium to plants on different types of agricultural land.] Runs 2002 - 2004. Project Leader(s): Öborn, Ingrid, Swedish University of Agricultural Sciences, SLU.

Item not publicly available online.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7265-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7265_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:57:31">http://orgprints.org/7052/</link><title>Organic cropping systems for higher and more stable cereal yields.</title><description>7.

{Project} ØKOKORNSIP: Organic cropping systems for higher and more stable cereal yields. [Økologiske dyrkingssystem for høgare og meir stabile kornavlingar.] Runs 2003 - 2007. Project Leader(s): Eltun, Ragnar, Bioforsk Norwegian Institute of Agronomical and Environmental Research.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7265-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7265_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:02:03">http://orgprints.org/24374/</link><title>Rolle des Phosphors als Steuerungsgröße des Stickstoffertrages und der Phytodiversität ökologisch bewirtschafteter Dauergrünlandbestände.</title><description>8.

{Project} PhosphorusLegumesDiversity: Rolle des Phosphors als Steuerungsgröße des Stickstoffertrages und der Phytodiversität ökologisch bewirtschafteter Dauergrünlandbestände. [Role of phosphorus as a key component for managing grasslands N-yield and phytodiversity in organic farming.] Runs 2013 - 2016. Project Leader(s): Müller, Dr. agr. Jürgen, Universität Rostock, Agrar- und Umweltwissenschaftliche Fakultät, D-Rostock.

Item not publicly available online.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7265-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7265_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:05:24">http://orgprints.org/7276/</link><title>Samverkan mellan mångformig djurhållning och lokal foderproduktion.</title><description>9.

{Project} Samverkan mellan mångformig djurhållning och lokal foderproduktion. [The synergy of diverse animal husbandry and local feed cropping.] Runs 2002 - 2004. Project Leader(s): Ciszuk, Paul, Swedish University of Agricultural Sciences, SLU.

Item not publicly available online.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7265-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7265_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:09:11">http://orgprints.org/2609/</link><title>Universität Kiel - Institut für Pflanzenbau und Pflanzenzüchtung.</title><description>10.

{Organization} Universität Kiel - Institut für Pflanzenbau und Pflanzenzüchtung. [University of Kiel - Institute of Crop Science and Plant Breeding.]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>