<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7451">buy animal farm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:09:23" name="Organic Eprints" id="FW14-e012"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e012-7451-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7451_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:09:26">http://orgprints.org/2679/</link><title>Socio-economic aspects of animal health and food safety in organic farming systems.</title><description>1.

Hovi, Malla; Martini, Andrea and Padel, Susanne (Eds.) (2003) Socio-economic aspects of animal health and food safety in organic farming systems. The University of Reading / Concerted Action: Sustaining Animal Health and Food Safety in Organic Farming. Proceedings of the 1st SAFO Workshop, Florence, Italy, 5-7 September 2003. [Unpublished]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7451-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7451_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:11:02">http://orgprints.org/10858/</link><title>Organic Food: Understanding the consumer and increasing sales.</title><description>2.

Anon, (2004) Organic Food: Understanding the consumer and increasing sales. Soil Association.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7451-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7451_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:14:11">http://orgprints.org/22310/</link><title>Entwicklung eines Konzepts zur Vermarktung von Öko-Ziegenlammfleisch aus melkenden Betrieben.</title><description>3.

Heid, Astrid and Hamm, Ulrich (2012) Entwicklung eines Konzepts zur Vermarktung von Öko-Ziegenlammfleisch aus melkenden Betrieben. [Development of a marketing concept for organic goat meat from dairy goat farms.] Universität Kassel, Fachbereich Ökologische Agrarwissenschaften, D-Witzenhausen, Fachgebiet Agrar- und Lebensmittelmarketing.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7451-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7451_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:18:20">http://orgprints.org/11000/</link><title>Consumer attitudes in North-west England to organic and regional food.</title><description>4.

Padel, S (2004) Consumer attitudes in North-west England to organic and regional food. In: Hopkins, A (Ed.) Organic farming: science and practice for profitable livestock and cropping. Occasional Symposium of the British Grassland Society, British Grassland Society (37), pp. 35-38.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7451-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7451_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:19:41">http://orgprints.org/434/</link><title>Reducing risks from E. coli 0157 on the organic farm.</title><description>5.

Patriquin, David G. (2000) Reducing risks from E. coli 0157 on the organic farm. Eco-Farm &amp; Garden, 2000, Summer.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7451-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7451_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:21:41">http://orgprints.org/10653/</link><title>Organic Marketing Initiatives and Rural Development.</title><description>6.

Schmid, Otto; Sanders, Juern and Midmore, Peter (2004) Organic Marketing Initiatives and Rural Development. OMIARD Reports, no. 7. School of Management and Business, University of Wales, Aberystwyth.

Restricted access</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7451-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7451_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:23:22">http://orgprints.org/4733/</link><title>Overview of international organic market development and potential export markets for organic products of Ukraine.</title><description>7.

Schneider, Monika; Richter, Toralf; Spahn, Christoph and Portmann, Katrin (2005) Overview of international organic market development and potential export markets for organic products of Ukraine. FiBL Project Report. Research Institute of Organic Agriculture (FiBL).</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7451-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7451_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:25:51">http://orgprints.org/2710/</link><title>Dairy farms: constraints and recommendations for enhancing health, welfare and food saftey (Workshop results).</title><description>8.

Smolders, G.; Walkenhorst, Michael and Padel, S. (2003) Dairy farms: constraints and recommendations for enhancing health, welfare and food saftey (Workshop results). In: Hovi, M.; Martini, A. and Padel, S. (Eds.) Socio-economic aspects of animal health and food safety in organic farming systems. Proceedings of the 1st SAFO Workshop. 5.-7. September 2003, Florence, Italy. SAFO Sustaining Animal Health and Food Safety in Organic Farming. A European Commission funded Concerted Action Project, pp. 91-93.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7451-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7451_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:28:28">http://orgprints.org/7500/</link><title>Feed production on farms without animals is not environmentally sustainable.</title><description>9.

Steinshamn, Håvard; Bleken, Marina A and Thuen, Erling (2006) Feed production on farms without animals is not environmentally sustainable. Paper at: Joint Organic Congress, Odense, Denmark, May 30-31, 2006.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e012-7451-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e012/7451_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:31:53">http://orgprints.org/25127/</link><title>“Healthy food” from healthy cows.</title><description>10.

Sundrum, Albert (2012) “Healthy food” from healthy cows. In: Konvalina, Petr (Ed.) Organic Farming and Food Production. InTech Book, Rijeka, chapter 5, pp. 95-120.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>