<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7031">Thomas test</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:21:32" name="LinkedIn Blog" id="FW14-e024"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e024-7031-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7031_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:21:33">http://blog.linkedin.com/2011/10/28/thomas-friedman/</link><title>Speaker Series: Thomas Friedman on his new book “That Used to Be Us”</title><description>* Jagan Bhamidipati

Speaker Series: Thomas Friedman on his new book “That Used to Be Us” Jagan Bhamidipati October 28, 2011

Ed. note: New York Times Columnist and renowned author, Thomas Friedman, made his second appearance at our LinkedIn Speaker series this past week. Here are some personal thoughts from Jagan, one of our colleagues who attended the event, as he recaps Tom’s presentation.   One of the truly great things about working at LinkedIn is being able to interact with some of the world’s most transformational thinkers who visit us during the LinkedIn Speaker Series. Last week…

* Topics:
* LinkedIn Speaker Series</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7031_01_thumb.jpg">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/3d2d1c1.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7031-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7031_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:25:47">http://blog.linkedin.com/2009/08/14/thomas-merlino-how-linkedin-helps-small-businesses-grow/</link><title>Win new clients by optimizing your LinkedIn profile keywords</title><description>* Guest Author

Win new clients by optimizing your LinkedIn profile keywords Guest Author August 14, 2009

This is part of our success story series where LinkedIn users share their best practices on using LinkedIn more effectively to advance their career or business. Today’s user story comes from Thomas Merlino, small business owner at InControl Technical, who discovered how LinkedIn could help his small business grow outside of where he lived. How I used LinkedIn as a beginner Never underestimate the power of social networking.  When I first signed up for a LinkedIn account, it was…

* Topics:
* LinkedIn Tips, 
* Profile</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7031_02_thumb.png">http://1.gravatar.com/avatar/1a38af3c28616b8a469d4b1e93016feb?s=72&amp;d=http%3A%2F%2F1.gravatar.com%2Favatar%2Fad516503a11cd5ca435acc9bb6523536%3Fs%3D72&amp;r=G</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7031-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7031_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:29:18">http://blog.linkedin.com/2007/10/22/linkedin-qa-eve-2/</link><title>LinkedIn Q&amp;A Event | Real Guy Kawasaki interviews Fake Steve Jobs</title><description>* Mario Sundar

LinkedIn Q&amp;A Event | Real Guy Kawasaki interviews Fake Steve Jobs Mario Sundar October 22, 2007

Have you ever wondered what goes in the mind of Fake Steve Jobs? On November 6th, LinkedIn will be hosting a live Q&amp;A session with senior editor at Forbes and popular tech blogger, Dan Lyons (of “Fake Steve Jobs” fame), which will be moderated by Guy Kawasaki, former Chief Evangelist at Apple and co-founder at Truemors (with questions from LinkedIn users). (from l – r: Dan Lyons and Guy Kawasaki | Source: Hyku) Further details below: * LinkedIn Q&amp;A Event |…

* Topics:
* Events</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7031_03_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/05/mariosundar.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>