<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7044">song of ice and fire</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:52:13" name="LinkedIn Blog" id="FW14-e024"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e024-7044-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7044_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:52:14">http://blog.linkedin.com/2013/07/31/a-linkedin-intern-tradition-flash-mobbing-the-company-all-hands/</link><title>A LinkedIn Intern Tradition: Flash Mobbing the Company All-Hands [VIDEO]</title><description>* A LinkedIn Intern Tradition: Flash Mobbing the Company All-Hands [VIDEO] Doris Tong July 31, 2013

It’s become tradition for each intern class at LinkedIn to put on a surprise performance during one of our bi-weekly All-Hands meetings. In 2010 our interns kicked off the now tradition with a rap. In 2011 they said sorry for party rocking by interrupting our CEO with a flash mob dance. In 2012 the interns set the world on fire with a one of kind rendition of We Are Young. And this year things went global, with our interns kicking off a 3-minute choreographed song-and-dance medley…

* Topics:
* Intern, 
* Life at LinkedIn, 
* Work at LinkedIn</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7044_01_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/themes/linkedin/images/transparent-fillin.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7044-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7044_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:54:24">http://blog.linkedin.com/2013/12/13/linkedins-got-talent-2013/</link><title>LinkedIn’s Got Talent: Two LinkedIn Employees Take on the Music Business</title><description>* LinkedIn’s Got Talent: Two LinkedIn Employees Take on the Music Business Dan Shapero December 13, 2013

From neurosurgeons turned data scientists to Olympic-caliber marathon runners, LinkedIn attracts a diverse group of uniquely talented employees. But what we saw on-stage at our first annual “LinkedIn’s Got Talent” Competition this year blew us away. Up against several strong employee musical acts, Jennie Cini and Tim McCarthy, members of the LinkedIn Marketing Solutions team in New York City, stole the show with their soulful performance of Bonnie Bishop and Al Anderson’s…

* Topics:
* Employee Stories, 
* Life at LinkedIn, 
* Work at LinkedIn</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7044_02_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/themes/linkedin/images/transparent-fillin.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7044-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7044_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:56:28">http://blog.linkedin.com/2012/01/20/top-5-stories-on-linkedin-concern-about-sopa-dominates-the-conversation/</link><title>Top 5 Stories on LinkedIn: Concern About SOPA Dominates The Conversation</title><description>* Daniel Roth

Top 5 Stories on LinkedIn: Concern About SOPA Dominates The Conversation Daniel Roth January 20, 2012

Not since the death of Steve Jobs in the fall of 2011 has one story so dominated the attention of professionals. The fight over the Stop Online Piracy Act, or SOPA — a U.S. House of Representatives bill designed to block online copyright violations took three of the top five headlines in our weekly look at the most-shared stories by 135+ million LinkedIn members. From professionals in the IT industry to aviation and aerospace workers, concern over how the Internet might work…

* Topics:
* LinkedIn News</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7044_03_thumb.jpg">http://m.c.lnkd.licdn.com/mpr/mpr/shrink_200_200/p/2/000/19c/320/0530915.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>