<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7056">ROADM</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:12:15" name="LinkedIn Blog" id="FW14-e024"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e024-7056-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7056_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:12:16">http://blog.linkedin.com/2013/07/23/your-inspiration-roadmap-more-than-60-ways-to-get-motivated/</link><title>Your Inspiration Roadmap: More Than 60 Ways to Get Motivated</title><description>* Your Inspiration Roadmap: More Than 60 Ways to Get Motivated Francesca Levy July 23, 2013

To do good work, we often reach for a vague thing we call inspiration. It’s hard to pin it down, but you know it when you see it. Inspiration adds joy and meaning to the process of creation, whether you’re producing an aria or a PowerPoint presentation. Sounds simple enough. So why is it that some of us are visited by only rare and fleeting spurts of inspiration, while others seem permanently driven by a grand sense of purpose? The answer may lie partly in demographics. A survey…

* Topics:
* Influencers</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7056_01_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/themes/linkedin/images/transparent-fillin.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7056-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7056_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:16:17">http://blog.linkedin.com/2013/05/21/what-new-graduates-need-to-know/</link><title>What New Graduates Need to Know</title><description>* What New Graduates Need to Know Francesca Levy May 21, 2013

If you suspect that your 20-something employee is sneering at you from behind the stack of copies you asked him to collate, research suggests you might be right. Three-quarters of professionals under age 30 think their skills exceed those of an entry-level job, a survey released today by LinkedIn shows. But workers over 30 were wary of this attitude, saying they doubted the younger generation’s work ethic. Perhaps more shockingly, 64 percent of all adults — young adults…

* Topics:
* Economic Graph, 
* Influencers</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7056_02_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/themes/linkedin/images/transparent-fillin.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7056-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7056_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:18:50">http://blog.linkedin.com/2012/11/17/thought-leaders-week-7-review/</link><title>This Week in Thought Leaders: The Great Thanksgiving Opt-Out, Halting the Brain Drain, More</title><description>* Chip Cutter

This Week in Thought Leaders: The Great Thanksgiving Opt-Out, Halting the Brain Drain, More Chip Cutter November 17, 2012

Ryan Holmes: 3 Reasons Why Your Company Should Pay Employees to Use Social Media The days of minimizing your Facebook profile when your boss walks by your desk may be coming to an end. Holmes, the CEO of HootSuite, says there’s a hidden benefit of employees tweeting, updating their Facebook profiles and managing their personal social networks on the job. It builds goodwill, for one, but it also does something powerful in breaking down corporate hierarchies between employees. Alexis…

* Topics:
* Influencers</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7056_03_thumb.jpg">https://media.licdn.com/mpr/mpr/wc_200_200/p/6/000/228/1ea/3fcee53.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7056-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7056_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:21:27">http://blog.linkedin.com/2012/06/09/an-update-on-taking-steps-to-protect-our-members/</link><title>An Update On Taking Steps To Protect Our Members</title><description>* Vicente Silveira

An Update On Taking Steps To Protect Our Members Vicente Silveira June 9, 2012

By now, many of you have read recent headlines reporting that 6.5 million LinkedIn hashed passwords were stolen and published on an unauthorized website. We…

* Topics:
* Security</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7056_04_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/vicentesilveira.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7056-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7056_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:24:49">http://blog.linkedin.com/2011/11/01/simple-mobile-design/</link><title>Simplifying LinkedIn’s Mobile Experience</title><description>* Frank Yoo

Simplifying LinkedIn’s Mobile Experience Frank Yoo November 1, 2011

This belongs to our blog series on the genesis and thinking behind the design of LinkedIn’s features. Check out similar posts here. – Ed.  Two…

* Topics:
* Design</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7056_05_thumb.jpg">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/0423604.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7056-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7056_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:25:36">http://blog.linkedin.com/2011/02/22/linkedin-year-in-review/</link><title>Year in Review: there's a web app for that.</title><description>* Dhananjay Ragade

Year in Review: there's a web app for that. Dhananjay Ragade February 22, 2011

Did you get the 2010 Year in Review email from LinkedIn? Now you can see all of your LinkedIn connections that made a career move in 2011, 2010, or 2009. Check…

* Topics:
* Engineering, 
* LinkedIn Hackdays, 
* LinkedIn Labs</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7056_06_thumb.jpg">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/0504fe7.jpeg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>