<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7057">web of science</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:26:36" name="LinkedIn Blog" id="FW14-e024"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e024-7057-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7057_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:26:37">http://blog.linkedin.com/2014/03/25/state-of-my-industry-80-influencers-on-where-business-is-heading-infographic/</link><title>State of my Industry: 80+ Influencers on Where Business is Heading [INFOGRAPHIC]</title><description>* State of my Industry: 80+ Influencers on Where Business is Heading [INFOGRAPHIC] Isabelle Roughol March 25, 2014

This post is part of a series in which LinkedIn Influencers analyze the state and future of their industry. Read all the posts here. Not every industry lives under the same sky. In print media or retail, there are whole websites dedicated to adding up layoff announcements. Meanwhile, mobile development or advanced manufacturing are so hungry for talent, you can get a 5-figure bonus just for referring a new hire. Some industries wither and with them the entire cities they built…

* Topics:
* Featured, 
* Influencers</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7057_01_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/themes/linkedin/images/transparent-fillin.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7057-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7057_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:28:51">http://blog.linkedin.com/2012/08/31/flying-across-the-world-for-a-summer-internship/</link><title>Flying Across the World for a Summer Internship</title><description>* Yuan Daisy Gao

Flying Across the World for a Summer Internship Yuan Daisy Gao August 31, 2012

Editor’s Note: This is part of a series of blog posts by LinkedIn’s rockstar summer interns. Today, we hear from one of our international interns Yuan Daisy Gao who is pursuing a Master of Engineering, Computer Science degree at Tsinghua University. When LinkedIn recruiter Jamie Thai woke me up one morning to give me my internship offer, I officially became one of LinkedIn’s first international interns. This summer, four interns from China and the UK flew across the world to…

* Topics:
* Intern, 
* Work at LinkedIn</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7057_02_thumb.jpg">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/daisy.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7057-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7057_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:33:10">http://blog.linkedin.com/2012/01/06/top-5-stories-of-the-week-ideating-buzzwords-educating-for-free-and-retailings-race-to-the-bottom/</link><title>Top 5 Stories of the Week: Ideating Buzzwords, Educating For Free, and Retailing's Race to the Bottom</title><description>* Daniel Roth

Top 5 Stories of the Week: Ideating Buzzwords, Educating For Free, and Retailing's Race to the Bottom Daniel Roth January 6, 2012

Hi, I hope all is well. A small favor: Would you mind socializing this blog post with your colleagues and ideating a response? Two sentences, three of the worst management terms of 2011, according to Business Insider. Some of the others: weaponize, socialize, internalize, ideate. I’m not sure I’ve ever heard weaponize used in a meeting, but maybe I’m just attending the wrong meetings. In any case, the last week which bridged 2011 and 2012 ideated some year-end…

* Topics:
* LinkedIn News</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7057_03_thumb.jpg">http://m.c.lnkd.licdn.com/mpr/mpr/shrink_200_200/p/2/000/19c/320/0530915.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7057-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7057_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:36:41">http://blog.linkedin.com/2011/05/19/lnkd-bell-ringing/</link><title>[Updated] LNKD: Changing the way professionals do business</title><description>* Nick Besbeas

[Updated] LNKD: Changing the way professionals do business Nick Besbeas May 19, 2011

Today marks an important milestone in LinkedIn’s history – we started trading at the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE) – following our recent IPO filing…

* Topics:
* Announcements, 
* Best Of</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7057_04_thumb.jpg">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/0324816.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7057-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7057_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:38:06">http://blog.linkedin.com/2009/12/11/linkedin-biotech/</link><title>How to use LinkedIn for Biotech Projects</title><description>* Guest Author

How to use LinkedIn for Biotech Projects Guest Author December 11, 2009

Ed. note: Nearly 54 million professionals across different industries use LinkedIn to their competitive advantage. Starting this month, we’d like to…

* Topics:
* LinkedIn Tips</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7057_05_thumb.png">http://1.gravatar.com/avatar/1a38af3c28616b8a469d4b1e93016feb?s=72&amp;d=http%3A%2F%2F1.gravatar.com%2Favatar%2Fad516503a11cd5ca435acc9bb6523536%3Fs%3D72&amp;r=G</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7057-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7057_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:40:32">http://blog.linkedin.com/2009/04/21/connect-with-your-future-hiring-manager-on-linkedin/</link><title>How LinkedIn helped me land my first job at Microsoft</title><description>* Guest Author

How LinkedIn helped me land my first job at Microsoft Guest Author April 21, 2009

[Ed. note: This belongs to our series of posts from LinkedIn users featuring tips for recent grads. Adam Conrad is a masters student in Computer Science at...

* Topics:
* LinkedIn for Students, 
* LinkedIn Users</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7057_06_thumb.png">http://1.gravatar.com/avatar/1a38af3c28616b8a469d4b1e93016feb?s=72&amp;d=http%3A%2F%2F1.gravatar.com%2Favatar%2Fad516503a11cd5ca435acc9bb6523536%3Fs%3D72&amp;r=G</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>