<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7067">used kindle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:52:25" name="LinkedIn Blog" id="FW14-e024"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e024-7067-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7067_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:52:26">http://blog.linkedin.com/2013/05/24/lunch-time-is-sacred-valuable-lessons-learned-from-working-in-brazil/</link><title>Lunch Time is Sacred: Valuable Lessons Learned from Working in Brazil [SLIDESHOW]</title><description>* Danielle Restivo

Lunch Time is Sacred: Valuable Lessons Learned from Working in Brazil [SLIDESHOW] Danielle Restivo May 24, 2013

When I told my Canadian colleagues that I had the truly awesome opportunity to work for two months in the LinkedIn Brazil office, they immediately imagined me working on a beach in the hot sun sipping fruity drinks. And who could blame them? I was fortunate enough to leave my home country in the dead of Canadian winter (think -20C/-4F) and travel to São Paulo, Brazil, where I worked for seven weeks at the local LinkedIn office. So I packed my bags, convinced my husband to join me…

* Topics:
* Employee Stories, 
* Work at LinkedIn</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7067_01_thumb.jpg">http://m.c.lnkd.licdn.com/mpr/mpr/shrink_200_200/p/6/000/233/100/0252c71.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7067-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7067_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:55:21">http://blog.linkedin.com/2013/02/01/productive-pampering-bobbi-brown/</link><title>LinkedIn's Posh Productive Pampering Event with Bobbi Brown Cosmetics in NYC [PHOTOS]</title><description>* Nicole Williams

LinkedIn's Posh Productive Pampering Event with Bobbi Brown Cosmetics in NYC [PHOTOS] Nicole Williams February 1, 2013

There’s nothing we love more here at LinkedIn than connecting talented professionals. Last night we invited dozens of fabulous female journalists (who work at outlets like CNBC, Cosmopolitan, Glamour, Reader’s Digest, TIME, etc.) to network and mingle with one another while chatting about how important their online professional brand is. LinkedIn’s event took place at CORE: club, a veritable power portal for the business elite, just off of Park Avenue in Manhattan.

* Topics:
* Consumer</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7067_02_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/05/nicolewilliams.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>