<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7078">count in korean</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:06:51" name="LinkedIn Blog" id="FW14-e024"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e024-7078-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7078_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:06:52">http://blog.linkedin.com/2011/11/30/korea-malaysia-indonesia/</link><title>And we're now LIVE in Bahasa Malaysia, Bahasa Indonesia and Korean!</title><description>* Arvind Rajan

And we're now LIVE in Bahasa Malaysia, Bahasa Indonesia and Korean! Arvind Rajan November 30, 2011

Ed note: Starting today, professionals in Malaysia, Indonesia and Korea can now sign-up for LinkedIn in their very own local language. This is a post from Arvind Rajan, Managing Director and Vice President of APAC and Japan at LinkedIn. Today, I am pleased to share LinkedIn.com is now available in in three new local languages Bahasa Indonesia, Bahasa Malaysia and Korean. As a truly global professional network we continue to grow and deepen our footprint in the Asia Pacific region…

* Topics:
* Announcements</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7078_01_thumb.jpg">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/PIC-Arvind-Rajan-.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7078-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7078_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:08:06">http://blog.linkedin.com/2013/04/17/new-mobile-experience-for-everyday-professional/</link><title>A New Mobile Experience Designed for the Everyday Professional [VIDEO]</title><description>* A New Mobile Experience Designed for the Everyday Professional [VIDEO] Tomer Cohen April 17, 2013

Our mobile audience has greatly evolved over the past year. Today, our mobile professionals span across the globe and represent a broad spectrum, from executives to young professionals and from road warriors to desk ninjas. The typical workday has also extended beyond the traditional 9-to-5 as professionals are continuously looking to gain advantage and stay one step ahead, every day. Today, we’re excited to unveil a brand new mobile phone experience, completely revamped with the…

* Topics:
* Android, 
* iPhone, 
* LinkedIn Mobile</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7078_02_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/themes/linkedin/images/transparent-fillin.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7078-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7078_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:11:56">http://blog.linkedin.com/2012/09/05/more-mobile-goodness/</link><title>More LinkedIn Mobile Goodness</title><description>* Joff Redfern

More LinkedIn Mobile Goodness Joff Redfern September 5, 2012

Today is an anniversary of sorts. 1 year, 21 days ago we launched an entirely new LinkedIn mobile experience for iPhone, Android, and the mobile web at touch.linkedin.com.  It was an entirely fresh start, focused on faster, simpler, better. A lot has happened since then. A year ago, 10% of the unique users visiting LinkedIn were using one of our mobile apps, today it’s over 23%. In April, we gave birth to an iPad app, and in May we followed with a shiny new Windows Phone App that…

* Topics:
* Android, 
* iPad, 
* iPhone, 
* LinkedIn Mobile</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7078_03_thumb.jpg">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/joffredfern.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7078-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7078_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:14:07">http://blog.linkedin.com/2010/07/19/linkedin-small-business/</link><title>How can social media help your small business grow</title><description>* Dan Yoo

How can social media help your small business grow Dan Yoo July 19, 2010

As part of our continuing series featuring our employees, we’re turning you over to Dan Yoo. Although many of our employees would describe themselves as…

* Topics:
* Employee Stories</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7078_04_thumb.jpg">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/395e7cf.jpeg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>