<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7106">active learning survey</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:47:36" name="LinkedIn Blog" id="FW14-e024"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e024-7106-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7106_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:47:37">http://blog.linkedin.com/2014/04/07/why-it-pays-to-be-adaptable-tips-to-future-proof-your-career/</link><title>Why it Pays to be Adaptable: Tips to Future-Proof Your Career [INFOGRAPHIC]</title><description>* Why it Pays to be Adaptable: Tips to Future-Proof Your Career [INFOGRAPHIC] Ariel Eckstein April 7, 2014

You see your dream job posted on LinkedIn. Unfortunately, it’s located halfway around the world and it’s just not the right time to make a big move. You have all the right skills for a challenging opportunity, but it’s in an industry you have little knowledge of which makes you nervous about applying. A role opens up at your current workplace in a different department – you’re really interested but you just don’t have time to speak to HR. Many of us have, or will be…

* Topics:
* Consumer, 
* Featured, 
* LinkedIn Talent Solutions</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7106_01_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/themes/linkedin/images/transparent-fillin.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7106-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7106_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:48:52">http://blog.linkedin.com/2013/09/24/what-the-best-in-business-look-for-when-they-hire/</link><title>What the Best in Business Look For When They Hire</title><description>* What the Best in Business Look For When They Hire Francesca Levy September 24, 2013

For those seeking a job, the rigorous application and interview process can be harrowing. But spare some sympathy for the hiring managers. Sifting through resumes and coaxing out revealing insights in interviews is its own exhausting grind. And what’s at stake is a company’s most important asset: its talent. More than 80 of LinkedIn’s Influencers — thought leaders and experts across industries who write original content for LinkedIn — had lots to say about this topic…

* Topics:
* Influencers</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7106_02_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/themes/linkedin/images/transparent-fillin.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7106-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7106_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:53:09">http://blog.linkedin.com/2011/10/25/mentoring-women/</link><title>INFOGRAPHIC: Women and Mentoring in the U.S.</title><description>* Nicole Williams

INFOGRAPHIC: Women and Mentoring in the U.S. Nicole Williams October 25, 2011

This is a guest post on best practices around social networking from Nicole Williams. For similar posts check out our series on networking tips and tricks here. – Ed. It may not surprise you, but LinkedIn’s latest study found (in a survey of nearly 1,000 female professionals in the U.S.) that 82 percent of women agree that having a mentor is important.  But what will knock your socks off is that considering the competitive employment landscape, and the universal belief that…

* Topics:
* Analytics, 
* Consumer, 
* Infographic</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7106_03_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/05/nicolewilliams.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7106-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7106_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:54:04">http://blog.linkedin.com/2007/07/06/linkedin-answ-1-6/</link><title>LinkedIn Answers: The impact of social media on business</title><description>* Mario Sundar

LinkedIn Answers: The impact of social media on business Mario Sundar July 6, 2007

LinkedIn Answers is a feature we introduced half a year ago, to help users leverage the inherent “wisdom of their professional network”. In the…

* Topics:
* Featured</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7106_04_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/05/mariosundar.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>