<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7109">best place to eat pho in new york</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:00:06" name="LinkedIn Blog" id="FW14-e024"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e024-7109-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7109_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:00:08">http://blog.linkedin.com/2014/01/09/the-linkedin-influencer-guide-to-creating-the-perfect-new-years-resolution/</link><title>The LinkedIn Influencer Guide to Creating the Perfect New Year's Resolution</title><description>* The LinkedIn Influencer Guide to Creating the Perfect New Year's Resolution Chip Cutter January 9, 2014

Ah, January. There’s something satisfying about the start of a new year, and with it, the promises we make to lose weight, get organized and spend more time with the people we love. It’s a moment when even our most ambitious goals seem achievable. So what’s the right way to make, and keep, those New Year’s resolutions? To find out, I turned to our Influencers, the business luminaries and authors who blog regularly on LinkedIn. This is a group of impossibly…

* Topics:
* Featured, 
* Influencers</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7109_01_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/themes/linkedin/images/transparent-fillin.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7109-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7109_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:01:52">http://blog.linkedin.com/2013/09/24/what-the-best-in-business-look-for-when-they-hire/</link><title>What the Best in Business Look For When They Hire</title><description>* What the Best in Business Look For When They Hire Francesca Levy September 24, 2013

For those seeking a job, the rigorous application and interview process can be harrowing. But spare some sympathy for the hiring managers. Sifting through resumes and coaxing out revealing insights in interviews is its own exhausting grind. And what’s at stake is a company’s most important asset: its talent. More than 80 of LinkedIn’s Influencers — thought leaders and experts across industries who write original content for LinkedIn — had lots to say about this topic…

* Topics:
* Influencers</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7109_02_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/themes/linkedin/images/transparent-fillin.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7109-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7109_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:05:03">http://blog.linkedin.com/2013/04/23/why-you-should-make-more-mistakes/</link><title>Why You Should Make More Mistakes</title><description>* Why You Should Make More Mistakes Francesca Levy April 23, 2013

Think about the last time you made a mortifying flub at work. The email that went to the entire company instead of its intended recipient, or the words that – even as you heard them come out of your mouth – you regretted saying to your boss. Whether you stumbled 15 years ago or last week, the misapprehension and dread it inspired probably feels just as fresh as when the mistake first happened. Big errors are burned into our memory so that we can learn from them. And even the most…

* Topics:
* Influencers</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7109_03_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/themes/linkedin/images/transparent-fillin.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7109-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7109_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:05:38">http://blog.linkedin.com/2013/01/26/top-influencer-posts-this-week-why-steve-jobs-hated-poaching-the-end-of-colleges-and-more/</link><title>Top Influencer Posts This Week: Why Steve Jobs Hated Poaching, The End...</title><description>* Chip Cutter

Top Influencer Posts This Week: Why Steve Jobs Hated Poaching, The End... Chip Cutter January 26, 2013

See Steve Jobs at his most prickly, learn why Mark Cuban thinks colleges may soon go out of business and dig into gourmet doughnuts in this week’s…

* Topics:
* Influencers</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7109_04_thumb.jpg">https://media.licdn.com/mpr/mpr/wc_200_200/p/6/000/228/1ea/3fcee53.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7109-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7109_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:06:28">http://blog.linkedin.com/2012/08/15/taking-an-online-professional-network-offline/</link><title>Taking My Online Professional Network Offline</title><description>* Linda Descano

Taking My Online Professional Network Offline Linda Descano August 15, 2012

Editor’s Note: Four months ago, LinkedIn and Citi launched Connect: Professional Women’s Network to create a place for women to discuss their careers…

* Topics:
* Connect</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7109_05_thumb.jpg">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/linda.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7109-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7109_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:08:27">http://blog.linkedin.com/2012/02/10/sitting-at-work-is-old-fashioned-and-other-top-stories-on-linkedin-this-week/</link><title>Sitting at Work Is Old Fashioned — And Other Top Stories on LinkedIn...</title><description>* Daniel Roth

Sitting at Work Is Old Fashioned — And Other Top Stories on LinkedIn... Daniel Roth February 10, 2012

There are a few things we used to expect from managers and no longer can, according to the most-shared stories by LinkedIn’s 150 million-plus members. No.

* Topics:
* LinkedIn News</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7109_06_thumb.jpg">http://m.c.lnkd.licdn.com/mpr/mpr/shrink_200_200/p/2/000/19c/320/0530915.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>