<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7174">seal team 6</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:47:31" name="LinkedIn Blog" id="FW14-e024"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e024-7174-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7174_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:47:32">http://blog.linkedin.com/2013/09/16/the-collapse-and-the-comeback/</link><title>Five Years Later: Lessons from the Financial Crisis</title><description>* Five Years Later: Lessons from the Financial Crisis Daniel Roth September 16, 2013

In his book on the 2008 financial crisis, RBC Wealth CEO John Taft conducted a brief meta-analysis, looking at who was being blamed for the financial crisis. He found nearly two dozen issues and “arch villains” fingered for the worst economic downturn since the Great Depression. The Congressional Financial Crisis Inquiry Commission blamed regulators, bankers, and derivatives, among others; a dissenting report pointed to another 10 causes. Legendary investor Jeremy Grantham took…

* Topics:
* Economic Graph, 
* Influencers</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7174_01_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/themes/linkedin/images/transparent-fillin.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7174-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7174_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:49:32">http://blog.linkedin.com/2007/07/27/antarctica-2007/</link><title>Antarctica 2007: Swimming with the Penguins!</title><description>* Guest Author

Antarctica 2007: Swimming with the Penguins! Guest Author July 27, 2007

From bicycle marathons benefiting AIDS to fire breathing at the Sydney Olympics; from plunging into the cold polar waters to then writing about it! Starting today, you’ll hear interesting stories and anecdotes from the LinkedIn team, in a column called “LinkedInside”. Here’s Ryan Gustafson‘s account of swimming with the penguins in Antarctica (don’t miss the Antarctic Polar Plunge video!): Antarctica: The end of the world. One of the most remote…

* Topics:
* Employee Stories</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7174_02_thumb.png">http://1.gravatar.com/avatar/1a38af3c28616b8a469d4b1e93016feb?s=72&amp;d=http%3A%2F%2F1.gravatar.com%2Favatar%2Fad516503a11cd5ca435acc9bb6523536%3Fs%3D72&amp;r=G</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>