<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7438">facebook privacy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:24:50" name="LinkedIn Blog" id="FW14-e024"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e024-7438-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7438_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:24:51">http://blog.linkedin.com/2012/03/23/linkedins-top-stories-of-the-week-want-a-job-hand-over-your-passwords/</link><title>LinkedIn's Top Stories of the Week: Want a Job? Hand Over Your Passwords</title><description>* Francesca Levy

LinkedIn's Top Stories of the Week: Want a Job? Hand Over Your Passwords Francesca Levy March 23, 2012

You may think you’re prepared for every question that could come up in a job interview. But here’s a new one: “what’s your Facebook password?” In one of the most widely shared stories on LinkedIn this week, the Associated Press reports that companies are getting aggressive about peeking at your social networking profiles. Many job hunters have tightened their Facebook privacy settings so that the details of their personal lives don’t jeopardize a…

* Topics:
* LinkedIn News</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7438_01_thumb.jpg">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/12/francesca.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7438-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7438_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:28:36">http://blog.linkedin.com/2013/12/04/the-role-of-social-media-in-college-admissions/</link><title>The Role of Social Media in College Admissions</title><description>* The Role of Social Media in College Admissions Dr. Kat Cohen December 4, 2013

  With all the buzz about the role of social media in almost every industry, it shouldn’t be surprising that it has increasingly become a significant part of the college admissions process. A Zinch survey last year found that 68% of students used social media to research schools, and 38% said they used it as a research tool when deciding where to enroll. This has prompted college and universities to use social media as an informative recruitment tool, with 97% of schools using…

* Topics:
* LinkedIn for Students</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7438_02_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/themes/linkedin/images/transparent-fillin.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7438-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7438_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:31:35">http://blog.linkedin.com/2011/01/12/linkedin-resumes-hackdays/</link><title>Resumes and Hackdays</title><description>* Jim Brikman

Resumes and Hackdays Jim Brikman January 12, 2011

Stop for a second and consider this question: where is your resume? If you’re like most people, it’s probably scattered across a half dozen Word documents somewhere on your computer; or maybe your old laptop; actually, you may even have to search the sent mail folder of your email to find it. It’s probably out of date and the thought of updating it and fighting with formatting issues makes you groan. And after all the effort you put into it, it still never looks quite right…

* Topics:
* LinkedIn Hackdays, 
* New LinkedIn Features</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7438_03_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/05/jimbrikman.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7438-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7438_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:32:52">http://blog.linkedin.com/2008/02/29/linkedin-news-r/</link><title>LinkedIn News Roundup: The New York Times, WSJ and more</title><description>* Krista Canfield

LinkedIn News Roundup: The New York Times, WSJ and more Krista Canfield February 29, 2008

The past few weeks have been busy ones here at LinkedIn. Have you heard of our homepage redesign or Status feature? Our most recent news announcement came…

* Topics:
* LinkedIn in the News</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7438_04_thumb.jpg">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/0a54ad8.jpeg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>