<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7445">marathon training</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:47:43" name="LinkedIn Blog" id="FW14-e024"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e024-7445-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7445_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:47:44">http://blog.linkedin.com/2011/06/02/linkedin-marathon-mom/</link><title>Who is LinkedIn's Marathon Mom?</title><description>* Barbara Sanchez

Who is LinkedIn's Marathon Mom? Barbara Sanchez June 2, 2011

Ed. note: This post is a part of our continuing blog series featuring our employees. Here, we hear from our very own Barbara Sanchez – a Sales Development specialist at LinkedIn’s office in Dublin, Ireland – who is also a new mom, and (as if that’s not enough) 2012 Olympic hopeful. You don’t run 100 miles a week without a little motivation. For me, that motivation comes from a love of sport. I’ve always been involved in running, cycling or swimming. I’ve competed in…

* Topics:
* Employee Stories</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7445_01_thumb.jpg">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/3dda8c7.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7445-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7445_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:50:17">http://blog.linkedin.com/2007/09/05/marathon/</link><title>Running with a purpose | AIDS Marathon</title><description>* Veronica Vallez

Running with a purpose | AIDS Marathon Veronica Vallez September 5, 2007

Veronica is a recruiting coordinator with a penchant for pretentious memoir, writing blurbs about herself and Post-It notes of varying sizes and colors. The flyer that reached my mailbox claimed that anyone, even non-runners, could train to complete a 26.2 mile marathon by just following the simple training program guidelines. I’ll admit, I was skeptical. I have been running for the past couple years but I’ve never surpassed 8 miles. Was this a message and how did the…

* Topics:
* Employee Stories, 
* LinkedIn for Good, 
* Work at LinkedIn</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7445_02_thumb.png">http://0.gravatar.com/avatar/0204ac70ba300bdf5245a296cb9ae20c?s=72&amp;d=http%3A%2F%2F0.gravatar.com%2Favatar%2Fad516503a11cd5ca435acc9bb6523536%3Fs%3D72&amp;r=G</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7445-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7445_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:50:56">http://blog.linkedin.com/2014/01/07/secrets-to-launching-a-successful-side-business/</link><title>Secrets to Launching a Successful Side-Business</title><description>* Secrets to Launching a Successful Side-Business Kimberly Palmer January 7, 2014

Side-gigs, from blogging and life coaching to freelance writing or web designing, are quickly becoming an essential part of building a successful career in the new economy. In addition to bringing in (even modest) extra income, they help us learn new skills, make new connections, and discover the true value of what we have to offer the world. When I launched my own side-business of selling money planners on the handmade marketplace Etsy, I hoped for little more than selling a few…

* Topics:
* Careers, 
* Consumer</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7445_03_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/themes/linkedin/images/transparent-fillin.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7445-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7445_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:54:44">http://blog.linkedin.com/2011/05/16/linkedin-armen/</link><title>LinkedIn and Bay to Breakers: A Passion for Winning</title><description>* Armen Vartanian

LinkedIn and Bay to Breakers: A Passion for Winning Armen Vartanian May 16, 2011

Ed. note: This post is a part of our continuing blog series featuring our colleagues’ stories. Today, we hear from our very own Armen Vartanian –…

* Topics:
* Employee Stories</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7445_04_thumb.jpg">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/12dd805.jpeg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7445-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7445_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:55:45">http://blog.linkedin.com/2010/05/05/linkedin-bay-to-breakers/</link><title>Come run with us and break a Guinness World Record at Bay to Brea...</title><description>* Armen Vartanian

Come run with us and break a Guinness World Record at Bay to Brea... Armen Vartanian May 5, 2010

Ed. note: This is a special edition post on folks working at LinkedIn talking about their true passion – at work and in the real world. This week’s…

* Topics:
* Events</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7445_05_thumb.jpg">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/12dd805.jpeg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>