<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7447">running shoes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:57:20" name="LinkedIn Blog" id="FW14-e024"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e024-7447-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7447_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:57:21">http://blog.linkedin.com/2014/01/09/the-linkedin-influencer-guide-to-creating-the-perfect-new-years-resolution/</link><title>The LinkedIn Influencer Guide to Creating the Perfect New Year's Resolution</title><description>* The LinkedIn Influencer Guide to Creating the Perfect New Year's Resolution Chip Cutter January 9, 2014

Ah, January. There’s something satisfying about the start of a new year, and with it, the promises we make to lose weight, get organized and spend more time with the people we love. It’s a moment when even our most ambitious goals seem achievable. So what’s the right way to make, and keep, those New Year’s resolutions? To find out, I turned to our Influencers, the business luminaries and authors who blog regularly on LinkedIn. This is a group of impossibly…

* Topics:
* Featured, 
* Influencers</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7447_01_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/themes/linkedin/images/transparent-fillin.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7447-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7447_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:59:01">http://blog.linkedin.com/2012/12/04/buzzwords-2012-tips/</link><title>Are Your Buzzwords a Buzzkill?: 3 Tips to Get Noticed</title><description>* Nicole Williams

Are Your Buzzwords a Buzzkill?: 3 Tips to Get Noticed Nicole Williams December 4, 2012

In the face of the down economy the strategic, disruptive approach is to identify influencers with extensive experience in creating problem—solving results. Yep, that’s a real life sentence, found in a real life publication. But what exactly does it say? In a word that actually means something: nothing. At a time when there is more content out there than you could ever possibly hope to read, quality—and not quantity—has become the absolute standard for standing out and getting…

* Topics:
* Consumer</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7447_02_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/05/nicolewilliams.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>