<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7503">uki</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:30:56" name="LinkedIn Blog" id="FW14-e024"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e024-7503-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7503_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:30:57">http://blog.linkedin.com/2014/02/11/linkedin-is-50-million-strong-in-asia-and-counting/</link><title>LinkedIn is 50 Million Strong in Asia, and Counting!</title><description>* LinkedIn is 50 Million Strong in Asia, and Counting! Hari Krishnan February 11, 2014

I’m delighted to announce that we just crossed the 50 million member mark in the Asia Pacific region! As we celebrate this milestone, I am humbled by the success of our members who are using LinkedIn to build their professional identities, networks and knowledge, and whom we proudly serve. It’s remarkable that our member base across the region has nearly tripled in a span of less than three years. Last year, we welcomed 7+ million new members in India, while 2+ million new members…

* Topics:
* Announcements, 
* Featured, 
* International</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7503_01_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/themes/linkedin/images/transparent-fillin.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7503-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7503_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:33:11">http://blog.linkedin.com/2013/09/16/the-collapse-and-the-comeback/</link><title>Five Years Later: Lessons from the Financial Crisis</title><description>* Five Years Later: Lessons from the Financial Crisis Daniel Roth September 16, 2013

In his book on the 2008 financial crisis, RBC Wealth CEO John Taft conducted a brief meta-analysis, looking at who was being blamed for the financial crisis. He found nearly two dozen issues and “arch villains” fingered for the worst economic downturn since the Great Depression. The Congressional Financial Crisis Inquiry Commission blamed regulators, bankers, and derivatives, among others; a dissenting report pointed to another 10 causes. Legendary investor Jeremy Grantham took…

* Topics:
* Economic Graph, 
* Influencers</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7503_02_thumb.png">http://blog.linkedin.com/wp-content/themes/linkedin/images/transparent-fillin.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e024-7503-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7503_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:36:03">http://blog.linkedin.com/2011/06/22/linkedin-slideshare/</link><title>Discovering People Through Content, and Content Through People</title><description>* Guest Author

Discovering People Through Content, and Content Through People Guest Author June 22, 2011

This belongs to a series of posts on how websites like Slideshare are integrating LinkedIn functionality on their site. Here’s Ross Mayfield, VP of Business Development at Slideshare on the integration of LinkedIn’s APIs on Slideshare and vice-versa. – Ed. Starting today, we’re launching a new integration with SlideShare and LinkedIn that will make it easier for you to share, discover, and engage with professional content on both networks. Below are the three new features…

* Topics:
* LinkedIn Developer Network</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e024/7503_03_thumb.png">http://1.gravatar.com/avatar/1a38af3c28616b8a469d4b1e93016feb?s=72&amp;d=http%3A%2F%2F1.gravatar.com%2Favatar%2Fad516503a11cd5ca435acc9bb6523536%3Fs%3D72&amp;r=G</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>