<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7003">Male circumcision</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:40:14" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7003-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7003_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:40:17">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=594A77CAE0EBC10E649D37BA45BDFBF7?doi=10.1.1.378.2005&amp;rank=1</link><title>STRATEGIES AND APPROACHES FOR MALE CIRCUMCISION PROGRAMMING</title><description>STRATEGIES AND APPROACHES FOR MALE CIRCUMCISION PROGRAMMING

by unknown authors

"... ﻿STRATEGIES AND APPROACHES FOR MALE CIRCUMCISION PROGRAMMING WHO MEETING REPORT 5 - 6 December 2006 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

The designations employed and the presentation of the material in this publication do not imply the expression of any opinion whatsoever on the part of the World Health Organization concerning the legal status of any country, territory, city or area or of its authorities, or concerning the delimitation of its frontiers or boundaries. Dotted lines on maps represent approximate border lines for which there may not yet be full agreement. The mention of specific companies or of certain manufacturers ’ products does not imply that they are endorsed or recommended by the World Health Organization in preference to others of a similar nature that are not mentioned. Errors and omissions excepted, the names of proprietary products are distinguished by initial capital letters. All reasonable precautions have been taken by the World Health Organization to verify the information contained in this publication. However, the published material is being distributed without warranty of any kind, either expressed or implied. The responsibility for the interpretation and use of the material lies with the reader. In no event shall the World Health Organization be liable for damages arising from its use. This publication contains the collective views of an international group of experts and does not necessarily represent the decisions or the stated</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7003-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7003_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:40:18">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=594A77CAE0EBC10E649D37BA45BDFBF7?doi=10.1.1.373.250&amp;rank=2</link><title>MOHSW SITUATION ANALYSIS FOR MALE CIRCUMCISION IN</title><description>MOHSW SITUATION ANALYSIS FOR MALE CIRCUMCISION IN

by In Tanzania, Mwanza Tanzania, Mwita Wambura, Joseph Mwanga, Jackline Mosha, Gerry Mshana, Frank Mosha, John Changalucha , 2009

"... ﻿SITUATION ANALYSIS FOR MALE CIRCUMCISION IN TANZANIA FINAL REPORT National Institute for Medical ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

All authors are based at NIMR Mwanza</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7003-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7003_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:40:19">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=594A77CAE0EBC10E649D37BA45BDFBF7?doi=10.1.1.248.4953&amp;rank=3</link><title>Male Circumcision and Risk for HIV Acquisition by Heterosexual Men</title><description>Male Circumcision and Risk for HIV Acquisition by Heterosexual Men

by unknown authors

"... ﻿Male Circumcision This fact sheet summarizes information in four areas of male circumcision: 1 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

This fact sheet summarizes information in four areas of &lt;em&gt;male&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;circumcision&lt;/em&gt;: 1) &lt;em&gt;male&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;circumcision&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7003-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7003_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:40:20">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=594A77CAE0EBC10E649D37BA45BDFBF7?doi=10.1.1.276.6506&amp;rank=4</link><title>Perspectives Does Male Circumcision Prevent HIV Infection?</title><description>Perspectives Does Male Circumcision Prevent HIV Infection?

by Nandi Siegfried

"... ﻿Perspectives Does Male Circumcision Prevent HIV Infection? Nandi Siegfried Open access, freely ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

with HIV/AIDS, many potential prevention measures against HIV infection have been explored. &lt;em&gt;Male&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7003-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7003_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:40:21">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=594A77CAE0EBC10E649D37BA45BDFBF7?doi=10.1.1.274.6198&amp;rank=5</link><title>Understanding the impact of male circumcision interventions on the spread</title><description>Understanding the impact of male circumcision interventions on the spread

by Timothy B. Hallett, Kanwarjit Singh, Jennifer A. Smith, Richard G. White, Laith J. Abu-raddad, Geoff P. Garnett \- of HIV in southern Africa. PLoS ONE 2008;3:e2212

"... ﻿Understanding the Impact of Male Circumcision Interventions on the Spread of HIV in Southern ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 7 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Background: Three randomised controlled trials have clearly shown that &lt;em&gt;circumcision&lt;/em&gt; of adult men</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7003-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7003_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:40:22">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=594A77CAE0EBC10E649D37BA45BDFBF7?doi=10.1.1.175.7603&amp;rank=6</link><title>Evidence for a Protective Effect of Male Circumcision</title><description>Evidence for a Protective Effect of Male Circumcision

by unknown authors

"... and Gaps 5 Evidence for a Protective Effect of Male Circumcision 5 Biology or Behavior: The Role ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

This publication was made possible through support provided by the Office of Health and Nutrition,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7003-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7003_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:40:23">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=594A77CAE0EBC10E649D37BA45BDFBF7?doi=10.1.1.373.739&amp;rank=7</link><title>Male circumcision for HIV prevention WHO Technical Advisory Group on Innovations in Male</title><description>Male circumcision for HIV prevention WHO Technical Advisory Group on Innovations in Male

by unknown authors

"... ﻿Male circumcision for HIV prevention meeting report WHO Technical Advisory Group on Innovations ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Requests for permission to reproduce or translate WHO publications –whether for sale or for non-commercial distribution – should be addressed to WHO Press through the WHO web site (www.who.int/about/licensing/ copyright_form/en/index.html). The designations employed and the presentation of the material in this publication do not imply the expression of any opinion whatsoever on the part of the World Health Organization concerning the legal status of any country, territory, city or area or of its authorities, or concerning the delimitation of its frontiers or boundaries. Dotted lines on maps represent approximate border lines for which there may not yet be full agreement. The mention of specific companies or of certain manufacturers ’ products does not imply that they are endorsed or recommended by the World Health Organization in preference to others of a similar nature that are not mentioned. Errors and omissions excepted, the names of proprietary products are distinguished by initial capital letters. All reasonable precautions have been taken by the World Health Organization to verify the information contained in this publication. However, the published material is being distributed without warranty of any kind, either expressed or implied. The responsibility for the interpretation and use of the material lies with the reader. In no event shall the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7003-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7003_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:40:24">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=594A77CAE0EBC10E649D37BA45BDFBF7?doi=10.1.1.208.9101&amp;rank=8</link><title>2006): “Male circumcision and AIDS: The macroeconomic impact of health crisis,” Working Paper</title><description>2006): “Male circumcision and AIDS: The macroeconomic impact of health crisis,” Working Paper

by Amrita Ahuja, Brian Wendell, Eric Werker

"... ﻿1 Male circumcision and AIDS: the macroeconomic impact of a health crisis Amrita Ahuja • Brian ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 11 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

the impact of the AIDS epidemic on African nations through 2005 using the &lt;em&gt;male&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;circumcision&lt;/em&gt; rate to identify</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7003-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7003_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:40:25">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=594A77CAE0EBC10E649D37BA45BDFBF7?doi=10.1.1.373.948&amp;rank=9</link><title>Information package on male circumcision and Hiv prevention insert 5 Implications for women</title><description>Information package on male circumcision and Hiv prevention insert 5 Implications for women

by unknown authors

"... ﻿Information package on male circumcision and Hiv prevention insert 5 Implications for women ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

provided evidence that &lt;em&gt;male&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;circumcision&lt;/em&gt; reduces the risk of HIV acquisition in men through heterosexual</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7003-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7003_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-15 13:40:26">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=594A77CAE0EBC10E649D37BA45BDFBF7?doi=10.1.1.354.8342&amp;rank=10</link><title>ORIGINAL PAPER Framing Male Circumcision to Promote its Adoption in Different Settings</title><description>ORIGINAL PAPER Framing Male Circumcision to Promote its Adoption in Different Settings

by Lee E. Klosinski, Sharif Sawires, Greg Szekeres, Mark Weston, Thomas J. Coates, F. D. Gilliam, R. A. Brooks, R. A. Brooks, A. A. Leibowitz, S. Sawires, T. J. Coates, S. Sawires, G. Szekeres, T. J. Coates, M. Weston , 2010

"... .com Abstract The effectiveness of male circumcision in preventing transmission of HIV from females to males has ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

The effectiveness of &lt;em&gt;male&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;circumcision&lt;/em&gt; in preventing transmission of HIV from females to &lt;em&gt;males&lt;/em&gt; has been established</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>