<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7007">Allen Ginsberg Howl review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:43:22" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7007-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7007_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:43:26">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=FD2C52EF91559F9EA44C0CCCD6D49A42?doi=10.1.1.403.8784&amp;rank=1</link><title>Oral Tradition, 22/1 (2007): 14-29 Dylan</title><description>Oral Tradition, 22/1 (2007): 14-29 Dylan

by The Nobel, Gordon Ball

"... , the Nobel Prize. My specialty is the poet Allen Ginsberg and the literature of the Beat Generation; I edited ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

, or folklore, or, for that matter, the Nobel Prize. My specialty is the poet &lt;em&gt;Allen&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Ginsberg&lt;/em&gt; and the literature</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7007-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7007_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:44:21">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=FD2C52EF91559F9EA44C0CCCD6D49A42?doi=10.1.1.422.5590&amp;rank=2</link><title>\- Health Link Authors and Reviewers</title><description>\- Health Link Authors and Reviewers

by Young Adult Cancers , 2008

"... • Contributors \- Panel of Experts \- Task Force Membership \- Health Link Authors and Reviewers \- Guideline ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

www.survivorshipguidelines.org</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7007-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7007_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:46:20">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=FD2C52EF91559F9EA44C0CCCD6D49A42?doi=10.1.1.79.9158&amp;rank=3</link><title>SEEK2: A Generalized Approach to Automatic Knowledge Base Refinement</title><description>SEEK2: A Generalized Approach to Automatic Knowledge Base Refinement

by Allen Ginsberg, Sholom Weiss, Peter Politakis , 1985

"... , and Welfare, Grant P41 RR02230. SEEK2: A GENERALIZED APPROACH TO AUTOMATIC KNOWLEDGE BASE REFINEMENT Allen ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 19 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper describes an approach to knowledge base refinement, an important aspect of knowledge acquisition. Knowledge base refinement is characterized by the addition, deletion, and alteration of rule-components in an existing knowledge base, in an attempt to improve an expert system's performance. SEEK2 extends the capabilities of its predecessor rule refinement system. SEEK [1], In this paper we describe the progress we have made since developing the original SEEK program: (a) SEEK2 works with a more general class of knowledge bases than SEEK, (b) SEEK2 has an &amp;quot;automatic pilot &amp;quot; capability, i.e., it can, if desired, perform all of the basic tasks involved in knowledge base refinement without human interaction, (c) a metalanguage for knowledge base refinement has been specified which describes both domain-independent and domain-specific metaknowledge about the refinement process.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7007-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7007_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:48:10">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=FD2C52EF91559F9EA44C0CCCD6D49A42?doi=10.1.1.335.4353&amp;rank=4</link><title>Activation of Rhoa and ROCK are essential for detachment of migrating leukocytes</title><description>Activation of Rhoa and ROCK are essential for detachment of migrating leukocytes

by Jacqueline Alblas, Laurien Ulfman, Peter Hordijk, Leo Koenderman \- Mol.Biol.Cell , 2001

"... , 2000; Revised Accepted 2000 Monitoring Editor: Mark Ginsberg Detachment of the rear of the cell from ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 20 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Detachment of the rear of the cell from its substratum is an important aspect of locomotion. The signaling routes involved in this adhesive release are largely unknown. One of the few candidate proteins to play a role is RhoA, because activation of RhoA in many cell types leads to contraction, a mechanism probably involved in detachment. To study the role of RhoA in detachment regulation, we analyzed several subsets of expert migratory leukocytes by video microscopy. In contrast to fast-migrating neutrophils, eosinophils do not detach the rear of the cell unless stimulated with serum. When measuring the amount of active RhoA, with the use of a GST-Rhotekin pulldown assay, we found that serum is an excellent activator of RhoA in granulocytes. Inhibition of RhoA or one of Rho’s target proteins, the kinase ROCK, in neutrophils leads to the phenotype seen in eosinophils: the rear of the cell is firmly attached to the substratum, whereas the cell body is highly motile. ROCK-inhibition leads to impaired migration of granulocytes in filters, on glass, and through endothelial monolayers. Also, the ROCK signaling pathway is involved in changes of integrin-mediated adhesion. Eosinophil transduction by a tat-fusion construct containing active RhoA resulted in detachment stimulation in the presence of chemoattractant. From these results we conclude that activation of the RhoA-ROCK pathway is essential</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7007-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7007_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:49:23">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=FD2C52EF91559F9EA44C0CCCD6D49A42?doi=10.1.1.26.1483&amp;rank=5</link><title>A Commonsense Language for Reasoning About Causation and Rational Action</title><description>A Commonsense Language for Reasoning About Causation and Rational Action

by Charles L. Ortiz, Jr. , 1999

"... might be inconsistent with those facts or events in the past. Allen [ 1984 ] also makes use of a causal ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 15 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Commonsense causal discourse requires a language with which to express varying degrees of causal connectedness. This paper presents a commonsense language for reasoning about action and causation whose semantics is expressed by way of counterfactuals. Causal relations are analyzed along several dimensions including notions of resource consumption, degree of responsibility, instrumentality, and degree of causal contribution. Grounding the semantics in a level of counterfactual reasoning is shown to play an important role in constraining the set of allowable event descriptions instantiating reports expressed by any of the relations in the language. These ideas are also applied to a causal analysis of rational action: by adopting an explanatory stance, one can characterize action through descriptions that refer to causal connections between mental states and actions. Such a causal analysis resolves some well-known difficulties in correctly ascribing agency and intentionality. Finally, an ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7007-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7007_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:50:34">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=FD2C52EF91559F9EA44C0CCCD6D49A42?doi=10.1.1.38.5936&amp;rank=6</link><title>The Devil's Invention: Asymptotic, Superasymptotic and Hyperasymptotic Series</title><description>The Devil's Invention: Asymptotic, Superasymptotic and Hyperasymptotic Series

by John P. Boyd \- Acta Applicandae , 1999

"... and Review Articles 23\. Summary 1\. Introduction Divergent asymptotic series are important in almost all ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 12 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

. Singular perturbation methods, such as the method of multiple scales and the method of matched asymptotic expansions, give series in a small parameter # which are asymptotic but (usually) divergent. In this survey, we use a plethora of examples to illustrate the cause of the divergence, and explain how this knowledge can be exploited to generate a "hyperasymptotic" approximation. This adds a second asymptotic expansion, with di#erent scaling assumptions about the size of various terms in the problem, to achieve a minimum error much smaller than the best possible with the original asymptotic series. (This rescale-and-add process can be repeated further.) Weakly nonlocal solitary waves are used as an illustration. Key words: Perturbation methods, asymptotic, hyperasymptotic, exponential smallness AMS: 34E05, 40G99, 41A60, 65B10 "Divergent series are the invention of the devil, and it is shameful to base on them any demonstration whatsoever." --- Niels Hendrik Abel, 1828 1. Introdu...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7007-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7007_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 23:52:46">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=FD2C52EF91559F9EA44C0CCCD6D49A42?doi=10.1.1.387.9311&amp;rank=7</link><title>High Performance Schools Inc.'s Best Practices Manual, Volume II. Modifications were developed by Eley</title><description>High Performance Schools Inc.'s Best Practices Manual, Volume II. Modifications were developed by Eley

by unknown authors

"... and the many authors and reviewers that provided input and feedback during the process of developing the report ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Smart Schools team and the many authors and &lt;em&gt;reviewers&lt;/em&gt; that provided input and feedback during the process</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7007-08"><link>http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=FD2C52EF91559F9EA44C0CCCD6D49A42?doi=10.1.1.170.9932&amp;rank=8</link><title>High Performance Schools Inc.'s Best Practices Manual, Volume II. The CHPS Best Practices Manual is</title><description>High Performance Schools Inc.'s Best Practices Manual, Volume II. The CHPS Best Practices Manual is

by unknown authors

"... and the many authors and reviewers that provided input and feedback during the process of developing the report ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Smart Schools team and the many authors and &lt;em&gt;reviewers&lt;/em&gt; that provided input and feedback during the process</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7007-09"><link>http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=FD2C52EF91559F9EA44C0CCCD6D49A42?doi=10.1.1.137.3575&amp;rank=9</link><title>Implications for IT Use</title><description>Implications for IT Use

by Natalia Levina, Emmanuelle Vaast

"... .vaast@(email omitted); * The authors have contributed equally to the paper Manuscript under review \-- please do not distribute without ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

* The authors have contributed equally to the paper Manuscript under &lt;em&gt;review&lt;/em&gt;\-- please do</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7007-10"><link>http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=FD2C52EF91559F9EA44C0CCCD6D49A42?doi=10.1.1.255.6301&amp;rank=10</link><title>Nanoscale Titanium Dioxide in Water</title><description>Nanoscale Titanium Dioxide in Water

by In Topical Sunscreen , 2010

"... This document has been reviewed in accordance with U.S. Environmental Protection Agency policy and approved ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Triangle Park, NC Disclaimer This document has been &lt;em&gt;reviewed&lt;/em&gt; in accordance with U.S. Environmental</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>