<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7014">Asian culture</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:05:37" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7014-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7014_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:05:39">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=56FFEDF6F91BF73527DFE9C7B3A63400?doi=10.1.1.122.8637&amp;rank=1</link><title>Hierarchical Dirichlet processes</title><description>Hierarchical Dirichlet processes

by Yee Whye Teh, Michael I. Jordan, Matthew J. Beal, David M. Blei \- Journal of the American Statistical Association , 2004

"... the population is divided into a set of groups; e.g., African, Asian and European subpopulations. We may not only ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 536 (55 self) \- Add to MetaCart

program. The authors wish to acknowledge helpful discussions with Lancelot James and Jim Pitman and the referees for useful comments. 1 We consider problems involving groups of data, where each observation within a group is a draw from a mixture model, and where it is desirable to share mixture components between groups. We assume that the number of mixture components is unknown a priori and is to be inferred from the data. In this setting it is natural to consider sets of Dirichlet processes, one for each group, where the well-known clustering property of the Dirichlet process provides a nonparametric prior for the number of mixture components within each group. Given our desire to tie the mixture models in the various groups, we consider a hierarchical model, specifically one in which the base measure for the child Dirichlet processes is itself distributed according to a Dirichlet process. Such a base measure being discrete, the child Dirichlet processes necessar-ily share atoms. Thus, as desired, the mixture models in the different groups necessarily share mixture components. We discuss representations of hierarchical Dirichlet processes in terms of</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7014-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7014_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:05:54">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=56FFEDF6F91BF73527DFE9C7B3A63400?doi=10.1.1.320.1159&amp;rank=2</link><title>Culture and the self: Implications for cognition, emotion, and motivation</title><description>Culture and the self: Implications for cognition, emotion, and motivation

by Hazel Rose Markus, Shinobu Kitayama \- Psychological Review , 1991

"... cognition, emotion, and motivation. Many Asian cultures have distinct conceptions of individuality ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 375 (9 self) \- Add to MetaCart

of individual experience, including cognition, emotion, and motivation. Many &lt;em&gt;Asian&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;cultures&lt;/em&gt; have distinct</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7014-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7014_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:06:15">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=56FFEDF6F91BF73527DFE9C7B3A63400?doi=10.1.1.210.9300&amp;rank=3</link><title>Meaning of 1 Running head: MEANING OF FOOD Meaning of Food in Asian Culture</title><description>Meaning of 1 Running head: MEANING OF FOOD Meaning of Food in Asian Culture

by Mei Guan, Mcnair Scholar, Diane Reddy Ph. D, Stephanie Calloway B. A

"... ﻿Meaning of 1 Running head: MEANING OF FOOD Meaning of Food in Asian Culture Mei Guan Mc ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

&lt;em&gt;Asian&lt;/em&gt; and Caucasian women investigating &lt;em&gt;cultural&lt;/em&gt; and personal meaning of food. Quantitative predictors</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7014-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7014_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:06:41">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=56FFEDF6F91BF73527DFE9C7B3A63400?doi=10.1.1.127.8508&amp;rank=4</link><title>and Development of GIS based on Asian Culture\-</title><description>and Development of GIS based on Asian Culture\-

by Kakumoto Shigeru, Kosugi Yukio, Hatayama Michinori, Kameda Hiroyuki

"... and Development of GIS based on Asian Culture \- KAKUMOTO Shigeru and KOSUGI Yukio Tokyo Institute of Technology ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

information is based on &lt;em&gt;culture&lt;/em&gt; and way of living of each country, we believe GIS based on &lt;em&gt;Asian&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;culture&lt;/em&gt; has</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7014-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7014_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:06:56">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=56FFEDF6F91BF73527DFE9C7B3A63400?doi=10.1.1.324.3588&amp;rank=5</link><title>World-wide web: The information universe</title><description>World-wide web: The information universe

by Tim Berners-lee, Robert Cailliau, Jean-françois Groff, Bernd Pollermann \- Electronic Netw0rkinn:Research. Applications and Policy, 8(2), Westport k ~ spring , 1992

"... all you need to know about electronic publishing, high-energy physics or for that matter Asian culture ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 196 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

-energy physics or for that matter &lt;em&gt;Asian&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;culture&lt;/em&gt;. If you are reading this article on paper, you can only dream</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7014-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7014_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:07:31">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=56FFEDF6F91BF73527DFE9C7B3A63400?doi=10.1.1.323.1567&amp;rank=6</link><title>Situational Differences in Dialectical Emotions 1 Running head: DIALECTICAL EMOTIONS, EAST ASIANS</title><description>Situational Differences in Dialectical Emotions 1 Running head: DIALECTICAL EMOTIONS, EAST ASIANS

by Janxin Leu, Batja Mesquita, Phoebe C. Ellsworth, Zhang Zhiyong, Yuan Huijuan, Emma Buchtel, Mayumi Karasawa, Takahiko Masuda

"... to expect that North American-East Asian cultural differences may be more pronounced in positive situations ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Past research generally suggests that East &lt;em&gt;Asians&lt;/em&gt; tolerate opposing feelings or dialectical</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7014-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7014_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:07:52">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=56FFEDF6F91BF73527DFE9C7B3A63400?doi=10.1.1.296.7276&amp;rank=7</link><title>Asians</title><description>Asians

by Rebecca Lobb, Andrew D Pinto, Aisha Lofters

"... culturally tailored health promotion services to South Asians in Mississauga and Brampton, the largest cities ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Using concept mapping in the knowledge-to-action process to compare stakeholder opinions on barriers to use of cancer screening among South</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7014-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7014_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:08:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=56FFEDF6F91BF73527DFE9C7B3A63400?doi=10.1.1.207.3663&amp;rank=8</link><title>Asian</title><description>Asian

by unknown authors

"... Immigration population Asians representing Control ethnicity born Include local institute least latest ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

declined data departments less Mortal India interventions blacks treatment international origin resistance race non-Hispanic compared proportion</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7014-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7014_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:08:22">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=56FFEDF6F91BF73527DFE9C7B3A63400?doi=10.1.1.408.1842&amp;rank=9</link><title>Asian</title><description>Asian

by Yin-wong Cheung, Jude Yuen, Cesifo Working, Paper No, Yin-wong Cheung, Jude Yuen , 2004

"... stochastic trend, business cycles, output losses, exchange rate regime, Asian economies. Yin-Wong Cheung ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

An electronic version of the paper may be downloaded</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7014-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7014_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:08:36">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=56FFEDF6F91BF73527DFE9C7B3A63400?doi=10.1.1.73.8091&amp;rank=10</link><title>Social Network Sites: A Definition A History of Social Network Sites Previous Scholarship</title><description>Social Network Sites: A Definition A History of Social Network Sites Previous Scholarship

by Nicole B. Ellison

"... consistent, the cultures that emerge around SNSs are varied. Most sites support the maintenance of pre ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 220 (6 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>