<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7036">holiday houses ardennes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:22:04" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7036-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7036_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:22:07">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1B02DE0DA6A3044C0957722A096BBA66?doi=10.1.1.195.9411&amp;rank=1</link><title>Holidays</title><description>Holidays

by Vic Garces, Local Wisdom

"... President Call for Papers 2 Member News 3 New Member Profiles 4 TS-SIS News 5 Local Wisdom 6 Happy Holidays ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

www.aallnet.org/chapter/ mall MALL Listserv To subscribe, point your browser to:</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7036-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7036_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:23:01">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1B02DE0DA6A3044C0957722A096BBA66?doi=10.1.1.13.1501&amp;rank=2</link><title>Analysis of a Campus-wide Wireless Network</title><description>Analysis of a Campus-wide Wireless Network

by David Kotz, Kobby Essien \- In Proceedings of ACM Mobicom , 2002

"... and fraternities, but also include some Dartmouth-owned housing for faculty and staff, and a residential facility ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 256 (16 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Understanding usage patterns in wireless local-area networks (WLANs) is critical for those who develop, deploy, and manage WLAN technology, as well as those who develop systems and application software for wireless networks. This paper presents results from the largest and most comprehensive trace of network activity in a large, production wireless LAN. For eleven weeks we traced the activity of nearly two thousand users drawn from a general campus population, using a campus-wide network of 476 access points spread over 161 buildings. Our study expands on those done by Tang and Baker, with a significantly larger and broader population. We found that residential traffic...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7036-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7036_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:24:13">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1B02DE0DA6A3044C0957722A096BBA66?doi=10.1.1.1.4372&amp;rank=3</link><title>The Changing Usage of a Mature Campus-wide Wireless Network</title><description>The Changing Usage of a Mature Campus-wide Wireless Network

by Tristan Henderson, David Kotz, Ilya Abyzov \- In Proceedings of ACM MOBICOM , 2004

"... -campus student housing or athletics facilities. We ignored the few (5%) sessions that visit these APs when ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 236 (11 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Wireless Local Area Networks (WLANs) are now commonplace on many academic and corporate campuses. As "Wi-Fi" technology becomes ubiquitous, it is increasingly important to understand trends in the usage of these networks.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7036-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7036_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:25:18">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1B02DE0DA6A3044C0957722A096BBA66?doi=10.1.1.132.3463&amp;rank=4</link><title>Why Bounded Rationality</title><description>Why Bounded Rationality

by John Conlisk, Garey Ramey \- Journal of Economic Literature , 1996

"... and Kenneth French 1988); predictable end-of-week, end-of-year, seasonal, and holiday effects (Thaler 1987 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 205 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Rothschild, and three most helpful referees. Very special thanks for many years of helpful insights are due to Richard Day and Luigi Ermini. Hamlet: “What a piece of work is a man! how noble in reason! how infinite in faculties!”</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7036-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7036_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:26:14">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1B02DE0DA6A3044C0957722A096BBA66?doi=10.1.1.199.4319&amp;rank=5</link><title>Analysis of Holiday Packages</title><description>Analysis of Holiday Packages

by Stephan Haroutunian, Pandelis Mitsis, Panos Pashardes, Stephan Haroutunian, Elis Mitsis

"... for the Hedonic Analysis of Holiday Packages Stephan Haroutunian Economics Research Centre University of Cyprus ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

the brochures of tour operators can be useful in explaining price variation between &lt;em&gt;holiday&lt;/em&gt; packages. Using</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7036-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7036_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:27:14">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1B02DE0DA6A3044C0957722A096BBA66?doi=10.1.1.169.1999&amp;rank=6</link><title>Holiday Inn near</title><description>Holiday Inn near

by Leo Hurwicz Turns, Spain Held At The , 2007

"... at the Holiday Inn near the West Bank campus, the event started at 1:45pm with opening remarks by University ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

hosted a 90th birthday celebration for Leo Hurwicz in the form of a conference</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7036-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7036_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:28:16">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1B02DE0DA6A3044C0957722A096BBA66?doi=10.1.1.121.8283&amp;rank=7</link><title>Constructing personal identities in holiday letters</title><description>Constructing personal identities in holiday letters

by Stephen P. Banks, Esther Louie, Martha Einerson

"... ﻿Constructing personal identities in holiday letters Stephen P. Banks University of Idaho Esther ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 3 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

A collection of &lt;em&gt;holiday&lt;/em&gt; letters is analyzed using the grounded theory method to generate a matrix</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7036-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7036_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:29:16">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1B02DE0DA6A3044C0957722A096BBA66?doi=10.1.1.392.4666&amp;rank=8</link><title>The Bankin2 and Insurance Holidays of 1933</title><description>The Bankin2 and Insurance Holidays of 1933

by Thomas F. Huertas, Joan L. Silverman

"... ﻿The Bankin2 and Insurance Holidays of 1933 Thomas F. Huertas and Joan L. Silverman During 1933 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

During 1933 there were two financial &lt;em&gt;holidays&lt;/em&gt;, one in banking and one in life insurance. The first</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7036-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7036_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:30:13">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1B02DE0DA6A3044C0957722A096BBA66?doi=10.1.1.321.2511&amp;rank=9</link><title>Private label price rigidity during holiday periods</title><description>Private label price rigidity during holiday periods

by Georg Müller, W Butterfield Rd, Th Floor, Mark Bergen, Shantanu Dutta, Daniel Levy \- Applied Economics Letters , 2006

"... ﻿Private Label Price Rigidity during Holiday Periods Georg Müller Strategic Pricing Group One ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 2 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Session participants at the American Economic Association Meetings for comments. We are particularly grateful to Walter Oi, the discussant at the NBER-CRIW conference, and to John Carlson, the discussant at the AEA meeting, for insightful comments and suggestions. We also thank Dennis Carlton, Haipeng (Allan) Chen, Bob Chirinko, Hashem Dezhbakhsh, Akshay Rao, Sourav Ray, as well as the Economics Seminar participants at Emory University and the Marketing Seminar participants at Harvard University and University of Minnesota, for useful comments and discussions. Finally, we thank the University of Chicago and Dominick’s for providing access to their data set. All authors contributed equally: we rotate co-authorship. The usual disclaimer applies.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7036-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7036_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:31:18">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1B02DE0DA6A3044C0957722A096BBA66?doi=10.1.1.178.2383&amp;rank=10</link><title>Holidays as announced Phone Numbers Reference 953-2888</title><description>Holidays as announced Phone Numbers Reference 953-2888

by Book Circ, Columbus Day , 800

"... -1645 Holidays as announced Phone Numbers Reference 953-2888 Book Circ 953-2230 Doc Circ 953-2348 Map Room 953 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Authority Collection The Authority collection is &lt;em&gt;housed&lt;/em&gt; in the east wing of the library</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>