<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7044">song of ice and fire</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:44:14" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7044-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7044_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:44:23">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A4228B2E308CE0D5BD43C4B164C56410?doi=10.1.1.206.2669&amp;rank=1</link><title>Random key predistribution schemes for sensor networks</title><description>Random key predistribution schemes for sensor networks

by Haowen Chan, Adrian Perrig, Dawn Song \- IN PROCEEDINGS OF THE 2003 IEEE SYMPOSIUM ON SECURITY AND PRIVACY , 2003

"... ﻿Random Key Predistribution Schemes for Sensor Networks 1 Haowen Chan Adrian Perrig Dawn Song 21 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 543 (15 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Key establishment in sensor networks is a challenging problem because asymmetric key cryptosystems are unsuitable for use in resource constrained sensor nodes, and also because the nodes could be physically compromised by an adversary. We present three new mechanisms for key establishment using the framework of pre-distributing a random set of keys to each node. First, in the q-composite keys scheme, we trade off the unlikeliness of a large-scale network attack in order to significantly strengthen random key predistribution’s strength against smaller-scale attacks. Second, in the multipath-reinforcement scheme, we show how to strengthen the security between any two nodes by leveraging the security of other links. Finally, we present the random-pairwise keys scheme, which perfectly preserves the secrecy of the rest of the network when any node is captured, and also enables node-to-node authentication and quorum-based revocation.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7044-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7044_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:45:25">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A4228B2E308CE0D5BD43C4B164C56410?doi=10.1.1.27.697&amp;rank=2</link><title>Competitive Hebbian Learning through Spike-Timing-Dependent Synaptic Plasticity</title><description>Competitive Hebbian Learning through Spike-Timing-Dependent Synaptic Plasticity

by Sen Song, Kenneth D. Miller, L. F. Abbott, Neuroscience Graduate Program , 2000

"... Competitive Hebbian Learning Through Spike-Timing-Dependent Synaptic Plasticity Sen Song, Kenneth ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 258 (5 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Hebbian models of development and learning require both activity-dependent synaptic plasticity and a mechanism that induces competition between different synapses. Recent experiments have characterized a form of long-term synaptic plasticity that depends on the relative timing of pre- and postsynaptic action potentials. In modeling studies, this form of synaptic modification, which we call spike-timing-dependent plasticity (STDP), automatically adjusts synaptic strengths so that the postsynaptic neuron becomes more sensitive to presynaptic spike timing. It has been argued that neurons in vivo operate in such a balanced or irregular ring mode, and STDP may thus explain how the required level of excitation arises and is maintained. Despite being synapse specific, STDP generates competition between different synapses because they compete for control of the timing of postsynaptic action potentials. By combining synaptic modification and competition, STPD can serve as a mechanism for competitiv...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7044-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7044_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:46:32">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A4228B2E308CE0D5BD43C4B164C56410?doi=10.1.1.94.6332&amp;rank=3</link><title>Re-place-ing Space: The Roles of Place and Space in Collaborative Systems</title><description>Re-place-ing Space: The Roles of Place and Space in Collaborative Systems

by Steve Harrison, Paul Dourish , 1996

"... to interpret a song or a dance as part of a presentation, if faced with it suddenly. It is a sense of place ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 251 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Many collaborative and communicative environments use notions of “space ” and spatial organisation to facilitate and structure interaction. We argue that a focus on spatial models is misplaced. Drawing on understandings from architecture and urban design, as well as from our own research findings, we highlight the critical distinction between “space ” and “place”. While designers use spatial models to support interaction, we show how it is actually a notion of “place ” which frames interactive behaviour. This leads us to re-evaluate spatial systems, and discuss how “place”, rather than “space”, can support CSCW design.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7044-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7044_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:47:34">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A4228B2E308CE0D5BD43C4B164C56410?doi=10.1.1.115.6364&amp;rank=4</link><title>Neuronal Synchrony: A Versatile Code for the Definition of Relations?</title><description>Neuronal Synchrony: A Versatile Code for the Definition of Relations?

by Wolf Singer

"... on the analysis of the firing patterns of individual neurons that have been recorded one by one in succession ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 229 (11 self) \- Add to MetaCart

on the analysis of the &lt;em&gt;firing&lt;/em&gt; patterns of individual neurons that have been recorded one by one in succession</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7044-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7044_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:48:34">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A4228B2E308CE0D5BD43C4B164C56410?doi=10.1.1.4.3270&amp;rank=5</link><title>The Princeton Shape Benchmark</title><description>The Princeton Shape Benchmark

by Philip Shilane, Patrick Min, Michael Kazhdan, Thomas Funkhouser \- In Shape Modeling International , 2004

"... to be included in meaningful experiments. For example, there were only two drill presses and three fire hydrants ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 208 (9 self) \- Add to MetaCart

In recent years, many shape representations and geometric algorithms have been proposed for matching 3D shapes. Usually, each algorithm is tested on a different (small) database of 3D models, and thus no direct comparison is available for competing methods.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7044-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7044_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:49:37">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A4228B2E308CE0D5BD43C4B164C56410?doi=10.1.1.174.2961&amp;rank=6</link><title>Mental Accounting Matters</title><description>Mental Accounting Matters

by H. Thaler \- JOURNAL OF BEHAVIORAL DECISION MAKING J. BEHAV. DEC. MAKING, 12: 183~206 (1999) , 1999

"... , and can be defined narrowly or broadly. A wellknown song implores poker players to 'never count your money ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 189 (5 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Mental accounting is the set of cognitive operations used by individuals and households to organize, evaluate, and keep track of financial activities. Making use of research on this topic over the past decade, this paper summarizes the current state of our knowledge about how people engage in mental accounting activities. Three components of mental accounting receive the most attention. This first captures how outcomes are perceived and experienced, and how decisions are made and subsequently evaluated. The accounting system provides the inputs to be both ex ante and ex post cost-benefit analyses. A second component of mental accounting involves the assignment of activities to specific accounts. Both the sources and uses of funds are labeled in real as well as in mental accounting systems. Expenditures are grouped into categories (housing, food, etc.) and spending is sometimes constrained by implicit or explicit budgets. The third component of mental accounting concerns the frequency with which accounts are evaluated and 'choice bracketing'. Accounts can be balanced daily,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7044-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7044_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:50:50">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A4228B2E308CE0D5BD43C4B164C56410?doi=10.1.1.116.6688&amp;rank=7</link><title>Recovering human body configurations: Combining segmentation and recognition</title><description>Recovering human body configurations: Combining segmentation and recognition

by Greg Mori, Xiaofeng Ren, Alexei A. Efros, Jitendra Malik \- In CVPR , 2004

"... the parts and finds the best assembly. Song et al. [13] detect corner features in video sequences and model ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 171 (8 self) \- Add to MetaCart

localized joints and limbs. (c) Segmentation mask associated with human figure. The goal of this work is to take an image such as the one in Figure 1(a), detect a human figure, and localize his joints and limbs (b) along with their associated pixel masks (c). In this work we attempt to tackle this problem in a general setting. The dataset we use is a collection of sports news photographs of baseball players, varying dramatically in pose and clothing. The approach that we take is to use segmentation to guide our recognition algorithm to salient bits of the image. We use this segmentation approach to build limb and torso detectors, the outputs of which are assembled into human figures. We present quantitative results on torso localization, in addition to shortlisted full body configurations. 1.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7044-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7044_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:52:00">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A4228B2E308CE0D5BD43C4B164C56410?doi=10.1.1.386.2693&amp;rank=8</link><title>Synaptic modification by correlated activity: Hebb’s postulate revisited</title><description>Synaptic modification by correlated activity: Hebb’s postulate revisited

by Guo-qiang Bi, Mu-ming Poo, Key Words \- Annual Review of Neuroscience , 2001

"... an axon of cell A is near enough to excite cell B or repeatedly or consistently takes part in firing it ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 126 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

in &lt;em&gt;firing&lt;/em&gt; it, some growth or metabolic change takes place in one or both cells such that A’s efficiency</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7044-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7044_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:53:07">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A4228B2E308CE0D5BD43C4B164C56410?doi=10.1.1.144.289&amp;rank=9</link><title>Collaborative activity and technological design: Task coordination in London Underground control rooms</title><description>Collaborative activity and technological design: Task coordination in London Underground control rooms

by Christian Heath, Paul Luff \- In , 1991

"... to a song to draw the DIA's attention to an emergent problem within the operation of the service ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 135 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Despite technical advances in CSCW over the past few years we still have relatively little understanding of the organisation of collaborative activity in real world. technologically supported, work environments. Indeed, it has been suggested that the failure of various technological applications may derive from its relative insensitivity to ordinary work practice and situated conduct. In this paper we discuss the possibility of utilising recent developments within social science, and in particular the naturalistic analysis of organisational conduct and interpersonal communication, as a basis for the design and development of tools and technologies to support collaborative work. Focussing on the Line Control Rooms on London Underground, a complex multimedia environment in transition, we begin to explicate the informal work practices and procedures whereby personnel systematically communicate information and coordinate a disparate collection of tasks and activities. These empirical investigations form the foundation to the design of new tools to support collaborative work in Line Control Rooms; technologies which will be sensitive to the ordinary conduct and practical skills of organisational personnel in the London Underground.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7044-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7044_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:54:21">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A4228B2E308CE0D5BD43C4B164C56410?doi=10.1.1.25.8432&amp;rank=10</link><title>Spatio-Temporal Data Types: An Approach to Modeling and Querying Moving Objects in Databases</title><description>Spatio-Temporal Data Types: An Approach to Modeling and Querying Moving Objects in Databases

by Martin Erwig, Ralf Hartmut Güting, Markus Schneider, Michalis Vazirgiannis , 1999

"... the polar ice cap grow? Does it move? . Where must glacier X have been at time Y (backward projection ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 135 (37 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Spatio-temporal databases deal with geometries changing over time. In general, geometries cannot only change in discrete steps, but continuously, and we are talking about moving objects. If only the position in space of an object is relevant, then moving point is a basic abstraction; if also the extent is of interest, then the moving region abstraction captures moving as well as growing or shrinking regions. We propose a new line of research where moving points and moving regions are viewed as three-dimensional (2D space + time) or higher-dimensional entities whose structure and behavior is captured by modeling them as abstract data types. Such types can be integrated as base (attribute) data types into relational, object-oriented, or other DBMS data models; they can be implemented as data blades, cartridges, etc. for extensible DBMSs. We expect these spatio-temporal data types to play a similarly fundamental role for spatio-temporal databases as spatial data types have played for sp...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>