<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7047">Dewar flask</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:16:51" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7047-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7047_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:16:54">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=31E92B424FE400DD375930DB7C0E10D9?doi=10.1.1.269.6222&amp;rank=1</link><title>Work Practices Using Vacuums</title><description>Work Practices Using Vacuums

by unknown authors , 2012

"... . Vacuum trap with connections clamped (arrows). Trap inserted into dewar flask (with polyethylene netting ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

inserted into &lt;em&gt;dewar&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;flask&lt;/em&gt; (with polyethylene netting) with lid covered (towel). Secure Traps Make sure</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7047-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7047_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:18:01">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=31E92B424FE400DD375930DB7C0E10D9?doi=10.1.1.380.4575&amp;rank=2</link><title>Calorimetric Studies of Palladium Alloy Cathodes Using FleischmannPons Dewar Type Cells</title><description>Calorimetric Studies of Palladium Alloy Cathodes Using FleischmannPons Dewar Type Cells

by Melvin H. Miles \- in 8th International Conference on Cold Fusion. 2000. Lerici (La Spezia), Italy: Italian Physical Society

"... ﻿Calorimetric Studies of Palladium Alloy Cathodes Using Fleischmann-Pons Dewar Type Cells Melvin H ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 3 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

My first three experiments conducted at NHE using the Fleischmann-Pons (F-P) &lt;em&gt;Dewar&lt;/em&gt; type cells</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7047-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7047_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:19:12">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=31E92B424FE400DD375930DB7C0E10D9?doi=10.1.1.281.2662&amp;rank=3</link><title>Frozen thin sections of fresh tissue for electron microscopy, with a description of pancreas and liver</title><description>Frozen thin sections of fresh tissue for electron microscopy, with a description of pancreas and liver

by Kent Christensen \- J . Cell Biol , 1972

"... -shape i Dewar flask with a knifeholder in its depths replaces the stage of the microtome ; a bar extends ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 4 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

to be cut on a virtually unmodified ultramicrotome kept at room temperature. A bowl-shape i &lt;em&gt;Dewar&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;flask&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7047-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7047_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:20:23">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=31E92B424FE400DD375930DB7C0E10D9?doi=10.1.1.273.5838&amp;rank=4</link><title>INHIBITION OF TRANSPLANTABLE MOUSE TUMOR GROWTH BY TISSUE EXTRACTS AND THEIR PROTEIN FRACTIONS</title><description>INHIBITION OF TRANSPLANTABLE MOUSE TUMOR GROWTH BY TISSUE EXTRACTS AND THEIR PROTEIN FRACTIONS

by D. A. M. A_cfadyen, Ernest Sturm, James, B. Murphy , 1939

"... of gestation. The material from the cow, when transportation was necessary, was placed immediately in a Dewar ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

of gestation. The material from the cow, when transportation was necessary, was placed immediately in a &lt;em&gt;Dewar&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7047-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7047_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:21:31">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=31E92B424FE400DD375930DB7C0E10D9?doi=10.1.1.210.8648&amp;rank=5</link><title>RESEARCH AND TECHNICAL NOTES Thermal contraction of Vespel SP-22 and</title><description>RESEARCH AND TECHNICAL NOTES Thermal contraction of Vespel SP-22 and

by Stycast From K To K

"... Stainless steel pushrod tube Stainless steel support tubes Test piece OFHC copper Dewar flask The authors ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

, and are immersed in liquid in a &lt;em&gt;dewar&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;flask&lt;/em&gt;. Expansion or contraction of the test piece relative to the copper</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7047-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7047_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:22:31">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=31E92B424FE400DD375930DB7C0E10D9?doi=10.1.1.389.7993&amp;rank=6</link><title>Midribs of Date Palm as a Raw Material for Wood-Cement Composite Industry in Saudi Arabia</title><description>Midribs of Date Palm as a Raw Material for Wood-Cement Composite Industry in Saudi Arabia

by Ramadan A. Nasser, Hamad A. Al-mefarrej

"... using a 2-litter Dewar flask. The suitability of date palm for this industry was made according ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

, hydration tests of net cement and date palm-cement mixture were carried out using a 2-litter &lt;em&gt;Dewar&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;flask&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7047-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7047_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:23:31">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=31E92B424FE400DD375930DB7C0E10D9?doi=10.1.1.281.8396&amp;rank=7</link><title>Fixation of neural tissues for electron microscope by perfusion with solutions of osmium tetroxide</title><description>Fixation of neural tissues for electron microscope by perfusion with solutions of osmium tetroxide

by Sanford L. Palay, S. M. Mcgee-russell, D. Phil (oxon, Mary A. Grillo, Ph. D \- J. Cell Biol , 1955

"... ). The perfusion apparatvs (Fig. 1) consisted of a glass reservoir shaped like a Dewar flask 1 from which a rubber ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 27 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper describes in detail a method for obtaining nearly uniform fixation of the nervous system by vascular perfusion with solutions of osmium tetroxide. Criteria are given for evaluating the degree of success achieved in the preservation of all the cellular components of the nervous system. The method permits analysis of the structural relations between cells at the electron microscopic level to an extent that has not been possible heretofore. One of the greatest impediments to the electron microscopy of the nervous system has been the inadequacy of the methods currently available for processing neural tissues. This technical deficiency is less evident in studies of the peripheral nervous system than in those of the central nervous system, where the exquisite susceptibility of the tissue to trauma and anoxia leads to severe, recognizable artifacts unless great care is taken</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7047-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7047_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:24:27">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=31E92B424FE400DD375930DB7C0E10D9?doi=10.1.1.405.681&amp;rank=8</link><title>A Quantitative Respirometric Method for Monitoring Compost Stability</title><description>A Quantitative Respirometric Method for Monitoring Compost Stability

by D. A. Iannottil

"... of change of oxygen level in air over a compost sample incubated in a flask at 37°C were converted to a rate ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

level in air over a compost sample incubated in a &lt;em&gt;flask&lt;/em&gt; at 37°C were converted to a rate of 0, uptake</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7047-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7047_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:25:27">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=31E92B424FE400DD375930DB7C0E10D9?doi=10.1.1.380.1416&amp;rank=9</link><title>Self-Polarisation of Fusion Diodes: From Excess Energy to Energy</title><description>Self-Polarisation of Fusion Diodes: From Excess Energy to Energy

by Fabrice David, John Giles

"... release. Here is the principle of our differential calorimeter: Two similar Dewar flasks contain distilled ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Conventionally, the cold fusion reaction produces heat. (1),(2) The authors have sought a different approach, wherein the device has no input energy, relying on the energy produced by cold fusion in the device. The device consists of diodes fabricated as powder, with a large surface junction made up of a semiconductor in contact with palladium charged with deuterium. The apparent fusion reactions take place in the junction between the semiconductor and the Palladium powder, which produces an excitation which is transmitted to the electrons. This excitation increases their energy and allows them to cross the bandgap of the semiconductor and pass into the conduction band, as in a photovoltaic cell. This energy very quickly appears as a spontaneous potential difference which can reach over 0.5 volt per junction. The potential drop concentrates on the junction region, and at a nano scale the electric field reaches considerable values, higher than the megavolt per meter, which constrains the deuterium nuclei and increases the probability of deuterium</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7047-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7047_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:26:25">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=31E92B424FE400DD375930DB7C0E10D9?doi=10.1.1.167.2566&amp;rank=10</link><title>Atmospheric Measurement Techniques Continuous measurements of atmospheric oxygen and carbon</title><description>Atmospheric Measurement Techniques Continuous measurements of atmospheric oxygen and carbon

by I. T. Van Der Laan-luijkx, R. E. M. Neubert, S. Van Der Laan, H. A. J. Meijer , 2010

"... infrared absorption instruments, respectively. Furthermore, the station includes an automated air flask ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

instruments, respectively. Furthermore, the station includes an automated air &lt;em&gt;flask&lt;/em&gt; sampler for laboratory</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>