<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7048">pictures auvergne</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:27:14" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7048-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7048_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:27:17">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E7D36881C99721C41574903380FF6579?doi=10.1.1.335.1305&amp;rank=1</link><title>CERDI-CNRS, Université d’Auvergne, and European Union Development Network</title><description>CERDI-CNRS, Université d’Auvergne, and European Union Development Network

by Jean-louis Arcand , 2004

"... Compliance and Rank Dependent Expected Utility JEAN-LOUIS ARCAND CERDI-CNRS, Université d’Auvergne ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Formulating the classic Allingham and Sandmo [1972] tax compliance problem under Rank Dependent Expected Utility (RDEU) provides a simple explanation for the “excess ” level of full compliance observed in empirical studies, which standard Expected Utility (EU) theory is unable to explain. RDEU provides a compelling answer to this puzzle, without the need for the moral sentiments or stigma arguments that have recently been advanced in the literature. Formally, we show that the threshold audit probability or penalty rate at which full compliance becomes optimal for the decisionmaker are significantly lower under RDEU axiomatics than in the EU case, and that the optimal level of underreporting is lower under RDEU. Numerical simulations using various parameterizations of the probability weighting function illustrate the large quantitative differences between the two models, while a simulation of underreporting rates in the US over the past 50 years shows how RDEU can go some way towards explaining the tax-compliance puzzle. Key words: rank-dependent expected utility, tax-compliance</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7048-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7048_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:28:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E7D36881C99721C41574903380FF6579?doi=10.1.1.302.7879&amp;rank=2</link><title>Pour l‟obtention du titre de Docteur ès Sciences Economiques Par</title><description>Pour l‟obtention du titre de Docteur ès Sciences Economiques Par

by Mouhamadou Moustapha Ly, Mr. Jean-louis Combes, Mr. Adama Diaw, Marc-alexandre Sénégas Professeur Université Montesquieu-bordeaux, Jean-louis Combes, Professeur Université D‟auvergne (cerdi, Adama Diaw, Professeur Université, Gaston Berger, Saint-louis Sénégal , 2011

"... ﻿Université d‟Auvergne Clermont-Ferrand I Faculté de Sciences Economiques et de Gestion Centre d ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

1 L’Université d’&lt;em&gt;Auvergne&lt;/em&gt; Clermont-1 n’entend donner aucune approbation ni improbation aux opinions</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7048-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7048_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:28:55">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E7D36881C99721C41574903380FF6579?doi=10.1.1.393.2646&amp;rank=3</link><title>Netherlands (2011)" Guiding Active Contours for Tree Leaf Segmentation and Identification ⋆</title><description>Netherlands (2011)" Guiding Active Contours for Tree Leaf Segmentation and Identification ⋆

by Guillaume Cerutti, Laure Tougne, Julien Mille, Antoine Vacavant, Didier Coquin, Domaine Universitaire, Annecy Le Vieux , 2011

"... , Université d’Auvergne, ISIT, F-63001, Clermont-Ferrand (antoine.vacavant@(email omitted);) 5 LISTIC ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract. In the process of tree identification from &lt;em&gt;pictures&lt;/em&gt; of leaves in a natural background</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7048-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7048_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:29:30">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E7D36881C99721C41574903380FF6579?doi=10.1.1.406.6811&amp;rank=4</link><title>The authors</title><description>The authors

by Nasser Ary Tanimoune, Cécile Batisse, Mary-françoise Renard, Nasser Ary Tanimoune, Clermont Fd

"... ) Cécile BATISSE Associate Professor, Clermont Université, Université d'Auvergne, CNRS, UMR 6587, CERDI ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Durbin specifications, we present a much clearer &lt;em&gt;picture&lt;/em&gt; of FDI dispersion and spatial convergence across</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7048-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7048_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:30:22">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E7D36881C99721C41574903380FF6579?doi=10.1.1.406.1997&amp;rank=5</link><title>Understanding Leaves in Natural Images- A Model-Based Approach for Tree Species Identification ✩</title><description>Understanding Leaves in Natural Images- A Model-Based Approach for Tree Species Identification ✩

by Guillaume Cerutti A, Laure Tougne A, Julien Mille A, Antoine Vacavant D, Didier Coquin E , 2013

"... , France c Université Lyon 1, LIRIS, UMR5205, F-69622, France d Clermont Université , Université d’Auvergne ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

to help recognize species, starting from a &lt;em&gt;picture&lt;/em&gt; of a leaf in a complex natural background. A two</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7048-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7048_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:31:12">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E7D36881C99721C41574903380FF6579?doi=10.1.1.10.2180&amp;rank=6</link><title>Structuration of Phenotypes / Genotypes through Galois Lattices and Implications</title><description>Structuration of Phenotypes / Genotypes through Galois Lattices and Implications

by Vincent Duquenne, Caroline Chabert, Améziane Cherfouh, Jean-maurice Delabar, Anne-lise Doyen, Douglas Pickering \- PROC. ICCS-2001 INTL. WORKSHOP ON CONCEPT LATTICES{BASED THEORY, METHODS, AND TOOLS FOR KNOWLEDGE DISCOVERY IN DATABASES , 2001

"... -consistent left-handers. The previous graphics give a clear picture on the hierarchies of actions ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 3 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The Galois Lattice of a binary relation formalizes it as a concept system, dually ordered in "extension" / "intension". All implications between conjunctions of properties holding in it are summarized by a (recursive) canonical basis -all basis having the same cardinality (see [MR #87k:08009]). We report</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7048-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7048_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:32:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E7D36881C99721C41574903380FF6579?doi=10.1.1.404.7271&amp;rank=7</link><title>A.: ReVeS Participation - Tree Species Classification using Random Forests and Botanical Features. In: Working notes of CLEF 2012 conference</title><description>A.: ReVeS Participation - Tree Species Classification using Random Forests and Botanical Features. In: Working notes of CLEF 2012 conference

by Guillaume Cerutti, Violaine Antoine, Laure Tougne, Julien Mille, Lionel Valet, Didier Coquin, Antoine Vacavant, Domaine Universitaire, Annecy Le Vieux , 2012

"... , Annecy le Vieux 5 Clermont Université , Université d’Auvergne, ISIT, F-63001, Clermont-Ferrand Abstract ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 3 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract. This paper summarizes the participation of the ReVeS project to the ImageCLEF 2012 Plant Identification task. Aiming to develop a system for tree leaf identification on mobile devices, our method is designed to cope with the challenges of complex natural images and to enable a didactic interaction with the user. The approach relies on a two step model-driven segmentation and on the evaluation of high-level characteristics that make a semantic interpretation possible, as well as more generic shape features. All these descriptors are combined in a random forest classification algorithm, and their significance evaluated. Our team ranks 4th overall, 3rd on natural images, which constitutes a very satisfying performance with respect to the project’s objectives. 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7048-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7048_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:33:02">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E7D36881C99721C41574903380FF6579?doi=10.1.1.164.3099&amp;rank=8</link><title>Proof of Property 1 – Overlapping Property</title><description>Proof of Property 1 – Overlapping Property

by Pierre Fite Georgel, Camp Tu München, Adrien Bartoli, Nassir Navab, Camp Tu München

"... Pierre Fite Georgel CAMP - TU München ∗ Adrien Bartoli Université d’Auvergne † Nassir Navab CAMP - TU ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

This appendix introduces the proofs of Property 1 and 2 related to the discretization scheme; and a new compact kernel that we use throughout our method. Notation. Matrix are in upper case bold (e.g. A) and vector in lower case bold (e.g. a). We consider two cameras: a source S and a target T. □ (a, b) ⊂ R 2 is the quad formed by the two points a ∈ R 2 and b ∈ R 2. o □(a,b) ∈ R 2 is the center of the quad □ (a, b) and c □(a,b) ∈ R 2×4 its four corners. E is the set of Essential Matrices [2]; it is a variety of dimension N (N ≤ 5) in R 9 (the set of 3 × 3 matrices). A. Overlapping properties As a reminder we redefine the relative rotation R (u) and translation t (u) cos (π − θ − α) 0 sin (π − θ − α) R (u) = ⎣ 0 1 0 ⎦, ⎡ − sin (π⎤ − θ − α) 0 cos (π − θ − α) sin (θ) t (u) = ⎣ 0 ⎦. cos (θ) (1) Property 1 Overlapping Property – See supplementary material for Proof ψ (u) = 0 ⇔ π + γS + γT &lt; θ + α &lt; 3π − γS − γT with γS (resp. γT) half the field of view of the source camera (resp. target). ψ (u) = 0 means no overlap.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7048-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7048_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:34:04">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E7D36881C99721C41574903380FF6579?doi=10.1.1.274.8650&amp;rank=9</link><title>Inequalities in Oral Health for Children with Disabilities: A French National Survey in Special Schools</title><description>Inequalities in Oral Health for Children with Disabilities: A French National Survey in Special Schools

by Martine Hennequin, Véronique Moysan, Didier Jourdan, Martine Dorin, Emmanuel Nicolas

"... 1,2 1 University of Auvergne (Clermont 1) EA 3847, Clermont-Ferrand, France, 2 CHU de Clermont ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Background: Despite wide recognition that children with disability often have poor oral health, few high quality, controlled results are available. Method: Twenty-four objective and subjective criteria covering feeding, autonomy, access to dental care, oral hygiene, oral disease, general health and behavior were evaluated in a observational cross-sectional study of 2,487 children with disability (DC group), 4,772 adolescents with disability (DA group) and 1,641 children without disability (NDC group). Five algorithms ranked the subjects according to clinical criteria in three original oral health indices: the Clinical Oral Health Index (COHI), indicating the level of oral health problems, the Clinical Oral Care Needs Index (COCNI) giving dental care need levels, and the Clinical Oral Prevention Index (COPI) determining possible needs in terms of dental education initiatives. Results: DC-group children presented poorer oral health and had greater needs in both treatment and preventive oral health actions than NDC-group children (OR = 3.97, 95 % CI = 3.25–4.86 for COHI; OR = 2.01, 95 % CI = 1.77–2.28 for COCNI; OR = 5.25, 95 % CI = 4.55–6.02 for COPI). These conditions were worse again in the DA group comparing to the DC group</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7048-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7048_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:35:29">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E7D36881C99721C41574903380FF6579?doi=10.1.1.382.2618&amp;rank=10</link><title>pone.0002564" DOI: 10.1371/journal.pone.0002564 Inequalities in Oral Health for Children with Disabilities: A French National Survey in Special Schools</title><description>pone.0002564" DOI: 10.1371/journal.pone.0002564 Inequalities in Oral Health for Children with Disabilities: A French National Survey in Special Schools

by Martine Hennequin, Véronique Moysan, Didier Jourdan, Martine Dorin, Emmanuel Nicolas

"... Jourdan 4 , Martine Dorin 3 , Emmanuel Nicolas 1,2 1 University of Auvergne (Clermont 1) EA 3847, Clermont ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Background: Despite wide recognition that children with disability often have poor oral health, few high quality, controlled results are available. Method: Twenty-four objective and subjective criteria covering feeding, autonomy, access to dental care, oral hygiene, oral disease, general health and behavior were evaluated in a observational cross-sectional study of 2,487 children with disability (DC group), 4,772 adolescents with disability (DA group) and 1,641 children without disability (NDC group). Five algorithms ranked the subjects according to clinical criteria in three original oral health indices: the Clinical Oral Health Index (COHI), indicating the level of oral health problems, the Clinical Oral Care Needs Index (COCNI) giving dental care need levels, and the Clinical Oral Prevention Index (COPI) determining possible needs in terms of dental education initiatives.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>