<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7052">hotel bruges</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:58:35" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7052-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7052_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:58:40">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A7F47E167443C5D3C065C51F648DB5CF?doi=10.1.1.362.5925&amp;rank=1</link><title>Orthopaedic Societies</title><description>Orthopaedic Societies

by Nico Verdonschot Phd, Johan Bellemans, Phd Md, Jan Victor, Phd Md , 2011

"... of the city of Bruges (Brugge), we made a selection of different hotels close (walking distance ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

of the International Society for Technology in Arthroplasty, which is</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7052-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7052_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:59:43">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A7F47E167443C5D3C065C51F648DB5CF?doi=10.1.1.203.1524&amp;rank=2</link><title>For Your Calendar..................................................2</title><description>For Your Calendar..................................................2

by Robert Roddy Md, Book Review

"... 18 months ago I visited the city of Bruges in Belgium. Bruges is beautiful and has become a post ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

I would like to thank the members of ASAP for giving me the privilege to serve as its President for the coming year. I hope those of you who were able to attend the recent meeting in Philadelphia enjoyed yourselves and found the presentations interesting. The meeting focused on various aspects of adolescent violence. My thanks to all who gave of their time to contribute. Our organization owes a great vote of thanks to our immediate Past President, Mark Wellek. Mark has over the past year been a champion in the cause of the abolition of the death penalty</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7052-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7052_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:01:08">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A7F47E167443C5D3C065C51F648DB5CF?doi=10.1.1.201.9761&amp;rank=3</link><title>THE CAPITAL MARKET BEFORE 1600*</title><description>THE CAPITAL MARKET BEFORE 1600*

by Meir Kohn, Jel Categories G , 1999

"... burghers of Bruges, Ghent, and Ypres (the drie steden) snapped up the issues of the smaller towns. 22 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

ABSTRACT: This paper describes the evolution of long-term debt and equity finance in medieval and early modern Europe. The main issuers of long-term debt were landowners and municipalities. The paper discusses the evolution of debt secured by land and the use by municipal borrowers of annuities and ‘funded debt ’ (securitization). The paper then describes the various forms of equity finance and how they addressed the corporate governance problem.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7052-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7052_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:02:07">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A7F47E167443C5D3C065C51F648DB5CF?doi=10.1.1.168.27&amp;rank=4</link><title>unknown title</title><description>unknown title

by unknown authors

"... will meet on the terrace of Hotel Villa Emilia (http://www.hotelvillaemilia.com/), Calle Calabria 115 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Inter 9 employs a creative drawing process based on what looks good to formulate entirely new ideas for enduring architectural issues. The unit encourages personal subjectivity and the ability of each student to defend the subjectivity of what looks good rather than the bogus objectivity of what is scientifically determined. Let’s not forget – architecture is an art, not a science. It questions the contemporary role of the drawing in architectural design and seeks to renew its vitality, and the project’s manufacture, via 3D printing techniques. The methods of mis-architecture include: mis-building, mis-shaping, mis-scaling, mis-reading, mis-constructing, mis-demeanours. Programme | Brief In 2009/10 Inter 9 will design the New Camp Nou in Barcelona. The club’s recent brief for the stadium redevelopment will be the guiding programmatic basis, but our own architectural and drawing processes will determine how you refashion the late-50s iron and concrete behemoth (designed by Francesc Mitjans-Miró, García Barbon and Soteras Mauri, 1957). Projects will be sited on the stadium’s current location, Avenida Arístides Maillol, will incorporate the existing field and stadium bowl, and will be geared to critiquing the typology’s perceived inflexibility.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7052-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7052_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:03:04">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A7F47E167443C5D3C065C51F648DB5CF?doi=10.1.1.169.2566&amp;rank=5</link><title>Latest News from the President of INNS 1</title><description>Latest News from the President of INNS 1

by Nikola Kasabov, Nikola Kasabov

"... , at the 18th European Symposium on Artificial Neural Networks (ESANN), 28-30 April 2010, Bruges, Belgium ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7052-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7052_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:04:07">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A7F47E167443C5D3C065C51F648DB5CF?doi=10.1.1.197.5527&amp;rank=6</link><title>“DEFINING, MEASURING AND EVALUATING CARRYING CAPACITY IN EUROPEAN TOURISM DESTINATIONS”</title><description>“DEFINING, MEASURING AND EVALUATING CARRYING CAPACITY IN EUROPEAN TOURISM DESTINATIONS”

by unknown authors

"... -2010 ..................... 4 Table 2: Overnight stays in hotels and similar establishments by residents and nonresidents ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Athens, 2002The Report “Material for a Document ” presents the findings from the Study “Defining, Measuring and Evaluating Carrying Capacity in European Tourism Destinations” (Contract number: B4-3040/2000/294577/MAR/D2), which was commissioned to the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7052-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7052_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:05:21">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A7F47E167443C5D3C065C51F648DB5CF?doi=10.1.1.198.9571&amp;rank=7</link><title>Overview</title><description>Overview

by unknown authors , 2001

"... ) Conference in Bruges. They were mainly interested in possible collaboration and sending staff to IRMM. Die ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

joint research centre</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7052-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7052_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:06:28">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A7F47E167443C5D3C065C51F648DB5CF?doi=10.1.1.138.2229&amp;rank=8</link><title>References</title><description>References

by unknown authors

"... -236. Ha, S.H. and Park, S.C. (1998): Application of data mining tools to hotel data mart on the Intranet ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

logistic normal regression. Journal of the American Statistical Association,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7052-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7052_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:07:34">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A7F47E167443C5D3C065C51F648DB5CF?doi=10.1.1.23.6548&amp;rank=9</link><title>Extensions of Linear Independent Component Analysis: Neural and Information-Theoretic Methods</title><description>Extensions of Linear Independent Component Analysis: Neural and Information-Theoretic Methods

by Petteri Pajunen

"... sources. In Proc. European Symposium on Articial Neural Networks (ESANN'97), pages 255260, Bruges, Belgium ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Obtaining information from measured data is a general problem which is encountered in numerous applications and fields of science. A goal of many data analysis methods is to transform the observed data into a representation which reveals the information contained in the data. Methods for obtaining such representations include principal component analysis, projection pursuit, cluster analysis, and neural unsupervised learning methods.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7052-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7052_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:08:45">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A7F47E167443C5D3C065C51F648DB5CF?doi=10.1.1.17.8581&amp;rank=10</link><title>Free-Space Optoelectronic Interconnections</title><description>Free-Space Optoelectronic Interconnections

by Philippe J. Marchand, Electronique Electrotechnique Automatique, Présentée À, L’université De Haute Alsace

"... in Computing, pp.541-545, Bruges, Belgium, June 1998. 62\. J. Ekman, P. Chandramani, R. Rozier, F. Kiamilev, J ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

this document I hope that the previous section of this introduction was sufficient to stimulate the technical appetite of the reader and entice him to pursue the reading of this document. In essence, this previous section abstracts out some of the work and beliefs that I have come to embrace after 7 years of research in the field of free-space optoelectronics</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>