<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7053">nintendo 3ds hack</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:09:54" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7053-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7053_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:09:58">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=49AFDADF832266998E52A389FEE0B684?doi=10.1.1.150.2868&amp;rank=1</link><title>Hacking the</title><description>Hacking the

by Nintendo Wii Remote, Johnny Chung Lee , 2006

"... ﻿T h e H a c k i n g T r a d i t i o n Hacking the Nintendo Wii Remote The global hacking community ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

The global &lt;em&gt;hacking&lt;/em&gt; community has collectively reverse-engineered a significant portion of one</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7053-02"><link>http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=49AFDADF832266998E52A389FEE0B684?doi=10.1.1.147.7660&amp;rank=2</link><title>Hacking Is Pervasive</title><description>Hacking Is Pervasive

by Joseph A. Paradiso, John Heidemann, Thomas G. Zimmerman

"... notably the Nintendo Wii, which is equipped with a 3D accelerometer, optical tracker, speaker, vibrator ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

computer system with malicious or criminal intent. However, &lt;em&gt;hacking’s&lt;/em&gt; older definitions are quite different</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7053-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7053_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:12:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=49AFDADF832266998E52A389FEE0B684?doi=10.1.1.389.2864&amp;rank=3</link><title>Forensic Analysis of the Nintendo Wii Game Console</title><description>Forensic Analysis of the Nintendo Wii Game Console

by Peter Stewart

"... ................................................................................. 25 3.3 Nintendo Wii Forensics ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

embodies the results of my own work and that it has been composed by myself. Following normal academic conventions, I have made due acknowledgement to the work of others. I give permission to the University of Strathclyde, Department of Computer and Information Sciences, to provide copies of the dissertation, at cost, to those who may in the future request a copy of the dissertation for private study or research. I give permission to the University of Strathclyde, Department of Computer and Information Sciences, to place a copy of the dissertation in a publicly available electronic archive.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7053-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7053_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:13:15">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=49AFDADF832266998E52A389FEE0B684?doi=10.1.1.173.8078&amp;rank=4</link><title>Designed to be Hacked: Benefits of user-side remanufacture in consumer electronics</title><description>Designed to be Hacked: Benefits of user-side remanufacture in consumer electronics

by Dominic Muren

"... ﻿Designed to be Hacked: Benefits of user-side remanufacture in consumer electronics Dominic Muren ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

enabling users to rearrange, fix, or otherwise &lt;em&gt;hack&lt;/em&gt; their parts into new devices at the end of the product</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7053-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7053_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:14:27">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=49AFDADF832266998E52A389FEE0B684?doi=10.1.1.190.1554&amp;rank=5</link><title>From Rule-Breaking to ROM-Hacking: Theorizing the Computer Game-as-Commodity</title><description>From Rule-Breaking to ROM-Hacking: Theorizing the Computer Game-as-Commodity

by Will Jordan

"... ﻿From Rule-Breaking to ROM-Hacking: Theorizing the Computer Game-as-Commodity Will Jordan ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

of game rules, I provide an account of emulation and ROM-&lt;em&gt;hacking&lt;/em&gt; communities as a cultural critique</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7053-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7053_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:15:18">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=49AFDADF832266998E52A389FEE0B684?doi=10.1.1.147.6645&amp;rank=6</link><title>Polylingual Topic Models</title><description>Polylingual Topic Models

by David Mimno, Hanna M. Wallach, Jason Naradowsky, David A. Smith, Andrew Mccallum

"... sentiment analysis of blog posts. They find, for example, that English blog posts about the Nintendo Wii ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 46 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Topic models are a useful tool for analyzing large text collections, but have previously been applied in only monolingual, or at most bilingual, contexts. Meanwhile, massive collections of interlinked documents in dozens of languages, such as Wikipedia, are now widely available, calling for tools that can characterize content in many languages. We introduce a polylingual topic model that discovers topics aligned across multiple languages. We explore the model’s characteristics using two large corpora, each with over ten different languages, and demonstrate its usefulness in supporting machine translation and tracking topic trends across languages. 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7053-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7053_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:16:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=49AFDADF832266998E52A389FEE0B684?doi=10.1.1.221.5925&amp;rank=7</link><title>Named Entity Recognition in Tweets: An Experimental Study</title><description>Named Entity Recognition in Tweets: An Experimental Study

by Alan Ritter, Sam Clark, Oren Etzioni , 2011

"... that they Will release the Nintendo 3DS in north America march 27 for $250 3 Government confirms blast n nuclear plants n ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 40 (7 self) \- Add to MetaCart

People tweet more than 100 Million times daily, yielding a noisy, informal, but sometimes informative corpus of 140-character messages that mirrors the zeitgeist in an unprecedented manner. The performance of standard NLP tools is severely degraded on tweets. This paper addresses this issue by re-building the NLP pipeline beginning with part-of-speech tagging, through chunking, to named-entity recognition. Our novel T-NER system doubles F1 score compared with the Stanford NER system. T-NER leverages the redundancy inherent in tweets to achieve this performance, using LabeledLDA to exploit Freebase dictionaries as a source of distant supervision. LabeledLDA outperforms cotraining, increasing F1 by 25 % over ten common entity types. Our NLP tools are available at:</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7053-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7053_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:16:56">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=49AFDADF832266998E52A389FEE0B684?doi=10.1.1.21.765&amp;rank=8</link><title>Doom as an Interface for Process Management</title><description>Doom as an Interface for Process Management

by Dennis Chao \- Proceedings of SIGCHI’01 , 2001

"... -Modernism, 3D user interfaces, vernacular, video games, visualization INTRODUCTION Those who use computers ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 22 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

, metaphors, operating systems, Post-Modernism, &lt;em&gt;3&lt;/em&gt;D user interfaces, vernacular, video games, visualization</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7053-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7053_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:17:57">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=49AFDADF832266998E52A389FEE0B684?doi=10.1.1.107.4530&amp;rank=9</link><title>The relevance of video games and gaming consoles to the higher and further education learning experience</title><description>The relevance of video games and gaming consoles to the higher and further education learning experience

by John Kirriemuir \- The Joint Information Systems Committee, TSW 02-01. Retrieved June , 2002

"... , and massive sustained sales of games consoles such as the Sony Playstation and Nintendo Game Boy series, have ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 12 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Video games have been a significant form of entertainment since the early 1970’s, appearing in a number of formats and locations: television-dependent consoles, portable games machine, games on LCD panels, amusement arcades and so on. Often, games technology has been combined with computing-oriented technologies, resulting in hybrid machines such as the ZX Spectrum, BBC</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7053-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7053_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:19:05">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=49AFDADF832266998E52A389FEE0B684?doi=10.1.1.136.9873&amp;rank=10</link><title>A Double Authentication Scheme To Detect Impersonation Attack</title><description>A Double Authentication Scheme To Detect Impersonation Attack

by Dijiang Huang, Amit Sinha, Deep Medhi \- IEEE International Conference on Communications (ICC 2003 , 2003

"... -1 10 -2 10 -3 DS (enc) DS (dec) DA SPF-Cisco 7513 10 -4 10 50 100 Number of Nodes 150 200 Fig. 3 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 10 (6 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract—In this paper, we present an authentication scheme to prevent impersonation attack in link state routing protocol. The existing authentication schemes are either simple to compute but vulnerable to attacks or too robust against attacks but has exponential computation cost. We introduce a Double Authentication (DA) scheme which provides authentication to the routing information data carried by the link state routing packets. In this scheme every router needs to sign the routing data twice with two different keys using a group keying scheme, which is based on oneway hash function. Based on our performance assessment, we found that this scheme is simpler to implement, computationally efficient and provides the degree of robustness desired with less communication overhead but has higher memory requirement.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>