<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7056">ROADM</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:43:09" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7056-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7056_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:43:11">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B62BF554FD634F781B28D40637CFB3BB?doi=10.1.1.227.8605&amp;rank=1</link><title>Advanced ROADM Networks</title><description>Advanced ROADM Networks

by M. D. Feuer, Sheryl L. Woodward

"... ﻿Advanced ROADM Networks M. D. Feuer and Sheryl L. Woodward AT&amp;T Labs - Research, Middletown, NJ ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

/drop multiplexers (&lt;em&gt;ROADMs&lt;/em&gt;), including colorless, directionless, contentionless, and gridless operation. Is ‘less</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7056-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7056_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:44:12">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B62BF554FD634F781B28D40637CFB3BB?doi=10.1.1.353.9477&amp;rank=2</link><title>ROADM System for Space Division Multiplexing with Spatial Superchannels</title><description>ROADM System for Space Division Multiplexing with Spatial Superchannels

by M. D. Feuer, L. E. Nelson, K. Abedin, X. Zhou, T. F. Taunay, J. F. Fini, B. Zhu, R. Isaac, R. Harel, G. Cohen, D. M. Marom

"... ﻿ROADM System for Space Division Multiplexing with Spatial Superchannels M. D. Feuer 1 , L. E ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract: A two-span SDM system includes the first &lt;em&gt;ROADM&lt;/em&gt; supporting spatial superchannels</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7056-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7056_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:45:21">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B62BF554FD634F781B28D40637CFB3BB?doi=10.1.1.353.6569&amp;rank=3</link><title>ROADM options in optical networks: flexible grid or not?</title><description>ROADM options in optical networks: flexible grid or not?

by Sheryl L. Woodward

"... ﻿ROADM options in optical networks: flexible grid or not? Sheryl L. Woodward AT&amp;T Labs ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract: Flexible-grid networks are attractive because they claim greater spectral efficiency and the ability to accommodate future modulation formats that may need wider channel bandwidths. We compare flexible-grid networks to alternative approaches. OCIS codes: (060.0060) Fiber optics and optical communications; (060.4250) Networks 1.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7056-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7056_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:46:27">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B62BF554FD634F781B28D40637CFB3BB?doi=10.1.1.20.250&amp;rank=4</link><title>Introducing optical transparency into core networks with R-OADMs</title><description>Introducing optical transparency into core networks with R-OADMs

by Neil Geary Georgia, Georgia Bernidaki, Andreas Antonopoulos, John Mitchell , 2002

"... ﻿Introducing optical transparency into core networks with R-OADMs Neil Geary†,Georgia Bernidaki ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

-Drop Multiplexers (&lt;em&gt;R-OADMs&lt;/em&gt;) seem set to transform the economics of optical core network architectures</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7056-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7056_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:47:24">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B62BF554FD634F781B28D40637CFB3BB?doi=10.1.1.278.4573&amp;rank=5</link><title>Cost Optimization Using Regenerator Site Concentration and Routing in ROADM Networks</title><description>Cost Optimization Using Regenerator Site Concentration and Routing in ROADM Networks

by Balagangadhar G Bathula, Rakesh K. Sinha, Angela L. Chiu, Mark D. Feuer, Guangzhi Li, Sheryl L. Woodward, Weiyi Zhang, Robert Doverspike, Peter Magill, Keren Bergman

"... ﻿Cost Optimization Using Regenerator Site Concentration and Routing in ROADM Networks Balagangadhar ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

(&lt;em&gt;ROADMs&lt;/em&gt;) will enable flexible pre-deployment of optoelectronic regenerators in future optical networks</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7056-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7056_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:48:26">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B62BF554FD634F781B28D40637CFB3BB?doi=10.1.1.308.3186&amp;rank=6</link><title>Routing Capability and Blocking Analysis of Dynamic ROADM Optical Networks (Category- II</title><description>Routing Capability and Blocking Analysis of Dynamic ROADM Optical Networks (Category- II

by Indumathi T. S, T. Srinivas, B. Siva Kumar

"... Analysis of Dynamic ROADM Optical Networks (Category - II) for Dynamic Traffic Indumathi T. S., T. Srinivas ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract—Reconfigurable optical add/drop multiplexers (&lt;em&gt;ROADMs&lt;/em&gt;) can be classified into three</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7056-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7056_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:49:34">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B62BF554FD634F781B28D40637CFB3BB?doi=10.1.1.164.5858&amp;rank=7</link><title>Optical WDM Networks: Traffic Grooming in Mesh Networks and Metro Networks using ROADMs</title><description>Optical WDM Networks: Traffic Grooming in Mesh Networks and Metro Networks using ROADMs

by Hongyue Zhu , 2005

"... Networks and Metro Networks using ROADMs Abstract Optical Fiber technology employing wavelength ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Optical Fiber technology employing wavelength-division multiplexing (WDM) has and continues to be investigated and commercially deployed to meet our ever-increasing bandwidth demands. WDM partitions the huge bandwidth of an optical fiber into many non-overlapping wavelength channels, each of which can operate at the data rate of 10 Gbps (or 40 Gbps or higher). This dissertation investigates design and modeling issues of optical WDM mesh networks, as well as ring networks. This dissertation first proposes a novel generic graph model for traffic grooming in heterogeneous WDM mesh networks so that low-speed traffic streams can be “groomed ” (or carried) by high-capacity wavelength channels. This model uses an auxiliary graph to represent the network state, which can accommodate various resource constraints. It can achieve different grooming policies by employing a simple shortest-path algorithm, and it can be applied to both static and dynamic trafficgrooming scenarios. A grooming policy determines how to carry the traffic in a certain situation.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7056-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7056_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:50:43">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B62BF554FD634F781B28D40637CFB3BB?doi=10.1.1.419.4893&amp;rank=8</link><title>OFC/NFOEC Technical Digest © 2012 OSA On Concentrating Regenerator Sites in ROADM Networks</title><description>OFC/NFOEC Technical Digest © 2012 OSA On Concentrating Regenerator Sites in ROADM Networks

by Balagangadhar G. Bathula, Rakesh K. Sinha, Angela L. Chiu, Mark D. Feuer, Guangzhi Li, Sheryl L. Woodward, Weiyi Zhang, Keren Bergman, Inwoong Kim, Paparao Palacharla

"... ﻿OFC/NFOEC Technical Digest © 2012 OSA On Concentrating Regenerator Sites in ROADM Networks ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract: Concentrating optical regenerators in a subset of nodes provides significant savings. We present a heuristic for choosing this subset. In the studied cases our results have 1 or 2 more sites than the minimum. OCIS codes: (060.4256) Networks, network optimization, (060.1155) All-optical networks I.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7056-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7056_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:51:52">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B62BF554FD634F781B28D40637CFB3BB?doi=10.1.1.193.4049&amp;rank=9</link><title>Multiplexer (MUX/DEMUX), Reconfigurable Optical Add-Drop</title><description>Multiplexer (MUX/DEMUX), Reconfigurable Optical Add-Drop

by Indumathi T. S, T. Srinivas, B. Siva Kumar

"... Analysis of Dynamic ROADM Optical Networks (Category - II) for Dynamic Traffic Indumathi T. S., T. Srinivas ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract—Reconfigurable optical add/drop multiplexers (&lt;em&gt;ROADMs&lt;/em&gt;) can be classified into three</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7056-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7056_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:53:02">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B62BF554FD634F781B28D40637CFB3BB?doi=10.1.1.396.5858&amp;rank=10</link><title>Research Article Wavelength- and Time-Selective Reconfigurable Optical Add/Drop Multiplexer Using Time-Frequency Domain Processing</title><description>Research Article Wavelength- and Time-Selective Reconfigurable Optical Add/Drop Multiplexer Using Time-Frequency Domain Processing

by Tsuyoshi Konishi, Ryosuke Itoh, Kazuyoshi Itoh

"... /drop multiplexer (ROADM) using timefrequency domain processing. The proposed ROADM is realized by allocating ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

-selective reconfigurable optical add/drop multiplexer (&lt;em&gt;ROADM&lt;/em&gt;) using timefrequency domain processing. The proposed &lt;em&gt;ROADM&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>