<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7059">doctor Amsterdam</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:16:36" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7059-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7059_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:16:41">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=17684B182BAEDDE540686184B6898625?doi=10.1.1.6.3035&amp;rank=1</link><title>Distributed Computing in Practice: The Condor Experience</title><description>Distributed Computing in Practice: The Condor Experience

by Douglas Thain, Todd Tannenbaum, Miron Livny \- Concurrency and Computation: Practice and Experience , 2005

"... of Wisconsin, Miron Livny combined his doctoral thesis on cooperative processing [47] with the powerful Crystal ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 345 (6 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Since 1984, the Condor project has enabled ordinary users to do extraordinary computing. Today, the project continues to explore the social and technical problems of cooperative computing on scales ranging from the desktop to the world-wide computational grid. In this chapter, we provide the history and philosophy of the Condor project and describe how it has interacted with other projects and evolved along with the field of distributed computing. We outline the core components of the Condor system and describe how the technology of computing must correspond to social structures. Throughout, we reflect on the lessons of experience and chart the course traveled by research ideas as they grow into production systems.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7059-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7059_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:17:45">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=17684B182BAEDDE540686184B6898625?doi=10.1.1.172.260&amp;rank=2</link><title>Prosodic Morphology: constraint interaction and satisfaction</title><description>Prosodic Morphology: constraint interaction and satisfaction

by John J. Mccarthy, Alan Prince , 1993

"... Theory. Doctoral dissertation. Amherst, MA: University of Massachusetts, Amherst. ROA-309. Alderete, John ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 283 (27 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Permission is hereby granted by the authors to reproduce this document, in whole or in part, for personal use, for instruction, or for any other non-commercial purpose. Table of Contents Acknowledgments.........................................................</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7059-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7059_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:18:53">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=17684B182BAEDDE540686184B6898625?doi=10.1.1.420.7300&amp;rank=3</link><title>and ENCORE Amsterdam</title><description>and ENCORE Amsterdam

by Francesca Lotti, Enrico Santarelli, Marco Vivarelli, Francesca Lotti, Bank Of Italy, Enrico Santarelli, Marco Vivarelli

"... Santarelli University of Bologna, Max Planck Institute of Economics Jena and ENCORE Amsterdam Marco Vivarelli ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

and &lt;em&gt;doctoral&lt;/em&gt; programs. IZA engages in (i) original and internationally competitive research in all fields</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7059-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7059_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:20:04">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=17684B182BAEDDE540686184B6898625?doi=10.1.1.343.1329&amp;rank=4</link><title>de Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam,</title><description>de Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam,

by Academisch Proefschrift, De Boelelaan, Harmen Jakob, Jens O. Andersen, Daniel Boer, Harmen J. Warringa, Thermodynamics Of, Jens O. Andersen, Daniel Boer, Harmen J. Warringa, Jens O. Andersen, Daniel Boer, Harmen J. Warringa, Thermodynamics Of , 2006

"... Thermodynamics of QCD-inspired theories ACADEMISCH PROEFSCHRIFT ter verkrijging van de graad Doctor aan de Vrije ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

ter verkrijging van de graad &lt;em&gt;Doctor&lt;/em&gt; aan</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7059-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7059_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:21:15">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=17684B182BAEDDE540686184B6898625?doi=10.1.1.270.9947&amp;rank=5</link><title>University of Amsterdam,</title><description>University of Amsterdam,

by Barbara C Van Munster, René Spijker, Rob J P M Scholten, Lotty Hooft , 2011

"... Center, University of Amsterdam, Amsterdam, The Netherlands 2 Dutch Cochrane Centre, Academic Medical ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

&lt; An additional appendix is published online only. To view this file please visit the journal online (www.jamia.bmj.com/ content/19/3.toc). 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7059-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7059_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:22:19">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=17684B182BAEDDE540686184B6898625?doi=10.1.1.43.5829&amp;rank=6</link><title>Functional Phonology -- Formalizing the interactions between articulatory and perceptual drives</title><description>Functional Phonology -- Formalizing the interactions between articulatory and perceptual drives

by Paulus Petrus Gerardus Boersma , 1998

"... and perceptual drives Academisch proefschrift ter verkrijging van de graad van doctor aan de Universiteit van ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 224 (24 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7059-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7059_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:23:28">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=17684B182BAEDDE540686184B6898625?doi=10.1.1.138.1000&amp;rank=7</link><title>aan de Universiteit van Amsterdam</title><description>aan de Universiteit van Amsterdam

by Rubèn Serral Gracià, Dr. J. S. Caux, Prof Dr. L. F. Cugliandolo, Dr. L. Leuzzi, Dr. L. G. Suttorp, Jordi Busquets Blanco, Daniele Moroni

"... ﻿Spin Bosons and Spin Glasses ACADEMISCH PROEFSCHRIFT ter verkrijging van de graad van doctor aan ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

ter verkrijging van de graad van &lt;em&gt;doctor&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7059-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7059_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:24:39">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=17684B182BAEDDE540686184B6898625?doi=10.1.1.224.5942&amp;rank=8</link><title>aan de Universiteit van Amsterdam</title><description>aan de Universiteit van Amsterdam

by Academisch Proefschrift, Jeroen Johannes Van Der Ham, Overige Leden, Dr. P. Grosso, Dr. H. Keus, Prof Dr. D. Simeonidou , 2010

"... Proefschrift ter verkrijging van de graad van doctor aan de Universiteit van Amsterdam op gezag van de Rector ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

ter verkrijging van de graad van &lt;em&gt;doctor&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7059-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7059_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:25:43">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=17684B182BAEDDE540686184B6898625?doi=10.1.1.126.8320&amp;rank=9</link><title>Reasoning in Description Logics</title><description>Reasoning in Description Logics

by F. M. Donini, M. Lenzerini, D. Nardi, A. Schaerf , 1997

"... , Complexity, and Semantic Issues. Doctoral dissertation, Dipartimento di Informatica e Sistemistica ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 215 (28 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7059-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7059_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:26:54">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=17684B182BAEDDE540686184B6898625?doi=10.1.1.421.2752&amp;rank=10</link><title>ENCORE Amsterdam, and IZA Bonn</title><description>ENCORE Amsterdam, and IZA Bonn

by Enrico Santarelli, Marco Vivarelli, Enrico Santarelli, Marco Vivarelli, Università Cattolica Piacenza , 2006

"... Santarelli University of Bologna, Max Planck Institute of Economics Jena, ENCORE Amsterdam, and IZA Bonn ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

and &lt;em&gt;doctoral&lt;/em&gt; programs. IZA engages in (i) original and internationally competitive research in all fields</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>