<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7061">startup advisors chicago</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:39:20" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7061-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7061_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:39:23">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=6C447BF1915A38B6D8950096F10553AE?doi=10.1.1.91.2433&amp;rank=1</link><title>Architectural Styles and the Design of Network-based Software Architectures</title><description>Architectural Styles and the Design of Network-based Software Architectures

by Roy Thomas Fielding , 2000

"... mentoring provided by Dick Taylor, my long-time advisor and committee chair. Mark Ackerman also deserves a ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 592 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The World Wide Web has succeeded in large part because its software architecture has been designed to meet the needs of an Internet-scale distributed hypermedia system. The Web has been iteratively developed over the past ten years through a series of modifications to the standards that define its architecture. In order to identify those aspects of the Web that needed improvement and avoid undesirable modifications, a model for the modern Web architecture was needed to guide its design, definition, and deployment. Software architecture research investigates methods for determining how best to partition a system, how components identify and communicate with each other, how information is communicated, how elements of a system can evolve independently, and how all of the above can be described using formal and informal notations. My work is motivated by the desire to understand and evaluate the architectural design of network-based application software through principled use of architectural constraints, thereby obtaining the functional, performance, and social properties desired of an architecture. An architectural style is a named, coordinated set of architectural constraints. This dissertation defines a framework for understanding software architecture via architectural styles and demonstrates how styles can be used to guide the architectural design of network-based application software. A survey of architectural styles for network-based applications is used to classify styles according to the architectural properties they induce on an architecture for distributed hypermedia. I then introduce the Representational State Transfer (REST) architectural style and describe how REST has been used to guide the design and development of the architecture for the modern Web. REST emphasizes scalability of component interactions, generality of interfaces, independent deployment of components, and intermediary components to reduce interaction latency, enforce security, and encapsulate legacy systems. I describe the software engineering principles guiding REST and the interaction constraints chosen to retain those principles, contrasting them to the constraints of other architectural styles. Finally, I describe the lessons learned from applying REST to the design of the Hypertext Transfer Protocol and Uniform Resource Identifier standards, and from their subsequent deployment in Web client and server software.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7061-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7061_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:40:42">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=6C447BF1915A38B6D8950096F10553AE?doi=10.1.1.139.5892&amp;rank=2</link><title>Common Risk Factors in the Returns On Stocks And Bonds</title><description>Common Risk Factors in the Returns On Stocks And Bonds

by Eugene F. Fama, Kenneth R. French \- Journal of Financial Economics , 1993

"... School of Business. University of Chicago, 1101 East 58th Street. Chicago. IL 60637, USA. *The comments ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 955 (24 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper identities five common risk factors in the returns on stocks and bonds. There are three stock-market factors: an overall market factor and factors related to firm size and book-to-market equity. There are two bond-market factors. related to maturity and default risks. Stock returns have shared variation due to the stock-market factors, and they are linked to bond returns through shared variation in the bond-market factors. Except for low-grade corporates. the bond-market factors capture the common variation in bond returns. Most important. the five factors seem to explain average returns on stocks and bonds. 1.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7061-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7061_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:41:50">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=6C447BF1915A38B6D8950096F10553AE?doi=10.1.1.319.4137&amp;rank=3</link><title>Formal and real authority in organizations</title><description>Formal and real authority in organizations

by Jean Tirole \- The Journal of Political Economy , 1997

"... of Chicago. All rights reserved. 0022-3808/97/0501-0001$01.50 12 JOURNAL OF POLITICAL ECONOMY pointed out ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 397 (11 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper develops a theory of the allocation of formal authority (the right to decide) and real authority (the effective control over decisions) within organizations, and it illustrates how a formally integrated structure can accommodate various degrees of "real" integration. Real authority is determined by the structure of information, which in turn depends on the allocation of formal authority. An increase in an agent's real authority promotes initiative but results in a loss of control for the principal. After spelling out (some of) the main determinants of the delegation of formal authority within organizations, the paper examines a number of factors that increase the subordinates ' real authority in a formally integrated structure: overload, lenient rules, urgency of decision, reputation, performance measurement, and multiplicity of superiors. Finally, the amount of communication in an organization is shown to depend on the allocation of formal authority. I.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7061-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7061_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:43:01">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=6C447BF1915A38B6D8950096F10553AE?doi=10.1.1.295.3609&amp;rank=4</link><title>Long-Run Policy Analysis and Long-Run Growth." Working Paper no. 3325</title><description>Long-Run Policy Analysis and Long-Run Growth." Working Paper no. 3325

by Author(s) Sergio Rebelo, Sergio Rebelo , 1990

"... of Political Economy, Vol. 99, No. 3 (Jun., 1991), pp. 500-521 Published by: The University of Chicago Press ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 306 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

you have obtained prior permission, you may not download an entire issue of a journal or multiple copies of articles, and you may use content in the JSTOR archive only for your personal, non-commercial use. Please contact the publisher regarding any further use of this work. Publisher contact information may be obtained at</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7061-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7061_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:44:18">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=6C447BF1915A38B6D8950096F10553AE?doi=10.1.1.204.6557&amp;rank=5</link><title>Advisor:</title><description>Advisor:

by Taro Mieno

"... ﻿WATER DEMAND IN THE CHICAGO METROPOLITAN AREA BY TARO MIENO B.S., Hokkaido University, 2007 THESIS ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

. Together, these constraints on water supply could limit economic and population growth in the &lt;em&gt;Chicago&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7061-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7061_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:45:26">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=6C447BF1915A38B6D8950096F10553AE?doi=10.1.1.261.681&amp;rank=6</link><title>Advisor:</title><description>Advisor:

by Ludwig-maximilians-universität München, Prof Dr, François Bry, Christoph Wieser , 2012

"... Supervisor: Advisor: Prof. Dr. François Bry Christoph Wieser Date: June 27, 2012Erklärung Ich erkläre hiermit ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Ich erkläre hiermit, dass ich die vorliegende Arbeit selbständig angefertigt, alle</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7061-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7061_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:46:35">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=6C447BF1915A38B6D8950096F10553AE?doi=10.1.1.302.8343&amp;rank=7</link><title>Advisor</title><description>Advisor

by École Doctorale Is, Syed Zahid Ahmed

"... , FRANCE) Examiner/Co- Advisor Co-Advisor Mr. Lionel TORRES Prof. at LIRMM/UM2 (Montpellier, FRANCE ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

eFPGAs: Explorations architecturales, integration système, et une enquête visionnaire industriel des technologies programmable by</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7061-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7061_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:47:48">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=6C447BF1915A38B6D8950096F10553AE?doi=10.1.1.140.6810&amp;rank=8</link><title>Advisors</title><description>Advisors

by Dennis Crutchfield, Independent Consultant, Herb Estrada, Independent Consultant, Richard Hobbins, Independent Consultant, Jeff Hedges Chevrontexaco , 2004

"... Engineering, Inc. Werner von Lensa; Forschungszentrum Juelich GmbH, Germany Advisors Jeff Hedges; Chevron ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Bechtel BWXT Idaho, LLC Disclaimer of Endorsement Reference herein to any specific commercial product, process, or service by trade name, trademark, manufacturer, or otherwise, does not necessarily constitute or imply its endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by the United States Government, the Idaho National Engineering and Environmental Laboratory, or Bechtel BWXT Idaho, LLC. The views and opinions of authors expressed herein do not necessarily state or reflect those of the United States</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7061-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7061_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:48:52">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=6C447BF1915A38B6D8950096F10553AE?doi=10.1.1.380.233&amp;rank=9</link><title>Advisor:</title><description>Advisor:

by Tony Chang, Tony Chang

"... mobile application Master of Engineering Capstone Project Report Author: Department: Advisor: Tony Chang ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

All rights reserved.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7061-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7061_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:49:58">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=6C447BF1915A38B6D8950096F10553AE?doi=10.1.1.208.4693&amp;rank=10</link><title>Advisor:</title><description>Advisor:

by E. Riedl, Steven E Riedl, Dave Casasent , 1986

"... by Steven E Riedl Carnegie-Mellon University Pittsburgh, PA March 1986 Advisor: Dave Casasent Support: NASA ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Optical Matrix-Vector (M-V) processors are designed to operate on parallel</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>