<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7069">Eames chair</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:50:43" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7069-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7069_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:50:52">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=D6845403538E575D770C340533ED9F0C?doi=10.1.1.404.502&amp;rank=1</link><title>Chair for InformationSystems</title><description>Chair for InformationSystems

by Manfred Pauli, Michael Schermann, Helmut Krcmar, Technische Universität München

"... manfred.pauli@(email omitted); Chair for InformationSystems Technische Universität München Boltzmannstraße 3 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

architecture management processes (&lt;em&gt;EAM&lt;/em&gt;) may provide a foundation for an integrated IT risk inventory. Based</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7069-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7069_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:51:58">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=D6845403538E575D770C340533ED9F0C?doi=10.1.1.178.6038&amp;rank=2</link><title>Evaluation and Extension of the EAM Pattern Catalog in a German Insurance Company Evaluierung und</title><description>Evaluation and Extension of the EAM Pattern Catalog in a German Insurance Company Evaluierung und

by Technische Universität München, Katharina Theresa Pflügler, Supervisor Prof, Dr. Florian Matthes, Alexander M. Ernst

"... structured approach is provided by the EAM Pattern Catalog which was developed at the chair for Software ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 2 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

, they are often inapplicable in practice as they are either too extensive or too abstract. The &lt;em&gt;EAM&lt;/em&gt; Pattern Catalog</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7069-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7069_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:53:07">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=D6845403538E575D770C340533ED9F0C?doi=10.1.1.164.5722&amp;rank=3</link><title>Session chair: Stephen Redding</title><description>Session chair: Stephen Redding

by Maurice Kugler, Eric Verhoogen, Discussants Jim Tybout, Beata Javorcik, Jan De Loecker, Maurice Kugler, Eric Verhoogen , 2009

"... . 2009 Session title: Trade, Product Turnover and Quality Session chair: Stephen Redding Discussants: Jim ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Beginning with Wilfred J. Ethier (1979, 1982), an important current of research has emphasized gains to trade from the greater availability of intermediate inputs, as opposed to the gains from the greater availability of consumption goods emphasized by Paul R. Krugman (1979) and others. It has been standard in this literature to model input varieties as symmetric, differentiated horizontally but not vertically. In contrast, anecdotal accounts, especially from developing countries, often stress the importance of gaining access to high-quality inputs on the import market. 1 In purely theoretical discussions, the need to distinguish between the number of inputs and the quality of those inputs can be avoided by treating different qualities of a given good as distinct varieties (see e.g. Paul Romer, 1994). But in empirical work one inherits the product categories and units of measurement in the data, and typically one must specify whether the greater-availability-of-inputs mechanism is expected to operate through an increase in the number of input categories or through an increase in the quality of inputs within categories. Because of data constraints — in particular because of a lack of information on input and output prices in standard plant-level datasets — it has been difficult to investigate the role of input quality differences, and recent empirical work,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7069-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7069_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:54:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=D6845403538E575D770C340533ED9F0C?doi=10.1.1.241.9893&amp;rank=4</link><title>unknown title</title><description>unknown title

by Heft X/x (x , 2008

"... Theoretical study of structure and energetics of gold clusters with the EAM method Denitsa Alamanova: Physical ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Theoretical study of structure and energetics of gold clusters with the &lt;em&gt;EAM&lt;/em&gt; method</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7069-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7069_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:55:10">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=D6845403538E575D770C340533ED9F0C?doi=10.1.1.195.9714&amp;rank=5</link><title>1 Why creating a NEW CHAIR? : Competence building for Innovation</title><description>1 Why creating a NEW CHAIR? : Competence building for Innovation

by Manuel V. Heitor, Manuel V. Heitor , 2000

"... ﻿Why creating a NEW CHAIR? : Competence building for Innovation Manuel V. Heitor mheitor ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Paper prepared to be presented together with a video show in the Workshop on:</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7069-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7069_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:56:22">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=D6845403538E575D770C340533ED9F0C?doi=10.1.1.206.633&amp;rank=6</link><title>Enterprise Architecture Management Pattern Catalog (Version 1.0</title><description>Enterprise Architecture Management Pattern Catalog (Version 1.0

by Alexander M. Ernst, Technische Universität München \- Chair for Informatics 19 (sebis), Technische Universität , 2008

"... ﻿Enterprise Architecture Management Patterns Alexander M. Ernst Chair for Informatics 19 Technische ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 25 (16 self) \- Add to MetaCart

of &lt;em&gt;EAM&lt;/em&gt; patterns to address typical recurring problems arising in this area. 1.1 Intended Audience</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7069-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7069_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:57:24">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=D6845403538E575D770C340533ED9F0C?doi=10.1.1.336.668&amp;rank=7</link><title>Excitotoxic lesions of the amygdala fail to produce impairments in visual learning for auditory secondary reinforcement but interfere with reinforcer devaluation effects in rhesus monkeys</title><description>Excitotoxic lesions of the amygdala fail to produce impairments in visual learning for auditory secondary reinforcement but interfere with reinforcer devaluation effects in rhesus monkeys

by David Gaffan, Elisabeth A. Murray \- J Neurosci , 1997

"... by the Human Frontiers Scientific Program Organization (E.A.M.) and the National Institute of Mental Health ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 33 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Aspiration lesions of the amygdala were found previously to produce a severe impairment in visual discrimination learning for auditory secondary reinforcement in rhesus monkeys (Gaffan and Harrison, 1987). To determine whether excitotoxic amygdala lesions would also produce this effect, we trained four naive rhesus monkeys on the same task. The monkeys were required to learn 40 new visual discrimination problems per session in a situation in which visual choices were guided by an auditory secondary reinforcer that had been previously associated with food reward. Bilateral excitotoxic lesions of the amygdala had no effect on the rate of learning visual discrimination problems for auditory secondary reinforcement. We also tested the amygdalectomized monkeys on a reinforcer devaluation task and compared their performance with a group of three normal monkeys. The monkeys first learned to discriminate</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7069-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7069_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:58:32">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=D6845403538E575D770C340533ED9F0C?doi=10.1.1.202.6209&amp;rank=8</link><title>Not a Sunday Afternoon Joyride..................................................1</title><description>Not a Sunday Afternoon Joyride..................................................1

by Wayne State, Jeff Howlett, Lisa S

"... State College Instructional Improvement grant. Many thanks to: The beneficent Dr. Alan Bruflat, Chair ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Instructional Improvement grant. Many thanks to: The beneficent Dr. Alan Bruflat, &lt;em&gt;Chair&lt;/em&gt;, Department of Language</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7069-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7069_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:59:41">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=D6845403538E575D770C340533ED9F0C?doi=10.1.1.105.6703&amp;rank=9</link><title>Safe and Sound: a safety-critical approach to security design. New Security Paradigms Workshop 2001</title><description>Safe and Sound: a safety-critical approach to security design. New Security Paradigms Workshop 2001

by Sacha Brostoff , 2001

"... , and people are the weakest link in the chair~ " The opposition recognized and exploited this state of affairs ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 25 (5 self) \- Add to MetaCart

s.brostoff @ cs. ucl.ac.uk This paper firstly argues that the design of security applications needs to consider more than technical elements. Since almost all security systems involve human users as well as technology, security should be considered, and designed as, a socio-technical work system. Secondly, we argue that safety-critical systems design has similar goals and issues to security design, and should thus provide a good starting point. Thirdly, we identify Reason's (1990) Generic Error Modeling</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7069-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7069_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:00:54">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=D6845403538E575D770C340533ED9F0C?doi=10.1.1.366.701&amp;rank=10</link><title>Context-based search for 3d models</title><description>Context-based search for 3d models

by Matthew Fisher, Pat Hanrahan \- In ACM SIGGRAPH Asia 2010 papers , 2010

"... nodes such as the Eames chair represent complete objects. Other nodes, such as the children of the Eames ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 13 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Figure 1: Scene modeling using a context search. Left: A user modeling a scene places the blue box in the scene and asks for models that belong at this location. Middle: Our algorithm selects models from the database that match the provided neighborhood. Right: The user selects a model from the list and it is inserted into the scene. All models pictured in this paper are used with permission from Google 3D Warehouse. Large corpora of 3D models, such as Google 3D Warehouse, are now becoming available on the web. It is possible to search these databases using a keyword search. This makes it possible for designers to easily include existing content into new scenes. In this paper, we describe a method for context-based search of 3D scenes. We first downloaded a large set of scene graphs from Google 3D Warehouse. These scene graphs were segmented into individual objects. We also extracted tags from the names of the models. Given the object shape, tags, and spatial relationship between pairs of objects, we can predict the strength of a relationship between a candidate model and an existing object in the scene. Using this function, we can perform context-based queries. The user specifies a region in the scene they are modeling using a 3D bounding box, and the system returns a list of related objects. We show that context-based queries perform better than keyword queries alone, and that without any keywords our algorithm still returns a relevant set of models.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>