<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7071">buy LP politics yellowjackets</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:13:25" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7071-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7071_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:13:31">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=371F5E08F76D47E6F4A2FBFDCA051393?doi=10.1.1.115.3723&amp;rank=1</link><title>Domain adaptation with structural correspondence learning</title><description>Domain adaptation with structural correspondence learning

by John Blitzer, Ryan Mcdonald, Fernando Pereira \- In EMNLP , 2006

"... data. Note that “investment”, “buy-outs”, and “jail” are all common nouns in the financial domain ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 153 (10 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Discriminative learning methods are widely used in natural language processing. These methods work best when their training and test data are drawn from the same distribution. For many NLP tasks, however, we are confronted with new domains in which labeled data is scarce or non-existent. In such cases, we seek to adapt existing models from a resourcerich source domain to a resource-poor target domain. We introduce structural correspondence learning to automatically induce correspondences among features from different domains. We test our technique on part of speech tagging and show performance gains for varying amounts of source and target training data, as well as improvements in target domain parsing accuracy using our improved tagger. 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7071-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7071_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:14:31">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=371F5E08F76D47E6F4A2FBFDCA051393?doi=10.1.1.170.9460&amp;rank=2</link><title>Revealed Political Power</title><description>Revealed Political Power

by Jinhui H. Bai, Roger Lagunoff , 2010

"... to the distribution LP as a The Political Lorenz curve since it gives a simple measure of political inequality ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

bias in a &lt;em&gt;political&lt;/em&gt; system. We model an infinite horizon, dynamic economy and its &lt;em&gt;political&lt;/em&gt; system from</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7071-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7071_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:15:44">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=371F5E08F76D47E6F4A2FBFDCA051393?doi=10.1.1.413.5893&amp;rank=3</link><title>Paper Series TITLE: The 2011 Basin Plan, Climate Change and the Buy-Back</title><description>Paper Series TITLE: The 2011 Basin Plan, Climate Change and the Buy-Back

by David Adamson

"... Change and the Buy-Back Authors: David Adamson Schools of Economics and Political Science The University ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

The long-term success of the Basin Plan and the &lt;em&gt;Buy&lt;/em&gt;-Back will be judged by the capacity</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7071-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7071_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:16:58">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=371F5E08F76D47E6F4A2FBFDCA051393?doi=10.1.1.203.173&amp;rank=4</link><title>On the Political Economy of Green Tax Reforms</title><description>On the Political Economy of Green Tax Reforms

by Toke Skovsgaard, Aidt Faculty Economics

"... ﻿On the Political Economy of Green Tax Reforms Toke Skovsgaard Aidt1 Faculty of Economics ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Work in progress. Comments are welcomed. Abstract. This paper offers a &lt;em&gt;political&lt;/em&gt; economy model</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7071-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7071_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:18:08">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=371F5E08F76D47E6F4A2FBFDCA051393?doi=10.1.1.107.569&amp;rank=5</link><title>Making by Making Strange: Defamiliarization and the Design of Domestic Technologies</title><description>Making by Making Strange: Defamiliarization and the Design of Domestic Technologies

by Genevieve Bell, Mark Blythe, Phoebe Sengers \- ACM Trans. Comput.-Hum. Interact , 2005

"... of the home find their way not only into our macro-politics, with gender, identity, and national politics ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 60 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper argues that because the home is so familiar, it is necessary to make it strange, or defamiliarize it, in order to open the design space for it. Critical approaches to technology design are of both practical and social importance in the home. Home appliances are loaded with cultural associations such as the gendered division of domestic labor that are easy to overlook. Further, homes are not the same everywhere – even in one country. Peoples ’ aspirations and desires differ greatly across and between cultures. The target of western domestic technology design is often not the user, but the consumer. Web refrigerators that create shopping lists, garbage cans that let advertisers know what is thrown away, cabinets that monitor their contents and order more when supplies are low are central to current images of the wireless, digital home of the future. Drawing from our research in the United States, the United Kingdom and Asia, we provide three different narratives of defamiliarization. A historical reading of American kitchens provides a lens with which to scrutinize new technologies of domesticity, an ethnographic account of an extended social unit in England problematizes taken-for-granted domestic technologies, and a comparative ethnography of the role of information and communication technologies in the daily lives of urban Asia's middle classes reveals the ways in which new technologies can be ‘captured ’ and domesticated in unexpected ways. In the final section of the paper, we build on these moments of defamiliarization to suggest a broad set of challenges and strategies for design in the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7071-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7071_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:19:12">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=371F5E08F76D47E6F4A2FBFDCA051393?doi=10.1.1.199.6233&amp;rank=6</link><title>CONSTITUTIONAL RULES AND COMPETITIVE POLITICS: THEIR EFFECTS ON SECESSIONISM</title><description>CONSTITUTIONAL RULES AND COMPETITIVE POLITICS: THEIR EFFECTS ON SECESSIONISM

by Albert Breton, Pierre Salmon

"... ﻿January 2002 CONSTITUTIONAL RULES AND COMPETITIVE POLITICS: THEIR EFFECTS ON SECESSIONISM Albert ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

of &lt;em&gt;political&lt;/em&gt; competition and on some meta-rules that contain procedures regulating the application</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7071-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7071_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:20:21">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=371F5E08F76D47E6F4A2FBFDCA051393?doi=10.1.1.194.7877&amp;rank=7</link><title>CENTER FOR AMERICAN POLITICS AND PUBLIC POLICY OCCASIONAL PAPER SERIES (91-4) IRAs and Household</title><description>CENTER FOR AMERICAN POLITICS AND PUBLIC POLICY OCCASIONAL PAPER SERIES (91-4) IRAs and Household

by William G. Gale, John Karl Scholz , 1990

"... ﻿CENTER FOR AMERICAN POLITICS AND PUBLIC POLICY OCCASIONAL PAPER SERIES (91-4) IRAs and Household ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

This paper examines the effects of Individual Retirement Accounts (IRAs) on household saving using data from the 1983-86 Survey of Consumer Finances. We construct a formal model of dynamic utility maximization that yields closed-form solutions for IRA and other saving. The model is used to illustrate the effects of annual contribution limits and other features of IRAs on non-IRA saving. After estimating the model, we simulate the effect of increasing the contribution limit on the overall level of saving. estimates suggest that only a small portion of increased IRA contributions Our would represent net additions to saving. This result differs from previous research, but is consistent with new evidence we present showing that households vith non-IRA financial assets exceeding $20,000 provided more than two-thirds of all IRA contributions in recent years, indicating great potential among IRA holders to shift taxable forms of saving into IRAs. We gratefully acknowledge the work of Robert Avery and Arthur Kenickell</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7071-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7071_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:21:20">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=371F5E08F76D47E6F4A2FBFDCA051393?doi=10.1.1.321.2791&amp;rank=8</link><title>Does Growth Cause Happiness, or Does Happiness Cause Growth</title><description>Does Growth Cause Happiness, or Does Happiness Cause Growth

by Charles Kenny \- Kyklos , 1999

"... . political and cultural modernization, it may also be that many in society find this process more painful ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 27 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

animal depends rlor on rvlzat he feels biit on wlmt Ize does; jiist cis /I~.Y virhle and vice consist riot i~z,feefin,p birr doing. iLINrcrls ~LII~L'I~LIs, Medit~rtiotrs. 1.r. 16. Tl~er-e is nothi~zg \\.vhiclz lzus yet been contrived by rlzarz by whiclz so rn~lclz lzappiness is produced as bjl a good tavern or inn. Bo.s~vel1. Life of Johtlson, iol vi, chap iii I.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7071-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7071_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:22:33">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=371F5E08F76D47E6F4A2FBFDCA051393?doi=10.1.1.132.7132&amp;rank=9</link><title>Dynamic Enfranchisement</title><description>Dynamic Enfranchisement

by William Jack, Roger Lagunoff \- Journal of Public Economics , 2006

"... political elite voluntarily dilute its political power by extending the voting franchise? This paper ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 14 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Why would a &lt;em&gt;political&lt;/em&gt; elite voluntarily dilute its &lt;em&gt;political&lt;/em&gt; power by extending the voting</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7071-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7071_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:23:43">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=371F5E08F76D47E6F4A2FBFDCA051393?doi=10.1.1.167.5018&amp;rank=10</link><title>Smart Institutions, Foolish Choices?: The Limited Partner Performance Puzzle</title><description>Smart Institutions, Foolish Choices?: The Limited Partner Performance Puzzle

by Josh Lerner, Antoinette Schoar, Wan Wong

"... investors are less likely to buy stocks on days with high trading volume (Barber and Odean (2003 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 23 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The returns that institutional investors realize from private equity investments differ dramatically across institutions. Using detailed and hitherto unexplored records of fund investors and performance, we document large heterogeneity in the performance of different classes of limited partners. In particular, endowments ’ annual returns are nearly 14 % greater than average. Funds selected by investment advisors and banks lag sharply. These results are robust to controlling for the type and year of the investment, as well as to the use of different specifications. Analyses of reinvestment decisions and young funds suggest that the results are not primarily due to endowments ’ greater access to established funds. Finally, we examine the differences in the choice of intermediaries across various institutional investors and their relationship to success. We find that LPs that have higher average IRRs also tend to invest in smaller and slower growing funds and have a smaller fraction of GPs in their geographic area.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>