<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7072">price gibson howard roberts custom</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:24:52" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7072-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7072_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:24:56">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A2D6287E1F4F6675464EA444362F2D49?doi=10.1.1.10.4290&amp;rank=1</link><title>Sketchpad: A man-machine graphical communication system</title><description>Sketchpad: A man-machine graphical communication system

by Ivan Edward Sutherland , 2003

"... distribution — executable versions were limited to a customized machine at the MIT Lincoln Laboratory — so its ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 522 (6 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The Sketchpad system uses drawing as a novel communication medium for a computer. The system contains input, output, and computation programs which enable it to interpret information drawn directly on a computer display. It has been used to draw electrical, mechanical, scientific, mathematical, and animated drawings; it is a general purpose system. Sketchpad has shown the most usefulness as an aid to the understanding of processes, such as the notion of linkages, which can be described with pictures. Sketchpad also makes it easy to draw highly repetitive or highly accurate drawings and to change drawings previously drawn with it. The many drawings in this thesis were all made with Sketchpad.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7072-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7072_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:25:57">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A2D6287E1F4F6675464EA444362F2D49?doi=10.1.1.390.9899&amp;rank=2</link><title>Dynamic capabilities and strategic management</title><description>Dynamic capabilities and strategic management

by David J. Teece, Gary Pisano, Amy Shuen \- Strategic Management Journal , 1997

"... b) and differently, when there are gross asymmetries in limit pricing (Milgrom and Roberts, 1982a ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 588 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The dynamic capabilities framework analyzes the sources and methods of wealth creation and capture by private enterprise firms operating in environments of rapid technological change. The competitive advantage of firms is seen as resting on distinctive processes (ways of coordinating and combining), shaped by the firm’s (specific) asset positions (such as the firm’s portfolio of difficult-to-trade knowledge assets and complementary assets), and the evolution path(s) it has adopted or inherited. The importance of path dependencies is amplified where conditions of increasing returns exist. Whether and how a firm’s competitive advantage is eroded depends on the stability of market demand, and the ease of replicability (expanding internally) and imitatability (replication by competitors). If correct, the framework suggests that private wealth creation in regimes of rapid technological change depends in large measure on honing internal technological, organizational, and managerial processes inside the firm. In short, identifying new opportunities and organizing effectively and efficiently to embrace them are generally more fundamental to private wealth creation than is strategizing, if by strategizing one means engaging in business conduct that keeps competitors off balance, raises rival’s costs, and excludes new entrants. © 1997 by John Wiley &amp; Sons, Ltd.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7072-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7072_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:27:09">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A2D6287E1F4F6675464EA444362F2D49?doi=10.1.1.321.346&amp;rank=3</link><title>Economic Action and Social Structure: The Problem of Embeddedness</title><description>Economic Action and Social Structure: The Problem of Embeddedness

by Mark Granovetter \- American Journal of Sociology , 1985

"... influences aggregate supply or demand or, therefore, prices or other terms of trade. As Albert Hirschman has ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1174 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

How behavior and institutions are affected by social relations is one of the classic questions of social theory. This paper concerns the extent to which economic action is embedded in structures of social relations, in modern industrial society. Although the usual neoclassical accounts provide an "undersocialized " or atomized-actor explanation of such action, reformist economists who attempt to bring social structure back in do so in the "oversocialized " way criticized by Dennis Wrong. Under- and oversocialized accounts are paradoxically similar in their neglect of ongoing structures of social relations, and a sophisticated account of economic action must consider its embeddedness in such structures. The argument is illustrated by a critique of Oliver Williamson's "markets and hierarchies " research program. INTRODUCTION: THE PROBLEM OF EMBEDDEDNESS How behavior and institutions are affected by social relations is one of the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7072-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7072_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:28:21">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A2D6287E1F4F6675464EA444362F2D49?doi=10.1.1.138.7942&amp;rank=4</link><title>Algorithmic mechanism design</title><description>Algorithmic mechanism design

by Noam Nisan, Amir Ronen \- Games and Economic Behavior , 1999

"... of agents here is very broad, incorporating attributes of code-mobility, artificial-intelligence, user-customization ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 563 (17 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We consider algorithmic problems in a distributed setting where the participants cannot be assumed to follow the algorithm but rather their own self-interest. As such participants, termed agents, are capable of manipulating the algorithm, the algorithm designer should ensure in advance that the agents ’ interests are best served by behaving correctly. Following notions from the field of mechanism design, we suggest a framework for studying such algorithms. Our main technical contribution concerns the study of a representative task scheduling problem for which the standard mechanism design tools do not suffice. Journal of Economic Literature</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7072-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7072_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:29:29">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A2D6287E1F4F6675464EA444362F2D49?doi=10.1.1.136.2762&amp;rank=5</link><title>ANALYSIS OF WIRELESS SENSOR NETWORKS FOR HABITAT MONITORING</title><description>ANALYSIS OF WIRELESS SENSOR NETWORKS FOR HABITAT MONITORING

by Joseph Polastre, Robert Szewczyk, Alan Mainwaring, David Culler, John Anderson , 2004

"... ﻿Chapter 18 ANALYSIS OF WIRELESS SENSOR NETWORKS FOR HABITAT MONITORING Joseph Polastre 1 , Robert ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1030 (18 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We provide an in-depth study of applying wireless sensor networks (WSNs) to real-world habitat monitoring. A set of system design requirements were developed that cover the hardware design of the nodes, the sensor network software, protective enclosures, and system architecture to meet the requirements of biologists. In the summer of 2002, 43 nodes were deployed on a small island off the coast of Maine streaming useful live data onto the web. Although researchers anticipate some challenges arising in real-world deployments of WSNs, many problems can only be discovered through experience. We present a set of experiences from a four month long deployment on a remote island. We analyze the environmental and node health data to evaluate system performance. The close integration of WSNs with their environment provides environmental data at densities previously impossible. We show that the sensor data is also useful for predicting system operation and network failures. Based on over one million 2 Polastre et. al. data readings, we analyze the node and network design and develop network reliability profiles and failure models.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7072-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7072_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:30:35">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A2D6287E1F4F6675464EA444362F2D49?doi=10.1.1.93.8759&amp;rank=6</link><title>Electronic Markets and Electronic Hierarchies</title><description>Electronic Markets and Electronic Hierarchies

by Robert I. Benjamin, Thomas W. Malone, Joanne Yates \- Communications of the ACM , 1987

"... STRUCTURES AND CORPORATE STRATEGIES Robert I. Benjamin Thomas W. Malone JoAnne Yates April 1986 CISR WP No ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 427 (10 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper analyzes the fundamental changes in market structures that may result from the increasing use of information technology. First, an analytic framework is presented and its usefulness is demonstrated in explaining several major historical changes in American business structures. Then, the framework is used to help explain how electronic markets and electronic hierarchies will allow closer integration of adjacent steps in the value added chains of our economy. The most surprising prediction is that information technology will lead to an overall shift toward proportionately more coordination by markets rather than by internal decisions within firms. Finally, several examples of companies where these changes are already occurring are used to illustrate the likely paths by which new market structures will evolve and the ways in which individual companies can take advantage of these changes.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7072-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7072_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:31:48">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A2D6287E1F4F6675464EA444362F2D49?doi=10.1.1.154.5491&amp;rank=7</link><title>Organizations</title><description>Organizations

by North Carolina A, Colin R. W, Earl O. Heady, Harvey J. Gold, Leonard W. Aur, Joseph C. Burns, Donald G. Davenport, Charles E. Main, Larry A. Nelson, Robert S. Sowell, Ronald E. Stinner , 1958

"... . Burns Donald G. Davenport Charles E. Main Larry A. Nelson Robert S. Sowell Ronald E. Stinner Will Getz ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 396 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Proceedings Editor:</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7072-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7072_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:32:55">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A2D6287E1F4F6675464EA444362F2D49?doi=10.1.1.111.3930&amp;rank=8</link><title>Internet Advertising and the Generalized Second Price Auction: Selling Billions of Dollars Worth</title><description>Internet Advertising and the Generalized Second Price Auction: Selling Billions of Dollars Worth

by Benjamin Edelman, Michael Ostrovsky, Michael Schwarz, Thank Drew Fudenberg, Louis Kaplow, Robin Lee, Paul Milgrom, Muriel Niederle, Ariel Pakes \- American Economic Review , 2005

"... ﻿Internet Advertising and the Generalized Second-Price Auction: Selling Billions of Dollars Worth ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 342 (16 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We investigate the “generalized second-&lt;em&gt;price&lt;/em&gt; ” (GSP) auction, a new mechanism used by search</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7072-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7072_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:34:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A2D6287E1F4F6675464EA444362F2D49?doi=10.1.1.12.8230&amp;rank=9</link><title>Financial Intermediation and Growth: Causality and Causes</title><description>Financial Intermediation and Growth: Causality and Causes

by Ross Levine, Norman Loayza, Thorsten Beck \- JOURNAL OF MONETARY ECONOMICS , 2000

"... , the University of Minnesota, the Central Bank of Chile as well as Robert King, Lant Pritchett, Andrei Shleifer ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 325 (36 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper evaluates (1) whether the exogenous component of financial intermediary development influences economic growth and (2) whether cross-country differences in legal and accounting systems (e.g., creditor rights, contract enforcement, and accounting standards) explain differences in the level of financial development. Using both traditional cross-section, instrumental variable procedures and recent dynamic panel techniques, we find that the exogenous components of financial intermediary development is positively associated with economic growth. Also, the data show that cross-country differences in legal and accounting systems help account for differences in financial development. Together, these findings suggest that legal and accounting reforms that strengthen creditor rights, contract enforcement, and accounting practices can boost financial development and accelerate economic growth.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7072-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7072_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:35:20">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A2D6287E1F4F6675464EA444362F2D49?doi=10.1.1.37.8120&amp;rank=10</link><title>A Scalable Comparison-Shopping Agent for the World-Wide Web</title><description>A Scalable Comparison-Shopping Agent for the World-Wide Web

by Robert B. Doorenbos, Oren Etzioni, Daniel S. Weld \- In Proceedings of the First International Conference on Autonomous Agents , 1997

"... A Scalable Comparison-Shopping Agent for the World-Wide Web Robert B. Doorenbos, Oren Etzioni ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 297 (18 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The Web is less agent-friendly than we might hope. Most information on the Web is presented in loosely structured natural language text with no agent-readable semantics. HTML annotations structure the display of Web pages, but provide virtually no insight into their content. Thus, the designers of intelligent Web agents need to address the following questions: (1) To what extent can an agent understand information published at Web sites? (2) Is the agent's understanding sufficient to provide genuinely useful assistance to users? (3) Is site-specific hand-coding necessary, or can the agent automatically extract information from unfamiliar Web sites? (4) What aspects of the Web facilitate this competence? In this paper we investigate these issues with a case study using the ShopBot. ShopBot is a fullyimplemented, domain-independent comparison-shopping agent. Given the home pages of several on-line stores, ShopBot autonomously learns how to shop at those vendors. After its learning is com...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>