<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7075">zimerman chopin ballade</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:38:28" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7075-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7075_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:38:32">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=C945E3E87924920F80AE83C1B5A93D9E?doi=10.1.1.309.2264&amp;rank=1</link><title>Articles YQX Plays Chopin</title><description>Articles YQX Plays Chopin

by Gerhard Widmer, Sebastian Flossmann, Maarten Grachten

"... ﻿Articles YQX Plays Chopin Gerhard Widmer, Sebastian Flossmann, and Maarten Grachten n This article ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

n This article is about AI research in the context of a complex artistic behavior: expressive music performance. A computer program is presented that learns to play piano with “expression” and that even won an international computer piano performance contest. A superficial analysis of an expressive performance generated by the system seems to suggest creative musical abilities. After a critical discussion of the processes underlying this behavior, we abandon the question of whether the system is really creative and turn to the true motivation that drives this research: to use AI methods to investigate and better understand music performance as a human creative behavior. A number of recent</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7075-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7075_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:39:49">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=C945E3E87924920F80AE83C1B5A93D9E?doi=10.1.1.188.4984&amp;rank=2</link><title>Maintaining skill across the life span: Magaloff’s entire Chopin at age 77</title><description>Maintaining skill across the life span: Magaloff’s entire Chopin at age 77

by Sebastian Flossmann, Werner Goebl, Gerhard Widmer

"... by the AEC All rights reserved Maintaining skill across the life span: Magaloff’s entire Chopin at age 77 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 4 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The study is based on a corpus containing the entire works of &lt;em&gt;Chopin&lt;/em&gt; performed by Nikita Magaloff</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7075-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7075_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:41:03">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=C945E3E87924920F80AE83C1B5A93D9E?doi=10.1.1.302.7307&amp;rank=3</link><title>Toward a model of performance errors: A qualitative review of Magaloff’s Chopin</title><description>Toward a model of performance errors: A qualitative review of Magaloff’s Chopin

by Sebastian Flossmann, Gerhard Widmer

"... ’s Chopin Sebastian Flossmann 1 and Gerhard Widmer 1,2 1 Department of Computational Perception, Johannes ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

measured performances: the complete works for solo piano by &lt;em&gt;Chopin&lt;/em&gt;, performed on stage by the Russian</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7075-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7075_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:42:12">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=C945E3E87924920F80AE83C1B5A93D9E?doi=10.1.1.188.5606&amp;rank=4</link><title>'s complete Chopin</title><description>'s complete Chopin

by Werner Goebl, Sebastian Flossmann, Gerhard Widmer , 2009

"... ’S COMPLETE CHOPIN Werner Goebl, Sebastian Flossmann, and Gerhard Widmer Department of Computational ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Nikita Magaloff, who played the complete work of &lt;em&gt;Chopin&lt;/em&gt; live on stage, on a computer-controlled grand</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7075-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7075_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:43:21">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=C945E3E87924920F80AE83C1B5A93D9E?doi=10.1.1.29.3660&amp;rank=5</link><title>Automatically Analyzing and Organizing Music Archives</title><description>Automatically Analyzing and Organizing Music Archives

by Andreas Rauber, Markus Frühwirth \- In Proceedings of the European Conference on Research and Advanced Technology for Digital Libraries (ECDL , 2001

"... , we nd unit (0=8) to represent the Funeral March (Chopin) as well as the Moonlight Sonata (Beethoven ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 41 (17 self) \- Add to MetaCart

. We are experiencing a tremendous increase in the amount of music being made available in digital form. With the creation of large multimedia collections, however, we need to devise ways to make those collections accessible to the users. While music repositories exist today, they mostly limit access to their content to query-based retrieval of their items based on textual meta-information, with some advanced systems supporting acoustic queries. What we would like to have additionally, is a way to facilitate exploration of musical libraries. We thus need to automatically organize music according to its sound characteristics in such a way that we nd similar pieces of music grouped together, allowing us to nd a classical section, or a hard-rock section etc. in a music repository. In this paper we present an approach to obtain such an organization of music data based on an extension to our SOMLib digital library system for text documents. Particularly, we employ the Self-Organizing Map to create a map of a musical archive, where pieces of music with similar sound characteristics are organized next to each other on the two-dimensional map display. Locating a piece of music on the map then leaves you with related music next to it, allowing intuitive exploration of a music archive. Keywords: Multimedia, Music Library, Self-Organizing Map (SOM), Exploration of Information Spaces, User Interface, MP3 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7075-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7075_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:44:34">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=C945E3E87924920F80AE83C1B5A93D9E?doi=10.1.1.207.2951&amp;rank=6</link><title>Music Performer Recognition Using an Ensemble of Simple Classifiers</title><description>Music Performer Recognition Using an Ensemble of Simple Classifiers

by Efstathios Stamatatos, Gerhard Widmer \- in Proceedings of the 15th European Conference on Artificial Intelligence (ECAI

"... . In the following experiments, Chopin's Ballade op. 38 will be used as the training material, and the Etude op.10 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 12 (6 self) \- Add to MetaCart

performances of 22 pianists playing two pieces by F. &lt;em&gt;Chopin&lt;/em&gt; is used in the presented experiments. Due</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7075-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7075_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:45:42">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=C945E3E87924920F80AE83C1B5A93D9E?doi=10.1.1.169.810&amp;rank=7</link><title>MATCH: A Music Alignment Tool CHest</title><description>MATCH: A Music Alignment Tool CHest

by Simon Dixon, Gerhard Widmer \- 6 th International Conference on Music Information Retrival (ISMIR , 2005

"... of recordings of 22 pianists playing 2 excerpts of solo piano music by Chopin (Etude in E Major, Op.10, no.3 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 35 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We present MATCH, a toolkit for aligning audio recordings of different renditions of the same piece of music, based on an efficient implementation of a dynamic time warping algorithm. A forward path estimation algorithm constrains the alignment path so that dynamic time warping can be performed with time and space costs that are linear in the size of the audio files. Frames of audio are represented by a positive spectral difference vector, which emphasises note onsets in the alignment process. In tests with Classical and Romantic piano music, the average alignment error was 41ms (median 20ms), with only 2 out of 683 test cases failing to align. The software is useful for content-based indexing of audio files and for the study of performance interpretation; it can also be used in real-time for tracking live performances. The toolkit also provides functions for displaying the cost matrix, the forward and backward paths, and any metadata associated with the recordings, which can be shown in real time as the alignment is computed.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7075-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7075_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:46:54">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=C945E3E87924920F80AE83C1B5A93D9E?doi=10.1.1.14.5186&amp;rank=8</link><title>Version 3.2, 26-March-2001, Final Version</title><description>Version 3.2, 26-March-2001, Final Version

by Melody Lead In, Werner Goebl A , 2001

"... is correct, the melody lead phenomenon should disappear at the finger-key level. Chopin’s Ballade op. 38 (45 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

in the played repertoire: homophonic textures, like the &lt;em&gt;Chopin&lt;/em&gt; excerpts used in this study, are seldom seen</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7075-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7075_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:48:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=C945E3E87924920F80AE83C1B5A93D9E?doi=10.1.1.302.6786&amp;rank=9</link><title>The Magaloff Project: An Interim Report</title><description>The Magaloff Project: An Interim Report

by Sebastian Flossmann, Werner Goebl, Maarten Grachten, Gerhard Widmer \- Journal of New Music Research , 2010

"... the scanned sheets. Figure 1 shows a screenshot of the program working on Chopin’s Ballade Op. 52. The example ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 6 (5 self) \- Add to MetaCart

for solo piano by Frédéric &lt;em&gt;Chopin&lt;/em&gt; on a Bösendorfer SE, a computer-controlled grand piano that precisely</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7075-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7075_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:49:04">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=C945E3E87924920F80AE83C1B5A93D9E?doi=10.1.1.14.9248&amp;rank=10</link><title>Asynchrony Versus Intensity As Cues For Melody Perception In Chords And Real Music</title><description>Asynchrony Versus Intensity As Cues For Melody Perception In Chords And Real Music

by Werner Goebl, Richard Parncutt \- Proc. of the 5th Triennial ESCOM Conference , 2003

"... the first nine bars of Chopin’s Ballade op. 38 as the test piece with the upper and upper middle voices ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 3 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

the effect of asynchrony only marginally. In Experiment III, a short musical excerpt by &lt;em&gt;Chopin&lt;/em&gt; was presented</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>