<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7076">Bouguereau</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:50:15" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7076-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7076_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:50:16">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=84BEDFBD9E514465DD4DD26267371E0D?doi=10.1.1.381.3831&amp;rank=1</link><title>by</title><description>by

by Paul Welsh, Paul Welsh

"... -Adolph Bouguereau (1825-1905).Two Peas in a Pod? A Case of Questionable Twins Part II by Paul Welsh Singapore ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

When a couple who had tried unsuccessfully for six years to have a baby naturally turned to one of the best known fertility clinics in the United States, they never imagined what would develop nine months later. The couple studied their options and eventually opted for in vitro fertilization to increase their opportunities of having children. Technicians at the prestigious clinic extracted several mature eggs from Hannah’s ovaries after several weeks of mild hormone treatments. Two of Hannah’s ova (eggs) were selected and later fertilized with sperm from her husband. The fertilized eggs were then transplanted back into Hannah’s uterus to continue their development. The in vitro fertilization (IVF) occurred in March and the following December the couple excitedly awaited the birth of twins. Hannah and Nathan Jones were ecstatic when healthy twin baby boys, Thomas and Darrell, were born. The differences in the Jones ’ twins weren’t that noticable at birth, but as the weeks passed and both infants started to grow, the parents watched in amazement as their children changed right before their eyes. One mellowed to a golden bronze and his dark hair turned curly, while the other displayed a milky complexion with straight, blond hair. “Right after the birth it wasn’t obvious to us, ” said Hannah, adding, “Thomas was a little lighter than Darrell. But after eight weeks I thought, this isn’t possible. ” Darrell’s skin was quite dark, and he had a much flatter nose than his brother. Questions 1. How are in vivo fertilization and in vitro fertilization similar? How are they different? 2. Are Darrell and Thomas fraternal or identical twins? How is the formation of fraternal twins different from the formation of identical twins? 3. In the time remaining, write down as many questions as you can that are raised by this story. Think of as many scenarios as you can that would lead to this situation.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7076-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7076_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:51:24">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=84BEDFBD9E514465DD4DD26267371E0D?doi=10.1.1.89.7297&amp;rank=2</link><title>A Lightweight Image Retrieval System for Paintings</title><description>A Lightweight Image Retrieval System for Paintings

by Thomas Lombardi, Sung-hyuk Cha

"... Greco, Aertsen 11 3.61 Memling, Toulouse-Lautrec 10 3.28 Bouguereau 9 2.95 Altdorfer, Cezanne 8 2 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 3 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

For describing and analyzing digital images of paintings we propose a model to serve as the basis for an interactive image retrieval system. The model defines two types of features: palette and canvas features. Palette features are those related to the set of colors in a painting while canvas features relate to the frequency and spatial distribution of those colors. The image retrieval system differs from previous retrieval systems for paintings in that it does not rely on image or color segmentation. The features specified in the model can be extracted from any image and stored in a database with other control information. Users select a sample image and the system returns the ten closest images as determined by calculating the Euclidean distance between feature sets. The system was tested with an initial dataset of 100 images (training set) and 90 sample images (testing set). In 81 percent of test cases, the system retrieved at least one painting by the same artist suggesting that the model is sufficient for the interactive classification of paintings by artist. Future studies aim to expand and refine the model for the classification of artwork according to artist and period style.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7076-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7076_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:52:33">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=84BEDFBD9E514465DD4DD26267371E0D?doi=10.1.1.204.4501&amp;rank=3</link><title>Wellcome Library, London The Fragrance of the Heifer’s Breath</title><description>Wellcome Library, London The Fragrance of the Heifer’s Breath

by Polyxeni Potter, Wrote English Historian Thomas Macaulay

"... , a French painter who worked in the tradition of William Bouguereau and Jean-Léon Gérôme ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Smallpox was “the most terrible of all the ministers of</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7076-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7076_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:53:50">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=84BEDFBD9E514465DD4DD26267371E0D?doi=10.1.1.307.1473&amp;rank=4</link><title>Heart Fastened to a Dying Animal</title><description>Heart Fastened to a Dying Animal

by Polyxeni Potter

"... Beaux-Arts. He also studied at the Académie Julian under William Bouguereau and Tony Robert-Fleury. Even ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

edea unsheathed a knife, and cut the old man’s “Mthroat, and letting the old blood out, filled the dry veins with the juice. When Aeson had absorbed it, part through his mouth, and part through the wound, the white of his hair and beard quickly vanished, and a dark color took its place. At a stroke his leanness went, and his pallor and dullness of mind. The deep hollows were filled with rounded flesh, and his limbs expanded. ” So wrote Ovid in the Metamorphoses about Medea performing a crude transfusion to rejuvenate the father of her beloved Jason. The “barbarian witch ” infused a concoction of “dark juices…. the wings and flesh of a vile screech-owl and the slavering foam of a sacrificed werewolf…. the scaly skin of a watersnake, the liver of a long-lived stag….” This story from antiquity traces human fascination with blood—at first with the loss of blood and its connection with weakness and death, later with blood transference from strong persons or animals to the infirm as therapy, usually by mouth. Interest and reports of attempts at some form of transfusion continued throughout the Middle Ages and up until the 1600s and William Harvey’s description of the human circulatory system, which ushered in a new era of attempts at transfusion. In addition to blood, experimentation involved beer, opium, and milk, infused directly into the veins and arteries of animals, which invariably died. “What if we transfused the blood of an Archbishop into a Quaker, ” joked Samuel Pepys in a 1666 diary entry making light of a hot topic of his day: taking blood from a beast and putting it into another beast or into the veins and arteries of a person. But on a more serious note, he wrote,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7076-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7076_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:55:02">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=84BEDFBD9E514465DD4DD26267371E0D?doi=10.1.1.367.1491&amp;rank=5</link><title>PLEASE DO NOT QUOTE WITHOUT PERMISSIONEducating the Aesthetic? Artistic Practice in the Twenty-first Century</title><description>PLEASE DO NOT QUOTE WITHOUT PERMISSIONEducating the Aesthetic? Artistic Practice in the Twenty-first Century

by Prof Michael Grenfell, Michael Grenfell , 2012

"... ’ artists such as Bouguereau. Bourdieu wanted to draw attention to Manet’s revolutionary achievement ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

In this paper, I discuss the approach that the French social philosopher Bourdieu is offering to consider the visual arts. Modern aesthetics has been a preoccupation of writers, artists and philosophers for well over two hundred years, since Kant gave it contemporary relevance by defining it as a unique part of human consciousness.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7076-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7076_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:56:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=84BEDFBD9E514465DD4DD26267371E0D?doi=10.1.1.200.3530&amp;rank=6</link><title>unknown title</title><description>unknown title

by unknown authors

"... , Degas, Monet, Bouguereau, and a large collection of Millet. One can easily imagine how thrilling ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

I am complete space. In order to identify myself I have to find my limit through form. The mark I make only serves to outline and never outlive a time void. A sense of needing a focus of form allows me to be – this being you now understand – but never the space. This artist statement written by Paul Arthur Dufour nearly fifty</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>