<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7080">lord of the rings hobbits theme</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:29:28" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7080-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7080_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:29:40">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E0DC5040AFAF4B074F764BEC90BD63FC?doi=10.1.1.196.1529&amp;rank=1</link><title>We Shall Be Hobbits: Beyond the Competitive Mindset</title><description>We Shall Be Hobbits: Beyond the Competitive Mindset

by Jochen Rick, Idris Hsi

"... : Concerning Hobbits In J.R.R. Tolkien’s epic series of books, The Lord of the Rings, a magic ring ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

of the unlikeliest of persons— a &lt;em&gt;hobbit&lt;/em&gt;. The &lt;em&gt;ring&lt;/em&gt; belongs to the dark &lt;em&gt;lord&lt;/em&gt; Sauron who only needs to regain it to once</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7080-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7080_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:30:48">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E0DC5040AFAF4B074F764BEC90BD63FC?doi=10.1.1.132.3463&amp;rank=2</link><title>Why Bounded Rationality</title><description>Why Bounded Rationality

by John Conlisk, Garey Ramey \- Journal of Economic Literature , 1996

"... : “Lord, what fools these mortals be!” Midsummer Night’s Dream, III.3.116. NEARLY EVERYONE would see ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 205 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Rothschild, and three most helpful referees. Very special thanks for many years of helpful insights are due to Richard Day and Luigi Ermini. Hamlet: “What a piece of work is a man! how noble in reason! how infinite in faculties!”</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7080-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7080_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:31:52">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E0DC5040AFAF4B074F764BEC90BD63FC?doi=10.1.1.18.5586&amp;rank=3</link><title>The Lord Of The Rings, Efficient Of Views At Dataware Houses</title><description>The Lord Of The Rings, Efficient Of Views At Dataware Houses

by Achour Mostéfaoui, Michel Raynal, Matthieu Roy, Divyakant Agrawal, Amr El Abbadi , 2002

"... ISSN 1166-8687 1441 THE LORD OF THE RINGS: EFFICIENT MAINTENANCE OF VIEWS AT DATA WAREHOUSES ACHOUR ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Data warehouses have become extremely important to support online analytical processing (OLAP) queries in databases. Since the data view that is obtained at a data warehouse is derived from multiple data sources that are continuously updated, keeping a data warehouse up-to-date becomes a crucial problem. An approach referred to as the incremental view maintenance is widely used. Unfortunately, a precise and formal definition of view maintenance (which can actually be seen as a distributed computation problem) does not exist. This paper develops a formal model for maintaining views at data warehouses in a distributed asynchronous system. We start by formulating the view maintenance problem in terms of abstract update and data integration operations and state the notions of correctness associated with data warehouse views. We then present a basic protocol and establish its proof of correctness. An efficient version of the proposed protocol is also provided, by incorporating several optimizations. Finally, we include the solution to a more general view formulation. So, this paper is mainly concerned with basic principles of distributed computing and their use to solve database related problems.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7080-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7080_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:33:07">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E0DC5040AFAF4B074F764BEC90BD63FC?doi=10.1.1.301.946&amp;rank=4</link><title>Representing Spatial Structure Through Maps and Language: Lord of the Rings Encodes the Spatial</title><description>Representing Spatial Structure Through Maps and Language: Lord of the Rings Encodes the Spatial

by Max M. Louwerse, Nick Benesh , 2012

"... .R.R. Tolkien in his map of Middle Earth and described as the setting in The Hobbit and the Lord of the Rings ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 2 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

-occurrences of cities in Tolkien’s &lt;em&gt;Lord&lt;/em&gt; of the &lt;em&gt;Rings&lt;/em&gt; trilogy and The &lt;em&gt;Hobbit&lt;/em&gt; predicted the authentic longitude</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7080-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7080_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:34:20">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E0DC5040AFAF4B074F764BEC90BD63FC?doi=10.1.1.230.2959&amp;rank=5</link><title>Thème COG — Systèmes cognitifs</title><description>Thème COG — Systèmes cognitifs

by Cyril Crassin, Fabrice Neyret, Sylvain Lefebvre, Thème Cog, Cyril Crassin, Fabrice Neyret, Sylvain Lefebvre , 2008

"... in recent movies (e.g., XXX, Lords of the Ring, the day after tomorrow, Pirates of the Caribbean ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

apport de recherche</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7080-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7080_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:35:28">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E0DC5040AFAF4B074F764BEC90BD63FC?doi=10.1.1.393.7664&amp;rank=6</link><title>ONE LORD AND SAVIOR FOR ALL? JESUS CHRIST AND RELIGIOUS DIVERSITY</title><description>ONE LORD AND SAVIOR FOR ALL? JESUS CHRIST AND RELIGIOUS DIVERSITY

by Harold A. Netland

"... ﻿ONE LORD AND SAVIOR FOR ALL? JESUS CHRIST AND RELIGIOUS DIVERSITY Harold A. Netland 1 Nathan ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Ephraim Lessing, contains a fascinating reworking of the classic parable of the three &lt;em&gt;rings&lt;/em&gt;. The parable</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7080-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7080_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:36:38">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E0DC5040AFAF4B074F764BEC90BD63FC?doi=10.1.1.160.747&amp;rank=7</link><title>Automatic Composition of Themed Mood Pieces</title><description>Automatic Composition of Themed Mood Pieces

by Heather Chan, Dan Ventura

"... ﻿Automatic Composition of Themed Mood Pieces Heather Chan and Dan Ventura Department of Computer ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 2 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract. Musical harmonization of a given melody is a nontrivial problem; slight variations in instrumentation, voicing, texture, and bass rhythm can lead to significant differences in the mood of the resulting piece. This study explores the possibility of automatic musical composition by using machine learning and statistical natural language processing to tailor a piece to a particular mood using an existing melody.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7080-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7080_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:37:50">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E0DC5040AFAF4B074F764BEC90BD63FC?doi=10.1.1.39.7281&amp;rank=8</link><title>Symmetry Breaking In Distributed Networks</title><description>Symmetry Breaking In Distributed Networks

by Alon Itai, Michael Rodeh \- Information and Computation , 1981

"... randomized algorithms. 2\. CHOOSING A LEADER IN A SYNCHRONOUS RING lord \- August 10, 1997 # # 3 2 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 70 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Given a &lt;em&gt;ring&lt;/em&gt; of n processors it is required to design the processors such that they will be able</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7080-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7080_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:39:03">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E0DC5040AFAF4B074F764BEC90BD63FC?doi=10.1.1.83.6637&amp;rank=9</link><title>Collaborative games: Lessons learned from boardgames</title><description>Collaborative games: Lessons learned from boardgames

by José P. Zagal, José P. Zagal, Jochen Rick, Jochen Rick, Idris Hsi, Idris Hsi \- Simulation &amp; Gaming , 2006

"... ) In LORD OF THE RINGS, you are a hobbit. Together with your fellow hobbits (2 to 5 players total), you ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 7 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Knizia’s &lt;em&gt;LORD&lt;/em&gt; OF THE &lt;em&gt;RINGS&lt;/em&gt;, considered by many to be the quintessential collaborative board game. Our</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7080-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7080_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:40:09">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E0DC5040AFAF4B074F764BEC90BD63FC?doi=10.1.1.19.7172&amp;rank=10</link><title>Improving an Ontology Refinement Method with Hyponymy Patterns</title><description>Improving an Ontology Refinement Method with Hyponymy Patterns

by Enrique Alfonseca, Suresh Manandhar , 2002

"... to the same reason, when processing excerpts from The Lord of the Rings (Tolkien, 1968), all hobbits 1 were ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 14 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

. The experiments have been performed by extending WordNet with concepts extracted from The &lt;em&gt;Lord&lt;/em&gt; of the &lt;em&gt;Rings&lt;/em&gt;.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>