<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7089">varese ionisation</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:40:11" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7089-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7089_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:40:23">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=973DBC81C56DEF8138FE34AAA64DE750?doi=10.1.1.380.1509&amp;rank=1</link><title>VARÈSE’S POÈME ÉLECTRONIQUE REGAINED: EVIDENCE FROM THE VEP PROJECT</title><description>VARÈSE’S POÈME ÉLECTRONIQUE REGAINED: EVIDENCE FROM THE VEP PROJECT

by Richard Dobson John, Ffitch Kees Tazelaar, Andrea Valle Vincenzo

"... with Ionisation and Déserts[1]. While recognising the primary importance of the Poème within Varèse’s output as a ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

, coordination and visual show), &lt;em&gt;Varèse&lt;/em&gt; (organized spatial sound delivered over 350 loudspeakers), Xenakis</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7089-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7089_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:41:28">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=973DBC81C56DEF8138FE34AAA64DE750?doi=10.1.1.79.4894&amp;rank=2</link><title>Acoustics, psychoacoustics and spectral music</title><description>Acoustics, psychoacoustics and spectral music

by Daniel Pressnitzer, Stephen Mcadams \- Contemporary Music Review , 1999

"... as in the percussion piece Ionisation by Edgar Varese (1933), the sound structure itself may be completely di erent ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 2 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Acoustics, psychoacoustics and spectral music 2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7089-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7089_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:42:35">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=973DBC81C56DEF8138FE34AAA64DE750?doi=10.1.1.307.5524&amp;rank=3</link><title>unknown title</title><description>unknown title

by F Luzzaro G M Rossolini , 2011

"... 21 7% 23 24% 24/25 12% / KPC VIM - 1 OXA - 48 No CRE detected 18 32% 22 18% 1: Milan; 2: Varese; 3 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Surveillance and outbreak reports Epidemic diffusion of KPC carbapenemase-producing Klebsiella pneumoniae in Italy: results of the first</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7089-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7089_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:43:43">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=973DBC81C56DEF8138FE34AAA64DE750?doi=10.1.1.309.1221&amp;rank=4</link><title>News</title><description>News

by L Pagani, F Luzzaro, Gm Rossolini, G M, M Lambiri, M Polemis, M Passiotou, A Vatopoulos, J Clement, G Macé, M Henaff, As Gobenceaux, C Feyeux, P Sagot, Jm Reynes , 2011

"... 21 7% 23 24% 24/25 12% / KPC VIM - 1 OXA - 48 No CRE detected 18 32% 22 18% 1: Milan; 2: Varese; 3 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Europe’s journal on infectious disease epidemiology, prevention and control</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7089-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7089_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:45:00">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=973DBC81C56DEF8138FE34AAA64DE750?doi=10.1.1.226.1276&amp;rank=5</link><title>OECD NUCLEAR ENERGY AGENCY ORGANISATION FOR ECONOMIC CO-OPERATION AND DEVELOPMENT</title><description>OECD NUCLEAR ENERGY AGENCY ORGANISATION FOR ECONOMIC CO-OPERATION AND DEVELOPMENT

by Superieures A Mev , 1991

"... de I'homme contre les myonnements ionisants et la priservation de 19environnement, la gestion des ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

(OCDE) a pour objectif de promouvoir des politiques visant:- h rtaliser la plus forte expansion de I'iconomie et de l'emploi et une progression du niveau de vie dans les pays Membres, tout en maintenant la stabilitt financikre, et B contribuer ainsi au dtveloppement de l'tconomie mondiale;- 3 contribuer B une saine expansion Cconomique dans les pays Membres, ainsi que les pays non-membres, en voie de dCveloppement Cconomique;- i contribuer h l'expansion du commerce mondial sur une base multllattrale et non discriminatoire conformCment aux obligations internationales. Les pays Membres originaires de I'OCDE sont: l'Allemagne, I'Autriche, la Belgique, le</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7089-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7089_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:46:10">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=973DBC81C56DEF8138FE34AAA64DE750?doi=10.1.1.275.1237&amp;rank=6</link><title>Second primary malignancies in thyroid cancer patients Clinical</title><description>Second primary malignancies in thyroid cancer patients Clinical

by C Langlois, M Schlumberger

"... of the registry of Varese, Lombardy, were used as reference rates for the patients included in the Italian cohort ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

The late health effects associated with radioiodine ( 131 I) given as treatment for thyroid cancer are difficult to assess since the number of thyroid cancer patients treated at each centre is limited. The risk of second primary malignancies (SPMs) was evaluated in a European cohort of thyroid cancer patients. A common database was obtained by pooling the 2-year survivors of the three major Swedish, Italian, and French cohorts of papillary and follicular thyroid cancer patients. A time-dependent analysis using external comparison was performed. The study concerned 6841 thyroid cancer patients, diagnosed during the period 1934–1995, at a mean age of 44 years. In all, 17 % were treated with external radiotherapy and 62 % received 131 I. In total, 576 patients were diagnosed with a SPM. Compared to the general population of each of the three countries, an overall significantly increased risk of SPM of 27 % (95% CI: 15–40) was seen in the European cohort. An increased risk of both solid tumours and leukaemias was found with increasing cumulative activity of 131 I administered, with an excess absolute risk of 14.4 solid cancers and of 0.8 leukaemias per GBq of 131 I and 10 5 person-years of follow-up. A relationship was found between 131 I administration and occurrence of bone and soft tissue, colorectal, and salivary gland cancers. These results strongly highlight the necessity to delineate the indications of 131 I treatment in</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7089-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7089_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:47:14">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=973DBC81C56DEF8138FE34AAA64DE750?doi=10.1.1.283.7572&amp;rank=7</link><title>incidence of</title><description>incidence of

by Aj Mcmichael, Gg Giles

"... pesticide exposure, hair dyes, diet, AIDS and ionising radiation) (Devesa and Fears, 1992). Meanwhile ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Have increases in solar ultraviolet exposure contributed to the rise in</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7089-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7089_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:48:02">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=973DBC81C56DEF8138FE34AAA64DE750?doi=10.1.1.291.8359&amp;rank=8</link><title>Nerve Injury Evoked Loss of Latexin Expression in Spinal Cord Neurons Contributes to the Development of</title><description>Nerve Injury Evoked Loss of Latexin Expression in Spinal Cord Neurons Contributes to the Development of

by Neuropathic Pain, Hilmar Nils Kühlein, Irmgard Tegeder, Christine Möser, Hee-young Lim, Annett Häussler, Katharina Spieth, Ingo Jennes, Rolf Marschalek, Tobias Beckhaus, Michael Karas, Markus Fauth, Corina Ehnert, Gerd Geisslinger, Ellen Niederberger

"... ) for desorption and ionisation with an acquisition mass range from 700 to 5000 m/z. The low mass gate was set ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Nerve injury leads to sensitization mechanisms in the peripheral and central nervous system which involve transcriptional and post-transcriptional modifications in sensory nerves. To assess protein regulations in the spinal cord after injury of the sciatic nerve in the Spared Nerve Injury model (SNI) we performed a proteomic analysis using 2D-difference gel electrophoresis (DIGE) technology. Among approximately 2300 protein spots separated on each gel we detected 55 significantly regulated proteins after SNI whereof 41 were successfully identified by MALDI-TOF MS. Out of the proteins which were regulated in the DIGE analyses after SNI we focused on the carboxypeptidase A inhibitor latexin because protease dysfunctions contribute to the development of neuropathic pain. Latexin protein expression was reduced after SNI which could be confirmed by Western Blot analysis, quantitative RT-PCR and in-situ hybridisation. The decrease of latexin was associated with an increase of the activity of carboxypeptidase A indicating that the balance between latexin and carboxypeptidase A was impaired in the spinal cord after peripheral nerve injury due to a loss of latexin expression in spinal cord neurons. This may contribute to the development of cold allodynia because normalization of neuronal latexin expression in the spinal cord by AAV-mediated latexin transduction or administration of a small molecule carboxypeptidase A inhibitor significantly reduced acetone-evoked nociceptive behavior after SNI. Our results show the usefulness of</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>