<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7090">eurovision 2012</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:49:07" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7090-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7090_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:49:11">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=28F89141B6F0DEB424A415021A56BBD5?doi=10.1.1.419.5674&amp;rank=1</link><title>Evidence for the influence of the mere-exposure effect on voting in the Eurovision Song Contest</title><description>Evidence for the influence of the mere-exposure effect on voting in the Eurovision Song Contest

by Diarmuid B. Verrier

"... . 7, No. 5, September 2012 Mere exposure in the Eurovision Song Contest 640 during which time viewers ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

stimuli to which they have previously been exposed. The &lt;em&gt;Eurovision&lt;/em&gt; Song Contest is a two-stage event</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7090-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7090_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:50:15">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=28F89141B6F0DEB424A415021A56BBD5?doi=10.1.1.393.1078&amp;rank=2</link><title>partial ranking data</title><description>partial ranking data

by Julien Jacques, Christophe Biernacki, Julien Jacques, Christophe Biernacki

"... ﻿hal-00743384, version 1 - 18 Oct 2012 Model-based clustering for multivariate partial ranking data ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

and the votes of the European countries to the &lt;em&gt;Eurovision&lt;/em&gt; song contest. For each application, the proposed model</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7090-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7090_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:51:25">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=28F89141B6F0DEB424A415021A56BBD5?doi=10.1.1.309.9182&amp;rank=3</link><title>The RaiNewsbook: Browsing Worldwide Multimodal News Stories by Facts, Entities and Dates</title><description>The RaiNewsbook: Browsing Worldwide Multimodal News Stories by Facts, Entities and Dates

by Maurizio Montagnuolo, Rai Radiotelevisione Italiana, Alberto Messina, Rai Radiotelevisione Italiana

"... ﻿WWW 2012 – Demos Track April 16–20, 2012, Lyon, France The RaiNewsbook: Browsing Worldwide ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

This paper presents a novel framework for multimodal news data aggregation, retrieval and browsing. News aggregations are contextualised within automatically extracted information such as entities (i.e. persons, places and organisations), temporal span, categorical topics, social networks popularity and audience scores. Further resources coming from professional repositories, and related to the aggregation topics, can be accessed as well. The system is accessible through a Web interface supporting interactive navigation and exploration of large-scale collections of news stories at the topic and context levels. Users can select news topics and subtopics interactively, building their personal paths towards worldwide events, main characters, dates and contents.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7090-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7090_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:52:33">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=28F89141B6F0DEB424A415021A56BBD5?doi=10.1.1.294.7224&amp;rank=4</link><title>Talk of the City: Our Tweets, Our Community Happiness</title><description>Talk of the City: Our Tweets, Our Community Happiness

by Daniele Quercia, Diarmuid Ò Séaghdha, Jon Crowcroft

"... , there is a growing literature on the development and evaluation Copyright c○ 2012, Association ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 4 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The literature of urban sociology and that of psychology have separately established two relationships: the first has linked characteristics of a community to its residents ’ well-being, the second has linked well-being of individuals to their use of words. No one has hitherto explored the potential transitive relationship- that between characteristics of a community and its residents’ use of words. We test this relationship by performing three steps. We consider Twitter users in a variety of London census communities; extract the subject matter of their tweets using “topic models”; and study the relationship between topics and community socio-economic well-being. We find that certain topics are correlated (positively and negatively) with community deprivation. Users in more deprived community tweet about wedding parties, matters expressed in Spanish/Portuguese, and celebrity gossips. By contrast, those in less deprived communities tweet about vacations, professional use of social media, environmental issues, sports, and health issues. We finally show that monitoring the subject matter of tweets not only offers insights into community well-being, but it is also a reasonable way of predicting community deprivation scores. 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7090-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7090_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:53:44">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=28F89141B6F0DEB424A415021A56BBD5?doi=10.1.1.406.3978&amp;rank=5</link><title>Collate</title><description>Collate

by Quentin Grimonprez, Needscompilation Yes , 2013

"... the ranking of the 8 common finalists of the Eurovision song contest from 2007 to 2012: 1: France, 2:Germany ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Description This package proposes a model-based clustering algorithm for ranking data. Multivariate rankings as well as partial rankings are taken into account. This algorithm is based on an extension of the Insertion Sorting Rank (ISR) model for ranking data, which is a meaningful and effective model parametrized by a position parameter (the modal ranking,quoted by mu) and a dispersion parameter (quoted by pi). The heterogeneity of the rank population is modelled by a mixture of ISR, whereas conditional independence assumption is considered for multivariate rankings.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7090-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7090_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:54:51">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=28F89141B6F0DEB424A415021A56BBD5?doi=10.1.1.308.6802&amp;rank=6</link><title>Segmentation and timbre- and rhythm-similarity in Electronic Dance Music</title><description>Segmentation and timbre- and rhythm-similarity in Electronic Dance Music

by Bruno Rocha, Niels Bogaards, Aline Honingh

"... that develops audio applications for mobile devices. The project ran from May 2012 until March 2013 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract. This report describes the digital humanities project on music similarity. The project is a collaboration between the University of Amsterdam and audio software company Elephantcandy. The project’s aim was to investigate timbre and rhythm similarity and to develop an application that finds similar segments of music. In this report three models are described, one for structural segmentation, one for timbre similarity, and one for rhythm similarity of electronic dance music (EDM). The segmentation algorithm performs well on an EDM dataset as well as on a standard MIREX dataset. The timbre similarity algorithm has been tested in a pilot study and preliminary results are presented. Issues related to segmentation and similarity are discussed. 1.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7090-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7090_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:55:59">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=28F89141B6F0DEB424A415021A56BBD5?doi=10.1.1.300.2891&amp;rank=7</link><title>Eliminating the Weakest Link: Making Manipulation Intractable</title><description>Eliminating the Weakest Link: Making Manipulation Intractable

by Jessica Davies, Nina Narodytska, Toby Walsh \- In: Proceedings of the National Conference on Artificial Intelligence (AAAI , 2012

"... 2012 Abstract Successive elimination of candidates is often a route to making manipulation intractable ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 3 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Successive elimination of candidates is often a route to making manipulation intractable to compute. We prove that eliminating candidates does not necessarily increase the computational complexity of manipulation. However, for many voting rules used in practice, the computational complexity increases. For example, it is already known that it is NP-hard to compute how a single voter can manipulate the result of single transferable voting(the elimination version of plurality voting). We show here that it is NP-hard to compute how a single voter can manipulate the result of the elimination version of veto voting, of the closely related Coombs ’ rule, and of the elimination versions of a general class of scoring rules.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7090-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7090_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:56:55">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=28F89141B6F0DEB424A415021A56BBD5?doi=10.1.1.222.7249&amp;rank=8</link><title>tech-i INSIGHT FROM EBU TECHNICAL Contents</title><description>tech-i INSIGHT FROM EBU TECHNICAL Contents

by Viewpoint Lieven Vermaele

"... of the Eurovision Network, our results included: • Tests and evaluation of new contribution codecs for the evolution ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7090-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7090_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:57:54">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=28F89141B6F0DEB424A415021A56BBD5?doi=10.1.1.393.2663&amp;rank=9</link><title>Producing "European " News</title><description>Producing "European " News

by Olivier Baisnée, Dominique Marchetti, Chandrika Mathur, Olivier Baisnée, Dominique Marchetti, European Studies Programme, Olivier Baisnee, Dominique Marchetti , 2012

"... ﻿Working Paper Series halshs-00665816, version 1 - 2 Feb 2012 2010/I Meenakshi Thapan and Maitrayee ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Case of the Pan-European News Channel Euronews</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7090-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7090_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:59:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=28F89141B6F0DEB424A415021A56BBD5?doi=10.1.1.402.2660&amp;rank=10</link><title>Information*Retrieval! A"workshop"at"ACM"SIGIR"2013"</title><description>Information*Retrieval! A"workshop"at"ACM"SIGIR"2013"

by unknown authors

"... participants and tasks, for full queries (left) and diluted queries (right). the Eurovision Song Contest home ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

community,)who)have)been)underrepresented)at)previous)EuroHCIR) conferences.)Thus)we)proposed)to)have)the)workshop)at)the)ACM)SIGIR) conference)in)Dublin.)Research,)Industry,)and)Position)papers)were)invited,)and) although)very)few)industry)submissions)were)received,)we)received)a)number)of) research)and)position)papers)focusing)on)the)intersection)of)IR)and)HCI) evaluations,)several)focusing)on)adapting)the)TREC)paradigm.)Many)interesting) system)and)demonstrator)papers)were)also)accepted.) Max"L."Wilson"</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>