<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7097">best dum blonds</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:08:38" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7097-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7097_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:08:41">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CCDB0D702DDFE37D2BA1EF27F22392E7?doi=10.1.1.81.5750&amp;rank=1</link><title>Cryptography and Data Security</title><description>Cryptography and Data Security

by Dorothy E. Denning, Peter, J. Denning , 1982

"... could pre- vent this. O f 0 o (HOW MANY BROWN- O | EYED, F[VE-FOOT- | BLONDES HAVE Oo L.H,ODEN MOLES? 0 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 503 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The rising abuse of computers and increasing threat to personal privacy through data banks have stimulated much interest m the techmcal safeguards for data. There are four kinds of safeguards, each related to but distract from the others. Access controls regulate which users may enter the system and subsequently whmh data sets an active user may read or wrote. Flow controls regulate the dissemination of values among the data sets accessible to a user. Inference controls protect statistical databases by preventing questioners from deducing confidential information by posing carefully designed sequences of statistical queries and correlating the responses. Statlstmal data banks are much less secure than most people beheve. Data encryption attempts to prevent unauthorized disclosure of confidential information in transit or m storage. This paper describes the general nature of controls of each type, the kinds of problems they can and cannot solve, and their inherent limitations and weaknesses. The paper is intended for a general audience with little background in the area.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7097-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7097_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:09:48">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CCDB0D702DDFE37D2BA1EF27F22392E7?doi=10.1.1.28.6847&amp;rank=2</link><title>Algebraic Algorithms for Sampling from Conditional Distributions</title><description>Algebraic Algorithms for Sampling from Conditional Distributions

by Persi Diaconis, Bernd Sturmfels \- Annals of Statistics , 1995

"... having 2 138:29. Their best estimate was "about 10%". Figure 1 shows a histogram from a Monte Carlo ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 192 (16 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We construct Markov chain algorithms for sampling from discrete exponential families conditional on a sufficient statistic. Examples include generating tables with fixed row and column sums and higher dimensional analogs. The algorithms involve finding bases for associated polynomial ideals and so an excursion into computational algebraic geometry.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7097-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7097_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:11:00">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CCDB0D702DDFE37D2BA1EF27F22392E7?doi=10.1.1.334.5138&amp;rank=3</link><title>The neural basis of human error processing: Reinforcement learning, dopamine, and the error-related negativity.” Psychological Review 109:679–709</title><description>The neural basis of human error processing: Reinforcement learning, dopamine, and the error-related negativity.” Psychological Review 109:679–709

by Clay B. Holroyd, Michael G. H. Coles

"... controller that is best suited for the task at hand. To address this issue, we follow a parallel approach ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 184 (12 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The authors present a unified account of 2 neural systems concerned with the development and expression of adaptive behaviors: a mesencephalic dopamine system for reinforcement learning and a “generic ” error-processing system associated with the anterior cingulate cortex. The existence of the error-processing system has been inferred from the error-related negativity (ERN), a component of the event-related brain potential elicited when human participants commit errors in reaction-time tasks. The authors propose that the ERN is generated when a negative reinforcement learning signal is conveyed to the anterior cingulate cortex via the mesencephalic dopamine system and that this signal is used by the anterior cingulate cortex to modify performance on the task at hand. They provide support for this proposal using both computational modeling and psychophysiological experimentation. Human beings learn from the consequences of their actions. Thorndike (1911/1970) originally described this phenomenon with his law of effect, which made explicit the commonsense notion that actions that are followed by feelings of satisfaction are more likely to be generated again in the future, whereas actions that are followed by negative outcomes are less likely to reoccur. This</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7097-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7097_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:12:16">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CCDB0D702DDFE37D2BA1EF27F22392E7?doi=10.1.1.330.6597&amp;rank=4</link><title>Mudding: Social phenomena in text-based virtual realities</title><description>Mudding: Social phenomena in text-based virtual realities

by Pavel Curtis \- In Proceedings of the 1992 Conference on the Directions and Implications of Advanced Computing , 1992

"... . To the best of my knowledge, male-presenting players are rarely if ever so challenged. Because ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 172 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

A MUD (Multi-User Dungeon or, sometimes, Multi-User Dimension) is a network-accessible, multi-participant, user-extensible virtual reality whose user interface is entirely textual. Participants (usually called players) have the appearance of being situated in an artificially-constructed place that also contains those other players who are connected at the same time. Players can communicate easily with each other in real time. This virtual gathering place has many of the social attributes of other places, and many of the usual social mechanisms operate there. Certain attributes of this virtual place, however, tend to have significant effects on social phenomena, leading to new mechanisms and modes of behavior not usually seen ‘IRL’ (in real life). In this paper, I relate my experiences and observations from having created and maintained a MUD for over a year. 1 A Brief Introduction to Mudding The Machine did not transmit nuances</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7097-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7097_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:13:18">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CCDB0D702DDFE37D2BA1EF27F22392E7?doi=10.1.1.408.8006&amp;rank=5</link><title>A Beautiful Blonde: a Nash coordination game ¤</title><description>A Beautiful Blonde: a Nash coordination game ¤

by Simon P. Anderson, Maxim Engers Y , 2002

"... ﻿A Beautiful Blonde: a Nash coordination game ¤ Simon P. Anderson and Maxim Engers y July 2002 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

In a memorable scene from the …lm ”A Beautiful Mind, ” John Nash explains to his friends how to direct their attentions to women in a bar. Game theorists who have seen the …lm point out that the proposed solution is not a Nash equilibrium. Here we determine the Nash equilibria to the attention game. The symmetric mixed strategy equilibrium has resembles a common property resource problem. It has perverse comparative static properties that are not borne out by experimental data. Finally, we discuss alternative ways of formulating the game.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7097-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7097_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:14:33">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CCDB0D702DDFE37D2BA1EF27F22392E7?doi=10.1.1.10.181&amp;rank=6</link><title>Incremental Induction of Decision Trees</title><description>Incremental Induction of Decision Trees

by Paul Utgoff Utgoff , 1989

"... ) Define a best to be an attribute with the lowest E-score. (b) For each value v best;i of a best , grow a ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 160 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This article presents an incremental algorithm for inducing decision trees equivalent to those formed by Quinlan's nonincremental ID3 algorithm, given the same training instances. The new algorithm, named ID5R, lets one apply the ID3 induction process to learning tasks in which training instances are presented serially.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7097-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7097_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:15:40">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CCDB0D702DDFE37D2BA1EF27F22392E7?doi=10.1.1.153.2194&amp;rank=7</link><title>Attribute and Simile Classifiers for Face Verification</title><description>Attribute and Simile Classifiers for Face Verification

by Neeraj Kumar, Alexander C. Berg, Peter N. Belhumeur, Shree K. Nayar \- In IEEE International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV , 2009

"... on the current state-of-the-art for the LFW data set, reducing the error rates compared to the current best by 23 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 143 (14 self) \- Add to MetaCart

data set, reducing the error rates compared to the current &lt;em&gt;best&lt;/em&gt; by 23.92 % and 26.34%, respectively</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7097-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7097_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:16:57">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CCDB0D702DDFE37D2BA1EF27F22392E7?doi=10.1.1.400.9835&amp;rank=8</link><title>On the Betti numbers of real varieties</title><description>On the Betti numbers of real varieties

by J. Milnor \- Proc. Amer. Math. Soc , 1964

"... for suggesting this problem to me. Remark A. This is certainly not a best possible estimate. (Compare Remark B ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 132 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

. This is certainly not a &lt;em&gt;best&lt;/em&gt; possible estimate. (Compare Remark B.) In the examples which I know, the sum</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7097-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7097_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:17:56">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CCDB0D702DDFE37D2BA1EF27F22392E7?doi=10.1.1.15.244&amp;rank=9</link><title>Discourse Referents</title><description>Discourse Referents

by Lauri Karttunen , 1969

"... Pase the best student is not used PefePentiaUy in a sentence such as Bill is the best student. -[-here ape thus ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 131 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

to refer to an individual at all. For example s it is clear that the phrase the &lt;em&gt;best&lt;/em&gt; student is not used</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7097-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7097_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:18:54">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CCDB0D702DDFE37D2BA1EF27F22392E7?doi=10.1.1.377.3750&amp;rank=10</link><title>Metric spaces and positive definite functions</title><description>Metric spaces and positive definite functions

by J. Schoenberg \- Transactions of the American Mathematical Society , 1938

"... (XlUl + ... + Xmum) ]dul ... dUm, where t/; is a non-negative even function such that its integral over the whole ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 128 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

generally EmP the pseudo-euclidean space of m real variables with the distance function p&gt; o. As p ~ 00 we get the space E = with the distance function maXi=l,...,m IXi- xl I.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>