<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7098">tour moscow</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:19:58" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7098-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7098_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:20:01">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=49264A6024343F2BAAABE679612438ED?doi=10.1.1.258.9687&amp;rank=1</link><title>MOSCOW NIGHTS: SPECTACULAR CONDENSERS</title><description>MOSCOW NIGHTS: SPECTACULAR CONDENSERS

by unknown authors , 2012

"... ﻿INTERMEDIATE 7 2012 / 2013 MOSCOW NIGHTS: SPECTACULAR CONDENSERS Summary: The unit explores design ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

into the whirlpools of leisure and entertainment behind flagrant &lt;em&gt;Moscow&lt;/em&gt; transformations to define hybrid typologies</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7098-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7098_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:21:01">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=49264A6024343F2BAAABE679612438ED?doi=10.1.1.317.8499&amp;rank=2</link><title>Université de Tours, Parc de Grandmont, F-37200 Tours (France)</title><description>Université de Tours, Parc de Grandmont, F-37200 Tours (France)

by David Polarski, Alexei A. Starobinsky A , 2008

"... Physique Mathématique, EP93 CNRS Université de Tours, Parc de Grandmont, F-37200 Tours (France) 2 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

The gravitational waves (GW) background generated in a double inflationary model, with two scalar fields mutually interacting through gravity only, and its relative contribution T/S to large-angle temperature fluctuations of the relic microwave background are investigated in detail. The relation between T/S and the slope of the GW spectrum nT is shown to be a discriminative test between a slow-roll inflation driven by one scalar field and more complicated models. It is found that the GW amplitude is not exactly zero in minima of spectral oscillations, this property being an observational, in principle, manifestation of GW being in a squeezed vacuum state during inflation. PACS Numbers: 04.62.+v, 98.80.Cq 0 Cosmological models in which the early Universe passed through two successive de Sitter (inflationary) phases of quasi-exponential expansion ([1]-[8] and other papers) are usually called double inflationary ones. The initial spectrum of adiabatic perturbations in these models is not approximately flat (i.e., n ≈ 1, or Harrison-</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7098-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7098_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:22:02">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=49264A6024343F2BAAABE679612438ED?doi=10.1.1.338.7154&amp;rank=3</link><title>Université de Tours, Parc de Grandmont, F-37200 Tours (France)</title><description>Université de Tours, Parc de Grandmont, F-37200 Tours (France)

by J. Lesgourgues, David Polarski, A. A. Starobinsky A , 2008

"... Mathématiques et de Physique Théorique, EP93 CNRS Université de Tours, Parc de Grandmont, F-37200 Tours (France ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Transition from quantum to semiclassical behaviour and loss of quantum coherence for inhomogeneous perturbations generated from a non-vacuum initial state in the early Universe is considered in the Heisenberg and the Schrödinger representations, as well as using the Wigner function. We show explicitly that these three approaches lead to the same prediction in the limit of large squeezing (i.e. when the squeezing parameter |rk | → ∞): each two-modes quantum state (k, − k) of these perturbations is equivalent to a classical perturbation that has a stochastic amplitude, obeying a non-gaussian statistics which depends on the initial state, and that belongs to the quasi-isotropic mode (i.e. it possesses a fixed phase). The Wigner function is not everywhere positive for any finite rk, hence its interpretation as a classical distribution function in phase space is impossible without some coarse graining procedure. However, this does not affect the transition to semiclassical behaviour since the Wigner function becomes concentrated near a classical trajectory in phase space when |rk | → ∞ even without coarse graining. Deviations of the statistics of the perturbations in real space from a Gaussian one lie below the cosmic variance level for the N-particles initial states with N = N(|k|) but may be observable for other initial states without statistical isotropy or with correlations between different k modes. As a way to look for this effect, it is proposed to measure 0 the kurtosis of the angular fluctuations of the cosmic microwave background temperature. PACS Numbers: 04.62.+v, 98.80.Cq, 98.80.Hw 1 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7098-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7098_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:22:57">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=49264A6024343F2BAAABE679612438ED?doi=10.1.1.376.2126&amp;rank=4</link><title>REVIEW Open Access Microwaves in the cold war: the Moscow</title><description>REVIEW Open Access Microwaves in the cold war: the Moscow

by J Mark Elwood

"... Access Microwaves in the cold war: the Moscow embassy study and its interpretation. Review of a ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

embassy study and its interpretation. Review of a retrospective cohort study</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7098-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7098_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:24:08">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=49264A6024343F2BAAABE679612438ED?doi=10.1.1.165.6753&amp;rank=5</link><title>The logic of generalized truth values. A tour into Philosophical Logic</title><description>The logic of generalized truth values. A tour into Philosophical Logic

by Heinrich Wansing, Heinrich Wansing, N. D. Entailment, The Logic, Heinrich Wansing

"... ﻿References ICCL Summer School 2008 The logic of generalized truth values. A tour ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7098-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7098_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:25:22">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=49264A6024343F2BAAABE679612438ED?doi=10.1.1.40.4224&amp;rank=6</link><title>LASSO: A Tool for Surfing the Answer Net</title><description>LASSO: A Tool for Surfing the Answer Net

by Dan Moldovan, Sanda Harabagiu, Marius Pasca, A Harabagiu, Rada Mihalcea, Roxana Gîrju, Richard Goodrum, Vasile Rus , 1999

"... from cellulose? how-far 1 1 distance How far is Yaroslavl from Moscow? Yaroslavl how-tall 3 3 number ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 56 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper presents the architecture, operation and results obtained with the Lasso system developed in the Natural Language Processing Laboratory at SMU. The system relies on a combination of syntactic and semantic techniques, and lightweight abductive inference to find answers. The search for the answer is based on a novel form of indexing called paragraph indexing. A score of 55.5% for short answers and 64.5% for long answers was achieved. Background Finding the answer to a question by returning a small fragment of a text, where the answer actually lies, is profoundly di erent from the task of information retrieval (IR) or information extraction (IE). Current IR systems allow us to locate full documents that might contain the pertinent information, leaving it to the user to extract the answer from a ranked list of texts. In contrast, IE systems extract the information of interest, provided it has been presented in a prede ned, target representation, known as template. The i...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7098-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7098_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:26:29">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=49264A6024343F2BAAABE679612438ED?doi=10.1.1.19.9401&amp;rank=7</link><title>The Structure and Performance of an Open-Domain Question Answering System</title><description>The Structure and Performance of an Open-Domain Question Answering System

by Dan Moldovan, Sanda Harabagiu, A Harabagiu, Marius Pasca, Rada Mihalcea, Roxana Girju, Richard Goodrum, Vasile Rus, I Background \- In Proceedings of the Conference of the Association for Computational Linguistics (ACL-2000 , 2000

"... with the material made from cellulose? how-far 1 1 DISTANCE How far is Yaroslavl from Moscow? Yaroslavl how-tall 3 3 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 53 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper presents the architecture, operation and results obtained with the LASSO Question Answering system developed in the Natural Language Processing Laboratory at SMU. To find answers, the system relies on a combination of syntactic and semantic techniques. The search for the answer is based on a novel form of indexing called paragraph indexing. A score of 55.5% for short answers and 64.5% for long answers was achieved at the TREC- 8 competition.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7098-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7098_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:27:35">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=49264A6024343F2BAAABE679612438ED?doi=10.1.1.366.6085&amp;rank=8</link><title>*-"/Xlr</title><description>*-"/Xlr 

by Moscow Air Show, David K. Barton, I Nlytetteu, Sergey Leonov, Er A. Lemansky, Scientific Director

"... ﻿I SPECIAL REPORT The 1993 Moscow Air Show David K. Barton i +,-) ^$lAvE,to) *-"/Xlr

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

to the &lt;em&gt;Moscow&lt;/em&gt; 1993 Air Show, which was held from August 31 to September 5, 1993. The show was held

Limits on Kaluza-Klein Models from COBE Results

by Yu Kubyshin, Jerome Martin

"... , Moscow State University, 117234 Moscow, Russia. \+ E-mail address: kubyshin@(email omitted); # On leave ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

from Nuclear Physics Institute, &lt;em&gt;Moscow&lt;/em&gt; State University, 117234 &lt;em&gt;Moscow&lt;/em&gt;, Russia. + E-mail address

Russian Privatization and Corporate Governance: What Went Wrong

by Bernard Black, Reinier Kraakman, Anna Tarassova, Bernard Black, Reinier Kraakman, Anna Tarassova, Bernard Black, Reinier Kraakman, Anna Tarassova \- Privatization and Company Restructuring in , 2000

"... .......................................................... 3 II. A CYNIC’S TOUR OF RUSSIAN PRIVATIZATION ................................ 8 A. Mass ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 41 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

In Russia and elsewhere, proponents of rapid, mass privatization of stateowned enterprises (ourselves among them) hoped that the profit incentives unleashed by privatization would soon revive faltering, centrally planned economies. The revival didn’t happen. We offer here some partial explanations. First, rapid mass privatization is likely to lead to massive selfdealing by managers and controlling shareholders unless (implausibly in the initial transition from central planning to markets) a country has a good infrastructure for controlling self-dealing. Russia accelerated the selfdealing process by selling control of its largest enterprises cheaply to crooks, who transferred their skimming talents to the enterprises they acquired, and used their wealth to further corrupt the government and block reforms that might constrain their actions. Second, profit incentives to restructure privatized businesses and create new ones can be swamped by the burden on business imposed by a combination of (among other things) a punitive tax system, official corruption, organized crime, and an unfriendly bureaucracy.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7098-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7098_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:28:49">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=49264A6024343F2BAAABE679612438ED?doi=10.1.1.51.1931&amp;rank=9</link><title>Limits on Kaluza-Klein Models from COBE Results</title><description>Limits on Kaluza-Klein Models from COBE Results

by Yu Kubyshin, Jerome Martin

"... , Moscow State University, 117234 Moscow, Russia. \+ E-mail address: kubyshin@(email omitted); # On leave ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

from Nuclear Physics Institute, &lt;em&gt;Moscow&lt;/em&gt; State University, 117234 &lt;em&gt;Moscow&lt;/em&gt;, Russia. + E-mail address</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7098-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7098_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:29:46">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=49264A6024343F2BAAABE679612438ED?doi=10.1.1.196.9300&amp;rank=10</link><title>Russian Privatization and Corporate Governance: What Went Wrong</title><description>Russian Privatization and Corporate Governance: What Went Wrong

by Bernard Black, Reinier Kraakman, Anna Tarassova, Bernard Black, Reinier Kraakman, Anna Tarassova, Bernard Black, Reinier Kraakman, Anna Tarassova \- Privatization and Company Restructuring in , 2000

"... .......................................................... 3 II. A CYNIC’S TOUR OF RUSSIAN PRIVATIZATION ................................ 8 A. Mass ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 41 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

In Russia and elsewhere, proponents of rapid, mass privatization of stateowned enterprises (ourselves among them) hoped that the profit incentives unleashed by privatization would soon revive faltering, centrally planned economies. The revival didn’t happen. We offer here some partial explanations. First, rapid mass privatization is likely to lead to massive selfdealing by managers and controlling shareholders unless (implausibly in the initial transition from central planning to markets) a country has a good infrastructure for controlling self-dealing. Russia accelerated the selfdealing process by selling control of its largest enterprises cheaply to crooks, who transferred their skimming talents to the enterprises they acquired, and used their wealth to further corrupt the government and block reforms that might constrain their actions. Second, profit incentives to restructure privatized businesses and create new ones can be swamped by the burden on business imposed by a combination of (among other things) a punitive tax system, official corruption, organized crime, and an unfriendly bureaucracy.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>