<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7102">vlc mac</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:04:10" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7102-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7102_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:04:14">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=3ED2D4367DB662AA9DE72CACB5B10A22?doi=10.1.1.33.1377&amp;rank=1</link><title>Pliers At Vlc2</title><description>Pliers At Vlc2

by Macfarlane Robertson Mccann, A. Macfarlane, S. E. Robertson, J. A. Mccann

"... ﻿PLIERS AT VLC2 * A. MacFarlane, *+ S.E.Robertson, * J.A.McCann * School of Informatics, City ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

: This paper describes experiments done on the &lt;em&gt;VLC&lt;/em&gt;2 collection at TREC-7. Methods used for indexing</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7102-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7102_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:05:19">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=3ED2D4367DB662AA9DE72CACB5B10A22?doi=10.1.1.390.3906&amp;rank=2</link><title>Virtual Cognitive MAC for Visible Light Communication System</title><description>Virtual Cognitive MAC for Visible Light Communication System

by Nam-tuan Le, Yeong Min Jang

"... ﻿International Journal of Smart Home Vol. 6, No. 2, April, 2012 Virtual Cognitive MAC for Visible ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

, the link quality will effect. In this article, new approach for multi-channel &lt;em&gt;MAC&lt;/em&gt; for visible light</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7102-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7102_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:06:31">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=3ED2D4367DB662AA9DE72CACB5B10A22?doi=10.1.1.257.6260&amp;rank=3</link><title>Low-Complexity Visible Light Networking with LED-to-LED Communication</title><description>Low-Complexity Visible Light Networking with LED-to-LED Communication

by Domenico Giustiniano, Stefan Mangold

"... Communication (VLC) is an emerging technology in which Light Emitting Diodes (LEDs) transport information ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract—Visible Light Communication (&lt;em&gt;VLC&lt;/em&gt;) is an emerging</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7102-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7102_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:07:35">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=3ED2D4367DB662AA9DE72CACB5B10A22?doi=10.1.1.21.2038&amp;rank=4</link><title>Exploiting Redundancy in Question Answering</title><description>Exploiting Redundancy in Question Answering

by Charles L. A. Clarke, Gordon V. Cormack, Thomas R. Lynam \- In Proceedings of SIGIR , 2001

"... the 3GB TREC-9 QA corpus in favor a larger corpus, the TREC 100GB VLC2 corpus [12,21]. Apart from its ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 93 (11 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Our goal is to automatically answer brief factual questions of the form "When was the Battle of Hastings?" or "Who wrote The Wind in the Willows?". Since the answer to nearly any such question can now be found somewhere on the Web, the problem reduces to finding potential answers in large volumes of data and validating their accuracy. We apply a method for arbitrary passage retrieval to the first half of the problem and demonstrate that answer redundancy can be used to address the second half. The success of our approach depends on the idea that the volume of available Web data is large enough to supply the answer to most factual questions multiple times and in multiple contexts. A query is generated from a question and this query is used to select short passages that may contain the answer from a large collection of Web data. These passages are analyzed to identify candidate answers. The frequency of these candidates within the passages is used to "vote" for the most likely answer. The ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7102-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7102_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:08:36">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=3ED2D4367DB662AA9DE72CACB5B10A22?doi=10.1.1.376.4968&amp;rank=5</link><title>LED-to-LED Visible Light Communication Networks ABSTRACT</title><description>LED-to-LED Visible Light Communication Networks ABSTRACT

by Stefan Schmid, Stefan Mangold, Giorgio Corbellini, Thomas R. Gross

"... : Concept art ( c○ Disney). LED-to-LED VLC adhoc network with PHY and MAC layers that use LEDs ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Visible Light Communication (&lt;em&gt;VLC&lt;/em&gt;) with Light Emitting Diodes (LEDs) as transmitters and receivers</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7102-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7102_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:09:44">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=3ED2D4367DB662AA9DE72CACB5B10A22?doi=10.1.1.384.8028&amp;rank=6</link><title>A SURVEY OF WIRELESS COMMUNICATION USING VISIBLE LIGHT</title><description>A SURVEY OF WIRELESS COMMUNICATION USING VISIBLE LIGHT

by M. V. Bhalerao, S. S. Sonavane, V. Kumar

"... . There are a PHY and a Media Access Control (MAC) as a common part of the transmitter and receiver of VLC. PHY ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

This paper introduces the concept of visible light communication (&lt;em&gt;VLC&lt;/em&gt;). The urgent need of &lt;em&gt;VLC&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7102-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7102_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:10:44">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=3ED2D4367DB662AA9DE72CACB5B10A22?doi=10.1.1.61.7206&amp;rank=7</link><title>Very Large Scale Retrieval and Web Search</title><description>Very Large Scale Retrieval and Web Search

by David Hawking, Nick Craswell , 2004

"... Together, the TREC Very Large Collection (VLC) Track and its successor the Web Track have run for seven ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 21 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Together, the TREC Very Large Collection (&lt;em&gt;VLC&lt;/em&gt;) Track and its successor the Web Track have run</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7102-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7102_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:11:47">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=3ED2D4367DB662AA9DE72CACB5B10A22?doi=10.1.1.177.9223&amp;rank=8</link><title>Video transport over ad hoc networks: Multistream coding with multipath transport</title><description>Video transport over ad hoc networks: Multistream coding with multipath transport

by Shiwen Mao, Student Member, Shunan Lin, Student Member, Shivendra S. Panwar, Senior Member, Yao Wang, Senior Member, Emre Celebi, Student Member \- IEEE J. Sel. Areas Commun , 2003

"... popular media access control (MAC) scheme, the carrier sensing multiple access/collision avoidance (CSMA ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 72 (6 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract—Enabling video transport over ad hoc networks is more challenging than over other wireless networks. The wireless links in an ad hoc network are highly error prone and can go down frequently because of node mobility, interference, channel fading, and the lack of infrastructure. However, the mesh topology of ad hoc networks implies that it is possible to establish multiple paths between a source and a destination. Indeed, multipath transport provides an extra degree of freedom in designing error resilient video coding and transport schemes. In this paper, we propose to combine multistream coding with multipath transport, to show that, in addition to traditional error control techniques, path diversity provides an effective means to combat transmission error in ad hoc networks. The schemes that we have examined are: 1) feedback based reference picture selection; 2) layered coding with selective automatic repeat request; and 3) multiple description motion compensation coding. All these techniques are based on the motion compensated prediction technique found in modern video coding standards. We studied the performance of these three schemes via extensive simulations using both Markov channel models and OPNET Modeler. To further validate the viability and performance advantages of these schemes, we implemented an ad hoc multiple path video streaming testbed using notebook computers and IEEE 802.11b cards. The results show that great improvement in video quality can be achieved over the standard schemes with limited additional cost. Each of these three video coding/transport techniques is best suited for a particular environment, depending on the availability of a feedback channel, the end-to-end delay constraint, and the error characteristics of the paths. Index Terms—Ad hoc networks, error resilience, IEEE 802.11, multipath transport, video transport, wireless networks.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7102-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7102_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:12:57">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=3ED2D4367DB662AA9DE72CACB5B10A22?doi=10.1.1.376.5267&amp;rank=9</link><title>A Demonstration of a Cross-Layer Cooperative Routing-MAC scheme in Multi-hop Ad-Hoc Networks</title><description>A Demonstration of a Cross-Layer Cooperative Routing-MAC scheme in Multi-hop Ad-Hoc Networks

by Jian Lin, Thanasis Korakis, Xiao Wang, Shunyuan Ye, Shivendra Panwar

"... ﻿A Demonstration of a Cross-Layer Cooperative Routing-MAC scheme in Multi-hop Ad-Hoc Networks Jian ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

of cooperation at the &lt;em&gt;MAC&lt;/em&gt; layer, in conjunction with the routing layer, in multi-hop ad-hoc networks</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7102-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7102_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:14:11">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=3ED2D4367DB662AA9DE72CACB5B10A22?doi=10.1.1.304.8149&amp;rank=10</link><title>The Very Large Collection and Web Tracks (Preprint version)</title><description>The Very Large Collection and Web Tracks (Preprint version)

by David Hawking, Nick Craswell , 2004

"... Together, the TREC Very Large Collection (VLC) Track and its successor the Web Track have run for seven ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Together, the TREC Very Large Collection (&lt;em&gt;VLC&lt;/em&gt;) Track and its successor the Web Track have run</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>