<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7106">active learning survey</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:51:47" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7106-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7106_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:51:52">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=14D2E579DF344FDB8EB85D611D62E303?doi=10.1.1.134.2462&amp;rank=1</link><title>Reinforcement learning: a survey</title><description>Reinforcement learning: a survey

by Leslie Pack Kaelbling, Michael L. Littman, Andrew W. Moore \- Journal of Artificial Intelligence Research , 1996

"... /96 Reinforcement Learning: A Survey Leslie Pack Kaelbling lpk@(email omitted); Michael L. Littman mlittman ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1298 (23 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper &lt;em&gt;surveys&lt;/em&gt; the field of reinforcement &lt;em&gt;learning&lt;/em&gt; from a computer-science perspective</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7106-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7106_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:52:54">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=14D2E579DF344FDB8EB85D611D62E303?doi=10.1.1.18.5535&amp;rank=2</link><title>Active Learning with Statistical Models</title><description>Active Learning with Statistical Models

by David A. Cohn, Zoubin Ghahramani, Michael I. Jordan , 1995

"... .B.C.L. Paper No. 110 Active Learning with Statistical Models David A. Cohn, Zoubin Ghahramani, and Michael I ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 529 (10 self) \- Add to MetaCart

then showhow the same principles may be used to select data for two alternative, statistically-based &lt;em&gt;learning&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7106-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7106_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:54:10">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=14D2E579DF344FDB8EB85D611D62E303?doi=10.1.1.131.2072&amp;rank=3</link><title>The Visual Analysis of Human Movement: A Survey</title><description>The Visual Analysis of Human Movement: A Survey

by D. M. Gavrila \- Computer Vision and Image Understanding , 1999

"... of the most active application domains in computer vision. This survey identifies a number of promising ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 580 (7 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The ability to recognize humans and their &lt;em&gt;activities&lt;/em&gt; by vision is key for a machine to interact</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7106-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7106_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:55:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=14D2E579DF344FDB8EB85D611D62E303?doi=10.1.1.17.6513&amp;rank=4</link><title>Machine Learning in Automated Text Categorization</title><description>Machine Learning in Automated Text Categorization

by Fabrizio Sebastiani, Consiglio Nazionale Delle Ricerche \- ACM Computing Surveys , 2002

"... ﻿Machine Learning in Automated Text Categorization Fabrizio Sebastiani Consiglio Nazionale delle ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1090 (20 self) \- Add to MetaCart

to this problem is based on machine &lt;em&gt;learning&lt;/em&gt; techniques: a general inductive process automatically builds a</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7106-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7106_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:56:23">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=14D2E579DF344FDB8EB85D611D62E303?doi=10.1.1.210.3372&amp;rank=5</link><title>Detecting faces in images: A survey</title><description>Detecting faces in images: A survey

by Ming-hsuan Yang, David J. Kriegman, Narendra Ahuja \- IEEE TRANSACTIONS ON PATTERN ANALYSIS AND MACHINE INTELLIGENCE , 2002

"... Detecting Faces in Images: A Survey Ming-Hsuan Yang, Member, IEEE, David J. Kriegman, Senior Member, IEEE ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 595 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Images containing faces are essential to intelligent vision-based human computer interaction, and research efforts in face processing include face recognition, face tracking, pose estimation, and expression recognition. However, many reported methods assume that the faces in an image or an image sequence have been identified and localized. To build fully automated systems that analyze the information contained in face images, robust and efficient face detection algorithms are required. Given a single image, the goal of face detection is to identify all image regions which contain a face regardless of its three-dimensional position, orientation, and the lighting conditions. Such a problem is challenging because faces are nonrigid and have a high degree of variability in size, shape, color, and texture. Numerous techniques have been developed to detect faces in a single image, and the purpose of this paper is to categorize and evaluate these algorithms. We also discuss relevant issues such as data collection, evaluation metrics, and benchmarking. After analyzing these algorithms and identifying their limitations, we conclude with several promising directions for future research.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7106-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7106_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:57:22">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=14D2E579DF344FDB8EB85D611D62E303?doi=10.1.1.221.2247&amp;rank=6</link><title>Wireless sensor networks: a survey</title><description>Wireless sensor networks: a survey

by I. F. Akyildiz, W. Su, Y. Sankarasubramaniam, E. Cayirci , 2002

"... survey I.F. Akyildiz, W. Su * , Y. Sankarasubramaniam, E. Cayirci Broadband and Wireless Networking ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1135 (21 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper describes the concept of sensor networks which has been made viable by the convergence of microelectro-mechanical systems technology, wireless communications and digital electronics. First, the sensing tasks and the potential sensor networks applications are explored, and a review of factors influencing the design of sensor networks is provided. Then, the communication architecture for sensor networks is outlined, and the algorithms and protocols developed for each layer in the literature are explored. Open research issues for the realization of sensor networks are</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7106-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7106_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:58:24">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=14D2E579DF344FDB8EB85D611D62E303?doi=10.1.1.103.1693&amp;rank=7</link><title>Semi-Supervised Learning Literature Survey</title><description>Semi-Supervised Learning Literature Survey

by Xiaojin Zhu , 2006

"... ﻿Semi-Supervised Learning Literature Survey Xiaojin Zhu Computer Sciences TR 1530 University ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 447 (8 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We review the literature on semi-supervised &lt;em&gt;learning&lt;/em&gt;, which is an area in machine &lt;em&gt;learning&lt;/em&gt; and more</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7106-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7106_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:59:35">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=14D2E579DF344FDB8EB85D611D62E303?doi=10.1.1.12.1457&amp;rank=8</link><title>Learning Patterns of Activity Using Real-Time Tracking</title><description>Learning Patterns of Activity Using Real-Time Tracking

by Chris Stauffer, W. Eric L. Grimson \- IEEE TRANSACTIONS ON PATTERN ANALYSIS AND MACHINE INTELLIGENCE , 2000

"... Learning patterns of activity using real-time tracking Chris Stauffer W. Eric L. Grimson ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 586 (10 self) \- Add to MetaCart

and &lt;em&gt;learns&lt;/em&gt; patterns of &lt;em&gt;activity&lt;/em&gt; from those observations. For extended sites, the system will require multiple</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7106-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7106_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:00:50">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=14D2E579DF344FDB8EB85D611D62E303?doi=10.1.1.16.4036&amp;rank=9</link><title>Support Vector Machine Active Learning with Applications to Text Classification</title><description>Support Vector Machine Active Learning with Applications to Text Classification

by Simon Tong , Daphne Koller \- JOURNAL OF MACHINE LEARNING RESEARCH , 2001

"... Support Vector Machine Active Learning with Applications to Text Classification Simon Tong simon ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 502 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

&lt;em&gt;active&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;learning&lt;/em&gt; with support vector machines, i.e., an algorithm for choosing which instances to request</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7106-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7106_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:01:56">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=14D2E579DF344FDB8EB85D611D62E303?doi=10.1.1.3.3531&amp;rank=10</link><title>Face Recognition: A Literature Survey</title><description>Face Recognition: A Literature Survey

by W. Zhao, R. Chellappa, P. J. Phillips, A. Rosenfeld , 2000

"... ﻿Face Recognition: A Literature Survey W. ZHAO Sarnoff Corporation R. CHELLAPPA University ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 850 (21 self) \- Add to MetaCart

... This paper provides an up-to-date critical &lt;em&gt;survey&lt;/em&gt; of still- and video-based face recognition</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>