<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7107">grimm episodes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:03:13" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7107-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7107_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:03:19">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=779794D47F1DC5B92581B92F584A4A10?doi=10.1.1.404.6686&amp;rank=1</link><title>References</title><description>References

by P. Bonasoni, P. Cristofanelli, F. Calzolari, U. Bonafè, F. Evangelisti, R. Van Dingenen, T. Colombo, Y. Balkanski , 2004

"... Aerosol-ozone correlations during dust transport episodes P. Bonasoni 1 , P. Cristofanelli 1 , F ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Aerosol-ozone correlations during dust transport &lt;em&gt;episodes&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7107-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7107_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:04:26">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=779794D47F1DC5B92581B92F584A4A10?doi=10.1.1.63.3291&amp;rank=2</link><title>A declarative model for simple narratives</title><description>A declarative model for simple narratives

by R. Raymond Lang \- Proceedings of the AAAI Fall Symposium on Narrative Intelligence , 1999

"... nineteenth century, Wilhelm and Jakob Grimm published their collections of traditional domestic tales (Grimm ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 17 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

pertaining to a culture. In the early nineteenth century, Wilhelm and Jakob &lt;em&gt;Grimm&lt;/em&gt; published their collections</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7107-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7107_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:05:27">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=779794D47F1DC5B92581B92F584A4A10?doi=10.1.1.380.872&amp;rank=3</link><title>The American Monsoon Systems</title><description>The American Monsoon Systems

by C. Roberto Mechoso, Andrew W. Robertson, Chester F. Ropelewski

"... **, and Alice M. Grimm*** *Department of Atmospheric and Oceanic Sciences, University of California Los Angeles ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

et al. (2004) and &lt;em&gt;Grimm&lt;/em&gt; et al. (2004) focus on each of the American monsoon systems in companion</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7107-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7107_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:06:49">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=779794D47F1DC5B92581B92F584A4A10?doi=10.1.1.175.4683&amp;rank=4</link><title>THE CONCEPT, POLICY USE AND MEASUREMENT OF STRUCTURAL UNEMPLOYMENT: ESTIMATING A TIME VARYING NAIRU ACROSS 21 OECD COUNTRIES</title><description>THE CONCEPT, POLICY USE AND MEASUREMENT OF STRUCTURAL UNEMPLOYMENT: ESTIMATING A TIME VARYING NAIRU ACROSS 21 OECD COUNTRIES

by Pete Richardson, David Rae, David Turner, et al. , 2000

"... , and to Rosemary Chahed, Jan-Cathryn Davies and Doris Grimm for document preparation. 2\. See, for example ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 28 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The structural rate of unemployment and associated non-accelerating inflation rate of unemployment (the NAIRU) are of major importance to the analysis of macro and structural economic developments, although in practice these concepts are not well defined and there is considerable uncertainty and controversy concerning their measurement and policy use. The present paper reviews a range of conceptual and analytical issues and related empirical studies to examine the usefulness and limitations of such concepts. A reduced-form Phillips curve approach is found the most suitable conceptual framework for representing the NAIRU as currently used by the OECD in its policy analysis and surveillance work. Three distinct classes of NAIRU concept are identified, distinguished by the time-frame in which they are defined, which map directly into the broad requirements for macro and structural policy analysis. In line with a number of recent empirical studies, this general approach is applied across the 21 OECD member countries, using methods which combine the estimation of reduced-form Phillips curve equations for each country using alternative filtering methods which allow the identification of time-varying NAIRU indicators.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7107-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7107_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:07:54">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=779794D47F1DC5B92581B92F584A4A10?doi=10.1.1.379.2217&amp;rank=5</link><title>Interactive Storytelling: A Player Modelling Approach</title><description>Interactive Storytelling: A Player Modelling Approach

by David Thue, Vadim Bulitko, Marcia Spetch, Eric Wasylishen \- Proceedings of the 3rd Conference on Artificial Intelligence and Interactive Digital Entertainment , 2007

"... of the player’s performance (Charles et al. 2005). For example, in SiN Episodes: Emergence, the likelihood of a ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 20 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

In recent years, the fields of Interactive Storytelling and Player Modelling have independently enjoyed increased interest in both academia and the computer games industry. The combination of these technologies, however, remains largely unexplored. In this paper, we present PaSSAGE (Player-Specific Stories via Automatically Generated Events), an interactive storytelling system that uses player modelling to automatically learn a model of the player’s preferred style of play, and then uses that model to dynamically select the content of an interactive story. Results from a user study evaluating the entertainment value of adaptive stories created by our system as well as two fixed, pre-authored stories indicate that automatically adapting a story based on learned player preferences can increase the enjoyment of playing a computer role-playing game for certain types of players.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7107-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7107_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:09:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=779794D47F1DC5B92581B92F584A4A10?doi=10.1.1.2.7467&amp;rank=6</link><title>Quaternary landscape ecology: Relevant scales in space and time</title><description>Quaternary landscape ecology: Relevant scales in space and time

by Hazel R. Delcourt, Paul A. Delcourt , 1988

"... ). The Quaternary is characterized by alternating episodes of glacial and interglacial climates. Each glacial ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 19 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Two primary goals of landscape ecologists are to (1) evaluate changes in ecological pattern and process on natural landscapes through time and (2) determine the ecological consequences of transforming natural landscapes to cultural ones. Paleoecological techniques can be used to reconstruct past landscapes and their changes through time; use of paleoecological methods of investigation in combination with geomorphic and paleoethnobiological data, historical records, and shorter-term ecological data sets makes it possible to integrate long-term ecological pattern and process on a nested series of temporal and spatial scales. `Natural experiments ' of the past can be used to test alternative hypotheses about the relative influences of environmental change, biological interactions, and human activities in structuring biotic communities within landscape mosaics. On the absolute time scale of the Quaternary Period, spanning the past 1.8 million years, current distributional ranges of the biota have taken shape and modern biotic communities have assembled. Quaternary environmental changes have influenced the development of natural landscapes over time scales of centuries to hundreds of thousands of years; human cultural evolution has resulted in the transformation of much of the biosphere from natural to cultural landscapes over the past 5,000 years. The Quaternary extends to and includes the present and the immediate future. Knowledge of landscape changes on a Quaternary time scale is essential to landscape ecologists who wish to have a context for predicting future trends on local, regional, and global scales.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7107-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7107_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:10:18">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=779794D47F1DC5B92581B92F584A4A10?doi=10.1.1.256.9005&amp;rank=7</link><title>(DOI: will be inserted by hand later) First results from TOO observations of the Aql X-1 field with INTEGRAL ⋆</title><description>(DOI: will be inserted by hand later) First results from TOO observations of the Aql X-1 field with INTEGRAL ⋆

by S. Molkov, A. Lutovinov, S. Grebenev , 2003

"... -ray bursts from Aql X-1 near the end of the general outburst episode. Key words. stars:binaries:general – X ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

+075. We also detected two X-ray bursts from Aql X-1 near the end of the general outburst &lt;em&gt;episode&lt;/em&gt;. Key</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7107-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7107_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:11:36">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=779794D47F1DC5B92581B92F584A4A10?doi=10.1.1.245.2735&amp;rank=8</link><title>Soft X-ray to Far Infrared luminosities ratio in star-forming galaxies: Predictions from synthesis models</title><description>Soft X-ray to Far Infrared luminosities ratio in star-forming galaxies: Predictions from synthesis models

by J. M. Mas-hesse, H. Otí-floranes, M. Cerviño , 801

"... of the star formation episode. Aims. We analyze the relation between the soft X-ray and far infrared ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

and supernova explosions, both directly linked to the strength of the star formation &lt;em&gt;episode&lt;/em&gt;. Aims. We analyze</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7107-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7107_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:12:47">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=779794D47F1DC5B92581B92F584A4A10?doi=10.1.1.254.747&amp;rank=9</link><title>Submitted to the Astrophysical Journal Simulating the Early Evolution of the Hard X-Ray Properties of a Young Stellar Population</title><description>Submitted to the Astrophysical Journal Simulating the Early Evolution of the Hard X-Ray Properties of a Young Stellar Population

by Michael S. Sipior, Michael Eracleous, Steinn Sigurdsson , 2003

"... episodes of vigorous star formation. Our simulated X-ray binary population reaches a maximum 2–10 ke ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

&lt;em&gt;episodes&lt;/em&gt; of vigorous star formation. Our simulated X-ray binary population reaches a maximum 2–10 ke</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7107-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7107_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:14:02">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=779794D47F1DC5B92581B92F584A4A10?doi=10.1.1.388.3910&amp;rank=10</link><title>at the peak of Whistler Mountain (2182 m above sea level),</title><description>at the peak of Whistler Mountain (2182 m above sea level),

by A. Steffen, M. Cubison, D. R. Worsnop, A. Van Donkelaar, R. V. Martin

"... to those observed at other remote, high elevation sites in North America. Episodes of enhanced aerosol ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

to those observed at other remote, high elevation sites in North America. &lt;em&gt;Episodes&lt;/em&gt; of enhanced aerosol</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>