<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7109">best place to eat pho in new york</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:27:17" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7109-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7109_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:27:29">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=78356C97AADAB0CAB8A262C13305CD5F?doi=10.1.1.47.6608&amp;rank=1</link><title>An introduction to Kolmogorov Complexity and its Applications: Preface to the First Edition</title><description>An introduction to Kolmogorov Complexity and its Applications: Preface to the First Edition

by Ming Li, Paul Vitanyi , 1997

"... . Finally, in order to place the subject in the appropriate historical and conceptual context we trace ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1689 (114 self) \- Add to MetaCart

University, Cambridge, Massachusetts, USA; the Computer Science Department of &lt;em&gt;York&lt;/em&gt; University, Ontario</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7109-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7109_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:28:42">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=78356C97AADAB0CAB8A262C13305CD5F?doi=10.1.1.111.5804&amp;rank=2</link><title>Introduction to Algorithms, second edition</title><description>Introduction to Algorithms, second edition

by Thomas H. Cormen, Charles E. Leiserson, Ronald L. Rivest, Clifford Stein \- BOOK , 2001

"... , England McGraw-Hill Book Company Boston Burr Ridge, IL Dubuque, IA Madison, WI New York San Francisco St ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 707 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

will build upon this base. Chapter 1 is an overview of algorithms and their &lt;em&gt;place&lt;/em&gt; in modern computing systems</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7109-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7109_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:29:53">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=78356C97AADAB0CAB8A262C13305CD5F?doi=10.1.1.157.6588&amp;rank=3</link><title>Xen and the art of virtualization</title><description>Xen and the art of virtualization

by Paul Barham, Boris Dragovic, Keir Fraser, Steven H, Tim Harris, Alex Ho, Rolf Neugebauer, Ian Pratt, Andrew Warfield \- In SOSP (2003

"... and/or a fee. SOSP’03, October 19–22, 2003, Bolton Landing, New York, USA. Copyright 2003 ACM 1 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1251 (28 self) \- Add to MetaCart

or functionality for speed. Few offer resource isolation or performance guarantees; most provide only &lt;em&gt;best&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7109-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7109_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:31:01">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=78356C97AADAB0CAB8A262C13305CD5F?doi=10.1.1.107.4597&amp;rank=4</link><title>The process group approach to reliable distributed computing</title><description>The process group approach to reliable distributed computing

by Kenneth P. Birman \- Communications of the ACM , 1993

"... seamless way, communication disruptions are far more common on wide-area links (say, from New York to Tokyo ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 516 (16 self) \- Add to MetaCart

systems have &lt;em&gt;placed&lt;/em&gt; emphasis on communication performance, overlooking the need for tools to integrate</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7109-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7109_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:32:12">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=78356C97AADAB0CAB8A262C13305CD5F?doi=10.1.1.10.9655&amp;rank=5</link><title>Image Quilting for Texture Synthesis and Transfer</title><description>Image Quilting for Texture Synthesis and Transfer

by Alexei A. Efros , William T. Freeman , 2001

"... is Copyright 2001 Estate of Pablo Picasso / Artists Rights Society (ARS), New York. References ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 514 (16 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We present a simple image-based method of generating novel visual appearance in which a &lt;em&gt;new&lt;/em&gt; image</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7109-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7109_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:33:24">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=78356C97AADAB0CAB8A262C13305CD5F?doi=10.1.1.206.1458&amp;rank=6</link><title>Metaphors We Live By</title><description>Metaphors We Live By

by George Lakoff, Mark Johnson , 1980

"... .What are the new trends in English criticism? Old-fashioned notions have no place in today’s society. He keeps up ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1328 (6 self) \- Add to MetaCart

1\. Make a list of some of the metaphors discussed by Lakoff and Johnson. Try inserting &lt;em&gt;new&lt;/em&gt; words</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7109-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7109_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:34:31">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=78356C97AADAB0CAB8A262C13305CD5F?doi=10.1.1.132.8548&amp;rank=7</link><title>Recognition-by-components: A theory of human image understanding</title><description>Recognition-by-components: A theory of human image understanding

by Irving Biederman \- Psychological Review , 1987

"... Biederman State University of New York at Buffalo The perceptual recognition of objects is conceptualized ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 726 (11 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The perceptual recognition of objects is conceptualized to be a process in which the image of the input is segmented at regions of deep concavity into an arrangement of simple geometric components, such as blocks, cylinders, wedges, and cones. The fundamental assumption of the proposed theory, recognition-by-components (RBC), is that a modest set of generalized-cone components, called geons (N ^ 36), can be derived from contrasts of five readily detectable properties of edges in a two-dimensional image: curvature, collinearity, symmetry, parallelism, and cotermmation. The detection of these properties is generally invariant over viewing position and image quality and consequently allows robust object perception when the image is projected from a novel viewpoint or is degraded. RBC thus provides a principled account of the heretofore undecided relation between the classic principles of perceptual organization and pattern recognition: The constraints toward regularization (Pragnanz) characterize not the complete object but the object's components. Representational power derives from an allowance of free combinations of the geons. A Principle of Componential Recovery can account for the major phenomena of object recognition: If an arrangement of two or three geons can be recovered from the input, objects can be quickly recognized even when they are occluded, novel, rotated in depth, or extensively degraded. The results from experiments on the perception of briefly presented pictures by human observers provide empirical support for the theory. Any single object can project an infinity of image configura-tions to the retina. The orientation of the object to the viewer can vary continuously, each giving rise to a different two-dimen-sional projection. The object can be occluded by other objects or texture fields, as when viewed behind foliage. The object need not be presented as a full-colored textured image but in-stead can be a simplified line drawing. Moreover, the object can even be missing some of its parts or be a novel exemplar of its</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7109-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7109_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:37:46">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=78356C97AADAB0CAB8A262C13305CD5F?doi=10.1.1.87.3586&amp;rank=8</link><title>Handbook of Genetic Algorithms</title><description>Handbook of Genetic Algorithms

by L. D. Davis, Melanie Mitchell \- Van Nostrand Reinhold , 1991

"... ﻿Review of L. D. Davis, Handbook of Genetic Algorithms. New York: Van Nostrand Reinhold, 1991 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1164 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Mimicking biological evolution and harnessing its power for adaptation are problems that have intrigued computer scientists for at least four decades. Genetic algorithms (GAs), invented by John Holland in the 1960s, are the most widely used approaches to computational evolution. In his book Adaptation in Natural and Artificial Systems (Holland, 1992, also reviewed in this issue), Holland presented GAs in a general theoretical framework for adaptation in nature. Holland’s motivation was largely scientific — he was attempting to understand and link diverse types of natural phenomena—but he also proposed potential engineering applications of GAs. Since the publication of Holland’s book, the field of GAs has grown into a significant sub-area of artificial intelligence and machine learning. Nowadays one can find several international conferences each year as well as a number of journals devoted to GAs and other “evolutionary computation ” approaches. Research on GAs has spread from computer science to engineering and, more recently, to fields such as molecular biology, immunology, economics, and physics. One result of this growth in interest has been a division of the field of GAs into several subspecies. One major division is between research on GAs as engineering tools and research</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7109-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7109_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:38:40">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=78356C97AADAB0CAB8A262C13305CD5F?doi=10.1.1.80.8909&amp;rank=9</link><title>Inductive Learning Algorithms and Representations for Text Categorization</title><description>Inductive Learning Algorithms and Representations for Text Categorization

by Susan Dumais, John Platt, Mehran Sahami, David Heckerman , 1998

"... : • factoids (e.g., Salomon_Brothers_International, April_8) • multi-word dictionary entries (e.g., New_York ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 501 (9 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Text categorization – the assignment of natural language texts to one or more predefined categories based on their content – is an important component in many information organization and management tasks. We compare the effectiveness of five different automatic learning algorithms for text categorization in terms of learning speed, realtime classification speed, and classification accuracy. We also examine training set size, and alternative document representations. Very accurate text classifiers can be learned automatically from training examples. Linear Support Vector Machines (SVMs) are particularly promising because they are very accurate, quick to train, and quick to evaluate. 1.1 Keywords Text categorization, classification, support vector machines, machine learning, information management.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7109-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7109_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:39:49">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=78356C97AADAB0CAB8A262C13305CD5F?doi=10.1.1.15.9610&amp;rank=10</link><title>DataGuides: Enabling Query Formulation and Optimization in Semistructured Databases</title><description>DataGuides: Enabling Query Formulation and Optimization in Semistructured Databases

by Roy Goldman, Jennifer Widom , 1997

"... not to the best of our knowledge been addressed. 1.2 Paper Outline Section 2 first reviews the data model ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 503 (14 self) \- Add to MetaCart

In semistructured databases there is no schema fixed in advance. To provide the benefits of a schema in such environments, we introduce DataGuides: concise and accurate structural summaries of semistructured databases. DataGuides serve as dynamic schemas, generated from the database; they are useful for browsing database structure, formulating queries, storing information such as statistics and sample values, and enabling query optimization. This paper presents the theoretical foundations of DataGuides along with an algorithm for their creation and an overview of incremental maintenance. We provide performance results based on our implementation of DataGuides in the Lore DBMS for semistructured data. We also describe the use of DataGuides in Lore, both in the user interface to enable structure browsing and query formulation, and as a means of guiding the query processor and optimizing query execution.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>