<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7119">chocolate photo</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:02:02" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7119-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7119_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:02:04">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=47EC0C4DBB0D4FC0FCCD257DA789D78C?doi=10.1.1.195.4116&amp;rank=1</link><title>\- INTELLIGENCE ALERT- 70,000 PSILOCYBIN MUSHROOM/CHOCOLATE CANDIES</title><description>\- INTELLIGENCE ALERT- 70,000 PSILOCYBIN MUSHROOM/CHOCOLATE CANDIES

by Seized Near Amarillo

"... 154 kilograms), suspected psilocybin mushroom/chocolate concoctions. The exhibits were seized Photo 1 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

The U.S. Attorney General has determined that the publication of this periodical is necessary in the transaction of the public</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7119-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7119_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:03:13">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=47EC0C4DBB0D4FC0FCCD257DA789D78C?doi=10.1.1.417.5342&amp;rank=2</link><title>Photo by Yann Arthus‐Bertrand.) Title Authors Tropical forest</title><description>Photo by Yann Arthus‐Bertrand.) Title Authors Tropical forest

by Øivind Due Trier, Øivind Due Trier , 2008

"... .” (Newman, 2002, p. vii; Photo by Yann Arthus‐Bertrand.)Title Authors Tropical forest Øivind Due Trier ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

the areas of information and communication technology and applied statistical modeling. The clients are a broad range of industrial, commercial and public service organizations in the national as well as the international market. Our scientific and technical capabilities are further developed in co‐operation with The Research Council of Norway and key customers. The results of our projects may take the form of reports, software, prototypes, and short courses. A proof of the confidence and appreciation our clients have for us is given by the fact that most of our new contracts are signed with previous customers. Front cover picture “Aerial view of a mangrove forest on the island of New Caledonia. The heart formation is not human made, but occurred naturally, as mangroves require brackish or saltwater contact at all times and the sandy, heart‐shaped area rises above the water table. ” (Newman, 2002, p. vii;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7119-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7119_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:04:22">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=47EC0C4DBB0D4FC0FCCD257DA789D78C?doi=10.1.1.120.5736&amp;rank=3</link><title>Automated Tag Clustering: Improving search and exploration in the tag space</title><description>Automated Tag Clustering: Improving search and exploration in the tag space

by Grigory Begelman \- In Proc. of the Collaborative Web Tagging Workshop at WWW’06 , 2006

"... are overwhelmingly more frequent than anything else. There are some 4,500 links tagged with chocolate and some 61 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 100 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

In this paper we discuss the use of clustering techniques to enhance the user experience and thus the success of collaborative tagging services. We show that clustering techniques can improve the user experience of current tagging services.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7119-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7119_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:05:30">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=47EC0C4DBB0D4FC0FCCD257DA789D78C?doi=10.1.1.198.6346&amp;rank=4</link><title>Survey of Supply and Demand Factors 593</title><description>Survey of Supply and Demand Factors 593

by David R Walwyn

"... ﻿HSRC photo library chaptertwenty-five BIOTECHNOLOGISTS David R Walwyn In this chapter Introduction ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

HSRC &lt;em&gt;photo&lt;/em&gt; library chaptertwenty-five</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7119-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7119_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:06:41">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=47EC0C4DBB0D4FC0FCCD257DA789D78C?doi=10.1.1.108.2974&amp;rank=5</link><title>Olfoto: Designing a smell-based interaction</title><description>Olfoto: Designing a smell-based interaction

by Stephen A. Brewster, David K. Mcgookin, Christopher A. Miller \- Proceedings of ACM CHI , 2006

"... into the use of smell for searching digital photo collections. Many people now have large photo libraries ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 11 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We present a study into the use of smell for searching digital &lt;em&gt;photo&lt;/em&gt; collections. Many people now</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7119-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7119_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:07:49">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=47EC0C4DBB0D4FC0FCCD257DA789D78C?doi=10.1.1.421.6152&amp;rank=6</link><title>The Virtual Factory: Exploring 3D worlds as industrial collaboration and control environments</title><description>The Virtual Factory: Exploring 3D worlds as industrial collaboration and control environments

by Maribeth Back, Timothy Childs, Anthony Dunnigan, Jonathan Foote, Sagar Gattepally, Bee Liew, Jun Shingu, Jim Vaughan

"... applications for factories. In collaboration with TCHO, a chocolate maker start-up in San Francisco, we have ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

with TCHO, a &lt;em&gt;chocolate&lt;/em&gt; maker start-up in San Francisco, we have built virtual mirror-world representations</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7119-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7119_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:08:59">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=47EC0C4DBB0D4FC0FCCD257DA789D78C?doi=10.1.1.369.4362&amp;rank=7</link><title>Department of Natural Resources for this plant’s</title><description>Department of Natural Resources for this plant’s

by Plant Symbol Fraf

"... ﻿CHOCOLATE LILY Fritillaria affinis (Schultes) Sealy Plant Symbol = FRAF2 Contributed By: USDA NRCS ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

wooden spade, or the fingers. &lt;em&gt;Chocolate&lt;/em&gt; lily bulbs were cooked immediately, or could be partially dried</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7119-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7119_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:10:07">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=47EC0C4DBB0D4FC0FCCD257DA789D78C?doi=10.1.1.43.7216&amp;rank=8</link><title>Perceptually Modulated Level of Detail for Virtual Environments</title><description>Perceptually Modulated Level of Detail for Virtual Environments

by Martin Reddy , 1997

"... , suggestions, friendly ears, timely distractions, and full-fat chocolate products when I needed them most ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 35 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This thesis presents a generic and principled solution for optimising the visual complexity of any arbitrary computer-generated virtual environment (VE). This is performed with the ultimate goal of reducing the inherent latencies of current virtual reality (VR) technology. Effectively, we wish to remove extraneous detail from an environment which the user cannot perceive, and thus modulate the graphical complexity of a VE with little or no perceptual artifacts. The work proceeds by investigating contemporary models and theories of visual perception and then applying these to the field of real-time computer graphics. Subsequently, a technique is devised to assess the perceptual content of a computer-generated image in terms of spatial frequency (c/deg), and a model of contrast sensitivity is formulated to describe a user's ability to perceive detail under various conditions in terms of this metric. This allows us to base the level of detail (LOD) of each object in a VE on a measure of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7119-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7119_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:11:14">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=47EC0C4DBB0D4FC0FCCD257DA789D78C?doi=10.1.1.332.1079&amp;rank=9</link><title>Variable number of tandem repeats in clinical strains of Haemophilus influenzae</title><description>Variable number of tandem repeats in clinical strains of Haemophilus influenzae

by Alex Van Belkum, Stewart Scherer, Willem Van Leeuwen, Diana Willemse, Loek Van Alphen, Henri Verbrugh \- Infect. Immun. 65:5017–5027. Downloaded from http://aem.asm.org/ on February 28, 2013 by PENN STATE UNIV , 1997

"... derived from a single clinical specimen or strains passaged for several weeks on chocolate agar plates ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 16 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

derived from a single clinical specimen or strains passaged for several weeks on &lt;em&gt;chocolate&lt;/em&gt; agar plates</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7119-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7119_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:12:23">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=47EC0C4DBB0D4FC0FCCD257DA789D78C?doi=10.1.1.335.8270&amp;rank=10</link><title>The Role of Anticipated Shame and Guilt on Consumer Self-Control</title><description>The Role of Anticipated Shame and Guilt on Consumer Self-Control

by Haeeun Chun, Vanessa M. Patrick, Deborah J. Macinnis, Haeeun Chun, Vanessa M. Patrick, Deborah J. Macinnis

"... relatively nonpowerful inducement-- a photo of a chocolate cake (as opposed to an actual real-life temptation ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

hedonic product. The results demonstrate that when offered a hedonic snack &lt;em&gt;(chocolate&lt;/em&gt; cake) consumers who</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>