<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7123">raleigh bike</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:33:22" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7123-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7123_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:33:24">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8B6B480C876F6B648E04F69EA39CD2D2?doi=10.1.1.368.8106&amp;rank=1</link><title>Research &amp; Report Prepared by the Raleigh Urban</title><description>Research &amp; Report Prepared by the Raleigh Urban

by Rachel Mukai Stark , 2011

"... of Public Realm Improvements in Raleigh, North Carolina January 1, 2011 Research &amp; Report Prepared ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

are lacking in daily exercise. The City of &lt;em&gt;Raleigh&lt;/em&gt; also understands the value of urban sidewalks is about more</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7123-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7123_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:33:46">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8B6B480C876F6B648E04F69EA39CD2D2?doi=10.1.1.103.9746&amp;rank=2</link><title>Flow Characteristics on Shared Hiking/Biking/Jogging Trails</title><description>Flow Characteristics on Shared Hiking/Biking/Jogging Trails

by Mark R. Virkler, Rajesh Balasubramanian

"... ﻿TRANSPORTATION RESEARCH RECORD 1636 Paper No. 98-0117 43 Flow Characteristics on Shared Hiking/Biking ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

hikers and joggers passing hikers. However, estimates for &lt;em&gt;bike&lt;/em&gt; passing &lt;em&gt;bike&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;bike&lt;/em&gt; passing jogger, &lt;em&gt;bike&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7123-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7123_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:33:57">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8B6B480C876F6B648E04F69EA39CD2D2?doi=10.1.1.173.7846&amp;rank=3</link><title>The Bikeway Network The City of Toronto is building a 1,000+ km Bikeway Network, and</title><description>The Bikeway Network The City of Toronto is building a 1,000+ km Bikeway Network, and

by unknown authors

"... ﻿The Bikeway Network The City of Toronto is building a 1,000+ km Bikeway Network, and new bike ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

new &lt;em&gt;bike&lt;/em&gt; lanes, sharrows, off-road paths and signed routes are added each year. This map shows all</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7123-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7123_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:34:28">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8B6B480C876F6B648E04F69EA39CD2D2?doi=10.1.1.417.6313&amp;rank=4</link><title>ISignal Cleamnce Timing for Bicyclists</title><description>ISignal Cleamnce Timing for Bicyclists

by Alan Wachtel, John Foresterand, David Pelz

"... car/bike collisions, the largest facility-associated cause.’ These conflicts typically occur when a ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

percent of urban car/&lt;em&gt;bike&lt;/em&gt; collisions, the largest facility-associated cause.’ These conflicts typically</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7123-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7123_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:34:40">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8B6B480C876F6B648E04F69EA39CD2D2?doi=10.1.1.352.3449&amp;rank=5</link><title>Bicycle commuting and facilities in major U.S. cities: If you build them, commuters will use them. Transportation Research Record 1828</title><description>Bicycle commuting and facilities in major U.S. cities: If you build them, commuters will use them. Transportation Research Record 1828

by Jennifer Dill, Theresa Carr , 2003

"... by bicycle if there were safe bike lanes. Similar surveys in Davis, CA and Seattle, WA found that 12 and 41 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 22 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Some surveys indicate that providing bicycle lanes and paths may encourage more people to commute by bicycle. The presence of a striped lane or separated path can increase a cyclist’s perception of safety. With growing concerns over traffic congestion and vehicle pollution, public policy makers are increasingly promoting bicycling as an alternative for commuting and other utilitarian trip purposes. States and local spending on bicycle facilities has increased significantly over the past decade. Previous studies have linked higher levels of bicycle commuting to various demographic and geographic variables. At least one analysis showed that cities with higher levels of bicycle infrastructure (lanes and paths) also saw higher levels of bicycle commuting. This research affirms that finding by analyzing data from 35 large cities across the U.S. This cross-sectional analysis improves on previous research by including a larger sample of cities, not including predominantly ‘college towns, ’ and using consistent data from the Census 2000 Supplemental Survey. While the analysis has limitations, it does support the assertion that new bicycle lanes in large cities will be used by commuters.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7123-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7123_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:34:52">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8B6B480C876F6B648E04F69EA39CD2D2?doi=10.1.1.250.9479&amp;rank=6</link><title>CHAPTER FOUR PEDESTRIAN FACILITY RECOMMENDATIONS</title><description>CHAPTER FOUR PEDESTRIAN FACILITY RECOMMENDATIONS

by unknown authors

"... City of Raleigh Pedestrian Plan | Chapter 4 sample comments from CommunityWalk around each example ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

the City’s technical team. Appendix C provides 79 City of &lt;em&gt;Raleigh&lt;/em&gt; Pedestrian Plan | Chapter 4 sample</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7123-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7123_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:35:13">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8B6B480C876F6B648E04F69EA39CD2D2?doi=10.1.1.332.7569&amp;rank=7</link><title>Poolview: Stream privacy for grassroots participatory sensing</title><description>Poolview: Stream privacy for grassroots participatory sensing

by Raghu K. Ganti, Nam Pham, Yu-en Tsai, Tarek F. Abdelzaher \- In Proc. of SenSys ’08 , 2008

"... permission and/or a fee. SenSys’08, November 5–7, 2008, Raleigh, North Carolina, USA. Copyright 2008 ACM 978 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 22 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper develops mathematical foundations and architectural components for providing privacy guarantees on stream data in grassroots participatory sensing applications, where groups of participants use privately-owned sensors to collectively measure aggregate phenomena of mutual interest. Grassroots applications refer to those initiated by members of the community themselves as opposed to by some governing or official entities. The potential lack of a hierarchical trust structure in such applications makes it harder to enforce privacy. To address this problem, we develop a privacy-preserving architecture, called PoolView, that relies on data perturbation on the client-side to ensure individuals’ privacy and uses community-wide reconstruction techniques to compute the aggregate information of interest. PoolView allows arbitrary parties to start new services, called pools, to compute new types of aggregate information for their clients. Both the client-side and server-side components of PoolView are implemented and available for download, including the data perturbation and reconstruction components. Two simple sensing services are developed for illustration; one computes traffic statistics from subscriber GPS data and the other computes weight statistics for a particular diet. Evaluation, using actual data traces collected by the authors, demonstrates the privacy-preserving aggregation functionality in PoolView.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7123-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7123_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:35:41">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8B6B480C876F6B648E04F69EA39CD2D2?doi=10.1.1.95.2827&amp;rank=8</link><title>Statistical characterization of MPEG VBR video at the SLICE layer</title><description>Statistical characterization of MPEG VBR video at the SLICE layer

by Michael R. Izquierdo, Douglas R. Reeves \- Proc. SPIE Multimedia computing and Networking , 1995

"... and Computer Engineering North Carolina State University Raleigh, North Carolina 27695 ABSTRACT In this paper ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 9 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

In this paper, we statistically characterized four VBR encoded video sequences, containing I/B/P frames, at the Slice layer with the goal of developing an accurate source model to better understand the bit-rate behavior of these sources. We presented the cells/slice distributions and showed that it is “heavy tailed” and fits the Pareto distribution better than Gamma. We showed that an 8-state Markov Chain fits the cells/slice distribution well, reaching steady state after 37 to 80 transitions (2 to 5 frames). We also showed that the autocorrelation function is quasi-periodic which is mostly due to the frame sequence pattern rather than spatial content. We discussed the impact of I/B/P sequences on multiplexing and dynamic bandwidth allocation and proposed a multiplexing method called Time Shifted Multiplexing (TSM); whereby, the multiplexer attempts to overlap I and P frames of one video stream with B frames of an other. This tends to reduce both Peak-to-Mean-Ratio and Coefficient-of-Variation of the multiplexed output stream. We showed that coefficient-of-variation reduced in half and bandwidth requirements reduced by 41 % using TSM. 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7123-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7123_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:35:54">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8B6B480C876F6B648E04F69EA39CD2D2?doi=10.1.1.194.954&amp;rank=9</link><title>Kubilins Transportation Group</title><description>Kubilins Transportation Group

by Lewis Stroud, Deutsch Contents

"... ﻿RALEIGH’S NEW DEVELOPMENT CODE DIAGNOSTIC &amp; APPROACH REPORT PUBLIC REVIEW DRAFT (2/1/10) MIXED ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7123-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7123_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:36:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8B6B480C876F6B648E04F69EA39CD2D2?doi=10.1.1.232.8058&amp;rank=10</link><title>Buses from Terrorism</title><description>Buses from Terrorism

by School Sites Sidewalks, From From, Perspective Perspective, Trb Trb Annual Annual Meeting , 2005

"... or bike would reduce vehicle emissions significantly. 11 The Dynamics of School Location and School ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

which serves the National Academy</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>