<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7132">massachusetts general hospital jobs</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:59:05" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7132-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7132_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:59:09">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B1C6EDD49F5F1AAABE4EFBEC5048FCC9?doi=10.1.1.115.7807&amp;rank=1</link><title>Molecular classification of cancer: class discovery and class prediction by gene expression monitoring</title><description>Molecular classification of cancer: class discovery and class prediction by gene expression monitoring

by T. R. Golub, D. K. Slonim, P. Tamayo, C. Huard, M. Gaasenbeek, J. P. Mesirov, H. Coller, M. L. Loh, J. R. Downing, M. A. Caligiuri, C. D. Bloomfield \- Science , 1999

"... ,5 * Although cancer classification has improved over the past 30 years, there has been no general approach ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1218 (14 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Although cancer classification has improved over the past 30 years, there has been no &lt;em&gt;general&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7132-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7132_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:59:28">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B1C6EDD49F5F1AAABE4EFBEC5048FCC9?doi=10.1.1.201.9742&amp;rank=2</link><title>Capitalism, Socialism and Democracy</title><description>Capitalism, Socialism and Democracy

by Joseph A. Schumpeter, In The S, Joseph A. Schumpeter , 1942

"... . General Motors downsized, but American autoworkers found more than 29,000 new jobs as Honda, Toyota ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 676 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

or method of economic change and not only never is but never can be stationary.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7132-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7132_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:59:47">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B1C6EDD49F5F1AAABE4EFBEC5048FCC9?doi=10.1.1.317.9673&amp;rank=3</link><title>The theory of planned behavior</title><description>The theory of planned behavior

by Icek Ajzen \- Organizational Behavior and Human Decision Processes , 1991

"... Behavior ICEK AJZEN University of Massachusetts at Amherst Research dealing with various aspects of ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 540 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Research dealing with various aspects of * the theory of planned behavior (Ajzen, 1985, 1987) is reviewed, and some unresolved issues are discussed. In broad terms, the theory is found to be well supported by empirical evidence. Intentions to perform behaviors of different kinds can be predicted with high accuracy from attitudes toward the behavior, subjective norms, and perceived behavioral control; and these intentions, together with perceptions of behavioral control, account for considerable variance in actual behavior. Attitudes, subjective norms, and perceived behavioral control are shown to be related to appropriate sets of salient behavioral, normative, and control beliefs about the behavior, but the exact nature of these relations is still uncertain. Expectancy — value formulations are found to be only partly successful in dealing with these relations. Optimal rescaling of expectancy and value measures is offered as a means of dealing with measurement limitations. Finally, inclusion of past behavior in the prediction equation is shown to provide a means of testing the theory*s sufficiency, another issue that remains unresolved. The limited available evidence concerning this question shows that the theory is predicting behavior quite well in comparison to the ceiling imposed by behavioral reliability. © 1991 Academic Press. Inc.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7132-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7132_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:00:01">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B1C6EDD49F5F1AAABE4EFBEC5048FCC9?doi=10.1.1.212.5949&amp;rank=4</link><title>An agent that assists web browsing</title><description>An agent that assists web browsing

by Henry Lieberman \- Proceedings of the Fourteenth International Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence (IJCAI-95 , 1995

"... ﻿Letizia: An Agent That Assists Web Browsing Henry Lieberman Media Laboratory Massachusetts ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 567 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

"Letizia Alvarez de Toledo has observed that this vast library is useless: rigorously speaking, a single volume ■ would be sufficient, a volume of ordinary format, printed in nine or ten point type, containing an infinite</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7132-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7132_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:00:14">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B1C6EDD49F5F1AAABE4EFBEC5048FCC9?doi=10.1.1.17.4154&amp;rank=5</link><title>An Efficient Boosting Algorithm for Combining Preferences</title><description>An Efficient Boosting Algorithm for Combining Preferences

by Raj Dharmarajan Iyer , Jr. , 1999

"... for the degree of Master of Science at the MASSACHUSETTS INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY September 1999 c Massachusetts ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 515 (18 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The problem of combining preferences arises in several applications, such as combining the results of different search engines. This work describes an efficient algorithm for combining multiple preferences. We first give a formal framework for the problem. We then describe and analyze a new boosting algorithm for combining preferences called RankBoost. We also describe an efficient implementation of the algorithm for certain natural cases. We discuss two experiments we carried out to assess the performance of RankBoost. In the first experiment, we used the algorithm to combine different WWW search strategies, each of which is a query expansion for a given domain. For this task, we compare the performance of RankBoost to the individual search strategies. The second experiment is a collaborative-filtering task for making movie recommendations. Here, we present results comparing RankBoost to nearest-neighbor and regression algorithms.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7132-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7132_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:00:29">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B1C6EDD49F5F1AAABE4EFBEC5048FCC9?doi=10.1.1.35.4167&amp;rank=6</link><title>End-To-End Arguments In System Design</title><description>End-To-End Arguments In System Design

by Jerome H. Saltzer, David P. Reed, David D. Clark , 1984

"... nature and to see how general it really is. The argument appeals to application requirements ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 831 (9 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper presents a design principle that helps guide placement of functions among the modules of a distributed computer system. The principle, called the end-to-end argument, suggests that functions placed at low levels of a system may be redundant or of little value when compared with the cost of providing them at that low level. Examples discussed in the paper include bit error recovery, security using encryption, duplicate message suppression, recovery from system crashes, and delivery acknowledgement. Low level mechanisms to support these functions are justified only as performance enhancements. Introduction</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7132-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7132_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:00:47">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B1C6EDD49F5F1AAABE4EFBEC5048FCC9?doi=10.1.1.99.8377&amp;rank=7</link><title>The interdisciplinary study of coordination</title><description>The interdisciplinary study of coordination

by Thomas W. Malone, Kevin Crowston \- ACM Computing Surveys , 1994

"... , Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, Massachusetts 02139 KEVIN CROWSTON University of Michigan ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 535 (14 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This survey characterizes an emerging research area, sometimes called coordination theory, that focuses on the interdisciplinary study of coordination. Research in this area uses and extends ideas about coordination from disciplines such as computer science, organization theory, operations research, economics, linguistics, and psychology. A key insight of the framework presented here is that coordination can be seen as the process of managing dependencies among activities. Further progress, therefore, should be possible by characterizing different kinds of dependencies and identifying the coordination processes that can be used to manage them. A variety of processes are analyzed from this perspective, and commonalities across disciplines are identified. Processes analyzed include those for managing shared resources, producer/consumer relationships, simultaneity constraints, and tank/subtask dependencies. Section 3 summarizes ways of applying a coordination perspective in three different domains: (1) understanding the effects of information technology on human organizations and markets, (2) designing cooperative work tools, and (3) designing distributed and parallel computer systems. In the final section, elements of a research</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7132-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7132_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:01:09">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B1C6EDD49F5F1AAABE4EFBEC5048FCC9?doi=10.1.1.111.5804&amp;rank=8</link><title>Introduction to Algorithms, second edition</title><description>Introduction to Algorithms, second edition

by Thomas H. Cormen, Charles E. Leiserson, Ronald L. Rivest, Clifford Stein \- BOOK , 2001

"... Clifford Stein Introduction to Algorithms Second Edition The MIT Press Cambridge, Massachusetts London ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 707 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This part will get you started in thinking about designing and analyzing algorithms. It is intended to be a gentle introduction to how we specify algorithms, some of the design strategies we will use throughout this book, and many of the fundamental ideas used in algorithm analysis. Later parts of this book will build upon this base. Chapter 1 is an overview of algorithms and their place in modern computing systems. This chapter defines what an algorithm is and lists some examples. It also makes a case that algorithms are a technology, just as are fast hardware, graphical user interfaces, object-oriented systems, and networks. In Chapter 2, we see our first algorithms, which solve the problem of sorting a sequence of n numbers. They are written in a pseudocode which, although not directly translatable to any conventional programming language, conveys the structure of the algorithm clearly enough that a competent programmer can implement it in the language of his choice. The sorting algorithms we examine are insertion sort, which uses an incremental approach, and merge sort, which uses a recursive technique known as “divide and conquer.” Although the time each requires increases with the value of n, the rate of increase differs between the two algorithms. We determine these running times in Chapter 2, and we develop a useful notation to express them. Chapter 3 precisely defines this notation, which we call asymptotic notation. It starts by defining several asymptotic notations, which we use for bounding algorithm running times from above and/or below. The rest of Chapter 3 is primarily a presentation of mathematical notation. Its purpose is more to ensure that your use of notation matches that in this book than to teach you new mathematical concepts.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7132-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7132_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:01:20">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B1C6EDD49F5F1AAABE4EFBEC5048FCC9?doi=10.1.1.14.5547&amp;rank=9</link><title>Word Association Norms, Mutual Information, and Lexicography</title><description>Word Association Norms, Mutual Information, and Lexicography

by Kenneth Ward Church, Patrick Hanks , 1990

"... is used in a very particular sense in the psycholinguistic literature. (Generally speaking, subjects ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 833 (10 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper will propose an objective measure based on the information theoretic notion of mutual information, for estimating word association norms from computer readable corpora. (The standard method of obtaining word association norms, testing a few thousand subjects on a few hundred words, is both costly and unreliable.) The proposed measure, the association ratio, estimates word association norms directly from computer readable corpora, making it possible to estimate norms for tens of thousands of words</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7132-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7132_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:01:43">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B1C6EDD49F5F1AAABE4EFBEC5048FCC9?doi=10.1.1.139.4370&amp;rank=10</link><title>Determinants of corporate borrowing</title><description>Determinants of corporate borrowing

by Stewart C. Myers, Stewart C. Myers \- Journal of Financial Economics , 1977

"... OF CORPORATE BORROWING Stewart C. Myers WP 875-76 September 1976 Sloan School of Management Massachusetts ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 733 (6 self) \- Add to MetaCart

There is an important gap in modern finance theory on the issue of corporate debt policy. The theory should be able to explain why the tax advantages of debt financing do not lead firms to borrow as much as possible, and it should explain the phrase "as much as possible."</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>