<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7133">museum of natural history</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:02:05" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7133-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7133_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:02:07">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=239E773263AE9B9C847155D1FD2860BD?doi=10.1.1.352.3495&amp;rank=1</link><title>American Museum of Natural History</title><description>American Museum of Natural History

by Ward Wheeler, Claudia P. Arango, Taran Grant, Daniel Janies, Andrés Varón, Julián Faivovich, Département Systématique Et Evolution, William Leo Smith, Gonzalo Giribet

"... of Invertebrate Zoology American Museum of Natural History Claudia P. Arango Division of Invertebrate Zoology ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Dynamic homology and phylogenetic systematics: a unified approach using POY / Ward Wheeler... [et al.]. p. cm. "Published in cooperation with NASA Fundamental Space Biology."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7133-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7133_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:02:19">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=239E773263AE9B9C847155D1FD2860BD?doi=10.1.1.231.9262&amp;rank=2</link><title>FIELD MUSEUM OF NATURAL HISTORY</title><description>FIELD MUSEUM OF NATURAL HISTORY

by Flora Costaricensis, William Burger, Family Acanthaceae, L. H. Durkee, William Burger, In The Flora Costaricensis Series, William Burger, Flora Costaricensis, William Burger, L. H. Durkee, William Burger , 1986

"... Burger December 31. 1986 Publication 1372 PUBLISHED BY FIELD MUSEUM OF NATURAL HISTORY114FLORA ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7133-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7133_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:02:33">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=239E773263AE9B9C847155D1FD2860BD?doi=10.1.1.403.5220&amp;rank=3</link><title>preserved at the Museum of Natural History of</title><description>preserved at the Museum of Natural History of

by Petronio C, Deposits Ternifine (algeria, Omo Valley, Ain Hanech (algeria

"... is involved in the morphometric study of some cranial remains, preserved at the Museum of Natural History ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract: Although there are several recent works about systematics of genus Hippopotamus during Pleistocene, great confusion still remains. In Author’s opinion Hippopotamus incognitus (referred to H. amphibius) and Hippopotamus tiberinus (referred to H. antiquus) are not valid species.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7133-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7133_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:02:53">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=239E773263AE9B9C847155D1FD2860BD?doi=10.1.1.244.9461&amp;rank=4</link><title>American Museum of Natural History</title><description>American Museum of Natural History

by Orsola De Marco, S. Wortel, Howard E. Bond, Dianne Harmer , 709

"... Museum of Natural History orsola@(email omitted); 2 Space Telescope Science Institute bond@(email omitted); 3 National ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Summary. A radial velocity (RV) survey to detect central stars in binary systems was carried out between 2002 and 2004. [5] reported that 10 out of 11 monitored stars exhibited strong RV variability, but periods were not detected. Since other mechanisms, such as wind variability, can cause apparent RV variations, we monitored 4 of the 10 RV-variable stars at echelle resolutions to determine the origin of the variability. Although RV changes are confirmed for all four stars, none of them can be ascribed to binarity at this time. However, only for IC 4593 is wind variability able to explain most (though not all) spectral variability. For BD+33 2642, no wind and no pulsations appear to be the origin of the RV changes. Finally, M 1-77 and M 2-54, both known to be irregular photometric variables, exhibit dramatic RV and line shape variability of the hydrogen and He I absorption lines, as well as large RV variability of weaker lines, which do not change in shape. There is no satisfactory explanation of this variability, though a combination of wind variability and pulsations is still the best guess at what makes these stars so variable. We suggest that luminous central stars are ill suited to detect spectroscopic binaries, because winds (and possibly pulsations) are pervasive and would mask even strong periodicities. It it likely that a sample of intrinsically faint central stars would more readily yield binary information.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7133-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7133_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:03:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=239E773263AE9B9C847155D1FD2860BD?doi=10.1.1.293.7753&amp;rank=5</link><title>American Museum of Natural History</title><description>American Museum of Natural History

by Joseph E. Tonna, Amy M. Balanoff, Matthew R. Lewin, Namjilmaa Sa, Mph Ω, Max Wintermark , 2010

"... Museum of Natural History ‡ Institute for Exploration and Travel Health, California Academy of Sciences ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Reprints available through open access at</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7133-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7133_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:03:19">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=239E773263AE9B9C847155D1FD2860BD?doi=10.1.1.366.5881&amp;rank=6</link><title>Museum of Natural History, Smithsonian Institution</title><description>Museum of Natural History, Smithsonian Institution

by Robert P. Reynolds, Steve W. Gotte, Carl H. Ernst, Series Publications, Of The, Smithsonian Institution, Smithsonian Contributions To Zoology, Robert P. Reynolds, Steve W. Gotte, Carl H. Ernst

"... of Type Specimens of Recent Crocodilia and Testudines in the National Museum of Natural History ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Emphasis upon publication as a means of “diffusing knowledge ” was expressed by the first Secretary of the Smithsonian. In his formal plan for the Institution, Joseph Henry outlined a program that included the following statement: “It is proposed to publish a series of reports, giving an account of the new discoveries in science, and of the changes made from year to year in all branches of knowledge. ” This theme of basic research has been adhered to through the years by thousands of titles issued in series publications under the Smithsonian imprint, commencing with Smithsonian Contributions to Knowledge in 1848 and continuing with the following active series:</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7133-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7133_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:03:40">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=239E773263AE9B9C847155D1FD2860BD?doi=10.1.1.401.4210&amp;rank=7</link><title>American Museum of Natural History\- Exhibitions</title><description>American Museum of Natural History\- Exhibitions

by Welcome Apirations, High School Library, Principal Ms, Shermila Bharat, Celebrate Black History, Art Cyclopedia, Frida Kahlo , 2012

"... ) ProCon.org Art and Museums American Museum of Natural History \- Exhibitions Art Cyclopedia Frida Kahlo ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Who am I? Who do I want to be? How do I get there? You can search the library catalog from school or from home. You can also check out the links, below, to find out about some terrific authors, books, resources, get help with your homework, and more! To search our library holdings, Click on the "Catalog " tab above Helpful Educational Links are below</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7133-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7133_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:03:56">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=239E773263AE9B9C847155D1FD2860BD?doi=10.1.1.169.6617&amp;rank=8</link><title>National Museum of Natural History............................................51</title><description>National Museum of Natural History............................................51

by unknown authors

"... ....................................................51 Systematic Botanist (Research Botanist) Smithsonian Institution, National Museum of Natural ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7133-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7133_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:04:16">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=239E773263AE9B9C847155D1FD2860BD?doi=10.1.1.46.1169&amp;rank=9</link><title>Visualizations of Earth Process for the American Museum of Natural History</title><description>Visualizations of Earth Process for the American Museum of Natural History

by Is To Ry

"... Visualizations of Earth Process for the American Museum of Natural History Abstract The American ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

The American &lt;em&gt;Museum&lt;/em&gt; of &lt;em&gt;Natural&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;History&lt;/em&gt; in New York City has built a new exhibit space---The Hall</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7133-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7133_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:04:36">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=239E773263AE9B9C847155D1FD2860BD?doi=10.1.1.192.9086&amp;rank=10</link><title>Type specimens of amphibians in the National Museum of Natural History,</title><description>Type specimens of amphibians in the National Museum of Natural History,

by M. Eulàlia, Gassó Miracle, Jan Willem Arntzen

"... Museum of Natural History, Leiden, The Netherlands M. EULÀLIA GASSÓ MIRACLE, LARS W. VAN DEN HOEK OSTENDE ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

www.mapress.com/zootaxa/</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>