<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7135">Ahmed Dogan assassination</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:07:59" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7135-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7135_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:08:00">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=FD55CF38510C776117F849C20E659BDF?doi=10.1.1.124.5822&amp;rank=1</link><title>Too much of a good thing? The proactive response dilemma</title><description>Too much of a good thing? The proactive response dilemma

by Peter Rosendorff, Todd S \- Journal of Conflict Resolution , 2004

"... against the Taliban and al-Qaida or Israel’s assassination of Hamas terrorists (Sheikh Ahmed Yassin ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 27 (8 self) \- Add to MetaCart

for International Studies, University of Southern California. The authors have profited from comments provided by an anonymous referee, Barry O’Neill, Geoffrey Heal, and Bruce Russett on an earlier draft. TOO MUCH OF A GOOD THING? THE PROACTIVE RESPONSE DILEMMA This paper presents a two-player proactive response game: the targeted government first chooses its measures to weaken the terrorists, and the terrorists then choose the type of event – normal or spectacular – whose outcome is dependent on proactive responses and nature. Unlike previous analyses, proactive policy has a downside by increasing grievances and, consequently, terrorist recruitment. If the government responds too harshly, its actions can empower the terrorists by providing a larger constituency. Aggressive antiterrorist actions, encouraged by a high perceived loss from terrorism and low marginal proactive costs, may result in spectacular events with dire consequences. If spectaculars are transferred abroad to soft targets, then proactive operations may be excessive from a global viewpoint as external costs are ignored. The analysis explains why some target nations engage in a modest level of offense, while a prime target chooses a large level.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7135-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7135_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:08:13">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=FD55CF38510C776117F849C20E659BDF?doi=10.1.1.259.5357&amp;rank=2</link><title>Low-Power Processor Architecture Exploration for Online Biomedical Signal Analysis</title><description>Low-Power Processor Architecture Exploration for Online Biomedical Signal Analysis

by Ahmed Yasir Dogan, Jeremy Constantin, David Atienza, Andreas Burg, Luca Benini

"... Lab. (ESL) - EPFL; Lausanne - 1015, Switzerland {ahmed.dogan,david.atienza}@(email omitted); 2 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

target workloads of online biomedical signal analysis, while exploiting near threshold com-2 A. Y. &lt;em&gt;Dogan&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7135-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7135_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:08:26">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=FD55CF38510C776117F849C20E659BDF?doi=10.1.1.18.1036&amp;rank=3</link><title>Some New Evidence on Determinants of Foreign Direct Investment in Developing Countries</title><description>Some New Evidence on Determinants of Foreign Direct Investment in Developing Countries

by H. Singh, Harinder Singh, Kwang W. Jun , 1995

"... and Ahmed (1979) found that "the number of regular (constitutional) changes in government leadership between ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 19 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper -- a product of the International Finance Division, International Economics Department -- is part of a larger effort in the department to analyze private capital flows and their policy implications for developing countries. Copies of the paper are available free from the World Bank, 1818 H Street NW, Washington, DC 20433. Please contact Sheilah KingWatson, room N3-040, telephone 202-473-1047, fax 202-522-3277, Internet address skingwatson@worldbank.org. November 1995. (41 pages) The Policy Research Working Paper Series disseminates the findings of work in progress to encourage the exchange of ideas about tevelopment issues. An objective of the series is to get the findings out quickly, even if the presentations are less than fully polished. The papers carry the names of the authors and should be used and cited accordingly. The findings, interpretations, and conclusions are the authors' own and should not be attributed to the IVorld Bank, its Executive Board of Directors, or any of its member countries</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7135-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7135_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:08:49">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=FD55CF38510C776117F849C20E659BDF?doi=10.1.1.222.2350&amp;rank=4</link><title>Chapter 11 – PRISON AND COMMUNITY-BASED DISENGAGEMENT AND DE-RADICALIZATION PROGRAMS FOR EXTREMIST INVOLVED IN MILITANT JIHADI TERRORISM IDEOLOGIES AND ACTIVITIES</title><description>Chapter 11 – PRISON AND COMMUNITY-BASED DISENGAGEMENT AND DE-RADICALIZATION PROGRAMS FOR EXTREMIST INVOLVED IN MILITANT JIHADI TERRORISM IDEOLOGIES AND ACTIVITIES

by Anne Speckhard

"... ”. The tactics employed include kidnappings; beheadings; assassinations; bombings in civilian areas and the use ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

; beheadings; &lt;em&gt;assassinations&lt;/em&gt;; bombings in civilian areas and the use of suicide missions labeled</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7135-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7135_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:09:09">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=FD55CF38510C776117F849C20E659BDF?doi=10.1.1.308.95&amp;rank=5</link><title>Scalable Dynamic Nonparametric Bayesian Models of Content and Users ∗</title><description>Scalable Dynamic Nonparametric Bayesian Models of Content and Users ∗

by Amr Ahmed, Eric Xing

"... ﻿Scalable Dynamic Nonparametric Bayesian Models of Content and Users ∗ Amr Ahmed 1 Eric Xing 2 1 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

. This paper is an extended abstract of the 2012 ACM SIGKDD best doctoral dissertation award of &lt;em&gt;Ahmed&lt;/em&gt; [2011]. 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7135-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7135_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:09:28">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=FD55CF38510C776117F849C20E659BDF?doi=10.1.1.415.7627&amp;rank=6</link><title>Proceedings of the Twenty-Third International Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence Scalable Dynamic Nonparametric Bayesian Models of Content and Users ∗</title><description>Proceedings of the Twenty-Third International Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence Scalable Dynamic Nonparametric Bayesian Models of Content and Users ∗

by Amr Ahmed, Eric Xing

"... Dynamic Nonparametric Bayesian Models of Content and Users ∗ Amr Ahmed 1 Eric Xing 2 1 Research @ Google ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

. This paper is an extended abstract of the 2012 ACM SIGKDD best doctoral dissertation award of &lt;em&gt;Ahmed&lt;/em&gt; [2011]. 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7135-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7135_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:09:46">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=FD55CF38510C776117F849C20E659BDF?doi=10.1.1.99.8393&amp;rank=7</link><title>An Overview of Content-Based Spam Filtering Techniques . Informatica 31:269–278</title><description>An Overview of Content-Based Spam Filtering Techniques . Informatica 31:269–278

by Ahmed Khorsi

"... ﻿An Overview of Content-Based Spam Filtering Techniques Ahmed Khorsi Department of Computer Science ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 12 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

So fast, so cheap, so efficient, Internet is nowadays incontestably communication mean of choice for personal, business and academic purposes. Unfortunately, Internet has not only this beautiful face. Malicious activities enjoy as well this so fast, cheap and efficient mean. The last decade, Internet worms took the lights. In the recent years, spams are invading one of the most used services of Internet: email. This paper summarizes most of techniques used to filter spams by analyzing the email content. Povzetek: Članek pregledno opisuje metode za filtriranje elektronske pošte. 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7135-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7135_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:10:07">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=FD55CF38510C776117F849C20E659BDF?doi=10.1.1.172.5799&amp;rank=8</link><title>Staying Informed: Supervised and Semi-Supervised Multi-view Topical Analysis of Ideological Perspective</title><description>Staying Informed: Supervised and Semi-Supervised Multi-view Topical Analysis of Ideological Perspective

by Amr Ahmed, Eric P. Xing

"... Perspective Amr Ahmed School of Computer Science Carnegie Mellon University amahmed@(email omitted); Eric P. Xing ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 9 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

With the proliferation of user-generated articles over the web, it becomes imperative to develop automated methods that are aware of the ideological-bias implicit in a document collection. While there exist methods that can classify the ideological bias of a given document, little has been done toward understanding the nature of this bias on a topical-level. In this paper we address the problem of modeling ideological perspective on a topical level using a factored topic model. We develop efficient inference algorithms using Collapsed Gibbs sampling for posterior inference, and give various evaluations and illustrations of the utility of our model on various document collections with promising results. Finally we give a Metropolis-Hasting inference algorithm for a semi-supervised extension with decent results. 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7135-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7135_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:10:33">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=FD55CF38510C776117F849C20E659BDF?doi=10.1.1.137.834&amp;rank=9</link><title>Learning Domain-Specific Information Extraction Patterns from the Web</title><description>Learning Domain-Specific Information Extraction Patterns from the Web

by Siddharth Patwardhan, et al. , 2006

"... , HAMAS, IRA Terrorist actions: assassinated, assassination, blew up, bombed, bombing, bombs, explosion ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 5 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Many information extraction (IE) systems rely on manually annotated training data to learn patterns or rules for extracting information about events. Manually annotating data is expensive, however, and a new data set must be annotated for each domain. So most IE training sets are relatively small. Consequently, IE patterns learned from annotated training sets often have limited coverage. In this paper, we explore the idea of using the Web to automatically identify domain-specific IE patterns that were not seen in the training data. We use IE patterns learned from the MUC-4 training set as anchors to identify domain-specific web pages and then learn new IE patterns from them. We compute the semantic affinity of each new pattern to automatically infer the type of information that it will extract. Experiments on the MUC-4 test set show that these new IE patterns improved recall with only a small precision loss.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7135-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7135_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:10:45">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=FD55CF38510C776117F849C20E659BDF?doi=10.1.1.134.5476&amp;rank=10</link><title>INTEGER PROGRAMMING APPROACHES FOR SOME NON-CONVEX AND STOCHASTIC OPTIMIZATION PROBLEMS</title><description>INTEGER PROGRAMMING APPROACHES FOR SOME NON-CONVEX AND STOCHASTIC OPTIMIZATION PROBLEMS

by James R. Luedtke , 2007

"... PROBLEMS Approved by: Professor Shabbir Ahmed, Advisor School of Industrial and Systems Engineering Georgia ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 3 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>