<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7136">Soccer trick</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:11:02" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7136-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7136_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:11:03">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=20C4E67F82F46074068889FD437FC7DD?doi=10.1.1.77.7376&amp;rank=1</link><title>Playing soccer with humanoid robots</title><description>Playing soccer with humanoid robots

by Sven Behnke \- KI – Zeitschrift Künstliche Intelligenz , 2006

"... ﻿Playing Soccer with Humanoid Robots Sven Behnke As step towards the long-term goal of winning ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 4 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Cup Federation added in 2002 a league for humanoid robots to its annual &lt;em&gt;soccer&lt;/em&gt; competitions. Now, the young</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7136-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7136_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:11:15">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=20C4E67F82F46074068889FD437FC7DD?doi=10.1.1.94.2502&amp;rank=2</link><title>Reinforcement Learning In Soccer Simulation</title><description>Reinforcement Learning In Soccer Simulation

by Javad Sha'bani, Ali Honarvar, Mohammad Morovati, Golnaz Abdollahian, Mona Mahmoodi

"... ﻿Reinforcement Learning In Soccer Simulation Javad Sha'bani, Ali Honarvar, Mohammad Morovati ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract. Being of a high complexity, most multi-agent systems are difficult to deal with by a hand-coded approach to decision making. In such complicated environments in which decision making processes should be controlled from both the individuals points ' of view and the whole team, the common approach to the subject is the Reinforcement Learning (RL) method which is mainly based on learning the optimal policy through mapping this task to an episodic reinforcement learning framework. Reinforcement learning is the problem of generating optimal behavior in a sequential decision making environment given the opportunity of interacting with it. Since the Robocop domain is a multi-agent dynamic environment, with notable features making it outstanding for multi-agent simulation benchmarks, it has been largely used as a basis for international multi-agent simulation competitions and research challenges. For this purpose, reinforcement learning problems should be made “understandable ” for “agents ” which are Robocop players in this case. To make the agents “aware ” of what they are intended to do, this paper will provide an overview of different methods and alternative approaches as a starting point for robocupers who are not familiar with reinforcement learning problems in the Robocop domain. 1.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7136-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7136_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:11:28">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=20C4E67F82F46074068889FD437FC7DD?doi=10.1.1.68.6818&amp;rank=3</link><title>MODELLING SOME NORWEGIAN SOCCER DATA</title><description>MODELLING SOME NORWEGIAN SOCCER DATA

by David R. Brillinger

"... SOME NORWEGIAN SOCCER DATA David R. Brillinger Statistics Department University of California, Berkeley ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Results of Norwegian Elite Division &lt;em&gt;soccer&lt;/em&gt; games are studied for the year 2003. Previous writers</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7136-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7136_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:11:48">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=20C4E67F82F46074068889FD437FC7DD?doi=10.1.1.2.2295&amp;rank=4</link><title>Karlsruhe Brainstormers - A Reinforcement Learning approach to robotic soccer</title><description>Karlsruhe Brainstormers - A Reinforcement Learning approach to robotic soccer

by M. Riedmiller, A. Merke, D. Meier, A. Hoffmann, A. Sinner, O. Thate, R. Ehrmann \- RoboCup-2000: Robot Soccer World Cup IV, LNCS

"... Karlsruhe Brainstormers - A Reinforcement Learning approach to robotic soccer M. Riedmiller, A ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 41 (7 self) \- Add to MetaCart

. Our long-term goal is to build a robot &lt;em&gt;soccer&lt;/em&gt; team where the decision making part is based</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7136-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7136_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:12:00">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=20C4E67F82F46074068889FD437FC7DD?doi=10.1.1.15.5291&amp;rank=5</link><title>KiRo - An autonomous table soccer player</title><description>KiRo - An autonomous table soccer player

by Thilo Weigel, Bernhard Nebel \- In Proc. Int. RoboCup Symposium ’02 , 2002

"... KiRo -- An autonomous table soccer player Thilo Weigel, Bernhard Nebel Institut fur Informatik ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 4 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper presents KiRo -- a system capable of playing table &lt;em&gt;soccer&lt;/em&gt; on a competitive level</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7136-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7136_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:12:14">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=20C4E67F82F46074068889FD437FC7DD?doi=10.1.1.131.435&amp;rank=6</link><title>Scheduling the Brazilian soccer tournament with fairness and broadcast objectives</title><description>Scheduling the Brazilian soccer tournament with fairness and broadcast objectives

by Celso C. Ribeiro, Sebastián Urrutia

"... ﻿Scheduling the Brazilian soccer tournament with fairness and broadcast objectives Celso C. Ribeiro ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 2 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract. The Brazilian &lt;em&gt;soccer&lt;/em&gt; tournament is organized every year by the Brazilian &lt;em&gt;Soccer&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7136-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7136_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:12:34">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=20C4E67F82F46074068889FD437FC7DD?doi=10.1.1.2.7533&amp;rank=7</link><title>Human-level AI's Killer Application: Interactive Computer Games</title><description>Human-level AI's Killer Application: Interactive Computer Games

by John E. Laird, Michael van Lent , 2001

"... and simulated soccer games. In RoboCup, the goal is to build the best soccerplaying robots, not to create ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 136 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

this article, we further motivate our proposal of using interactive computer games for AI research, review previous research on AI and games, and present the different game genres and the roles that human-level AI could play within these genres. We then describe the research issues and AI techniques that are relevant to each of these roles. Our conclusion is that interactive computer games provide a rich environment for incremental research on human-level AI</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7136-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7136_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:12:47">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=20C4E67F82F46074068889FD437FC7DD?doi=10.1.1.53.9399&amp;rank=8</link><title>PPS (Petrin Pallo Seura), a team of soccer playing agents</title><description>PPS (Petrin Pallo Seura), a team of soccer playing agents

by Petri Ikonen , 1998

"... PPS (Petrin Pallo Seura), a team of soccer playing agents 25 February 1998 1 PPS (Petrin Pallo ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

this report) was to set the method preference and method context, and sometimes omitting methods, for the behaviours in "play on" mode, also deciding what agent to take on what roll (e.g free-kicker, corner-kicker). 3 Managing multiple agents</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7136-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7136_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:13:07">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=20C4E67F82F46074068889FD437FC7DD?doi=10.1.1.186.5548&amp;rank=9</link><title>Teaching Old Dogs New Tricks: Incremental Multimap Regression for Interactive Robot Learning from</title><description>Teaching Old Dogs New Tricks: Incremental Multimap Regression for Interactive Robot Learning from

by Daniel H Grollman , 2010

"... ﻿Abstract of “Teaching Old Dogs New Tricks: Incremental Multimap Regression for Interactive Robot ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 2 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We consider autonomous robots as having associated control policies that determine their actions in response to perceptions of the environment. Often, these controllers are explicitly transferred from a human via programmatic description or physical instantiation. Alternatively, Robot Learning from Demonstration (RLfD) can enable a robot to learn a policy from observing only demonstrations of the task itself. We focus on interactive, teleoperative teaching, where the user manually controls the robot and provides demonstrations while receiving learner feedback. With regression, the collected perception-actuation pairs are used to directly estimate the underlying policy mapping. This dissertation contributes an RLfD methodology for interactive, mixed-initiative learning of unknown tasks. The goal of the technique is to enable users to implicitly instantiate autonomous robot controllers that perform desired tasks as well as the demonstrator, as measured by task-specific metrics. With standard regression techniques, we show that such “on-par” learning is restricted to policies typified by a many-to-one mapping (a unimap) from perception to actuation. Thus, controllers representable as multi-state Finite State Machines (FSMs) and that exhibit a one-tomany mapping (a multimap) cannot be learnt. To be able to do so we must address the three issues of model selection (how many subtasks or FSM states), policy learning (for each subtask),</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7136-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7136_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 15:13:28">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=20C4E67F82F46074068889FD437FC7DD?doi=10.1.1.69.7574&amp;rank=10</link><title>A branch-and-cut algorithm for scheduling the highly-constrained Chilean soccer tournament</title><description>A branch-and-cut algorithm for scheduling the highly-constrained Chilean soccer tournament

by Thiago F. Noronha, Celso C. Ribeiro, Guillermo Duran, Sebastian Souyris, Andres Weintraub

"... ﻿A branch-and-cut algorithm for scheduling the highly-constrained Chilean soccer tournament Thiago ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 3 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract. The Chilean &lt;em&gt;soccer&lt;/em&gt; championship follows the structure of a compact single round robin</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>