<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7155">ted talk mooc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 16:08:58" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7155-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7155_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 16:09:00">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=EA582DA5B3E7CA3C9853157B3B585D1D?doi=10.1.1.15.3481&amp;rank=1</link><title>Multiparty Communication Complexity</title><description>Multiparty Communication Complexity

by Danny Dolev, Tomás Feder , 1989

"... to exchange with each one. We can neither talk to all parties as in the two pa,rty model, nor obtain all CH ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 614 (21 self) \- Add to MetaCart

A given Boolean function has its input distributed among many parties. The aim is to determine which parties to tMk to and what information to exchange with each of them in order to evaluate the function while minimizing the total communication. This paper shows that it is possible to obtain the Boolean answer deterministically with only a polynomial increase in communication with respect to the information lower bound given by the nondeterministic communication complexity of the function.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7155-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7155_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 16:09:23">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=EA582DA5B3E7CA3C9853157B3B585D1D?doi=10.1.1.225.165&amp;rank=2</link><title>Distributed hierarchical processing in the primate cerebral cortex</title><description>Distributed hierarchical processing in the primate cerebral cortex

by Daniel J. Felleman, David C. Van Essen \- Cereb Cortex , 1991

"... and cross talk between streams at successive stages of processing. It is likely that these complexities ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 511 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

In recent years, many new cortical areas have been identified in the macaque monkey. The number of identified connections between areas has increased even more dramatically. We report here on (1) a summary of the layout of cortical areas associated with vision and with other modalities, (2) a computerized database for storing and representing large amounts of information on connectivity patterns, and (3) the application of these data to the analysis of hierarchical organization of the cerebral cortex. Our analysis concentrates on the visual system, which includes 25 neocortical areas that are predominantly or exclusively visual in function, plus an additional 7 areas that we regard as visual-association areas on the basis of their extensive visual inputs. A total of 305 connections among these 32 visual and</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7155-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7155_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 16:09:42">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=EA582DA5B3E7CA3C9853157B3B585D1D?doi=10.1.1.296.5944&amp;rank=3</link><title>Direct manipulation: a step beyond programming languages</title><description>Direct manipulation: a step beyond programming languages

by Ben Shneiderman \- Computer , 1983

"... , but the amalgam does convey an image of the truly pleased user. As I talked with these enthusiasts and examined ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 487 (11 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Direct manipulation systems offer the satisfying experience of operating on visible objects. The computer becomes transparent, and users can concentrate on their tasks.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7155-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7155_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 16:10:03">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=EA582DA5B3E7CA3C9853157B3B585D1D?doi=10.1.1.107.2757&amp;rank=4</link><title>A taxonomy of web search</title><description>A taxonomy of web search

by Andrei Broder \- SIGIR FORUM , 2002

"... on 145 queries against the WT10g collection, distributed by CSIRO. (See http://www.ted ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 438 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Classic IR (information retrieval) is inherently predicated on users searching for information, the socalled "information need". But the need behind a web search is often not informational -- it might be navigational (give me the url of the site I want to reach) or transactional (show me sites where I can perform a certain transaction, e.g. shop, download a file, or find a map). We explore this taxonomy of web searches and discuss how global search engines evolved to deal with web-specific needs.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7155-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7155_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 16:10:23">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=EA582DA5B3E7CA3C9853157B3B585D1D?doi=10.1.1.296.7620&amp;rank=5</link><title>Will Massive Online Open Courses (MOOCs) Change Education?</title><description>Will Massive Online Open Courses (MOOCs) Change Education?

by Daniel M. Russell, Scott Klemmer

"... in her TED talk [2], “…a 2% error rate in a class of 100 students in barely detectable; in a MOOC ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

As has been apparent for the past several months, &lt;em&gt;MOOCs&lt;/em&gt; (Massive Online Open Courseware) have</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7155-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7155_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 16:10:43">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=EA582DA5B3E7CA3C9853157B3B585D1D?doi=10.1.1.112.3771&amp;rank=6</link><title>Smart cars on smart roads: Problems of control</title><description>Smart cars on smart roads: Problems of control

by Pravin Varaiya, Pravin Varaiya \- IEEE Transactions on Automatic Control , 1993

"... a toll, stopping for gas, listening to the ra.dio, using the telephone, talking to passengers ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 238 (18 self) \- Add to MetaCart

have been inadvertently introduced.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7155-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7155_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 16:11:03">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=EA582DA5B3E7CA3C9853157B3B585D1D?doi=10.1.1.410.4924&amp;rank=7</link><title>The Electronic Journal for English as a Second Language What’s with the MOOCs?</title><description>The Electronic Journal for English as a Second Language What’s with the MOOCs?

by Vance Stevens

"... ages in his TED Talk on the AI MOOC, http://www.i-­‐programmer.info/news/150-­‐training ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

The world of higher education is abuzz with this &lt;em&gt;MOOC&lt;/em&gt; thing. The success of the connectivist &lt;em&gt;MOOC&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7155-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7155_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 16:11:25">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=EA582DA5B3E7CA3C9853157B3B585D1D?doi=10.1.1.20.417&amp;rank=8</link><title>The Free Haven Project: Distributed Anonymous Storage Service</title><description>The Free Haven Project: Distributed Anonymous Storage Service

by Roger Dingledine, Michael J. Freedman, David Molnar \- In Proceedings of the Workshop on Design Issues in Anonymity and Unobservability , 2000

"... . It is not enough simply to talk about "anonymous" storage and publication. In section 2, we enumerate the many ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 204 (7 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We present a design for a system of anonymous storage which resists the attempts of powerful adversaries to find or destroy any stored data. We enumerate distinct notions of anonymity for each party in the system, and suggest a way to classify anonymous systems based on the kinds of anonymity provided. Our design ensures the availability of each document for a publisher-specified lifetime. A reputation system provides server accountability by limiting the damage caused from misbehaving servers. We identify attacks and defenses against anonymous storage services, and close with a list of problems which are currently unsolved.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7155-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7155_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 16:11:45">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=EA582DA5B3E7CA3C9853157B3B585D1D?doi=10.1.1.417.3944&amp;rank=9</link><title>Improving learning in MOOCs with Cognitive Science</title><description>Improving learning in MOOCs with Cognitive Science

by Joseph Jay Williams

"... ﻿Improving learning in MOOCs with Cognitive Science Joseph Jay Williams 1 1 University ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract. &lt;em&gt;MOOCs&lt;/em&gt; and other platforms for online education are having a tremendous impact</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7155-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7155_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 16:12:04">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=EA582DA5B3E7CA3C9853157B3B585D1D?doi=10.1.1.56.4306&amp;rank=10</link><title>Using Collaborative Plans to Model the Intentional Structure of Discourse</title><description>Using Collaborative Plans to Model the Intentional Structure of Discourse

by Karen Elizabeth Lochbaum \- Computational Linguistics , 1994

"... . Barbara has taught me just about all I know about doing research, writing papers, giving talks ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 198 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

An agent's ability to understand an utterance depends upon its ability to relate that utterance to the preceding discourse. The agent must determine whether the utterance begins a new segment of the discourse, completes the current segment, or contributes to it. The intentional structure of the discourse, comprised of discourse segment purposes and their interrelationships, plays a central role in this process (Grosz and Sidner, 1986). In this thesis, we provide a computational model for recognizing intentional structure and utilizing it in discourse processing. The model specifies how an agent's beliefs about the intentions underlying a discourse affects and are affected by its subsequent discourse. We characterize this process for both interpretation and generation and then provide specific algorithms for modeling the interpretation process. The collaborative planning framework of SharedPlans (Lochbaum, Grosz, and Sidner, 1990; Grosz and Kraus, 1993) provides the basis for our model ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>