<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7173"> severed spinal cord</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:07:15" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7173-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7173_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:07:17">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=977FDF773D2277EB1CBC61FB33041C54?doi=10.1.1.271.9287&amp;rank=1</link><title>in Severe Spinal Cord Injury</title><description>in Severe Spinal Cord Injury

by Susana Martiñón, Elisa García, Gabriel Gutierrez-ospina, Humberto Mestre, Antonio Ibarra

"... Is Ineffective in Severe Spinal Cord Injury Susana Martiñón 1 , Elisa García 1,2 , Gabriel Gutierrez-Ospina 3 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

&lt;em&gt;cord&lt;/em&gt; contusion (SCC; moderate or &lt;em&gt;severe&lt;/em&gt;) or a &lt;em&gt;spinal&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;cord&lt;/em&gt; transection (SCT; complete or incomplete</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7173-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7173_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:07:36">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=977FDF773D2277EB1CBC61FB33041C54?doi=10.1.1.381.877&amp;rank=2</link><title>Some philosophical problems from the standpoint of artificial intelligence</title><description>Some philosophical problems from the standpoint of artificial intelligence

by John McCarthy, Patrick J. Hayes \- AI, IN MACHINE INTELLIGENCE 4, MELTZER AND MICHIE (EDS , 1969

"... that receives the nerve impulses from the spinal cord and transmits them to the muscles. If we break ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1483 (25 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7173-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7173_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:07:49">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=977FDF773D2277EB1CBC61FB33041C54?doi=10.1.1.368.2254&amp;rank=3</link><title>Some studies in machine learning using the game of Checkers</title><description>Some studies in machine learning using the game of Checkers

by Arthur L. Samuel \- IBM JOURNAL OF RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT , 1959

"... . poinn and the process can be repeated. This look-ahead procc;dure is carried several moves in advance ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 612 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Two machine-learning procedures have been investigated in some detail using the game of checkers. Enough work has been done to verify the fact that a computer can be programmed so that it will learn to play a better game of checkers than can be played by the person who wrote the program. Furthermore, it can learn to do this in a remarkably short period of time (8 or 10 hours of machine-playing time) when given only the rules of the game, a sense of direction, and a redundant and incomplete list of parameters which are thought to have something to do with the game, but whose correct signs and relative weights are unknown and unspecified. The principles of machine learning verified by these experiments are, of course, applicable to many other situations.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7173-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7173_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:08:07">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=977FDF773D2277EB1CBC61FB33041C54?doi=10.1.1.14.5614&amp;rank=4</link><title>Automatic Acquisition of Hyponyms from Large Text Corpora</title><description>Automatic Acquisition of Hyponyms from Large Text Corpora

by Marti A. Hearst , 1992

"... -recognition techniques. Thus one could say by interpreting sentence (S1) ac- cording to (In-b) we are applying pattern ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 876 (5 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We describe a method for the automatic acquisition of the hyponymy lexical relation from unrestricted text. Two goals motivate the approach: (i) avoidante of the need for pre-encoded knowledge and (ii) applicability across a wide range of text. We identify a set of lexico-syntactic patterns that are easily recognizable, that occur frequently and across text genre boundaries, and that indisputably indicate the lexical relation of interest. We describe a method for discovering these patterns and suggest that other lexical relations will also he acquirable iu this way. A subset of the acquisitiou algorithm is implemented and the results are used to augment and critique the structure of a large hand-built thesaurus. Extensions and applications to areas such as information retrieval are suggested.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7173-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7173_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:08:29">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=977FDF773D2277EB1CBC61FB33041C54?doi=10.1.1.335.7866&amp;rank=5</link><title>Tangible bits: towards seamless interfaces between people, bits and atoms</title><description>Tangible bits: towards seamless interfaces between people, bits and atoms

by Hiroshi Ishii, Brygg Ullmer \- Proceedings of the SIGCHI conference on Human factors in computing systems, ACM Press: 234--241 , 1997

"... mouse, windows, icons, property sheets, and modeless interactions. The Star also set several important ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1044 (54 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper presents our vision of Human Computer Interaction (HCI): "Tangible Bits. " Tangible Bits allows users to "grasp &amp; manipulate " bits in the center of users’ attention by coupling the bits with everyday physical objects and architectural surfaces. Tangible Bits also enables users to be aware of background bits at the periphery of human perception using ambient display media such as light, sound, airflow, and water movement in an augmented space. The goal of Tangible Bits is to bridge the gaps between both cyberspace and the physical environment, as well as the foreground and background of human activities. This paper describes three key concepts of Tangible Bits: interactive surfaces; the coupling of bits with graspable physical objects; and ambient media for background awareness. We illustrate these concepts with three prototype systems – the metaDESK, transBOARD and ambientROOM – to identify underlying research issues. Keywords tangible user interface, ambient media, graspable user interface, augmented reality, ubiquitous computing, center and periphery, foreground and background</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7173-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7173_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:08:46">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=977FDF773D2277EB1CBC61FB33041C54?doi=10.1.1.14.1729&amp;rank=6</link><title>Distributional Clustering Of English Words</title><description>Distributional Clustering Of English Words

by Fernando Pereira, Naftali Tishby, Lillian Lee \- In Proceedings of the 31st Annual Meeting of the Association for Computational Linguistics , 1993

"... for automatically classifying words ac- cording to their contexts of use have both scien- tific and practical ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 549 (28 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We describe and evaluate experimentally a method for clustering words according to their dis- tribution in particular syntactic contexts. Words are represented by the relative frequency distributions of contexts in which they appear, and relative entropy between those distributions is used as the similarity measure for clustering. Clusters are represented by average context distributions derived from the given words according to their probabilities of cluster membership. In many cases, the clusters can be thought of as encoding coarse sense distinctions. Deterministic annealing is used to find lowest distortion sets of clusters: as the an- nealing parameter increases, existing clusters become unstable and subdivide, yielding a hierarchi- cal "soft" clustering of the data. Clusters are used as the basis for class models of word coocurrence, and the models evaluated with respect to held-out test data.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7173-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7173_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:09:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=977FDF773D2277EB1CBC61FB33041C54?doi=10.1.1.14.2230&amp;rank=7</link><title>Interpretation as Abduction</title><description>Interpretation as Abduction

by Jerry R. Hobbs, Mark Stickel, Paul Martin, Douglas Edwards , 1990

"... provide several examples. In Section 5 we describe briefly the type hierarchy that is essential for making ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 585 (26 self) \- Add to MetaCart

An approach to abductive inference developed in the TACITUS project has resulted in a dramatic simplification of how the problem of interpreting texts is conceptualized. Its use in solving the local pragmatics problems of reference, compound nominals, syntactic ambiguity, and metonymy is described and illustrated. It also suggests an elegant and thorough integration of syntax, semantics, and pragmatics. 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7173-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7173_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:09:28">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=977FDF773D2277EB1CBC61FB33041C54?doi=10.1.1.201.9742&amp;rank=8</link><title>Capitalism, Socialism and Democracy</title><description>Capitalism, Socialism and Democracy

by Joseph A. Schumpeter, In The S, Joseph A. Schumpeter , 1942

"... of several hundred thousand and an even greater number of new jobs. We should not let the small net gains ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 676 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

or method of economic change and not only never is but never can be stationary.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7173-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7173_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:09:41">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=977FDF773D2277EB1CBC61FB33041C54?doi=10.1.1.19.9180&amp;rank=9</link><title>A Maximum-Entropy-Inspired Parser</title><description>A Maximum-Entropy-Inspired Parser

by Eugene Charniak , 1999

"... events fl(a, b, c), f2(a, b), and f3(a, c) and combine them in the model ac- cording to Equation 3 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 821 (18 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We present a new parser for parsing down to Penn tree-bank style parse trees that achieves 90.1% average precision/recall for sentences of length 40 and less, and 89.5% for sentences of length 100 and less when trained and tested on the previously established [5,9,10,15,17] "stan- dard" sections of the Wall Street Journal tree- bank. This represents a 13% decrease in error rate over the best single-parser results on this corpus [9]. The major technical innova- tion is the use of a "maximum-entropy-inspired" model for conditioning and smoothing that let us successfully to test and combine many different conditioning events. We also present some partial results showing the effects of different conditioning information, including a surprising 2% improvement due to guessing the lexical head's pre-terminal before guessing the lexical head.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7173-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7173_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:10:02">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=977FDF773D2277EB1CBC61FB33041C54?doi=10.1.1.90.9484&amp;rank=10</link><title>The 4+1 view model of architecture</title><description>The 4+1 view model of architecture

by Philippe B. Kruchten \- IEEE SOFTWARE , 1995

"... to address the concerns of all “customers.” Several authors have noted the problem of architectural ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 416 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The 4+1 View Model organizes a description of a software architecture using five concurrent views, each of which addresses a specific set of concerns. Architects capture their design decisions in four views and use the fifth view to illustrate and validate them.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>