<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7174">seal team 6</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:10:15" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7174-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7174_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:10:17">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B6A26C205DF1C97A7ADFEFFAA8FC3698?doi=10.1.1.9.6021&amp;rank=1</link><title>Training Support Vector Machines: an Application to Face Detection</title><description>Training Support Vector Machines: an Application to Face Detection

by Edgar Osuna, Robert Freund, Federico Girosi , 1997

"... team (AT&amp;T Bell Labs.) that can be seen as a new method for training polynomial, neural network ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 561 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

learning technique developed by V. Vapnik and his &lt;em&gt;team&lt;/em&gt; (AT&amp;T Bell Labs.) that can be seen as a new method</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7174-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7174_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:10:38">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B6A26C205DF1C97A7ADFEFFAA8FC3698?doi=10.1.1.20.5519&amp;rank=2</link><title>The STATEMATE Semantics of Statecharts</title><description>The STATEMATE Semantics of Statecharts

by David Harel, Amnon Naamad , 1996

"... version of this semantics was developed by a team about.10 years ago. With the added experience ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 533 (11 self) \- Add to MetaCart

by a &lt;em&gt;team&lt;/em&gt; about.10 years ago. With the added experience of the users of the system it has since been</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7174-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7174_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:10:52">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B6A26C205DF1C97A7ADFEFFAA8FC3698?doi=10.1.1.148.3671&amp;rank=3</link><title>The WEKA Data Mining Software: An Update</title><description>The WEKA Data Mining Software: An Update

by Mark Hall, Eibe Frank, Geoffrey Holmes, Bernhard Pfahringer, Peter Reutemann, Ian H. Witten

"... an introduction to the WEKA workbench, reviews the history of the project, and, in light of the recent 3.6 stable ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 605 (11 self) \- Add to MetaCart

, and, in light of the recent 3.&lt;em&gt;6&lt;/em&gt; stable release, briefly discusses what has been added since the last</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7174-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7174_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:11:14">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B6A26C205DF1C97A7ADFEFFAA8FC3698?doi=10.1.1.132.4212&amp;rank=4</link><title>A Field Study of the Software Design Process for Large Systems</title><description>A Field Study of the Software Design Process for Large Systems

by Bill Curtis, Herb Krasner, Neil Iscoe \- Communications of the ACM , 1988

"... ’ development environments that reduced software productivity and quality. Some members of our team have been ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 507 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The problems of designing large software systems were studied through interviewing personnel from 17 large projects. A layered behavioral model is used to analyze how three lgf these problems-the thin spread of application domain knowledge, fluctuating and conflicting requirements, and communication bottlenecks and breakdowns-affected software productivity and quality through their impact on cognitive, social, and organizational processes.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7174-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7174_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:11:27">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B6A26C205DF1C97A7ADFEFFAA8FC3698?doi=10.1.1.136.2762&amp;rank=5</link><title>ANALYSIS OF WIRELESS SENSOR NETWORKS FOR HABITAT MONITORING</title><description>ANALYSIS OF WIRELESS SENSOR NETWORKS FOR HABITAT MONITORING

by Joseph Polastre, Robert Szewczyk, Alan Mainwaring, David Culler, John Anderson , 2004

"... .5. Section 18.6 contains related work and Section 18.7 concludes. 18.2 Habitat Monitoring Many research ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1030 (18 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We provide an in-depth study of applying wireless sensor networks (WSNs) to real-world habitat monitoring. A set of system design requirements were developed that cover the hardware design of the nodes, the sensor network software, protective enclosures, and system architecture to meet the requirements of biologists. In the summer of 2002, 43 nodes were deployed on a small island off the coast of Maine streaming useful live data onto the web. Although researchers anticipate some challenges arising in real-world deployments of WSNs, many problems can only be discovered through experience. We present a set of experiences from a four month long deployment on a remote island. We analyze the environmental and node health data to evaluate system performance. The close integration of WSNs with their environment provides environmental data at densities previously impossible. We show that the sensor data is also useful for predicting system operation and network failures. Based on over one million 2 Polastre et. al. data readings, we analyze the node and network design and develop network reliability profiles and failure models.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7174-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7174_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:11:49">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B6A26C205DF1C97A7ADFEFFAA8FC3698?doi=10.1.1.332.8432&amp;rank=6</link><title>Moses: Open Source Toolkit for Statistical Machine Translation”. ACL-2007</title><description>Moses: Open Source Toolkit for Statistical Machine Translation”. ACL-2007

by Hieu Hoang, Alexandra Birch, Chris Callison-burch, Richard Zens, Marcello Federico, Nicola Bertoldi, Chris Dyer, Brooke Cowan, Wade Shen, Christine Moran, Ondřej Bojar, Alexandra Constantin, Evan Herbst , 2007

"... Bojar Charles University 6 Alexandra Constantin Williams College 7 Evan Herbst Cornell 8 1 pkoehn ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 875 (45 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We describe an open-source toolkit for statistical machine translation whose novel contributions are (a) support for linguistically motivated factors, (b) confusion network decoding, and (c) efficient data formats for translation models and language models. In addition to the SMT decoder, the toolkit also includes a wide variety of tools for training, tuning and applying the system to many translation tasks. 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7174-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7174_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:12:08">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B6A26C205DF1C97A7ADFEFFAA8FC3698?doi=10.1.1.91.2433&amp;rank=7</link><title>Architectural Styles and the Design of Network-based Software Architectures</title><description>Architectural Styles and the Design of Network-based Software Architectures

by Roy Thomas Fielding , 2000

"... ...................................................................................................................13 1.6 Patterns and Pattern Languages ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 592 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The World Wide Web has succeeded in large part because its software architecture has been designed to meet the needs of an Internet-scale distributed hypermedia system. The Web has been iteratively developed over the past ten years through a series of modifications to the standards that define its architecture. In order to identify those aspects of the Web that needed improvement and avoid undesirable modifications, a model for the modern Web architecture was needed to guide its design, definition, and deployment. Software architecture research investigates methods for determining how best to partition a system, how components identify and communicate with each other, how information is communicated, how elements of a system can evolve independently, and how all of the above can be described using formal and informal notations. My work is motivated by the desire to understand and evaluate the architectural design of network-based application software through principled use of architectural constraints, thereby obtaining the functional, performance, and social properties desired of an architecture. An architectural style is a named, coordinated set of architectural constraints. This dissertation defines a framework for understanding software architecture via architectural styles and demonstrates how styles can be used to guide the architectural design of network-based application software. A survey of architectural styles for network-based applications is used to classify styles according to the architectural properties they induce on an architecture for distributed hypermedia. I then introduce the Representational State Transfer (REST) architectural style and describe how REST has been used to guide the design and development of the architecture for the modern Web. REST emphasizes scalability of component interactions, generality of interfaces, independent deployment of components, and intermediary components to reduce interaction latency, enforce security, and encapsulate legacy systems. I describe the software engineering principles guiding REST and the interaction constraints chosen to retain those principles, contrasting them to the constraints of other architectural styles. Finally, I describe the lessons learned from applying REST to the design of the Hypertext Transfer Protocol and Uniform Resource Identifier standards, and from their subsequent deployment in Web client and server software.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7174-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7174_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:12:20">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B6A26C205DF1C97A7ADFEFFAA8FC3698?doi=10.1.1.19.3462&amp;rank=8</link><title>Probabilistic Roadmaps for Path Planning in High-Dimensional Configuration Spaces</title><description>Probabilistic Roadmaps for Path Planning in High-Dimensional Configuration Spaces

by Lydia Kavraki, Petr Svestka, Jean-claude Latombe, Mark Overmars \- IEEE INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON ROBOTICS AND AUTOMATION , 1996

"... , in Sections 4, 5, and 6 we apply our method to planar articulated robots. In Section 4 we describe specific ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 890 (113 self) \- Add to MetaCart

A new motion planning method for robots in static workspaces is presented. This method proceeds in two phases: a learning phase and a query phase. In the learning phase, a probabilistic roadmap is constructed and stored as a graph whose nodes correspond to collision-free configurations and whose edges correspond to feasible paths between these configurations. These paths are computed using a simple and fast local planner. In the query phase, any given start and goal configurations of the robot are connected to two nodes of the roadmap; the roadmap is then searched for a path joining these two nodes. The method is general and easy to implement. It can be applied to virtually any type of holonomic robot. It requires selecting certain parameters (e.g., the duration of the learning phase) whose values depend on the scene, that is the robot and its workspace. But these values turn out to be relatively easy to choose, Increased efficiency can also be achieved by tailoring some components of the method (e.g., the local planner) to the considered robots. In this paper the method is applied to planar articulated robots with many degrees of freedom. Experimental results show that path planning can be done in a fraction of a second on a contemporary workstation (=150 MIPS), after learning for relatively short periods of time (a few dozen seconds)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7174-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7174_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:12:34">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B6A26C205DF1C97A7ADFEFFAA8FC3698?doi=10.1.1.101.5199&amp;rank=9</link><title>An Overview of Workflow Management: From Process Modeling to Workflow Automation Infrastructure</title><description>An Overview of Workflow Management: From Process Modeling to Workflow Automation Infrastructure

by Diimitrios Georgakopoulos, Mark Hornick, Amit Sheth \- DISTRIBUTED AND PARALLEL DATABASES , 1995

"... conclusions and some perspective on future expectations are presented in Section 6. 2\. Workflows and workflow ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 549 (25 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Today’s business enterprises must deal with global competition, reduce the cost of doing business, and rapidly develop new services and products. To address these requirements enterprises must constantly reconsider and optimize the way they do business and change their information systems and applications to support evolving business processes. Workflow technology facilitates these by providing methodologies and software to support (i) business process modeling to capture business processes as workflow specifications, (ii) business process reengineering to optimize specified processes, and (iii) workflow automation to generate workflow implementations from workflow specifications. This paper provides a high-level overview of the current workflow management methodologies and software products. In addition, we discuss the infrastructure technologies that can address the limitations of current commercial workflow technology and extend the scope and mission of workflow management systems to support increased workflow automation in complex real-world environments involving heterogeneous, autonomous, and distributed information systems. In particular, we discuss how distributed object management and customized transaction management can support further advances in the commercial state of the art in this area.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7174-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7174_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 17:12:54">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B6A26C205DF1C97A7ADFEFFAA8FC3698?doi=10.1.1.118.9444&amp;rank=10</link><title>Secure spread spectrum watermarking for multimedia</title><description>Secure spread spectrum watermarking for multimedia

by Ingemar J. Cox, Joe Kilian, F. Thomson Leighton, Talal Shamoon \- IEEE TRANSACTIONS ON IMAGE PROCESSING , 1997

"... ﻿IEEE TRANSACTIONS ON IMAGE PROCESSING, VOL. 6, NO. 12, DECEMBER 1997 1673 Secure Spread Spectrum ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 802 (10 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper presents a secure (tamper-resistant) algorithm for watermarking images, and a methodology for digital watermarking that may be generalized to audio, video, and multimedia data. We advocate that a watermark should be constructed as an independent and identically distributed (i.i.d.) Gaussian random vector that is imperceptibly inserted in a spread-spectrum-like fashion into the perceptually most significant spectral components of the data. We argue that insertion of a watermark under this regime makes the watermark robust to signal processing operations (such as lossy compression, filtering, digital-analog and analog-digital conversion, requantization, etc.), and common geometric transformations (such as cropping, scaling, translation, and rotation) provided that the original image is available and that it can be succesfully registered against the transformed watermarked image. In these cases, the watermark detector unambiguously identifies the owner. Further, the use of Gaussian noise, ensures strong resilience to multiple-document, or collusional, attacks. Experimental results are provided to support these claims, along with an exposition of pending open problems.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>