<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7218">edward kennedy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 18:52:26" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7218-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7218_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 18:52:27">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=41B2BC72F6381A94B0EE30351D88CEE4?doi=10.1.1.318.6405&amp;rank=1</link><title>Trade Policy and Economic Growth: A Skeptic's Guide to the Cross-National Evidence</title><description>Trade Policy and Economic Growth: A Skeptic's Guide to the Cross-National Evidence

by Francisco Rodríguez, Dani Rodrik, Francisco Rodríguez, Dani Rodrik \- Macroeconomics Annual 2000, Ben Bemanke and , 2000

"... 79 Kennedy Street Cambridge, MA 02138 (617) 495-9454 We thank Dan Ben-David, Sebastian Edwards ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 395 (18 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Andrew Warner for generously sharing their data with us. We are particularly grateful to Ben-David, Frankel, Romer, Sachs, Warner and Romain Wacziarg for helpful e-mail exchanges. We have benefited greatly from discussions in seminars at the University of California at Berkeley,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7218-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7218_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 18:52:44">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=41B2BC72F6381A94B0EE30351D88CEE4?doi=10.1.1.224.8562&amp;rank=2</link><title>Kennedy Space Center Library Archives</title><description>Kennedy Space Center Library Archives

by Barbara E. Green, Early Human, Spaceflight Firsts , 2003

"... &amp; Human Mission Firsts Kennedy Space Center Library Archives Kennedy Space Center, Florida ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

publications available in the &lt;em&gt;Kennedy&lt;/em&gt; Space Center Library Archives. The list is divided into four sections</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7218-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7218_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 18:53:03">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=41B2BC72F6381A94B0EE30351D88CEE4?doi=10.1.1.407.6089&amp;rank=3</link><title>The Edward Westermarck Lecture, 2003</title><description>The Edward Westermarck Lecture, 2003

by Nancy D. Munn

"... Spacetime and memory in nineteenthcentury, pre-Civil War New York The Edward Westermarck Lecture, 2003 Nancy ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

this lecture in memory of &lt;em&gt;Edward&lt;/em&gt; Westermarck. Westermarck had a long-term interest in articulating</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7218-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7218_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 18:53:21">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=41B2BC72F6381A94B0EE30351D88CEE4?doi=10.1.1.374.726&amp;rank=4</link><title>Testing Lifting Bodies at Edwards By</title><description>Testing Lifting Bodies at Edwards By

by A Not-for, Profit Corporation, Robert G. Hoey , 1994

"... at the Kennedy Space Center or Edwards Air Force Base merits little more than a brief segment on the evening news ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

The image above is a reproduction of the mural commissioned by NASA Dryden and created</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7218-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7218_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 18:53:40">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=41B2BC72F6381A94B0EE30351D88CEE4?doi=10.1.1.286.7355&amp;rank=5</link><title>OntheDynamicsofLightQuarksinQCD KhalilBitar,RobertG.Edwards,UrsM.Heller,andA.D.Kennedy</title><description>OntheDynamicsofLightQuarksinQCD KhalilBitar,RobertG.Edwards,UrsM.Heller,andA.D.Kennedy

by unknown authors

"... ﻿OntheDynamicsofLightQuarksinQCD KhalilBitar,RobertG.Edwards,UrsM.Heller,andA.D.Kennedy ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

quarks.Weshowthatitispossibletoreachregionsofparameterspacewithlightpionsm0:2=ausingWilson fermions.IftheHybridMolecularDynamics(HMD)algorithmisusedwiththesameparametersitgivesincorrect results.Wealsopresentpreliminaryresultsusingahigher-orderintegrationscheme. Inthispaper,wesetoutwiththeobjectiveof examiningtheeectsofHerrorsintheintegrationofHamilton'sequationsofmotion.Wehave performedtestsusing2avorsofWilsonfermions at=5:30,=0:1675and0:1677ona16332</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7218-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7218_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 18:53:57">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=41B2BC72F6381A94B0EE30351D88CEE4?doi=10.1.1.196.5253&amp;rank=6</link><title>Technical Change, Inequality, and The Labor Market</title><description>Technical Change, Inequality, and The Labor Market

by Daron Acemoglu \- Journal of Economic Literature , 2002

"... Ahmad (1965), Charles Kennedy (1964), Paul Samuelson (1970), Yujiro Hayami and Vernon Ruttan (1970 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 154 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This essay discusses the effect of technical change on wage inequality. I argue that the behavior of wages and returns to schooling indicates that technical change has been skill-biased during the past sixty years. Furthermore, the recent increase in inequality is most likely due to an acceleration in skill bias. In contrast to twentiethcentury developments, much of thr technical change during the early nineteenth century appears to be skill-replacing. I suggest that this is because the increased supply of unskilled workers in the English cities made the introduction of these technologies profitable. On the other hand, the twentieth century has been characterized by skillbiased technical change because the rapid increase in the supply of skilled workers has induced the development of skill-complementary technologies. The recent acceleration in skill bias is in turn likely to have been a response to the acceleration in the supply of skills during the past several decades.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7218-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7218_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 18:54:17">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=41B2BC72F6381A94B0EE30351D88CEE4?doi=10.1.1.262.2438&amp;rank=7</link><title>Slice sampling</title><description>Slice sampling

by Radford M. Neal \- Annals of Statistics , 2000

"... Carlo or other dynamical methods (Duane, Kennedy, Pendleton, and Roweth 1987; Horowitz 1991; Neal 1994 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 147 (5 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract. Markov chain sampling methods that automatically adapt to characteristics of the distribution being sampled can be constructed by exploiting the principle that one can sample from a distribution by sampling uniformly from the region under the plot of its density function. A Markov chain that converges to this uniform distribution can be constructed by alternating uniform sampling in the vertical direction with uniform sampling from the horizontal ‘slice ’ defined by the current vertical position, or more generally, with some update that leaves the uniform distribution over this slice invariant. Variations on such ‘slice sampling ’ methods are easily implemented for univariate distributions, and can be used to sample from a multivariate distribution by updating each variable in turn. This approach is often easier to implement than Gibbs sampling, and more efficient than simple Metropolis updates, due to the ability of slice sampling to adaptively choose the magnitude of changes made. It is therefore attractive for routine and automated use. Slice sampling methods that update all variables simultaneously are also possible. These methods can adaptively choose the magnitudes of changes made to each variable, based on the local properties of the density function. More ambitiously, such methods could potentially allow the sampling to adapt to dependencies between variables by constructing local quadratic approximations. Another approach is to improve sampling efficiency by suppressing random walks. This can be done using ‘overrelaxed ’ versions of univariate slice sampling procedures, or by using ‘reflective ’ multivariate slice sampling methods, which bounce off the edges of the slice.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7218-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7218_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 18:54:40">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=41B2BC72F6381A94B0EE30351D88CEE4?doi=10.1.1.38.2212&amp;rank=8</link><title>Texture Modification of the Shuttle Landing Facility Runway at Kennedy Space Center</title><description>Texture Modification of the Shuttle Landing Facility Runway at Kennedy Space Center

by Robert Daugherty And, Robert H. Daugherty, Thomas J. Yager

"... -0001 NASA Technical Paper 3626 Texture Modification of the Shuttle Landing Facility Runway at Kennedy Space ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

this report is for</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7218-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7218_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 18:54:57">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=41B2BC72F6381A94B0EE30351D88CEE4?doi=10.1.1.362.1963&amp;rank=9</link><title>John Kenneth Galbraith (#78) An Inventory of His Personal Papers At the John F. Kennedy Library</title><description>John Kenneth Galbraith (#78) An Inventory of His Personal Papers At the John F. Kennedy Library

by The John, F. Kennedy

"... Morris Udall (1976) and Senator Edward Kennedy (1980). Though he eventually broke with President Lyndon B ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

www.jfklibrary.org</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7218-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7218_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 18:55:15">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=41B2BC72F6381A94B0EE30351D88CEE4?doi=10.1.1.178.6617&amp;rank=10</link><title>Charles Nelson, Bureau of the Census Edward Welniak Jr., Bureau of the Census</title><description>Charles Nelson, Bureau of the Census Edward Welniak Jr., Bureau of the Census

by Joan Turek, Department Of Health, Human Services

"... and Human Services Fritz Scheuren, NORC University of Chicago Charles Nelson, Bureau of the Census Edward ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

The Annual Social and Economic Supplement (ASEC) to the Current Population Survey (CPS) is the source of official Federal statistics on poverty 2. U.S. poverty estimates based on the poverty thresholds originally developed by Molly Orshansky of the Social Security Administration in 1963-1964 3 are published annually.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>