<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7242">hague convention</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:00:10" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7242-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7242_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:00:12">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=C7BCB97948B9556DF65FF66B89DC7042?doi=10.1.1.153.186&amp;rank=1</link><title>of Parties in The Hague?</title><description>of Parties in The Hague?

by unknown authors

"... at the forthcoming 6 th UNFCCC Conference of Parties in The Hague? An analysis of current climate negotiations ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

6 th UNFCCC Conference</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7242-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7242_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:00:29">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=C7BCB97948B9556DF65FF66B89DC7042?doi=10.1.1.183.1893&amp;rank=2</link><title>The Hague, the Netherlands</title><description>The Hague, the Netherlands

by unknown authors

"... , 2010 The Hague, the Netherlands File No: 2620-107 Publications: http ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

EMCDDA–Europol joint publications</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7242-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7242_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:00:49">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=C7BCB97948B9556DF65FF66B89DC7042?doi=10.1.1.169.2299&amp;rank=3</link><title>Design Corps, The Hague</title><description>Design Corps, The Hague

by Photography Cover Margret Verwijk

"... /SB Printing OBT bv, The Hague Design Corps, The Hague Lay-out Eindeloos, The Hague Photography cover Margret ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Taking a stand for women, peace and securityDutch National Action Plan on Resolution 1325 Taking a stand for women, peace and security2 Policy Department DSI/SB</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7242-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7242_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:01:08">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=C7BCB97948B9556DF65FF66B89DC7042?doi=10.1.1.186.1590&amp;rank=4</link><title>iii</title><description>iii

by Jeffrey L. Edleson, Ph. D, Gita Mehrotra M. S. W, William Vesneski, Luz Lopez Ph. D, Sudha Shetty Esq

"... position or policies of the U.S. Department of Justice. Final Report: Hague Convention and Domestic ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

.S. Department of Justice. Final Report: &lt;em&gt;Hague&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Convention&lt;/em&gt; and Domestic Violence Page i of 404 Multiple</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7242-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7242_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:01:30">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=C7BCB97948B9556DF65FF66B89DC7042?doi=10.1.1.400.4706&amp;rank=5</link><title>16 th Annual Meeting at The Hague</title><description>16 th Annual Meeting at The Hague

by Jeroen Guinée, Lauran Van Oers, Arjan De Koning, Wil Tamis, Jeroen Guinée, Lauran Van Oers, Arjan De Koning, Wil Tamis, The Netherlands

"... Approaches for Conservation Agriculture on 8 May 2006 at the SETAC-Europe 16 th Annual Meeting at The Hague ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Please mention report number, and name and address to whom the report is to be sent. Concurrent spreadsheets can be downloaded from</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7242-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7242_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:01:48">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=C7BCB97948B9556DF65FF66B89DC7042?doi=10.1.1.353.6871&amp;rank=6</link><title>Design Corps, The Hague Cover design Eindeloos, The Hague Lay-out Eindeloos, The Hague Cover</title><description>Design Corps, The Hague Cover design Eindeloos, The Hague Lay-out Eindeloos, The Hague Cover

by Ordercode Osdr /e

"... Water Supply and Sanitation Programmes Shinyanga Region, Tanzania 1990-2006Printing OBT, The Hague ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

www.minbuza.nl/iob</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7242-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7242_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:02:08">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=C7BCB97948B9556DF65FF66B89DC7042?doi=10.1.1.197.7477&amp;rank=7</link><title>The Economics of a Lost Deal: Kyoto- The Hague\- Marrakesh</title><description>The Economics of a Lost Deal: Kyoto- The Hague\- Marrakesh

by Jean-charles Hourcade, Frédéric Ghersi, Jean-charles Hourcade, Frédéric Ghersi, Jean-charles Hourcade, Frédéric Ghersi

"... ﻿The Economics of a Lost Deal : Kyoto - The Hague \- Marrakesh Jean-Charles Hourcade Frédéric Ghersi ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper examines prospects for compromise between competing perspectives on four key climate change issues: costs, level of domestic action, environmental integrity, and developing world involvement. It focuses on the policy issues stemming from the uncertainty about abatement costs. Based on extensive simulations of a model integration tool, SAP12 (Stochastic Assessment of Climate Policies, 12 models), the analysis considers options for finetuning the Kyoto Protocol, such as concrete ceilings or levies on carbon imports; "environmental restoration payments " to be made on excess emissions; and credits for sequestration activities in Annex B countries. It demonstrates that the restoration payment (implemented through a safety valve) emerges as a superior means of addressing the cost uncertainty issue. The paper concludes that had this approach been taken at the COP6 climate negotiations, there would have been substantial room for compromise on payments of $35 to $100 per ton of carbon. Examining the Marrakech climate accord, it derives some lessons for attempts at completing Kyoto's unfinished business or at moving on to a new framework.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7242-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7242_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:02:28">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=C7BCB97948B9556DF65FF66B89DC7042?doi=10.1.1.7.8007&amp;rank=8</link><title>September 12-15, 1999, The Hague, The Netherlands</title><description>September 12-15, 1999, The Hague, The Netherlands

by Smart Load Cells, J. H. Correia, J. G. Rocha, C. Couto

"... , The Hague, The Netherlands Smart Load Cells: an Industrial Application J. H. Correia, J. G. Rocha, C. Couto ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

This paper describes a data acquisition solution using a single-chip RISC type microcontroller with very few other active and passive components around, taking advantage of the ratiometric functioning of the load cells. The need for thermally stable circuits and components is minimized through the use of the same amplification chain for both signal and reference, together with software calibration. The amplification and filtering is done through switched-capacitors techniques, controlled by the microcontroller. Moreover, this option allows the choice of the proper scale according to the platform, with periodically and automatically calibration. The analog-to-digital conversion is done using the single ramp approach controlled by the microcontroller, which does all the digital processing required as well the external transmission of the data for a local network following the nine-bit protocol. The conversion time was around 13 ms. For an industrial platform of 8 smart load cells the weighing tests show errors below 100 gr. in 400 kg. The paper also describes an example of software calibration of a multi-load cell weighbridge using one processor per smart load cell</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7242-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7242_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:02:48">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=C7BCB97948B9556DF65FF66B89DC7042?doi=10.1.1.218.174&amp;rank=9</link><title>SPB Academic Publishing bv, The Hague A</title><description>SPB Academic Publishing bv, The Hague A

by Byron T. Kesner, Vernon Meentemeyer

"... ﻿Landscape Ecology vol. 2 no. 3 pp 151-163 (1989) SPB Academic Publishing bv, The Hague A regional ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

regional analysis of total nitrogen in an agricultural landscape</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7242-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7242_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:03:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=C7BCB97948B9556DF65FF66B89DC7042?doi=10.1.1.422.6827&amp;rank=10</link><title>Convention on the Conservation of European Wildlife and Habitats (Bern Convention)</title><description>Convention on the Conservation of European Wildlife and Habitats (Bern Convention)

by Piero Genovesi, Clare Shine, Council Europe, Publishing French

"... of the Parties to the CBD, The Hague, April 2002) CMS Convention on the Conservation of Migratory Species of Wild ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

on invasive alien species</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>