<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7252">welch corgi</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:30:21" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7252-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7252_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:30:24">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=63118B6CA584697758BE06805944C802?doi=10.1.1.29.1195&amp;rank=1</link><title>Question Answering in Webclopedia</title><description>Question Answering in Webclopedia

by Eduard Hovy, Laurie Gerber, Ulf Hermjakob, Michael Junk, Chin-yew Lin \- In Proceedings of the Ninth Text REtrieval Conference (TREC-9 , 2000

"... Welch, GE chairman... ... ...Chairman John Welch said ...GE ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 88 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

SHAPE ADJECTIVE COLOR DISEASE TEXT NARRATIVE* GENERAL-INFO DEFINITION USE EXPRESSION-ORIGIN HISTORY WHY-FAMOUS BIO ANTECEDENT INFLUENCE CONSEQUENT CAUSE-EFFECT METHOD-MEANS CIRCUMSTANCE-MEANS REASON EVALUATION PRO-CON CONTRAST RATING COUNSEL-ADVICE 6 To create the QA Typology, we analyzed 17,384 questions and their answers (downloaded from answers.com); see (Gerber, 2001). The Typology contains 94 nodes, of which 47 are leaf nodes; a section of it appears in Figure 2. Each Typology node has been annotated with examples and typical patterns of expression of both Question and Answer, as indicated in Figure 3 for Proper-Person. Question examples Question templates Who was Johnny Mathis' high school track coach? who be &lt;entity&gt;'s &lt;role&gt; Who was Lincoln's Secretary of State? Who was President of Turkmenistan in 1994? who be &lt;role&gt; of &lt;entity&gt; Who is the composer of Eugene Onegin? Who is the CEO of General Electric? Actual answers Answer templates Lou Vasquez, track ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7252-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7252_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:30:41">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=63118B6CA584697758BE06805944C802?doi=10.1.1.22.8952&amp;rank=2</link><title>Question Answering in Webclopedia</title><description>Question Answering in Webclopedia

by Eduard Hovy Laurie, Laurie Gerber, Ulf Hermjakob, Michael Junk, Chin-yew Lin \- In Proceedings of the Ninth Text REtrieval Conference (TREC-9 , 2000

"... Welch, GE chairman... ... ...Chairman John Welch said ...GE ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

SHAPE ADJECTIVE COLOR DISEASE TEXT NARRATIVE* GENERAL-INFO DEFINITION USE EXPRESSION-ORIGIN HISTORY WHY-FAMOUS BIO ANTECEDENT INFLUENCE CONSEQUENT CAUSE-EFFECT METHOD-MEANS CIRCUMSTANCE-MEANS REASON EVALUATION PRO-CON CONTRAST RATING COUNSEL-ADVICE To create the QA Typology, we analyzed 17,384 questions and their answers (downloaded from answers.com); see (Gerber, 2001). The Typology contains 94 nodes, of which 47 are leaf nodes; a section of it appears in Figure 2. Each Typology node has been annotated with examples and typical patterns of expression of both Question and Answer, as indicated in Figure 3 for Proper-Person. Question examples Question templates Who was Johnny Mathis' high school track coach? who be &lt;entity&gt;'s &lt;role&gt; Who was Lincoln's Secretary of State? Who was President of Turkmenistan in 1994? who be &lt;role&gt; of &lt;entity&gt; Who is the composer of Eugene Onegin? Who is the CEO of General Electric? Actual answers Answer templates Lou Vasquez, track coa...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>