<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7261">elvish language</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:55:05" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7261-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7261_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:55:07">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=456F53F5AF959C46868C42C84287DA68?doi=10.1.1.343.1599&amp;rank=1</link><title>representations and scalable machine learning algorithms.</title><description>representations and scalable machine learning algorithms.

by The Sparseptron, A. Smith, André F. T. Martins

"... ﻿feature Linguistic Structure Prediction with the Sparseptron Recent advances in natural language ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

&lt;em&gt;languages&lt;/em&gt; (NLs), like English, are full of ambiguity (unlike programming &lt;em&gt;languages&lt;/em&gt;, which are designed</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7261-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7261_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:55:26">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=456F53F5AF959C46868C42C84287DA68?doi=10.1.1.16.5342&amp;rank=2</link><title>Metaphors of Movement -- A User Interface for Manipulating Time-Oriented, Skeletal Plans</title><description>Metaphors of Movement -- A User Interface for Manipulating Time-Oriented, Skeletal Plans

by Robert Kosara , 1999

"... to be identified correctly). Part I Problem Analysis 3 Chapter 2 The Language Asbru The letters are Elvish ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 7 (5 self) \- Add to MetaCart

of timeoriented, This user interface is called AsbruView, and is based on the plan representation &lt;em&gt;language&lt;/em&gt; Asbru</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7261-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7261_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:55:47">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=456F53F5AF959C46868C42C84287DA68?doi=10.1.1.158.5574&amp;rank=3</link><title>Local Community Identification in Social Networks</title><description>Local Community Identification in Social Networks

by Jiyang Chen, Osmar R. Zaïane, Y Goebel

"... # ... Grammar of an Elvish Language from LoR # J.R.R. Tolkien Companion and Guide # The Rise of Tolkienian ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 3 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

There has been much recent research on identifying global community structure in networks. However, most existing approaches require complete information of the graph in question, which is impractical for some networks, e.g. the World Wide Web (WWW). Algorithms for local community detection have been proposed but their results usually contain many outliers. In this paper, we propose a new measure of local community structure, coupled with a two-phase algorithm that extracts all possible candidates first, and then optimizes the community hierarchy. We compare our results with previous methods on real world networks such as the co-purchase network from Amazon. Experimental results verify the feasibility and effectiveness of our approach. 1.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7261-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7261_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:56:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=456F53F5AF959C46868C42C84287DA68?doi=10.1.1.393.2688&amp;rank=4</link><title>Do nonlinguists practice linguistics? An anti-eliminative approach to folk theories</title><description>Do nonlinguists practice linguistics? An anti-eliminative approach to folk theories

by Marie-anne Paveau

"... by virtue of having invented fictional languages, including the much celebrated Elvish language. A similar ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

‗Oh, stop calling me Madam, it‘s so annoying! Henever says the things I want to hear,he only saysthings that get on my nerves ‘ (a second-hand goods dealer, Paris, September 2008, 20 th arrondissement; translated from the French)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7261-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7261_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:56:26">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=456F53F5AF959C46868C42C84287DA68?doi=10.1.1.97.2637&amp;rank=5</link><title>Connecting Worlds. Fantasy Role-Playing Games, Ritual Acts and the Magic Circle</title><description>Connecting Worlds. Fantasy Role-Playing Games, Ritual Acts and the Magic Circle

by Drs Marinka Copier \- Proc. DIGRA 2005 Conference: Changing Views – Worlds in Play , 2005

"... were even programmed with an optional "Elvish" font […].” [7, Stanford University 1976] Therefore ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 7 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

From a cultural history and game theoretical perspective my work focuses on the relationship between the fantasy subculture, fantasy role-playing games and the daily life of their participants in the Netherlands. Main research themes are the construction of game/play space and identities. Within this context I elaborate in this paper on the usefulness of the term magic circle (Johan Huizinga). I will argue why in game research the current use of the term magic circle is problematic. We can understand the term differently when returning to the context in which Huizinga introduced the magic circle as ritual play-ground. According to him ritual is play and play is ritual. Referring back to his work Homo Ludens (1938) I will discuss the various relationships between role-play and ritual performance. I will argue that fantasy role-playing consists of collections of performances or ritual acts, in which players construct the game/play space, identities and meaning. Keywords</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7261-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7261_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:56:43">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=456F53F5AF959C46868C42C84287DA68?doi=10.1.1.379.9170&amp;rank=6</link><title>Address for correspondence:</title><description>Address for correspondence:

by Iris Berent, Gila Ghavami, Samantha Murphy, Iris Berent

"... , plural of loovk) and regular plurals whose phonological form is attested in the language, hence ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

in the &lt;em&gt;language&lt;/em&gt;, hence, relatively frequent (e.g., loonks). Despite the rarity of their sound patterns</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7261-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7261_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:57:01">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=456F53F5AF959C46868C42C84287DA68?doi=10.1.1.114.8873&amp;rank=7</link><title>The naming system venture</title><description>The naming system venture

by Hans Reiser , 2001

"... considered that languages sometimes convey structure by word endings (tags), and sometimes by word order ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

For too long the file system has been semantically impoverished in comparison with database and keyword systems. It is time to change! The current lack of features makes it much easier to use the latest set theoretic models rather than older models of relational algebra or hypertext. The current file system syntax fits nicely into the newer model. The utility of an operating system is more proportional to the number of connections possible between its components than it is to the number of those components. Namespace fragmentation is the most important determinant of that number of possible connections between OS components. Unix at its beginning increased the strategy. Let’s take the file system namespace, and one-by-one eliminate the reasons why the filesystem is inadequate for what other namespaces are used for, one missing feature at a time. Only once we have done so will the hobbles be removed from OS architects, or even OS conspiracies. Yet before doing that, we need a core architecture for the semantics to ensure we end up with a coherent whole. This paper suggests a set theoretic model for those semantics. The relational models would at times unacceptably add structure to information, the keyword models would at times delete structure, and purely hierarchical models would create information mazes. Reworking their primitives is required to synthesize the best attributes of these models in a way that allows one the flexibility to tailor the level of structure to the need of the moment. The set theoretic model I propose has a syntax that is Linux, MacOS, and DOS file system syntax upwardly compatible, as well as CORBA naming layer upwardly compatible. This is a planning document for the next major version of ReiserFS, that is, a description of vaporware. It is useful to ReiserFS users and contributors who want to know where we are going, and why we are building all sorts of strange optimizations into the storage layer (and especially those who are willing to help shape the vision in the course of discussions on the reiserfs-list@namesys.com mailing list...). Currently the storage layer for ReiserFS is working and useful as an everyday FS with conventional semantics. That storage layer is available as a GPL’d Linux kernel patch at</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7261-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7261_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:57:19">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=456F53F5AF959C46868C42C84287DA68?doi=10.1.1.370.2224&amp;rank=8</link><title>‘Theory’, ‘Practice ’ and Imagination in the Creative Industries</title><description>‘Theory’, ‘Practice ’ and Imagination in the Creative Industries

by unknown authors

"... languages such as klingon or elvish are usually regarded as merely fodder for sociologists, who treat them ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

In this brief paper, I would like to discuss new forms of the imagination and the relation between intellectual practices and other forms of practice, particularly those in the artistic and creative arena and how these might operate within the new setting of the Creative Industries project at QUT. I might emphasise that rather than offering any directly practical nuts and bolts suggestions, I simply want to offer a few frameworks and ideas for reflection. I will begin by noting a change in the way we currently structure relations between imagination, rational knowledge and other social activity. I will then go on to explain what exactly I mean by ‘practice ’ and the capacity of this definition to do away with traditional hierarchical distinctions between theory and practice. Thirdly, I will like Stuart Cunningham in the second session in this series draw a distinction between the cultural industries and the creative industries ‐ but from quite a different angle. Fourthly, I shall detail the emergence of new forms of imagination in the Western industrialised world and make some general suggestions about how the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7261-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7261_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 20:57:37">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=456F53F5AF959C46868C42C84287DA68?doi=10.1.1.379.3769&amp;rank=9</link><title>Phonological familiarity or</title><description>Phonological familiarity or

by Iris Berent, Steven Pinker

"... , inflection, morphology, phonology In explaining patterns of language, it is virtually impossible to avoid ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

The dislike of regular plurals in compounds</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>