<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7274">detroit riot</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 21:26:23" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7274-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7274_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 21:26:25">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8D8ED6C2097DD7358521DD456CEA898B?doi=10.1.1.194.5212&amp;rank=1</link><title>The Labor Market Effects of the 1960s Riots</title><description>The Labor Market Effects of the 1960s Riots

by William J. Collins, Robert A. Margo, William J. Collins, Robert A. Margo, William J. Collins \- Brookings-Wharton Papers on Urban Affairs, 2004. Washington D.C., The Brookings Institution , 2004

"... of the 1960s. There were close to 50 riots in that year, including one in Detroit in which 34 people were ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 3 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Market Effects of the 1960s &lt;em&gt;Riots&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7274-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7274_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 21:26:43">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8D8ED6C2097DD7358521DD456CEA898B?doi=10.1.1.197.7833&amp;rank=2</link><title>www.vanderbilt.edu/econ The Labor Market Effects of the 1960s Riots</title><description>www.vanderbilt.edu/econ The Labor Market Effects of the 1960s Riots

by William J. Collins, Robert A. Margo, William J. Collins, Robert A. Margo, Ilyana Kuziemko, Deirdre Mccloskey, Daniel Myers, Janet Pack, Jasmin Sethi, Seymour Spilerman , 2003

"... , and although the riot was not as severe as Detroit’s in terms of fatalities, looting and property destruction ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

of &lt;em&gt;riots&lt;/em&gt; erupted in American cities, resulting in large numbers of injuries, deaths, and arrests, as well</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7274-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7274_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 21:27:02">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8D8ED6C2097DD7358521DD456CEA898B?doi=10.1.1.420.1299&amp;rank=3</link><title>Changes in the Segregation of Whites from Blacks during the 1980s: Small Steps toward a More Racially Integrated Society</title><description>Changes in the Segregation of Whites from Blacks during the 1980s: Small Steps toward a More Racially Integrated Society

by Reynolds Farley, William H. Frey, Reynolds Farley, William H. Frey \- Center. The University of Michigan , 1992

"... segregated from whites in Detroit and Chicago than they are in Sacramento or Riverside?). This approach ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 37 (5 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Residential segregation between blacks and whites persists in urban America. However; evidence from the 1990 Census suggests that peak segregation levels were reached in the past. We evaluate segregation patterns in 1990 and trends in segregation between 1980 and 1990 for the 232 U.S. metropolitan areas with substantial black populations. We review the historical forces that intensified segregation for much of the twentieth century, and identify key developments after 1960 that challenged institutionalized segregation. The results suggest that the modest declines in segregation observed during the 1970s continued through the 1980s. While segregation decreased in most metropolitan areas, the magnitude of these changes was uneven. Testing hypotheses developed from an ecological model, we find that the lowest segregation levels in 1990 and the largest percentage decreases in segregation scores between 1980 and 1990 occurred in young, southern and western metropolitan areas with significant recent housing construction. Because the black population continues to migrate to such areas, residential segregation between blacks and whites should decline further; but remain well above that for Hispanics or Asians.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7274-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7274_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 21:27:23">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8D8ED6C2097DD7358521DD456CEA898B?doi=10.1.1.196.3231&amp;rank=4</link><title>Planned abandonment: the neighborhood life-cycle theory and national urban policy. Housing Policy Debate 11(1</title><description>Planned abandonment: the neighborhood life-cycle theory and national urban policy. Housing Policy Debate 11(1

by John T. Metzger

"... of Housing and Urban Development after the urban riots of the 1960s and used by local planners to encourage ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 6 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

after the urban &lt;em&gt;riots&lt;/em&gt; of the 1960s and used by local planners to encourage the “deliberate dispersal</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7274-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7274_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 21:27:41">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8D8ED6C2097DD7358521DD456CEA898B?doi=10.1.1.204.3528&amp;rank=5</link><title>SEPTEMBER 1992 APUBUCAnON OF DOW JONES &amp; COMPANY INC. Boomi~g, Suburban, and</title><description>SEPTEMBER 1992 APUBUCAnON OF DOW JONES &amp; COMPANY INC. Boomi~g, Suburban, and

by William P, William H. Frey, New Orleans Parish, Demographics William, H. Frey, Auanta Ga, Newaltl Nt

"... to wealthy, and so do their neighborhoods. Most ofthe people who live in riot-torn South Central Los Angeles ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

people who live in &lt;em&gt;riot&lt;/em&gt;-torn South Central Los Angeles are black, for example, but blacks are also a</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7274-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7274_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 21:27:54">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8D8ED6C2097DD7358521DD456CEA898B?doi=10.1.1.13.4162&amp;rank=6</link><title>International Conference on Engineering Education August 18--21, 2002, Manchester, U.K.</title><description>International Conference on Engineering Education August 18--21, 2002, Manchester, U.K.

by Engineering Education Coalitions, Donald R. Falkenburg , 2002

"... of programs to underpin its educational objectives. Founded in 1968 after the urban riots in Detroit ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

to intelligent and practical action to overcome racism, poverty and injustice in &lt;em&gt;Detroit&lt;/em&gt; and its suburbs). Funded</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7274-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7274_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 21:28:13">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8D8ED6C2097DD7358521DD456CEA898B?doi=10.1.1.310.6&amp;rank=7</link><title>Do Local Economic Development Programs Work? Evidence from the Federal Empowerment Zone Program,” unpublished manuscript</title><description>Do Local Economic Development Programs Work? Evidence from the Federal Empowerment Zone Program,” unpublished manuscript

by Matias Busso, Patrick Kline, Matias Busso, Patrick Kline , 2007

"... Los Angeles riots. In 1993, Congress authorized the creation of a series of Empowerment Zones ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 11 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper evaluates the impact of Round I of the federal urban Empowerment Zone (EZ) program on neighborhood level labor and housing market outcomes over the period 1994-2000. Using four decades of Census data in conjunction with information on the proposed boundaries of rejected EZs, we find that neighborhoods receiving EZ designation experienced substantial improvements in labor market conditions and moderate increases in rents relative to rejected and future zones. These effects were accompanied by small changes in the demographic composition of the neighborhoods, though evidence from disaggregate Census tabulations suggests that these changes account for little of the observed improvements.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7274-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7274_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 21:28:35">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8D8ED6C2097DD7358521DD456CEA898B?doi=10.1.1.162.2255&amp;rank=8</link><title>Did the Introduction of Food Stamps Affect Birth Outcomes in California?</title><description>Did the Introduction of Food Stamps Affect Birth Outcomes in California?

by Janet Currie , 2006

"... , products not generally included in the surplus commodities program. For example, families in Detroit ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 7 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7274-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7274_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 21:28:51">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8D8ED6C2097DD7358521DD456CEA898B?doi=10.1.1.376.4341&amp;rank=9</link><title>Evaluating Claims Costs Arising Out of Political Disorder and Civil Unrest</title><description>Evaluating Claims Costs Arising Out of Political Disorder and Civil Unrest

by George Maher

"... interruption claims. Riots clearly have caused, in many cases, very substantial loss of life. However, coverage ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

As insurers go global, they become more exposed to losses arising from political unrest and terrorist activity. Historically, while many of these exposures were excluded, there is increasing pressure to include them or provide alternative arrangements. Reinsurers are also taking a broader approach to coverages in this area. This paper discmses coverage issues and ways of estimating PML's, as well as the review of underlying conditions and capital reqtfircments necessary to absorb catastrophe claims. This is done by considering the type of political unrest that is likely to arise in different territories and veq, large claims or claims of a catastrophic nature. It also discusses techniques for cvahmting both tile frequency and severity of such claims. The paper also refers to other financing techniques of the way the reinsurance programmes [nay bc structured to be cost effective in this area. Some other practical issues are also introduced. The paper builds on the authors ' experience of working with a number of specialist companies operating in these types of areas. Hntroduc~ion</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7274-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7274_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 21:29:08">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8D8ED6C2097DD7358521DD456CEA898B?doi=10.1.1.41.2955&amp;rank=10</link><title>Baseball, Optimization and the World Wide Web</title><description>Baseball, Optimization and the World Wide Web

by Ilan Adler, Alan L. Erera, Dorit S. Hochbaum, Eli V. Olinick , 1999

"... 1: RIOT Web site declares Giants eliminated from first place on 9/8/96. The optimization community ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 2 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The competition for baseball playoff spots -- the fabled "pennant race" -- is one of the most closely-watched American sports traditions. Baseball fans, known for their love of statistics, check newspapers and web sites daily looking for measures of their team's progress (or lack thereof !). While traditionally-reported playoff race statistics such as games back and "magic number" are informative, they are overly conservative and ignore the remaining schedule of games. By using optimization techniques, one can model schedule effects explicitly and determine when a team has locked up a playoff spot or is truly "mathematically eliminated" from contention. This paper describes the Baseball Playoff Races web site, a popular site developed at Berkeley that provides automatic daily updates of new, optimization-based playoff race statistics. During the development of the site, it was found that the first-place elimination status of all teams in a division can be determined using a single linear prog...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>