<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7293">basil recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:17:13" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7293-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7293_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:17:14">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=30064FCBD7B753B3A9A20F395C644749?doi=10.1.1.421.3486&amp;rank=1</link><title>Recipe recommendation using ingredient networks</title><description>Recipe recommendation using ingredient networks

by Chun-yuen Teng, Yu-ru Lin, Lada A. Adamic

"... chicken with basil dressing”, chicken is assigned a higher weight than basil. Instead of modeling recipes ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

The recording and sharing of cooking &lt;em&gt;recipes&lt;/em&gt;, a human activity dating back thousands of years</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7293-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7293_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:17:33">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=30064FCBD7B753B3A9A20F395C644749?doi=10.1.1.139.3528&amp;rank=2</link><title>INDIVIDUAL DIFFERENCES AND THEIR IMPLICATIONS FOR THEORIES OF LANGUAGE DEVELOPMENT</title><description>INDIVIDUAL DIFFERENCES AND THEIR IMPLICATIONS FOR THEORIES OF LANGUAGE DEVELOPMENT

by Elizabeth Bates, Philip S. Dale, Donna Thal

"... . Oxford: Basil Blackwell, 1995. Like every other aspect of human development, language development ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 45 (6 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7293-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7293_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:17:45">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=30064FCBD7B753B3A9A20F395C644749?doi=10.1.1.193.2750&amp;rank=3</link><title>Good Stuff from Our Kitchen</title><description>Good Stuff from Our Kitchen

by Lee C. Adkins, Kathy Adkins, Lee C. Adkins

"... and bottle washer) wanted to write down all of the commonly used recipes that have been gathering in our ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

) and I (head cook and bottle washer) wanted to write down all of the commonly used &lt;em&gt;recipes&lt;/em&gt; that have been</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7293-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7293_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:18:00">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=30064FCBD7B753B3A9A20F395C644749?doi=10.1.1.405.3257&amp;rank=4</link><title>First-Person Cooking: A DualPerspective Interactive Kitchen Counter</title><description>First-Person Cooking: A DualPerspective Interactive Kitchen Counter

by Sarah Mennicken, Thorsten Karrer, Peter Russell \- In Ext. Ab. CHI 2010, ACM , 2010

"... @(email omitted); Abstract Hobby chefs have various ways to learn cooking—paper recipes or cooking shows, for example ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 3 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Hobby chefs have various ways to learn cooking—paper &lt;em&gt;recipes&lt;/em&gt; or cooking shows, for example. However</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7293-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7293_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:18:17">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=30064FCBD7B753B3A9A20F395C644749?doi=10.1.1.174.3580&amp;rank=5</link><title>Strength Is Ignorance; Slavery Is Freedom: Managing Culture in Modern Organizations</title><description>Strength Is Ignorance; Slavery Is Freedom: Managing Culture in Modern Organizations

by Hugh Willmott \- Journal of Management Studies , 1993

"... , UK . © Basil Blackwell Ltd 1993 . Published by Blackwell Publishers, 108 Cowley Road, Oxford OX4 UF ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 36 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The article subjects the assumptions and prescriptions of the 'Corporate Culture ' literature to critical scrutiny. The body of the article is devoted to teasing out the distinctive basis of its appeal compared with earlier management theory. It is seen to build upon earlier efforts (e.g. 'theory Y') to constitute a self-disciplining form of employee subjectivity by asserting that 'practical autonomy ' is conditional upon the development of a strong corporate culture. The paper illuminates the dark side of this project by drawing attention to the subjugating and totalitarian implications of its excellence/ quality prescriptions. To this end, parallels are drawn with the philosophy ofcontrol favoured by the Party in Orwell's Nineteen Eighty-Four. Specifically, the paper critiques the 'doublethink ' contention that autonomy can be realized in monocultural conditions that systematically constrain opportunities to wrestle with competing values standpoints and their associated life projects.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7293-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7293_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:18:31">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=30064FCBD7B753B3A9A20F395C644749?doi=10.1.1.416.449&amp;rank=6</link><title>Learning user tastes: a first step to generating healthy meal plans?</title><description>Learning user tastes: a first step to generating healthy meal plans?

by Morgan Harvey, Bernd Ludwig, David Elsweiler

"... key factors contributing to how recipes are rated by analysing the results of a longterm study (n=123 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

that people will like. In this work we investigate key factors contributing to how &lt;em&gt;recipes&lt;/em&gt; are rated</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7293-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7293_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:18:50">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=30064FCBD7B753B3A9A20F395C644749?doi=10.1.1.33.3129&amp;rank=7</link><title>Replication of Experimental Results in Software Engineering</title><description>Replication of Experimental Results in Software Engineering

by Andrew Brooks, John Daly, James Miller, Marc Roper, Murray Wood \- IEEE Transactions on Software Engineering , 1996

"... of any recipe-improving when attempting a replication and on the level of reported detail required, as a ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 25 (9 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Carrying out empirical studies is widely held to be of importance. A view less widely held is that experiments should be replicated externally to verify and validate the original results. This paper serves two main functions. First, the need for external replications is established. The role of replication in experimental software engineering is discussed. Without the confirming power of external replications, results in experimental software engineering should only be provisionally accepted, if at all. An extension to the framework for experimentation in software engineering by Basili et al [5] is proposed to differentiate between the various kinds of internal and external replication and their powers of confirmation and to allow a better appreciation of the context of a piece of empirical work. Second, this paper presents a concrete example of an external replication of an experiment which tested the benefits to maintenance of using modular code against non-modular (monolithic) code....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7293-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7293_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:19:11">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=30064FCBD7B753B3A9A20F395C644749?doi=10.1.1.393.7654&amp;rank=8</link><title>South of the Border Freshness Vegetarian Dishes of Latin America By</title><description>South of the Border Freshness Vegetarian Dishes of Latin America By

by Myrna Trejo Dedication

"... ” kitchen where you will find healthy and delicious meals just waiting for you. The recipes in this cookbook ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

where you will find healthy and delicious meals just waiting for you. The &lt;em&gt;recipes&lt;/em&gt; in</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7293-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7293_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:19:30">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=30064FCBD7B753B3A9A20F395C644749?doi=10.1.1.174.5107&amp;rank=9</link><title>English Almanacs and Animal Health Care in the Seventeenth Century</title><description>English Almanacs and Animal Health Care in the Seventeenth Century

by Louise Hill Curth , 2000

"... failed, readers could also obtain recipes for remedies and treatments in almanacs. Most people probably ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

. When such efforts failed, readers could also obtain &lt;em&gt;recipes&lt;/em&gt; for remedies and treatments in almanacs</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7293-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7293_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:19:43">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=30064FCBD7B753B3A9A20F395C644749?doi=10.1.1.36.944&amp;rank=10</link><title>Discourse with Disposable Computers: How and Why you will talk to your tomatoes</title><description>Discourse with Disposable Computers: How and Why you will talk to your tomatoes

by David Arnold, Bill Segall, Julian Boot, Andy Bond, Melfyn Lloyd, Simon Kaplan \- USENIX Workshop on Embedded Systems , 1999

"... recipes, select one, and check your pantry for the necessary ingredients. Your tomatoes have cheerfully ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 21 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Beyond ubiquitous computing, is the advent of disposable computing, occurring when the price of an embedded computer becomes insignificant compared to the cost of goods. Current software and network architectures and their associated programming paradigms will not scale to this new world. The necessity of catering for the constant change in number and type of devices of interest to a user, as well as their sheer quantity, dictates new approaches to construction of software systems based on more flexible models. We propose that distributed event notification forms a fundamental requirement for systems of this scale, and discuss the advantages of undirected communication over current interaction models. Our experience with Elvin, a prototype notification system motivates the discussion and serves as illustration of its possibilities.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>