<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7294">assumption of mary</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:20:03" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7294-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7294_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:20:04">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B199605CCE78060DF151A4F8D6844F84?doi=10.1.1.132.8548&amp;rank=1</link><title>Recognition-by-components: A theory of human image understanding</title><description>Recognition-by-components: A theory of human image understanding

by Irving Biederman \- Psychological Review , 1987

"... assumption of the proposed theory, recognition-by-components (RBC), is that a modest set of generalized ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 726 (11 self) \- Add to MetaCart

, such as blocks, cylinders, wedges, and cones. The fundamental &lt;em&gt;assumption&lt;/em&gt; of the proposed theory, recognition</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7294-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7294_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:20:18">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B199605CCE78060DF151A4F8D6844F84?doi=10.1.1.14.5868&amp;rank=2</link><title>The Generative Lexicon</title><description>The Generative Lexicon

by James Pustejovsky \- Computational Linguistics , 1991

"... would like to establish two basic assumptions that will figure prominently in my suggestions for a ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 919 (35 self) \- Add to MetaCart

this paper, I will discuss four major topics relating to current research in lexical semantics: methodology, descriptive coverage, adequacy of the representation, and the computational usefulness of representations. In addressing these issues, I will discuss what I think are some of the central problems facing the lexical semantics community, and suggest ways of best approaching these issues. Then, I will provide a method for the decomposition of lexical categories and outline a theory of lexical semantics embodying a notion of cocompositionality and type coercion, as well as several levels of semantic description, where the semantic load is spread more evenly throughout the lexicon. I argue that lexical decomposition is possible if it is performed generatively. Rather than assuming a fixed set of primitives, I will assume a fixed number of generative devices that can be seen as constructing semantic expressions. I develop a theory of Qualia Structure, a representation language for lexical items, which renders much lexical ambiguity in the lexicon unnecessary, while still explaining the systematic polysemy that words carry. Finally, I discuss how individual lexical structures can be integrated into the larger lexical knowledge base through a theory of lexical inheritance. This provides us with the necessary principles of global organization for the lexicon, enabling us to fully integrate our natural language lexicon into a conceptual whole</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7294-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7294_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:20:38">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B199605CCE78060DF151A4F8D6844F84?doi=10.1.1.130.4453&amp;rank=3</link><title>Using Bayesian networks to analyze expression data</title><description>Using Bayesian networks to analyze expression data

by Nir Friedman, Michal Linial, Iftach Nachman \- Journal of Computational Biology , 2000

"... ﻿JOURNAL OF COMPUTATIONAL BIOLOGY Volume 7, Numbers 3/4, 2000 Mary Ann Liebert, Inc. Pp. 601 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 731 (16 self) \- Add to MetaCart

DNA hybridization arrays simultaneously measure the expression level for thousands of genes. These measurements provide a “snapshot ” of transcription levels within the cell. A major challenge in computational biology is to uncover, from such measurements, gene/protein interactions and key biological features of cellular systems. In this paper, we propose a new framework for discovering interactions between genes based on multiple expression measurements. This framework builds on the use of Bayesian networks for representing statistical dependencies. A Bayesian network is a graph-based model of joint multivariate probability distributions that captures properties of conditional independence between variables. Such models are attractive for their ability to describe complex stochastic processes and because they provide a clear methodology for learning from (noisy) observations. We start by showing how Bayesian networks can describe interactions between genes. We then describe a method for recovering gene interactions from microarray data using tools for learning Bayesian networks. Finally, we demonstrate this method on the S. cerevisiae cell-cycle measurements of Spellman et al. (1998). Key words: gene expression, microarrays, Bayesian methods. 1.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7294-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7294_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:20:53">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B199605CCE78060DF151A4F8D6844F84?doi=10.1.1.32.9956&amp;rank=4</link><title>A Comparative Study on Feature Selection in Text Categorization</title><description>A Comparative Study on Feature Selection in Text Categorization

by Yiming Yang, Jan O. Pedersen , 1997

"... , will be computationally intractable unless an independence assumption (often not true) among features is imposed ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 947 (13 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper is a comparative study of feature selection methods in statistical learning of text categorization. The focus is on aggressive dimensionality reduction. Five methods were evaluated, including term selection based on document frequency (DF), information gain (IG), mutual information (MI), a Ø 2 -test (CHI), and term strength (TS). We found IG and CHI most effective in our experiments. Using IG thresholding with a knearest neighbor classifier on the Reuters corpus, removal of up to 98% removal of unique terms actually yielded an improved classification accuracy (measured by average precision) . DF thresholding performed similarly. Indeed we found strong correlations between the DF, IG and CHI values of a term. This suggests that DF thresholding, the simplest method with the lowest cost in computation, can be reliably used instead of IG or CHI when the computation of these measures are too expensive. TS compares favorably with the other methods with up to 50% vocabulary redu...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7294-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7294_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:21:08">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B199605CCE78060DF151A4F8D6844F84?doi=10.1.1.26.9108&amp;rank=5</link><title>CYC: A Large-Scale Investment in Knowledge Infrastructure</title><description>CYC: A Large-Scale Investment in Knowledge Infrastructure

by Douglas Lenat \- Communications of the ACM , 1995

"... , and millions more have been inferred and cached by CYC. This article examines the fundamental assumptions ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 688 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This article examines the fundamental</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7294-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7294_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:21:26">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B199605CCE78060DF151A4F8D6844F84?doi=10.1.1.54.7045&amp;rank=6</link><title>GOLOG: A Logic Programming Language for Dynamic Domains</title><description>GOLOG: A Logic Programming Language for Dynamic Domains

by Hector J. Levesque, Raymond Reiter, Yves Lespérance, Fangzhen Lin, Richard B. Scherl , 1994

"... in the successor situation. The solution to the frame problem of [23] rests on a completeness assumption, which ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 505 (65 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper proposes a new logic programming language called GOLOG whose interpreter automatically maintains an explicit representation of the dynamic world being modeled, on the basis of user supplied axioms about the preconditions and effects of actions and the initial state of the world. This allows programs to reason about the state of the world and consider the effects of various possible courses of action before committing to a particular behavior. The net effect is that programs may be written at a much higher level of abstraction than is usually possible. The language appears well suited for applications in high level control of robots and industrial processes, intelligent software agents, discrete event simulation, etc. It is based on a formal theory of action specified in an extended version of the situation calculus. A prototype implementation in Prolog has been developed.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7294-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7294_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:21:38">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B199605CCE78060DF151A4F8D6844F84?doi=10.1.1.33.2176&amp;rank=7</link><title>Wrapper Induction for Information Extraction</title><description>Wrapper Induction for Information Extraction

by Nicholas Kushmerick , 1997

"... . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . 166 7.5 Verifying Assumption 4.1: Short page fragments . . . . . . . . . . . . 166 7.6 Verifying ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 519 (30 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The Internet presents numerous sources of useful information---telephone directories, product catalogs, stock quotes, weather forecasts, etc. Recently, many systems have been built that automatically gather and manipulate such information on a user's behalf. However, these resources are usually formatted for use by people (e.g., the relevant content is embedded in HTML pages), so extracting their content is difficult. Wrappers are often used for this purpose. A wrapper is a procedure for extracting a particular resource's content. Unfortunately, hand-coding wrappers is tedious. We introduce wrapper induction, a technique for automatically constructing wrappers. Our techniques can be described in terms of three main contributions. First, we pose the problem of wrapper construction as one of inductive learn...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7294-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7294_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:21:58">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B199605CCE78060DF151A4F8D6844F84?doi=10.1.1.18.4016&amp;rank=8</link><title>Alignment by Maximization of Mutual Information</title><description>Alignment by Maximization of Mutual Information

by Paul A. Viola , 1995

"... of illumination. In our derivation, few assumptions are made about the natureofthe imaging process. As a result ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 751 (13 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7294-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7294_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:22:17">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B199605CCE78060DF151A4F8D6844F84?doi=10.1.1.212.5185&amp;rank=9</link><title>Using information content to evaluate semantic similarity in a taxonomy</title><description>Using information content to evaluate semantic similarity in a taxonomy

by Philip Resnik \- In Proceedings of the 14th International Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence (IJCAI-95 , 1995

"... sentences like Mary ate a pear and knows that peach and pear have similar behavior. The literature on corpus ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 731 (6 self) \- Add to MetaCart

philip.resnikfleast.sun.com This paper presents a new measure of semantic similarity in an IS-A taxonomy, based on the notion of information content. Experimental evaluation suggests that the measure performs encouragingly well (a correlation of r = 0.79 with a benchmark set of human similarity judgments, with an upper bound of r = 0.90 for human subjects performing the same task), and significantly better than the traditional edge counting approach (r = 0.66). 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7294-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7294_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 22:22:30">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B199605CCE78060DF151A4F8D6844F84?doi=10.1.1.42.559&amp;rank=10</link><title>Mitigating Routing Misbehavior in Mobile Ad Hoc Networks</title><description>Mitigating Routing Misbehavior in Mobile Ad Hoc Networks

by Sergio Marti, T. J. Giuli, Kevin Lai, Mary Baker \- INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON MOBILE COMPUTING AND NETWORKING , 2000

"... , and Mary Baker Department of Computer Science Stanford University Stanford, CA 94305 U.S.A {smarti ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 767 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper describes two techniques that improve throughput in an ad hoc network in the presence of nodes that agree to forward packets but fail to do so. To mitigate this problem, we propose categorizing nodes based upon their dynamically measured behavior. We use a watchdog that identies misbehaving nodes and a pathrater that helps routing protocols avoid these nodes. Through simulation we evaluate watchdog and pathrater using packet throughput, percentage of overhead (routing) transmissions, and the accuracy of misbehaving node detection. When used together in a network with moderate mobility, the two techniques increase throughput by 17% in the presence of 40% misbehaving nodes, while increasing the percentage of overhead transmissions from the standard routing protocol's 9% to 17%. During extreme mobility, watchdog and pathrater can increase network throughput by 27%, while increasing the overhead transmissions from the standard routing protocol's 12% to 24%.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>