<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7326">volcanoe eruption</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 23:31:33" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7326-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7326_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 23:31:34">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=769F42277EC77932F4CF6119C2901A3F?doi=10.1.1.262.761&amp;rank=1</link><title>Predictability of Volcano Eruption: lessons from a basaltic effusive volcano.</title><description>Predictability of Volcano Eruption: lessons from a basaltic effusive volcano.

by Jean-robert Grasso, Ilya Zaliapin , 2003

"... .data-an] 5 Dec 2003 Predictability of Volcano Eruption: lessons from a basaltic effusive volcano. Jean ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

&lt;em&gt;Volcano&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;eruption&lt;/em&gt; forecast remains a challenging and controversial problem despite the fact</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7326-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7326_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 23:31:47">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=769F42277EC77932F4CF6119C2901A3F?doi=10.1.1.294.7539&amp;rank=2</link><title>Volcano</title><description>Volcano

by Julien Chaput, Julien Chaput

"... eruptions is identified at Erebus volcano using a small dense array, thus demonstrating the satisfaction ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

scales. Works detailing high frequency coda-related seismic interferometry applied to Erebus &lt;em&gt;volcano&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7326-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7326_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 23:31:59">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=769F42277EC77932F4CF6119C2901A3F?doi=10.1.1.262.2440&amp;rank=3</link><title>Modeling eruptions of Karymsky volcano</title><description>Modeling eruptions of Karymsky volcano

by A. Ozerov, I. Ispolatov, J. Lees , 2001

"... ﻿Modeling eruptions of Karymsky volcano A. Ozerov ∗ , I. Ispolatov † , and J. Lees ¶ ∗ ...Russian ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Strombolian-type &lt;em&gt;volcanos&lt;/em&gt;. These patterns include major events (explosions) which follow each other every 10</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7326-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7326_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 23:32:19">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=769F42277EC77932F4CF6119C2901A3F?doi=10.1.1.330.9937&amp;rank=4</link><title>Fidelity and yield in a volcano monitoring sensor network</title><description>Fidelity and yield in a volcano monitoring sensor network

by Geoff Werner-allen, Konrad Lorincz, Jeff Johnson, Jonathan Lees, Matt Welsh \- In Proc. 7th USENIX Symposium on Operating Systems Design and Implementation (OSDI 2006 , 2006

"... ) to understand physical processes occurring within the volcano, such as magma migration and eruption mechanisms ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 169 (9 self) \- Add to MetaCart

, an active &lt;em&gt;volcano&lt;/em&gt; in Ecuador. Each of the 16 sensors continuously sampled seismic and acoustic data at 100</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7326-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7326_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 23:32:39">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=769F42277EC77932F4CF6119C2901A3F?doi=10.1.1.25.404&amp;rank=5</link><title>Interpretation and Utility of Infrasonic Records from Erupting Volcanoes</title><description>Interpretation and Utility of Infrasonic Records from Erupting Volcanoes

by J.B. Johnson, R.C. Aster, M.C. Ruiz , 2001

"... ﻿Interpretation and Utility of Infrasonic Records from Erupting Volcanoes submitted to JVGR October ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 4 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

respective &lt;em&gt;volcano&lt;/em&gt;. Finally we compare the infrasound records and &lt;em&gt;eruptive&lt;/em&gt; activity from these &lt;em&gt;volcanoes&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7326-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7326_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 23:32:52">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=769F42277EC77932F4CF6119C2901A3F?doi=10.1.1.333.1558&amp;rank=6</link><title>Exploring links between physical and probabilistic models of volcanic eruptions: The Soufrière</title><description>Exploring links between physical and probabilistic models of volcanic eruptions: The Soufrière

by C. B. Connor, R. S. J. Sparks, R. M. Mason, C. Bonadonna, S. R. Young

"... links between physical and probabilistic models of volcanic eruptions: The Soufrière Hills Volcano ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

of permeability and gas escape. Our experience with the Soufrière Hills &lt;em&gt;Volcano&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;eruption&lt;/em&gt; sequence suggests</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7326-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7326_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 23:33:11">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=769F42277EC77932F4CF6119C2901A3F?doi=10.1.1.232.3755&amp;rank=7</link><title>As the Turbine Turns... Jet Engines and Erupting Volcanos</title><description>As the Turbine Turns... Jet Engines and Erupting Volcanos

by Turbo Expo, Walter Dibartolomeo, Roland Fischer, Gary Mercer

"... -Sponsored University Research Program 53 Professional Development 54 As the Turbine Turns... Jet Engines and Erupting ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Vancouver are now available online at www.turboexpo.org! Early registration discount ends May 9. KEYNOTE SPEAKERS ANNOUNCED Three leaders from the aeroengine and power generation industry will highlight current development needs</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7326-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7326_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 23:33:24">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=769F42277EC77932F4CF6119C2901A3F?doi=10.1.1.88.3499&amp;rank=8</link><title>Deploying a wireless sensor network on an active volcano</title><description>Deploying a wireless sensor network on an active volcano

by Konrad Lorincz, Matt Welsh, Omar Marcillo, Jeff Johnson, Mario Ruiz, Jonathan Lees \- IEEE Internet Computing , 2006

"... the erupting volcano. In August 2005, we deployed a larger, more capable network on Volcán Reventador ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 142 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Augmenting heavy and power-hungry data collection equipment with lighter, smaller wireless sensor network nodes leads to faster,larger deployments. Arrays comprising dozens of wireless sensor nodes are now possible,allowing scientific studies that aren’t feasible with traditional instrumentation. Designing sensor networks to support volcanic studies requires addressing the high data rates and high data fidelity these studies demand. The authors ’ sensor-network application for volcanic data collection relies on triggered event detection and reliable data retrieval to meet bandwidth and data-quality demands. Wireless sensor networks — in which numerous resource-limited nodes are linked via low-bandwidth wireless radios — have been the focus of intense research during the past few years. Since their conception, they’ve excited a range of scientific communities because of their potential to facilitate data acquisition and scientific studies. Collaborations between computer scientists and other domain scientists have produced networks that can record data at a scale and resolution not previously possible. Taking this progress one step further, wireless sensor networks can potentially advance the pursuit of geophysical studies of volcanic activity. Two years ago, our team of computer scientists at Harvard University began collaborating with volcanologists at the University of North Carolina, the University of New Hampshire, and the Instituto</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7326-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7326_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 23:33:43">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=769F42277EC77932F4CF6119C2901A3F?doi=10.1.1.88.3793&amp;rank=9</link><title>Monitoring Volcanic Eruptions with a Wireless Sensor Network</title><description>Monitoring Volcanic Eruptions with a Wireless Sensor Network

by Geoffrey Werner-allen, Jeff Johnson, Mario Ruiz, Jonathan Lees, Matt Welsh \- in Proceedings of the Second European Workshop on Wireless Sensor Networks (EWSN’05 , 2005

"... structure of the volcano, and differentiate true eruptions from noise or other signals (e.g., mining ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 109 (7 self) \- Add to MetaCart

&lt;em&gt;eruptions&lt;/em&gt; with low-frequency acoustic sensors. We developed a wireless sensor array and deployed it in July</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7326-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7326_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 23:33:57">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=769F42277EC77932F4CF6119C2901A3F?doi=10.1.1.364.613&amp;rank=10</link><title>volcanic eruptions</title><description>volcanic eruptions

by Steven A. Ackerman, Anthony J. Schreiner, Timothy J. Schmit, Harold M. Woolf, Jun Li, Michael Pavolonis

"... 2 is known. The sensitivity is demonstrated on two volcanic eruptions of the Soufrière Hills Volcano ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

2 is known. The sensitivity is demonstrated on two volcanic &lt;em&gt;eruptions&lt;/em&gt; of the Soufrière Hills &lt;em&gt;Volcano&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>