<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7401">yo mama jokes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:57:10" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7401-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7401_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:57:14">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1D4F9343E52112CD588B3EEB7967A9B1?doi=10.1.1.366.6274&amp;rank=1</link><title>Joke Retrieval: Recognizing the Same Joke Told Differently</title><description>Joke Retrieval: Recognizing the Same Joke Told Differently

by Lisa Friedl, James Allan

"... manually removed items like one-liners (which included “yo mama” jokes), quotes, funny but true stories ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

In a corpus of &lt;em&gt;jokes&lt;/em&gt;, a human might judge two documents to be the "same &lt;em&gt;joke&lt;/em&gt; " even if characters</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7401-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7401_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:57:34">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1D4F9343E52112CD588B3EEB7967A9B1?doi=10.1.1.418.8344&amp;rank=2</link><title>The “Who’s Yo Daddy? ” Problem Or: Solvin ’ Concurren ’ Axcess Issues wit Computers, Yo</title><description>The “Who’s Yo Daddy? ” Problem Or: Solvin ’ Concurren ’ Axcess Issues wit Computers, Yo

by Dr. Donna, M. Malayeri, Heather Miller, Pppoe Pp, Herr Doctor, Doktor Klaus

"... ﻿The “Who’s Yo Daddy?” Problem Or: Solvin’ Concurren’ Axcess Issues wit Computers, Yo Dr. Donna M ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Computer Science research can solve many real-world problems. Here we describe our novel research, Uniqueness Types, and how it applies both to multi-threaded programs and to real world scenarios. In particular, we solve issues that commonly arise in popular daytime sociological science documentaries. 1 1.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7401-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7401_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:57:47">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1D4F9343E52112CD588B3EEB7967A9B1?doi=10.1.1.342.8630&amp;rank=3</link><title>D.: Enriching Very Large Ontologies Using the WWW</title><description>D.: Enriching Very Large Ontologies Using the WWW

by Eneko Agirre, Olatz Ansa, Eduard Hovy, David Martínez \- In: Proc. of 1st International Workshop on Ontology Learning (OL 2000). Held in Conjunction with the 14th European Conference on Artificial Intelligence (ECAI , 2000

"... person) AND NOT (’man’... OR ’broth of a boy’ OR # sense 2 ’son’ OR... OR ’mama’s boy’ OR # sense 3 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 104 (5 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract. This paper explores the possibility to exploit text on the world wide web in order to enrich the concepts in existing ontologies. First, a method to retrieve documents from the WWW related to a concept is described. These document collections are used 1) to construct topic signatures (lists of topically related words) for each concept in WordNet, and 2) to build hierarchical clusters of the concepts (the word senses) that lexicalize a given word. The overall goal is to overcome two shortcomings of WordNet: the lack of topical links among concepts, and the proliferation of senses. Topic signatures are validated on a word sense disambiguation task with good results, which are improved when the hierarchical clusters are used. 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7401-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7401_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:58:07">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1D4F9343E52112CD588B3EEB7967A9B1?doi=10.1.1.201.7348&amp;rank=4</link><title>Data mining for electronic music distribution</title><description>Data mining for electronic music distribution

by François Pachet, Gert Westermann, Damien Laigre \- In Proceedings of WedelMusic , 2001

"... FATHER S WORDS COMIN FROM THE HEART OF THE GHETTO (1994 YO MAMA) 2:54 GIL SCOTT HERON NEW YORK CITY GLORY ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 29 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Music classification is a key ingredient for electronic music distribution. Because of the lack of standards in music classification – or the lack of enforcement of existing standards – there is a huge amount of unclassified titles of music in the world. In this paper we propose a method of classification based on musical data mining techniques that uses co-occurrence and correlation analysis for classification. This method allows for the rapid extraction of similarities between musical titles or artists. We investigate the usability of radio playlists and compilation CD databases for our data mining technique, and we compare the generated results with human similarity judgments. Based on a clustering technique, we show that interesting clusters can reveal specific music genres and allow classifying titles of music in a kind of objective manner. 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7401-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7401_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:58:21">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1D4F9343E52112CD588B3EEB7967A9B1?doi=10.1.1.194.6178&amp;rank=5</link><title>Segmentation of glides with tonal alignment as reference</title><description>Segmentation of glides with tonal alignment as reference

by Yi Xu, Fang Liu \- In Proceedings of 7th International Conference On Spoken Language Processing , 2002

"... . In a sequence of two CV syllables such as /mama/, the boundary between the two syllables can be said ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 4 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

sequence of two CV syllables such as /&lt;em&gt;mama&lt;/em&gt;/, the boundary between the two syllables can be said</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7401-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7401_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:58:40">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1D4F9343E52112CD588B3EEB7967A9B1?doi=10.1.1.72.6177&amp;rank=6</link><title>Does learning a language require the child to reconceptualize the world</title><description>Does learning a language require the child to reconceptualize the world

by Susan Carey \- Lingua , 1994

"... of a view that even yo infants represent at least one sortal concept, physical object, which provides ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 4 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

the Quine/Piaget position, in favor of a view that even &lt;em&gt;yo&lt;/em&gt; infants represent at least one sortal concept</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7401-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7401_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:58:52">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1D4F9343E52112CD588B3EEB7967A9B1?doi=10.1.1.294.9758&amp;rank=7</link><title>Tweets from Justin Bieber’s Heart: The Dynamics of the “Location ” Field in User Profiles</title><description>Tweets from Justin Bieber’s Heart: The Dynamics of the “Location ” Field in User Profiles

by Brent Hecht, Lichan Hong, Bongwon Suh, H. Chi

"... “Wherever yo mama at” received an actual spatial footprint: in southwest Siberia. Since Yahoo! Geocoder ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 20 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Little research exists on one of the most common, oldest, and most utilized forms of online social geographic information: the “location ” field found in most virtual community user profiles. We performed the first in-depth study of user behavior with regard to the location field in Twitter user profiles. We found that 34 % of users did not provide real location information, frequently incorporating fake locations or sarcastic comments that can fool traditional geographic information tools. When users did input their location, they almost never specified it at a scale any more detailed than their city. In order to determine whether or not natural user behaviors have a real effect on the “locatability ” of users, we performed a simple machine learning experiment to determine whether we can identify a user’s location by only looking at what that user tweets. We found that a user’s country and state can in fact be determined easily with decent accuracy, indicating that users implicitly reveal location information, with or without realizing it. Implications for location-based services and privacy are discussed.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7401-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7401_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:59:13">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1D4F9343E52112CD588B3EEB7967A9B1?doi=10.1.1.388.3108&amp;rank=8</link><title>Thomas K. GreathouseClimate Modeling of Giant Planets: The Saturnian Seasonal Stratosphere</title><description>Thomas K. GreathouseClimate Modeling of Giant Planets: The Saturnian Seasonal Stratosphere

by Shadrian Brittany Strong, John H. Lacy, Daniel T. Jaffe, J. Craig Wheeler, Paul Harvey, Shadrian Brittany Strong

"... OF PHILOSOPHY THE UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS AT AUSTIN May 2008Dedicated to Mama, Dresden, and Kit.Acknowledgments I ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

for my first ever AAS meeting in 2000, and who has always encouraged me to learn and excel (te amo; &lt;em&gt;yo&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7401-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7401_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:59:27">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1D4F9343E52112CD588B3EEB7967A9B1?doi=10.1.1.14.5214&amp;rank=9</link><title>Intelligent Camera Planning for Computer Graphics</title><description>Intelligent Camera Planning for Computer Graphics

by Jonathan H Pickering, Yo Dd , 2003

"... in partial fulfilment of the requirements for the degree of Doctor of Philosophy. University of York York YO ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 9 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The virtual cameras used in computer graphics are normally controlled by user input or they are generated by a simple rule, which might require them to remain in position relative to a moving object. In this thesis an alternative method of control is proposed in which camera set-ups are derived from a description of the properties of the picture the camera is intended to produce. An analysis of the requirements of such a declarative system and possible methods of achieving them has been carried out, and is presented.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7401-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7401_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:59:47">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1D4F9343E52112CD588B3EEB7967A9B1?doi=10.1.1.303.4766&amp;rank=10</link><title>Finding Bursty Topics From Microblogs</title><description>Finding Bursty Topics From Microblogs

by Open Access, Qiming Diao, Jing Jiang, Feida Zhu, Ee Peng Lim, Qiming Diao, Jing Jiang, Feida Zhu, Ee-peng Lim

"... , awards, (1) why didnt 2ne1 win this time! Mnet Asian bang, mama, win, (2) 2ne1. you deserved that urgh ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 5 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Microblogs such as Twitter reflect the general public’s reactions to major events. Bursty topics from microblogs reveal what events have attracted the most online attention. Although bursty event detection from text streams has been studied before, previous work may not be suitable for microblogs because compared with other text streams such as news articles and scientific publications, microblog posts are particularly diverse and noisy. To find topics that have bursty patterns on microblogs, we propose a topic model that simultaneously captures two observations: (1) posts published around the same time are more likely</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>