<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7403">usc trojans</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:03:01" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7403-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7403_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:03:10">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=354FAE90C85ABF1AFFC4E72BF589C9BC?doi=10.1.1.45.7077&amp;rank=1</link><title>Trojan: A High-Performance Simulator for Shared Memory Architectures</title><description>Trojan: A High-Performance Simulator for Shared Memory Architectures

by Daeyeon Park, Rafael H. Saavedra \- Proceedings of the 29th Annual Simulation Symposium , 1996

"... -0781 fdaeyeon, saavedrag@cs.usc.edu Abstract This paper presents an execution-driven simulator called Trojan ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 6 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper presents an execution-driven simulator called &lt;em&gt;Trojan&lt;/em&gt;, which is an extended version</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7403-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7403_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:03:29">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=354FAE90C85ABF1AFFC4E72BF589C9BC?doi=10.1.1.160.3012&amp;rank=2</link><title>Bayesian surprise attracts human attention</title><description>Bayesian surprise attracts human attention

by Laurent Itti, et al. , 2009

"... is over; the USC-Trojans football team is on a winning streak; my wallet is in my possession; my car ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 135 (6 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7403-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7403_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:03:44">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=354FAE90C85ABF1AFFC4E72BF589C9BC?doi=10.1.1.35.997&amp;rank=3</link><title>A Taxonomy of Computer Program Security Flaws, with Examples</title><description>A Taxonomy of Computer Program Security Flaws, with Examples

by Carl Landwehr, Alan R. Bull, John P. Mcdermott, William, S. Choi , 1993

"... California (USC/ISI), attempted to characterize operating system security flaws. The RISOS final report ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 133 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper provides a taxonomy for computer program security flaws together with an appendix that carefully documents 50 actual security flaws. These flaws have all been described previously in the open literature, but in widely separated places. For those new to the field of computer security, they provide a good introduction to the characteristics of security flaws and how they can arise. Because these flaws were not randomly selected from a valid statistical sample of such flaws, we make no strong claims concerning the likely distribution of actual security flaws within the taxonomy. However, this method of organizing security flaw data can help those who have custody of more representative samples to organize them and to focus their efforts to remove and, eventually, to prevent the introduction of security flaws. Categories and Subject Descriptors: D.4.6[Operating Systems]:Security and Protection---access</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7403-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7403_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:04:03">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=354FAE90C85ABF1AFFC4E72BF589C9BC?doi=10.1.1.393.8923&amp;rank=4</link><title>20th Annual USC National Trauma, Emergency Surgery, and Surgical</title><description>20th Annual USC National Trauma, Emergency Surgery, and Surgical

by Critical Care Symposium , 2013

"... Carmen A. Puliafito, M.D., M.B.A. Keck School of Medicine of USC USC Trojan Marching Band and 3 rd Marine ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7403-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7403_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:04:14">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=354FAE90C85ABF1AFFC4E72BF589C9BC?doi=10.1.1.422.1556&amp;rank=5</link><title>Backing Trojan Asteroids in Periodic and Quasi-Periodic Orbits around the Jupiter Lagrange Points</title><description>Backing Trojan Asteroids in Periodic and Quasi-Periodic Orbits around the Jupiter Lagrange Points

by Fariba Ariaei, Edmond Jonckheere, Stephan Bohacek

"... ﻿Backing Trojan Asteroids in Periodic and Quasi-Periodic Orbits around the Jupiter Lagrange Points ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

is linearized around the natural dynamics of the &lt;em&gt;Trojan&lt;/em&gt; body, leading to an LDV niodel of the tracking error</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7403-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7403_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:04:32">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=354FAE90C85ABF1AFFC4E72BF589C9BC?doi=10.1.1.160.2825&amp;rank=6</link><title>RAID-x: A New Distributed Disk Array for I/O-Centric Cluster Computing</title><description>RAID-x: A New Distributed Disk Array for I/O-Centric Cluster Computing

by Kai Hwang, Hai Jin, Roy Ho \- In proceedings of the Ninth IEEE International Symposium on High Performance Distributed Computing , 2000

"... performance results on the Trojans cluster built at USC in 1999\. Throughout the paper, we discuss the issues ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 16 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

performance results on the &lt;em&gt;Trojans&lt;/em&gt; cluster built at &lt;em&gt;USC&lt;/em&gt; in 1999. Throughout the paper, we discuss the issues</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7403-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7403_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:04:44">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=354FAE90C85ABF1AFFC4E72BF589C9BC?doi=10.1.1.198.2709&amp;rank=7</link><title>Associate Editors</title><description>Associate Editors

by Susan L. Wampler, Darren Schenck, Kevin Durkin, Eric Mankin, Stephen Allison, Marianne Afifi

"... of Southern California Information Services B1BL10TECH_USC Annual_Report_Edition &gt; 2002 PHOTO TK l ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

ing &lt;em&gt;USC&lt;/em&gt; recruit outstanding new faculty and conduct ground-breaking research. Partnerships</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7403-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7403_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:05:04">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=354FAE90C85ABF1AFFC4E72BF589C9BC?doi=10.1.1.74.8764&amp;rank=8</link><title>Trusted P2P transactions with fuzzy reputation aggregation</title><description>Trusted P2P transactions with fuzzy reputation aggregation

by Shanshan Song, Kai Hwang, Runfang Zhou, Yu-kwong Kwok \- IEEE Internet Computing , 2005

"... Networks on April 1, 2005. All rights reserved by the authors. Corresponding author: Kai Hwang, USC ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 45 (7 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Internet commerce is facing a problem of distrust among participating sellers and buyers. This article presents a new fuzzy-logic approach to aggregating peer reputation using public-domain trace data. Based on the analysis and simulation experiments over the eBay trace, the authors demonstrate the efficacy and robustness of the eTrust and EigenTrust reputation systems to facilitate trusted P2P transactions. __________________________________ The Internet has enabled e-commerce or e-auction based commodity exchanges among strangers throughout the world. Internet commerce is wide open in that each participant can sign on and off asynchronously at will [7]. The e-transaction is mostly conducted at a peer-to-peer (P2P) level. The P2P environment does not involve a central entity to mediate the exchanges. The P2P transactions can be carried out point-to-point or point-to-multipoint, anonymously. Thus, it is crucial to have an effective trust management system based on peer reputations. This system must be built with public-domain e-commerce data such as the eBay trace file, which allows participants to locate trustworthy partners to exchange commodity over the Internet.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7403-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7403_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:05:18">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=354FAE90C85ABF1AFFC4E72BF589C9BC?doi=10.1.1.165.5879&amp;rank=9</link><title>A Guide for New Staff and</title><description>A Guide for New Staff and

by Southern California

"... .................................................. 50USC New Staff and Faculty Orientation Guide A Message from the President Welcome to the Trojan ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

This guide is intended for use by &lt;em&gt;USC&lt;/em&gt; faculty and staff in their orientation programs. Information</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7403-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7403_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:05:35">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=354FAE90C85ABF1AFFC4E72BF589C9BC?doi=10.1.1.364.9077&amp;rank=10</link><title>A Credibility-based Model of Computer System Security Shaw-Cheng</title><description>A Credibility-based Model of Computer System Security Shaw-Cheng

by unknown authors

"... @(email omitted); Abstract “Despite the possible presence of Trojan Horses in the user’s process, the reference monitor has ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

“Despite the possible presence of &lt;em&gt;Trojan&lt;/em&gt; Horses in the user’s process, the reference monitor has</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>