<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7404">kobe bryant</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:05:48" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7404-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7404_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:05:49">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E5970B195AC52542B589D796F748D733?doi=10.1.1.392.191&amp;rank=1</link><title>Defining Scandal in Sports: Media and Corporate Sponsor Perspectives</title><description>Defining Scandal in Sports: Media and Corporate Sponsor Perspectives

by Stephanie Hughes, Matt Shank

"... at the University of Colorado or the Kobe Bryant rape case raise serious questions about the impact of sports ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

such as the recruiting scandal at the University of Colorado or the &lt;em&gt;Kobe&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Bryant&lt;/em&gt; rape case raise serious questions about</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7404-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7404_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:06:08">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E5970B195AC52542B589D796F748D733?doi=10.1.1.360.5987&amp;rank=2</link><title>NFHS REPORT Following Lead of Pros Not Always Best Choice</title><description>NFHS REPORT Following Lead of Pros Not Always Best Choice

by B. Gardner, Nfhs Executive Director, Rick Wulkow, Nfhs President

"... basketball players have spent hour after hour on the court trying to pattern their game after that of Kobe ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

after hour on the court trying to pattern their game after that of &lt;em&gt;Kobe&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Bryant&lt;/em&gt; or LeBron James. High</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7404-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7404_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:06:20">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E5970B195AC52542B589D796F748D733?doi=10.1.1.111.4093&amp;rank=3</link><title>Probabilistic skylines on uncertain data</title><description>Probabilistic skylines on uncertain data

by Jian Pei, Bin Jiang, Xuemin Lin, Yidong Yuan \- In Proceedings of the 33rd International Conference on Very Large Data Bases (VLDB’07), Viena , 2007

"... , 721 games, the 0.2-skyline includes 14 players. Among them, Hakeem Olajuwon and Kobe Bryant ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 63 (16 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Uncertain data are inherent in some important applications. Although a considerable amount of research has been dedicated to modeling uncertain data and answering some types of queries on uncertain data, how to conduct advanced analysis on uncertain data remains an open problem at large. In this paper, we tackle the problem of skyline analysis on uncertain data. We propose a novel probabilistic skyline model where an uncertain object may take a probability to be in the skyline, and a p-skyline contains all the objects whose skyline probabilities are at least p. Computing probabilistic skylines on large uncertain data sets is challenging. We develop two efficient algorithms. The bottom-up algorithm computes the skyline probabilities of some selected instances of uncertain objects, and uses those instances to prune other instances and uncertain objects effectively. The top-down algorithm recursively partitions the instances of uncertain objects into subsets, and prunes subsets and objects aggressively. Our experimental results on both the real NBA player data set and the benchmark synthetic data sets show that probabilistic skylines are interesting and useful, and our two algorithms are efficient on large data sets, and complementary to each other in performance. 1.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7404-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7404_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:06:40">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E5970B195AC52542B589D796F748D733?doi=10.1.1.117.9104&amp;rank=4</link><title>Wikipedia as Participatory journalism: reliable sources? metrics for evaluating collaborative media as a news resource</title><description>Wikipedia as Participatory journalism: reliable sources? metrics for evaluating collaborative media as a news resource

by Andrew Lih \- In Proceedings of the 5th International Symposium on Online Journalism , 2004

"... ,12 . Whether to reveal the name of the woman involved in the rape trial of basketball player Kobe Bryant has ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 60 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Wikipedia is an Internet-based, user contributed encyclopedia that is collaboratively edited, and utilizes the wiki concept – the idea that any user on the Internet can change any page within the Web site, even anonymously. Paradoxically, this seemingly chaotic process has created a highly regarded reference on the Internet. Wikipedia has emerged as the largest example of participatory journalism to date – facilitating many-to-many communication among users editing articles, all working towards maintaining a neutral point of view — Wikipedia’s mantra. This study examines the growth of Wikipedia and analyzes the crucial technologies and community policies that have enabled the project to prosper. It also analyzes Wikipedia’s articles that have been cited in the news media, and establishes a set of metrics based on established encyclopedia taxonomies and analyzes the trends in Wikipedia being used as a source.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7404-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7404_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:06:54">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E5970B195AC52542B589D796F748D733?doi=10.1.1.119.4572&amp;rank=5</link><title>Retrieval Effectiveness of an Ontology-Based Model for Information Selection</title><description>Retrieval Effectiveness of an Ontology-Based Model for Information Selection

by Latifur Khan, Dennis Mcleod, Eduard Hovy \- The VLDB Journal , 2004

"... , player “Bryant Kobe,” “Bryant Mark,” “Reeves Bryant” share common word “Bryant,” which may of course ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 44 (15 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Technology in the field of digital media generates huge amounts of non-textual information, audio, video, and images, along with more familiar textual information. The potential for exchange and retrieval of information is vast and daunting. The key problem in achieving efficient and userfriendly retrieval is the development of a search mechanism to guarantee delivery of minimal irrelevant information (high precision) while insuring relevant information is not overlooked (high recall). The traditional solution employs keyword-based search. The only documents retrieved are</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7404-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7404_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:07:13">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E5970B195AC52542B589D796F748D733?doi=10.1.1.137.8475&amp;rank=6</link><title>On High Dimensional Skylines</title><description>On High Dimensional Skylines

by Chee-Yong Chan, H.V. Jagadish, Kian-Lee Tan, Anthony K. H. Tung, Zhenjie Zhang \- EDBT 2006 , 2006

"... 1975 6781 Charles Barkley 1987 8578 Kobe Bryant 2002 9271 Kareem Abdul-Jabbar 1975 9400 dimensions ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 33 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

In many decision-making applications, the skyline query is frequently used to find a set of dominating data points (called skyline points) in a multidimensional dataset. In a high-dimensional space skyline points no longer offer any interesting insights as there are too many of them. In this paper, we introduce a novel metric, called skyline frequency that compares and ranks the interestingness of data points based on how often they are returned in the skyline when different number of dimensions (i.e., subspaces) are considered. Intuitively, a point with a high skyline frequency is more interesting as it can be dominated on fewer combinations of the dimensions. Thus, the problem becomes one of finding top-k frequent skyline points. But the algorithms thus far proposed for skyline computation typically do not scale well with dimensionality. Moreover, frequent skyline computation requires that skylines be computed for each of an exponential number of subsets of the dimensions. We present efficient approximate algorithms to address these twin difficulties. Our extensive performance study shows that our approximate algorithm can run fast and compute the correct result on large data sets in high-dimensional spaces.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7404-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7404_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:07:25">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E5970B195AC52542B589D796F748D733?doi=10.1.1.234.1806&amp;rank=7</link><title>TIMELIKE SURFACES OF CONSTANT MEAN CURVATURE ±1 IN ANTI-DE SITTER 3-SPACE H 3 1 (−1)</title><description>TIMELIKE SURFACES OF CONSTANT MEAN CURVATURE ±1 IN ANTI-DE SITTER 3-SPACE H 3 1 (−1)

by Sungwook Lee , 2006

"... in PSL2R via Bryant type representation formulae. These Bryant type representation formulae are used ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

of Lorentz holomorphic and Lorentz antiholomorphic null curves in PSL2R via &lt;em&gt;Bryant&lt;/em&gt; type representation</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7404-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7404_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:07:44">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E5970B195AC52542B589D796F748D733?doi=10.1.1.2.3205&amp;rank=8</link><title>Anti-Aliasing on the Web</title><description>Anti-Aliasing on the Web

by Jasmine Novak, Prabhakar Raghavan, Andrew Tomkins , 2004

"... , and the Kobe Bryant case. Our selections were motivated by the volume of posting on the board, and our ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 20 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

It is increasingly common for users to interact with the web using a number of di#erent aliases. This trend is a doubleedged sword. On one hand, it is a fundamental building block in approaches to online privacy. On the other hand, there are economic and social consequences to allowing each user an arbitrary number of free aliases. Thus, there is great interest in understanding the fundamental issues in obscuring the identities behind aliases.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7404-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7404_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:07:57">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E5970B195AC52542B589D796F748D733?doi=10.1.1.387.4387&amp;rank=9</link><title>Audio Structuring and Personalized Retrieval Using Ontologies</title><description>Audio Structuring and Personalized Retrieval Using Ontologies

by Latifur Khan, Dennis Mcleod \- In Proceedings of IEEE Advances in Digital Libraries, Library of Congress

"... may be shared by multiple concepts’ synonymous lists. For example, player “Bryant Kobe,” “Bryant Mark ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 18 (7 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The goal of this work is to improve the accuracy (precision and recall) and communication effectiveness of a database system response to a user information request, by utilizing a domain-specific ontology. This ontology is employed, along with user profile information, to automatically select and deliver appropriate information units from a database. Specifically, the focus here is on multimedia audio databases: we are developing a Personal AudioCast system at the USC Integrated Media Systems Center which creates and delivers to an end-user personalized audio programs constructed from an audio database. Techniques are developed to segment and structure audio information, process user requests to generate custom audio results, create and optimize SQL queries, and present the results to the user. 1.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7404-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7404_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:08:17">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E5970B195AC52542B589D796F748D733?doi=10.1.1.400.2011&amp;rank=10</link><title>1.3: 1.3: Estimating the prevalence of a disease (Bernoulli Data). DATA: imaginary.</title><description>1.3: 1.3: Estimating the prevalence of a disease (Bernoulli Data). DATA: imaginary.

by unknown authors

"... : imaginary. Page: 18. 1.4 1.4: Kobe Bryant’s field goals in NBA (Binomial data). DATA: Sports data from ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

2.1: 2.1: A simple example: risk measures in medical research. DATA: imaginary.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>