<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7411">lenin mausoleum open</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:14:16" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7411-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7411_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:14:19">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=60B04226B4432D8291388BE72F91BEA2?doi=10.1.1.309.5161&amp;rank=1</link><title>Zhaoling: The Mausoleum of Emperor Tang Taizong</title><description>Zhaoling: The Mausoleum of Emperor Tang Taizong

by Xiuqin Zhou, Victor H. Mair , 2009

"... ﻿SINO-PLATONIC PAPERS Number 187 April, 2009 Zhaoling: The Mausoleum of Emperor Tang Taizong ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

www.sino-platonic.org SINO-PLATONIC PAPERS is an occasional series edited by Victor H. Mair. The purpose of the series is to make available to specialists and the interested public the results of research that, because of its unconventional or controversial nature, might otherwise go unpublished. The editor actively encourages younger, not yet well established, scholars and independent authors to submit manuscripts for consideration. Contributions in any of the major scholarly languages of the world, including Romanized Modern Standard Mandarin (MSM) and Japanese, are acceptable. In special circumstances, papers written in one of the Sinitic topolects (fangyan) may be considered for publication. Although the chief focus of Sino-Platonic Papers is on the intercultural relations of China with other peoples, challenging and creative studies on a wide variety of philological subjects will be entertained. This series is not the place for safe, sober, and stodgy presentations. Sino-Platonic Papers prefers lively work that, while taking reasonable risks to advance the field, capitalizes on brilliant new insights into the development of civilization. The only style-sheet we honor is that of consistency. Where possible, we prefer the usages of the Journal of Asian Studies. Sinographs (hanzi, also called tetragraphs [fangkuaizi]) and other unusual symbols should be kept to an absolute minimum. Sino-Platonic Papers emphasizes substance over form. Submissions are regularly sent out to be refereed and extensive editorial suggestions for revision may be offered. Manuscripts should be double-spaced with wide margins and submitted in duplicate. A set of "Instructions for Authors " may be obtained by contacting the editor. Ideally, the final draft should be a neat, clear camera-ready copy with high blackand-white contrast. Sino-Platonic Papers is licensed under the Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 2.5 License. To view a copy of this license, visit</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7411-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7411_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:14:33">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=60B04226B4432D8291388BE72F91BEA2?doi=10.1.1.278.407&amp;rank=2</link><title>Mitochondrial DNA Evidence for a Diversified Origin of Workers Building Mausoleum for First Emperor</title><description>Mitochondrial DNA Evidence for a Diversified Origin of Workers Building Mausoleum for First Emperor

by Qingbo Duan, Li Jin , 2008

"... ﻿Mitochondrial DNA Evidence for a Diversified Origin of Workers Building Mausoleum for First ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

of shedding light on origins of these samples who were supposed to be workers building the &lt;em&gt;mausoleum&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7411-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7411_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:14:53">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=60B04226B4432D8291388BE72F91BEA2?doi=10.1.1.2.992&amp;rank=3</link><title>Towards the Self-Annotating Web</title><description>Towards the Self-Annotating Web

by Philipp Cimiano, Siegfried Handschuh, Siegfried H, Steffen Staab , 2004

"... Universal Business Language or HumanMarkuphttp://www.oasis-open.org. 3 www.uddi.org Copyright is held ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 133 (10 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The success of the Semantic Web depends on the availability of ontologies as well as on the proliferation of web pages annotated with metadata conforming to these ontologies. Thus, a crucial question is where to acquire these metadata. In this paper we propose PANKOW (Pattern-based Annotation through Knowledge on the Web), a method which employs an unsupervised, pattern-based approach to categorize instances with regard to an ontology. The approach is evaluated against the manual annotations of two human subjects. The approach is implemented in OntoMat, an annotation tool for the Semantic Web and shows very promising results.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7411-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7411_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:15:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=60B04226B4432D8291388BE72F91BEA2?doi=10.1.1.130.792&amp;rank=4</link><title>MobiLenin combining a multi-track music video, personal mobile phones and a public display</title><description>MobiLenin combining a multi-track music video, personal mobile phones and a public display

by Jürgen Scheible, Timo Ojala, Mediateam Oulu \- In: Proc. of the ACM conf. on Multimedia, ACM Press , 2005

"... ﻿MobiLenin – Combining A Multi-Track Music Video, Personal Mobile Phones and A Public Display ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 19 (5 self) \- Add to MetaCart

-conventional distributed humancomputer interface for multi-user interactive entertainment. The proposed Mobi&lt;em&gt;Lenin&lt;/em&gt; system</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7411-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7411_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:15:25">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=60B04226B4432D8291388BE72F91BEA2?doi=10.1.1.290.324&amp;rank=5</link><title>Open Access</title><description>Open Access

by Wlodzimierz Klonowski

"... ://www.nonlinearbiomedphys.com/content/5/1/7 RESEARCH Open Access Econobiophysics - game of choosing. Model of selection or election ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

selection or election process with diverse accessible information</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7411-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7411_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:15:39">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=60B04226B4432D8291388BE72F91BEA2?doi=10.1.1.177.9502&amp;rank=6</link><title>THE RISE OF HITLER By</title><description>THE RISE OF HITLER By

by Antony C. Sutton, Antony C. Sutton , 1976

"... Establishment, in three significant twentieth-century historical events: the 1917 Lenin\- Trotsky Revolution ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

significant twentieth-century historical events: the 1917 &lt;em&gt;Lenin&lt;/em&gt;\-</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7411-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7411_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:15:57">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=60B04226B4432D8291388BE72F91BEA2?doi=10.1.1.348.9883&amp;rank=7</link><title>RESEARCH ARTICLE Open Access</title><description>RESEARCH ARTICLE Open Access

by Juan Carlos Guevara-arauza, José Jesús, Órnelas Paz, Sergio Rosales Mendoza, Ruth Elena, Soria Guerra, Luz María, Teresita Paz Maldonado, Diana Jaqueline, Pimentel González

"... ://journal.chemistrycentral.com/content/5/1/10 RESEARCH ARTICLE Open Access Biofunctional activity of tortillas and bars enhanced with nopal ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Biofunctional activity of tortillas and bars enhanced with nopal. Preliminary assessment of functional effect after intake on the oxidative status in healthy volunteers</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7411-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7411_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:16:10">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=60B04226B4432D8291388BE72F91BEA2?doi=10.1.1.271.7828&amp;rank=8</link><title>REVIEW Open Access</title><description>REVIEW Open Access

by Alisher B Latypov

"... /1/32 REVIEW Open Access The Soviet doctor and the treatment of drug addiction: “A difficult and most ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

The Soviet doctor and the treatment of drug addiction: “A difficult and most ungracious task”</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7411-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7411_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:16:30">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=60B04226B4432D8291388BE72F91BEA2?doi=10.1.1.399.3388&amp;rank=9</link><title>RESEARCH Open Access</title><description>RESEARCH Open Access

by Severe Battambang, Referral Hospital, Chanthap Lon, Ans Timmermans, Nillawan Buathong, Samon Nou, Youry Se, Ngo Sitthy, Soklyda Chann, Jeffrey Sherwood, Lenin Koy, Mengchour Char, Delia Bethell, David Saunders

"... Open Access Severe malaria in Battambang Referral Hospital, an area of multidrug resistance in Western ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

an area of multidrug resistance in Western-Cambodia: a retrospective analysis of cases from 2006–2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7411-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7411_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:16:44">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=60B04226B4432D8291388BE72F91BEA2?doi=10.1.1.154.9125&amp;rank=10</link><title>VTrack: Accurate, Energy-aware Road Traffic Delay Estimation Using Mobile Phones</title><description>VTrack: Accurate, Energy-aware Road Traffic Delay Estimation Using Mobile Phones

by Arvind Thiagarajan, Lenin Ravindranath, Katrina Lacurts, Sivan Toledo, Jakob Eriksson, Samuel Madden, Hari Balakrishnan, U. Illinois Chicago

"... Thiagarajan, Lenin Ravindranath, Katrina LaCurts, Sivan Toledo Jakob Eriksson Samuel Madden, Hari Balakrishnan ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 43 (6 self) \- Add to MetaCart

/or cellular triangulation— &lt;em&gt;opens&lt;/em&gt; up the attractive possibility of using position samples from drivers ’ phones</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>