<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7413">alkan piano</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 19:38:37" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7413-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7413_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 19:38:47">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=66E54CD6AA3DB51425E2389A87CE6602?doi=10.1.1.32.5049&amp;rank=1</link><title>A New Method for Tracking Modulations in Tonal Music in Audio Data Format</title><description>A New Method for Tracking Modulations in Tonal Music in Audio Data Format

by Hendrik Purwins, Benjamin Blankertz, Klaus Obermayer \- INTERNATIONAL JOINT CONFERENCE ON NEURAL NETWORKS , 2000

"... is calculated from a minor third c -- e[ (played on piano) with three bins per half-tone (left figure). We yield ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 17 (8 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Cq-profiles are 12-dimensional vectors, each component referring to a pitch class. They can be employed to represent keys. Cq-profiles are calculated with the constant Q filter bank [4]. They have the following advantages: (i) They correspond to probe tone ratings. (ii) Calculation is possible in real-time. (iii) Stability is obtained with respect to sound quality. (iv) They are transposable. By using the cq-profile technique as a simple auditory model in combination with the SOM [11] an arrangement of keys emerges, that resembles results from psychological experiments [13], and from music theory [1]. Cq-profiles are reliably applied to modulation tracking by introducing a special distance measure.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7413-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7413_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 19:39:37">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=66E54CD6AA3DB51425E2389A87CE6602?doi=10.1.1.419.6869&amp;rank=2</link><title>Industrial Aplication of Catalytic Systems for n-Heptane</title><description>Industrial Aplication of Catalytic Systems for n-Heptane

by Laura Olivia Alemán-vázquez, José Luis Cano-domínguez, Enelio Torres-garcía, José Roberto Villagómez-ibarra

"... number, in the 86 to 94 range, and a low environmental impact. Alkanes, as a family, have much lower ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7413-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7413_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 19:40:27">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=66E54CD6AA3DB51425E2389A87CE6602?doi=10.1.1.194.1762&amp;rank=3</link><title>The characterization by chromatographic methods of petroleum fractions from thermocatalytical</title><description>The characterization by chromatographic methods of petroleum fractions from thermocatalytical

by Claudia Irina Koncsag, Mariana Popescu, Cornelia Balbae, Gabriela Stanciu

"... analyzed by the GC method PIANO, ASTM D 5443-04, with a HP 6890 apparatus, with the following columns: OV ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7413-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7413_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 19:41:20">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=66E54CD6AA3DB51425E2389A87CE6602?doi=10.1.1.140.8940&amp;rank=4</link><title>Toroidal Modals in Tonal Theory and Pitch-Class Analysis</title><description>Toroidal Modals in Tonal Theory and Pitch-Class Analysis

by Hendrik Purwins, Benjamin Blankertz, Klaus Obermayer , 2007

"... of information captured in CQ profiles from complete but short pieces of piano music (Purwins et al. 2004b ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

The doubly circular relations of the major and minor keys based on all twelve pitchclasses can be depicted in toroidal models. We demonstrate a convergence of derivations from the different bases of conventional harmonic theory and recent experiments in music psychology. We present a formalization of the music-theoretical derivation from Gottfried Weber’s 1817 chart of tone-centers by using a topographic ordering map. We find the results to be consistent with Krumhansl and Kessler’s 1982 visualization of perceptual ratings.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7413-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7413_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 19:42:08">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=66E54CD6AA3DB51425E2389A87CE6602?doi=10.1.1.218.735&amp;rank=5</link><title>in collaboration with ARCO Products Company</title><description>in collaboration with ARCO Products Company

by J. E. Shepherd, C. D. Nuyt, J. J. Lee, J. E. Woodrow , 2000

"... on the fuel and chromatography (PIANO1 analysis) to characterize the liquid fuel. 2.1 Fuel Preparation ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Prepared for and supported by the National Transportation Safety Board</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7413-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7413_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 19:43:20">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=66E54CD6AA3DB51425E2389A87CE6602?doi=10.1.1.389.2457&amp;rank=6</link><title>Design and Use of Nanostructured Single-Site Heterogeneous Catalysts for the Selective Transformation of Fine Chemicals</title><description>Design and Use of Nanostructured Single-Site Heterogeneous Catalysts for the Selective Transformation of Fine Chemicals

by Vladimiro Dal Santo, Francesca Liguori, Claudio Pirovano, Matteo Guidotti , 2010

"... .P.) 2 CNR-Istituto di Chimica dei Composti OrganoMetallici, via Madonna del Piano, Sesto F.no (FI ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7413-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7413_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 19:44:26">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=66E54CD6AA3DB51425E2389A87CE6602?doi=10.1.1.389.2726&amp;rank=7</link><title>New Chiral Phosphoramidite Complexes of Iron as Catalytic Precursors in the Oxidation of Activated Methylene Groups</title><description>New Chiral Phosphoramidite Complexes of Iron as Catalytic Precursors in the Oxidation of Activated Methylene Groups

by Pushkar Shejwalkar, Nigam P. Rath, Eike B. Bauer , 2010

"... are especially attracted by iron catalyzed oxidations of alkanes [40,41]. Alkanes are rather unreactive ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7413-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7413_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 19:45:14">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=66E54CD6AA3DB51425E2389A87CE6602?doi=10.1.1.284.8346&amp;rank=8</link><title>Primer Perception Space—The Final Frontier</title><description>Primer Perception Space—The Final Frontier

by Lars Chittka, Axel Brockmann

"... piano keyboard. Because of the parallel processing of receptor information from the cochlea, we can hear ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Open access, freely available online Jakob von Uexküll coined the term Umwelt to describe the subjective world of animals. The world that animals perceive is not an objective, veridical representation of the physical world, he argued, but is instead a product of the particular sense organs that each species has acquired in its evolutionary history [1]. Many animals have sensory abilities that humans don’t, such as a magnetic compass sense in birds [2] or sensitivity to electric fields in fish [3]. But even within sensory modalities shared by many animals, such as vision, hearing, and olfaction, there are strong differences between species. For example, bees, but not humans, can see UV light [4,5] and smell carbon dioxide [6], and bats can hear ultrasound [7]. But what exactly is the structure of the perceptual worlds proposed by von Uexküll? Can we draw</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7413-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7413_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 19:45:56">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=66E54CD6AA3DB51425E2389A87CE6602?doi=10.1.1.372.8258&amp;rank=9</link><title>‘As Fast as One Possibly Can …’ Virtuosity, a Truth of Musical Performance? 1 in Critical Musicological Reflections. Essays in Honour of Derek B. Scott</title><description>‘As Fast as One Possibly Can …’ Virtuosity, a Truth of Musical Performance? 1 in Critical Musicological Reflections. Essays in Honour of Derek B. Scott

by Stan Hawkins, Aldershot Ashgate, Antoine Hennion , 2013

"... unknown dimensions, particularly through the development of the modern piano in the early nineteenth ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Virtuosity is a concept that has the double advantage of being transverse with respect to different musical genres and of pointing at performance 2 – at music that is not fixed by the score. These are two characteristics that directly refer to approaches developed by Derek Scott, which he has done by focusing, as I intend to do, on the nineteenth century – a period when great divides were established. 3 These divides still govern current musical practices, and perhaps even more, the academic disciplines that target them. In the course of the questioning of the opposition between popular and art music as carried out by critical musicology, 4 and mirroring its focus on the notion of performance, 5 I have decided to pay respect to the way musicians themselves have taken on the constitutional ambivalence of virtuosity. Indeed, for them this refers less to the specific property some types of music or artists possess than to a distanced attraction – a dangerous temptation, an impossible injunction of which they need to be wary. Undoubtedly, virtuosity is part of indigenous musicians ’ vocabulary – it signifies the height of a musician’s skills or the seductive prowess of an illusionist. Used both by specialists and by amateurs, the word is powerful in its critical load, albeit positive or</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7413-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7413_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 19:46:34">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=66E54CD6AA3DB51425E2389A87CE6602?doi=10.1.1.173.4524&amp;rank=10</link><title>Institute of Genetics and Physiology, Hebei Academy of Agricultural and Forestry Sciences,</title><description>Institute of Genetics and Physiology, Hebei Academy of Agricultural and Forestry Sciences,

by Joseph Bouton A, Zeng-yu Wang A , 2010

"... control transpiration (Hart 1987; Annicchiarico and Piano 2004). As white clover is often grown together ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Improvement of drought tolerance in white clover (Trifolium repens) by transgenic expression of a transcription factor gene WXP1</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>