<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7424">best italian food Rome</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:47:01" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7424-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7424_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:47:03">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=63852F9AC0A9360403674C05FD0FF8B5?doi=10.1.1.26.5563&amp;rank=1</link><title>The Digital Michelangelo Project: 3D Scanning of Large Statues</title><description>The Digital Michelangelo Project: 3D Scanning of Large Statues

by Marc Levoy, Szymon Rusinkiewicz, Brian Curless, Matt Ginzton, Jeremy Ginsberg, Kari Pulli, David Koller, Sean Anderson, Jonathan Shade, Lucas Pereira, James Davis, Duane Fulk , 2000

"... of ancient Rome. Our largest single dataset is of the David - 2 billion polygons and 7,000 color images ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 400 (8 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Romae, a giant marble map of ancient &lt;em&gt;Rome&lt;/em&gt;. Our largest single dataset is of the David - 2 billion</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7424-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7424_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:47:22">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=63852F9AC0A9360403674C05FD0FF8B5?doi=10.1.1.197.5565&amp;rank=2</link><title>Time Discounting and Time Preference: A Critical Review</title><description>Time Discounting and Time Preference: A Critical Review

by Shane Frederick, George Loewenstein \- Journal of Economic Literature , 2002

"... -denial required to delay gratification. As N.W. Senior, the best-known advocate this “abstinence” perspective ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 349 (12 self) \- Add to MetaCart

www.people.cornell.edu/pages/edo1/.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7424-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7424_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:47:45">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=63852F9AC0A9360403674C05FD0FF8B5?doi=10.1.1.17.8558&amp;rank=3</link><title>ROCK: A Robust Clustering Algorithm for Categorical Attributes</title><description>ROCK: A Robust Clustering Algorithm for Categorical Attributes

by Sudipto Guha, Rajeev Rastogi, Kyuseok Shim \- In Proc.ofthe15thInt.Conf.onDataEngineering , 2000

"... may consist of predominantly married customers with infants who buy diapers, baby food, toys etc. (in ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 337 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Clustering, in data mining, is useful to discover distribution patterns in the underlying data. Clustering algorithms usually employ a distance metric based (e.g., euclidean) similarity measure in order to partition the database such that data points in the same partition are more similar than points in different partitions. In this paper, we study clustering algorithms for data with boolean and categorical attributes. We show that traditional clustering algorithms that use distances between points for clustering are not appropriate for boolean and categorical attributes. Instead, we propose a novel concept of links to measure the similarity/proximity between a pair of data points. We develop a robust hierarchical clustering algorithm ROCK that employs links and not distances when merging clusters.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7424-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7424_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:48:33">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=63852F9AC0A9360403674C05FD0FF8B5?doi=10.1.1.180.8715&amp;rank=4</link><title>Supersense Tagger for Italian</title><description>Supersense Tagger for Italian

by Davide Picca, Alfio Massimiliano Gliozzo, Massimiliano Ciaramita \- In Proceedings of LREC 2008 , 2008

"... ﻿Supersense Tagger for Italian Davide Picca, Alfio Massimiliano Gliozzo, Massimiliano Ciaramita ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 4 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

In this paper we present the procedure we followed to develop the &lt;em&gt;Italian&lt;/em&gt; Super Sense Tagger</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7424-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7424_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:48:57">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=63852F9AC0A9360403674C05FD0FF8B5?doi=10.1.1.357.1990&amp;rank=5</link><title>All Roads Lead to Rome:</title><description>All Roads Lead to Rome:

by Sherri Goodman , 2011

"... -depth analylsis and results-oriented solutions to help government leaders choose the best course of action ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

-depth analylsis and results-oriented solutions to help government leaders choose the &lt;em&gt;best&lt;/em&gt; course of action</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7424-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7424_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:49:38">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=63852F9AC0A9360403674C05FD0FF8B5?doi=10.1.1.156.7332&amp;rank=6</link><title>Computing and Modeling Unit, Rome,</title><description>Computing and Modeling Unit, Rome,

by Giovanni Lavorgna, Biotech Dept, Alessandro Marongiu, Simone Melchionna, Paolo Palazzari, Vittorio Rosato, Paolo Verrecchia

"... Marongiu ENEA Informatic Unit Portici, Ylichron s.r.l, Rome alessandro.marongiu@(email omitted); Simone ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Discovering co-operative Transcription Factors (TF's) within the genome is a computationally challenging problem, tackled through Monte Carlo-like analysis by the Co-Bind code, developed at the Department of Genetics of the St. Louis Washington University. Due to its statistical nature, Co-Bind is characterized by very long execution times, order of days on current high-end workstations, and could benefit from parallelization and a wise optimization, performed at both the algorithmic and coding levels. This work presents the results achieved by parallelizing Co-Bind and optimising the parallel code and shows that, on a 16-processor architecture, a speedup greater than two orders of magnitude is achieved with respect to the serial version released by the code’s authors. 1.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7424-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7424_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:50:03">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=63852F9AC0A9360403674C05FD0FF8B5?doi=10.1.1.97.8944&amp;rank=7</link><title>Integrating subject field codes into wordnet</title><description>Integrating subject field codes into wordnet

by Bernardo Magnini, Gabriela Cavaglià , 2000

"... for a specific domain. The best approssimation of SFCs are the field labels used in dictionaries (e ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 139 (8 self) \- Add to MetaCart

In this paper, we present a lexical resource where WordNet synsets are annotated with Subject Field Codes. We discuss both the methodological issues we dealt with and the annotation techniques used. A quantitative analysis of the resource coverage, as well as a qualitative evaluation of the proposed annotations, are reported. 1.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7424-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7424_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:50:29">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=63852F9AC0A9360403674C05FD0FF8B5?doi=10.1.1.156.6649&amp;rank=8</link><title>Eclipse Italian Community</title><description>Eclipse Italian Community

by Angelo Gargantini, Metodi Matematici , 2009

"... ﻿Angelo Gargantini (Ed) Eclipse-IT 2009 Eclipse-IT 2009 4th Italian Workshop on Eclipse ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

This volume contains the papers presented at EclipseIT 09, the 4th &lt;em&gt;Italian&lt;/em&gt; Workshop on Eclipse</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7424-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7424_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:50:53">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=63852F9AC0A9360403674C05FD0FF8B5?doi=10.1.1.163.7409&amp;rank=9</link><title>Modelling an Italian Talking Head</title><description>Modelling an Italian Talking Head

by C. Pelachaud \- In: AVSP 2001: 2001; Aalborg, Denmark,2001

"... ﻿MODELLING AN ITALIAN TALKING HEAD C. Pelachaud Dipartimento di Informatica e Sistemistica ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 9 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Our goal is to create a natural &lt;em&gt;Italian&lt;/em&gt; talking face with, in particular, lip-readable movements</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7424-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7424_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:52:13">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=63852F9AC0A9360403674C05FD0FF8B5?doi=10.1.1.202.375&amp;rank=10</link><title>Andrea Stoppa is an Economist at ProcomAGR in Rome Italy.</title><description>Andrea Stoppa is an Economist at ProcomAGR in Rome Italy.

by Dermot J. Hayes, Sergio H. Lence , 2003

"... @(email omitted);, or by telephone at 515-294-8960. Andrea Stoppa is an Economist at ProcomAGR in Rome Italy. The authors thank ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

much of the information in the case study on Brunello di Montalcino wine. They also thank Federico Mariotti of 3A Parco Tecnologico Agroalimentare for his kind assistance in providing information about third-party certification. FARMER-OWNED BRANDS?</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>