<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7426">game bmx boy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:09:34" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7426-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7426_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:09:35">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=6071313CC4742E35E148B12F8FFA5C9E?doi=10.1.1.217.2021&amp;rank=1</link><title>Bayesian Data Analysis</title><description>Bayesian Data Analysis

by Andrew Gelman, Christian Robert, Nicolas Chopin, Judith Rousseau , 1995

"... ) to be nearly unreadable, a book too much of a product of its time in its enthusiasm for game theory as a ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1230 (47 self) \- Add to MetaCart

I actually own a copy of Harold Jeffreys’s Theory of Probability but have only read small bits of it, most recently over a decade ago to confirm that, indeed, Jeffreys was not too proud to use a classical chi-squared p-value when he wanted to check the misfit of a model to data (Gelman, Meng and Stern, 2006). I do, however, feel that it is important to understand where our probability models come from, and I welcome the opportunity to use the present article by Robert, Chopin and Rousseau as a platform for further discussion of foundational issues. 2 In this brief discussion I will argue the following: (1) in thinking about prior distributions, we should go beyond Jeffreys’s principles and move toward weakly informative priors; (2) it is natural for those of us who work in social and computational sciences to favor complex models, contra Jeffreys’s preference for simplicity; and (3) a key generalization of Jeffreys’s ideas is to explicitly include model checking in the process of data analysis.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7426-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7426_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:10:44">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=6071313CC4742E35E148B12F8FFA5C9E?doi=10.1.1.38.6442&amp;rank=2</link><title>Semantic Similarity in a Taxonomy: An Information-Based Measure and its Application to Problems of Ambiguity in Natural Language</title><description>Semantic Similarity in a Taxonomy: An Information-Based Measure and its Application to Problems of Ambiguity in Natural Language

by Philip Resnik , 1999

"... in the Roman Catholic Church, and a game played by children. WordNet does not use node labels like doctor1, but ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 416 (9 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This article presents a measure of semantic similarityinanis-a taxonomy based on the notion of shared information content. Experimental evaluation against a benchmark set of human similarity judgments demonstrates that the measure performs better than the traditional edge-counting approach. The article presents algorithms that take advantage of taxonomic similarity in resolving syntactic and semantic ambiguity, along with experimental results demonstrating their e#ectiveness. 1. Introduction Evaluating semantic relatedness using network representations is a problem with a long history in arti#cial intelligence and psychology, dating back to the spreading activation approach of Quillian #1968# and Collins and Loftus #1975#. Semantic similarity represents a special case of semantic relatedness: for example, cars and gasoline would seem to be more closely related than, say, cars and bicycles, but the latter pair are certainly more similar. Rada et al. #Rada, Mili, Bicknell, &amp; Blett...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7426-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7426_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:15:11">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=6071313CC4742E35E148B12F8FFA5C9E?doi=10.1.1.318.7914&amp;rank=3</link><title>Digital Game-Based Learning</title><description>Digital Game-Based Learning

by Marc Prensky

"... . And while years ago the group attracted to video and computer games was almost entirely adolescent boys ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 205 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

” video and computer &lt;em&gt;games&lt;/em&gt; has the positive effect of enhancing students ’ visual selective attention</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7426-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7426_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:16:35">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=6071313CC4742E35E148B12F8FFA5C9E?doi=10.1.1.46.2526&amp;rank=4</link><title>Exploring Common Conceptions About Boys and Electronic Games</title><description>Exploring Common Conceptions About Boys and Electronic Games

by Joan Lawry, Rena Upitis, Maria Klawe, Ann Anderson, Kori Inkpen, Mutindi Ndunda, David Hsu, Steve Leroux, Kamran Sedighian \- Journal of Computer in Math and Science Teaching , 1995

"... Exploring Common Conceptions About Boys and Electronic Games Joan Lawry, Rena Upitis, Maria Klawe ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 19 (8 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Electronic &lt;em&gt;games&lt;/em&gt; are an integral part of many &lt;em&gt;boys&lt;/em&gt;' lives. Based on observations made over a two</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7426-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7426_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:18:30">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=6071313CC4742E35E148B12F8FFA5C9E?doi=10.1.1.321.7844&amp;rank=5</link><title>Gorillas in our midst: sustained inattentional blindness for dynamic events</title><description>Gorillas in our midst: sustained inattentional blindness for dynamic events

by Daniel J Simons, Christopher F Chabris \- Perception , 1999

"... .) One of the events was a hand-slapping game in which one player extended his hands with palms up ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 148 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract. With each eye fixation, we experience a richly detailed visual world. Yet recent work on visual integration and change detection reveals that we are surprisingly unaware of the details of our environment from one view to the next: we often do not detect large changes to objects and scenes ('change blindness'). Furthermore, without attention, we may not even perceive objects ('inattentional blindness'). Taken together, these findings suggest that we perceive and remember only those objects and details that receive focused attention. In this paper, we briefly review and discuss evidence for these cognitive forms of 'blindness'. We then present a new study that builds on classic studies of divided visual attention to examine inattentional blindness for complex objects and events in dynamic scenes. Our results suggest that the likelihood of noticing an unexpected object depends on the similarity of that object to other objects in the display and on how difficult the priming monitoring task is. Interestingly, spatial proximity of the critical unattended object to attended locations does not appear to affect detection, suggesting that observers attend to objects and events, not spatial positions. We discuss the implications of these results for visual representations and awareness of our visual environment. 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7426-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7426_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:23:03">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=6071313CC4742E35E148B12F8FFA5C9E?doi=10.1.1.142.8286&amp;rank=6</link><title>Cheap and Fast — But is it Good? Evaluating Non-Expert Annotations for Natural Language Tasks</title><description>Cheap and Fast — But is it Good? Evaluating Non-Expert Annotations for Natural Language Tasks

by Rion Snow, Daniel Jurafsky, Andrew Y. Ng

"... of games, including the ESPGame for labeling images (von Ahn and Dabbish, 2004) and Verbosity ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 141 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Human linguistic annotation is crucial for many natural language processing tasks but can be expensive and time-consuming. We explore the use of Amazon’s Mechanical Turk system, a significantly cheaper and faster method for collecting annotations from a broad base of paid non-expert contributors over the Web. We investigate five tasks: affect recognition, word similarity, recognizing textual entailment, event temporal ordering, and word sense disambiguation. For all five, we show high agreement between Mechanical Turk non-expert annotations and existing gold standard labels provided by expert labelers. For the task of affect recognition, we also</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7426-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7426_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:25:55">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=6071313CC4742E35E148B12F8FFA5C9E?doi=10.1.1.224.5668&amp;rank=7</link><title>digital games</title><description>digital games

by Sonja Kröger, Emese Domahidi, Thorsten Qu

"... ﻿The game boys’ network. A network analysis of the German digital games industry. Sonja Kröger ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

The &lt;em&gt;game&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;boys&lt;/em&gt; ’ network. A network analysis of the German</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7426-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7426_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:30:49">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=6071313CC4742E35E148B12F8FFA5C9E?doi=10.1.1.360.1375&amp;rank=8</link><title>The Game Boys ’ Network. A Network Analysis of the German</title><description>The Game Boys ’ Network. A Network Analysis of the German

by Digital Games Industry, Sonja Kröger, Emese Domahidi, Thorsten Qu

"... ﻿The Game Boys’ Network. A Network Analysis of the German Digital Games Industry. Sonja Kröger ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

This paper aims to map the German digital &lt;em&gt;games&lt;/em&gt; industry. Using expert interviews and social</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7426-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7426_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:35:48">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=6071313CC4742E35E148B12F8FFA5C9E?doi=10.1.1.194.6831&amp;rank=9</link><title>3\. Development for the Game Boy Advance Console</title><description>3\. Development for the Game Boy Advance Console

by Andy Matange, Michael Daly

"... &amp; Michael Daly Contents: 1\. Introduction 2\. Rules of the Game 3\. Development for the Game Boy Advance ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7426-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7426_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:36:24">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=6071313CC4742E35E148B12F8FFA5C9E?doi=10.1.1.190.935&amp;rank=10</link><title>for Every Girl and Boy</title><description>for Every Girl and Boy

by Nea President Dennis Van Roekel

"... ﻿An NEA policy brief Mathematics and Science for Every Girl and Boy Research tells us ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Research tells us that education is not a zero-sum &lt;em&gt;game&lt;/em&gt;. High achievement for one group of students</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>