<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7428">rainy afternoon kids craft</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:40:54" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7428-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7428_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:40:55">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=3E1ED9A416437DFE80A7C74E676EFC6C?doi=10.1.1.153.1531&amp;rank=1</link><title>Corn Replant Decision-Making</title><description>Corn Replant Decision-Making

by R. L. (bob Nielsen , 2006

"... by the field every afternoon taking the kids to baseball practice. Make a wise decision about the merits ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

by the field every &lt;em&gt;afternoon&lt;/em&gt; taking the &lt;em&gt;kids&lt;/em&gt; to baseball practice. Make a wise decision about the merits</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7428-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7428_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:42:52">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=3E1ED9A416437DFE80A7C74E676EFC6C?doi=10.1.1.353.3528&amp;rank=2</link><title>Genetic effects, relationships and heritability of some growth traits in Nigeria crossbreed goats</title><description>Genetic effects, relationships and heritability of some growth traits in Nigeria crossbreed goats

by unknown authors

"... and allowed to browse on the University paddock in the afternoon. Live body weights were recorded weekly from ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

with concentrates at 200-300g per goat per day and allowed to browse on the University paddock in the &lt;em&gt;afternoon&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7428-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7428_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:46:43">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=3E1ED9A416437DFE80A7C74E676EFC6C?doi=10.1.1.301.7845&amp;rank=3</link><title>Studies on Fish Landing Census of Bay of Bengal at Puri Sea-Shore in Odisha</title><description>Studies on Fish Landing Census of Bay of Bengal at Puri Sea-Shore in Odisha

by Dr. Suchismita Mohapatra, A. K. Patra

"... in the landing during rainy season. The fish captured from the various quarters of Puri sea were transported ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

in the landing during &lt;em&gt;rainy&lt;/em&gt; season. The fish captured from the various quarters of Puri sea were transported</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7428-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7428_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:51:15">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=3E1ED9A416437DFE80A7C74E676EFC6C?doi=10.1.1.170.8860&amp;rank=4</link><title>Submitted by the Founding Group of the</title><description>Submitted by the Founding Group of the

by Imani Charter, School Lynn

"... ’t work because kids come in with the mind set that they are just going to get this little piece of paper ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

and programs don’t work because &lt;em&gt;kids&lt;/em&gt; come in with the mind set that they are just going to get this little</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7428-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7428_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:52:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=3E1ED9A416437DFE80A7C74E676EFC6C?doi=10.1.1.298.3479&amp;rank=5</link><title>PREPARED FOR ADOLESCENT GIRLS “BOOT CAMP ” WORKSHOP Rural Case Study: Tool # 2</title><description>PREPARED FOR ADOLESCENT GIRLS “BOOT CAMP ” WORKSHOP Rural Case Study: Tool # 2

by unknown authors

"... spaces with a leadership cadre of indigenous girls” Note: The case study tool has been crafted using data ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

been &lt;em&gt;crafted&lt;/em&gt; using data from existing Organization Y girls programs to provide an example of how your</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7428-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7428_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:55:13">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=3E1ED9A416437DFE80A7C74E676EFC6C?doi=10.1.1.187.3363&amp;rank=6</link><title>Does Movie Violence Increase Violent Crime?” Quartery</title><description>Does Movie Violence Increase Violent Crime?” Quartery

by Gordon Dahl, Stefano Dellavigna \- Journal of Economics , 2009

"... , Mikael Priks, Uri Simonsohn provided useful comments. We would like to thank kids ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 12 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

What is the short-run impact of media violence on crime? Laboratory experiments in psychology find that exposure to media violence increases aggression. In this paper, we provide field evidence on this question. We exploit variation in the violence of blockbuster movies from 1995 to 2004, and study the effect on same-day assaults. We find that violent crime decreases on days with larger theater audiences for violent movies. The effect is partly due to incapacitation: between 6PM and 12AM, an increase of one million in the audience for violent movies reduces violent crime by 0.5 to 0.9 percent. After exposure to the movie, between 12AM and 6AM, crime is reduced by an even larger percentage (albeit from a lower base). This decrease does not appear to be due only to a cathartic effect specific to violent movies, since non-violent movies that appeal to young males have a similar effect. The finding is most likely due to a substitution away from other activities (with higher levels of violence) both during and after the movie, and a decrease in alcohol consumption. Overall, we find no evidence of a temporary surge in violent crime due to exposure to movie violence as would be predicted by the laboratory experiments. Rather, our estimates suggest that in the short-run violent movies deter 175 assaults daily. The differences compared to the experimental results can be explained by experimental procedures and sorting into violent movies in the field. Our design does not allow us to estimate long-run effects.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7428-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7428_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:55:57">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=3E1ED9A416437DFE80A7C74E676EFC6C?doi=10.1.1.300.3215&amp;rank=7</link><title>SELECTION OF BLACK BENGAL BREEDING BUCKS BASED ON PROGENY GROWTH PERFORMANCE AT NUCLEUS BREEDING</title><description>SELECTION OF BLACK BENGAL BREEDING BUCKS BASED ON PROGENY GROWTH PERFORMANCE AT NUCLEUS BREEDING

by Md. Nazmul Haque, Syed Sakhawat Husain, M. A. M. Yahia Kh, Auvijit Saha , 2012

"... months of age were 1.08, 4.66, 7.51, 10.29 and 13.67 kg, respectively. Sex of kid has significant (p˂0 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

. Sex of &lt;em&gt;kid&lt;/em&gt; has significant (p˂0.01) effect only on body weights at 6, 9 and 12 months of age. Type</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7428-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7428_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:59:22">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=3E1ED9A416437DFE80A7C74E676EFC6C?doi=10.1.1.303.981&amp;rank=8</link><title>We feel fine and searching the emotional web</title><description>We feel fine and searching the emotional web

by Sepandar D. Kamvar \- In Proceedings of WSDM , 2011

"... to specific questions like: do Europeans feel sad more than Americans? Does rainy weather affect how we feel ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 12 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We present We Feel Fine, an emotional search engine and web-based artwork whose mission is to collect the world’s emotions to help people better understand themselves and others. We Feel Fine continuously crawls blogs, microblogs, and social networking sites, extracting sentences that include the words “I feel ” or “I am feeling”, as well as the gender, age, and location of the people authoring those sentences. The We Feel Fine search interface allows users to search or browse over the resulting sentence-level index, asking questions such as “How did young people in Ohio feel when Obama was elected? ” While most research in sentiment analysis focuses on algorithms for extraction and classification of sentiment about given topics, we focus instead on building an interface that provides an engaging means of qualitative exploration of emotional data, and a flexible data collection and serving architecture that enables an ecosystem of data analysis applications. We use our observations on the usage of We Feel Fine to suggest a class of visualizations called Experiential Data Visualization, which focus on immersive item-level interaction with data. We also discuss the implications of such visualizations for crowdsourcing qualitative research in the social sciences.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7428-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7428_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:03:09">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=3E1ED9A416437DFE80A7C74E676EFC6C?doi=10.1.1.391.7093&amp;rank=9</link><title>INTERPRETING DIGITAL GAMING PRACTICES: SINGSTAR AS A TECHNOLOGY OF WORK</title><description>INTERPRETING DIGITAL GAMING PRACTICES: SINGSTAR AS A TECHNOLOGY OF WORK

by Fletcher Gordon

"... in crafting and strengthening social linkages amongst players. Our examination of the play and experience ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

be thought of as glue technology that assists in &lt;em&gt;crafting&lt;/em&gt; and strengthening social linkages amongst players</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7428-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7428_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:06:51">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=3E1ED9A416437DFE80A7C74E676EFC6C?doi=10.1.1.395.9906&amp;rank=10</link><title>B.: Context Relevance Assessment for Recommender Systems</title><description>B.: Context Relevance Assessment for Recommender Systems

by Linas Baltrunas, Bernd Ludwig, Francesco Ricci \- In: Proceedings of the 2011 International Conference on Intelligent User Interfaces , 2011

"... biking; theater event; folk festival, arts and crafts event; church or monastery; museum; spa ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 4 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Research on context aware recommender systems is taking for granted that context matters. But, often attempts to show the influence of context have failed. In this paper we consider the problem of quantitatively assessing context relevance. For this purpose we are assuming that users can imagine a situation described by a contextual feature, and judge if this feature is relevant for their decision making task. We have designed a UI suited for acquiring such information in a travel planning scenario. In fact, this interface is generic and can also be used for other domains (e.g., music). The experimental results show that it is possible to identify the contextual factors that are relevant for the given task and that the relevancy depends on the type of the place of interest to be included in the plan.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>