<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7430">conflict mali</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:37:04" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7430-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7430_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:37:07">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=97CFBC6E2F528C4BC1464E152058F84E?doi=10.1.1.248.8568&amp;rank=1</link><title>CONFLICT IN NORTHERN MALI CHIEF CHARACTERISTICS</title><description>CONFLICT IN NORTHERN MALI CHIEF CHARACTERISTICS

by Wayne G. Wouters, Andrei Belik, Nela Grebovic, Jeff Willows

"... ﻿FRICTION ALONG THE SAHELIAN FAULT LINE: AZAWAD AND ETHNIC CONFLICT IN NORTHERN MALI Policy ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

lines also appears germane to both the current and past ethnic &lt;em&gt;conflicts&lt;/em&gt; in &lt;em&gt;Mali&lt;/em&gt;. 5 Though</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7430-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7430_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:37:47">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=97CFBC6E2F528C4BC1464E152058F84E?doi=10.1.1.118.1870&amp;rank=2</link><title>Secure routing for structured peer-to-peer overlay networks</title><description>Secure routing for structured peer-to-peer overlay networks

by Miguel Castro, Peter Druschel, Ayalvadi Ganesh, Antony Rowstron, Dan S. Wallach , 2002

"... with conflicting interests are allowed to join. Even in a closed system of sufficiently large scale, it may be un ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 358 (12 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Structured peer-to-peer overlay networks provide a sub-strate for the construction of large-scale, decentralized applications, including distributed storage, group com-munication, and content distribution. These overlays are highly resilient; they can route messages correctly even when a large fraction of the nodes crash or the network partitions. But current overlays are not secure; even a small fraction of malicious nodes can prevent correct message delivery throughout the overlay. This prob-lem is particularly serious in open peer-to-peer systems, where many diverse, autonomous parties without pre-existing trust relationships wish to pool their resources. This paper studies attacks aimed at preventing correct message delivery in structured peer-to-peer overlays and presents defenses to these attacks. We describe and eval-uate techniques that allow nodes to join the overlay, to maintain routing state, and to forward messages securely in the presence of malicious nodes. 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7430-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7430_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:42:10">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=97CFBC6E2F528C4BC1464E152058F84E?doi=10.1.1.306.5112&amp;rank=3</link><title>Security Management in Northern Mali: Criminal Networks and Conflict Resolution Mechanisms</title><description>Security Management in Northern Mali: Criminal Networks and Conflict Resolution Mechanisms

by Kalilou Sidibé, Kalilou Sidibé, Kalilou Sidibé , 2012

"... REPORT 77 IDS RESEARCH REPORT 77 Security Management in Northern Mali: Criminal Networks and Conflict ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

The Institute of Development Studies is one of the world's leading charities for research, teaching and communications on international development. Founded in 1966, the Institute enjoys an international reputation based on the quality of its work and the rigour with which it applies academic skills to real world challenges. Its purpose is to understand and explain the world, and to try to change it – to influence as well as to inform. IDS hosts six dynamic research programmes, five popular postgraduate courses, and a family of worldclass web-based knowledge services. These three spheres are integrated in a unique combination – as a development knowledge hub, IDS is connected into and is a convenor of networks throughout the world. The Institute is home to approximately 80 researchers, 50 knowledge services staff, 50 support staff and about 150 students at any one time. But the IDS community extends far beyond, encompassing an extensive network of partners, former staff and students across the development community worldwide. For further information on IDS publications and for a free catalogue, contact:</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7430-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7430_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:45:59">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=97CFBC6E2F528C4BC1464E152058F84E?doi=10.1.1.174.6230&amp;rank=4</link><title>Mali’s Food Security Challenges: An Overview by Duncan Boughton, John</title><description>Mali’s Food Security Challenges: An Overview by Duncan Boughton, John

by Nango Dembélé

"... ﻿USAID Mali, Office of Economic Growth Partners Meeting on Strategic Brainstorming – Scaling Up ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

&lt;em&gt;Mali&lt;/em&gt; has a high incidence of malnutrition. The fourth Demographic and Health survey reports</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7430-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7430_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:49:46">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=97CFBC6E2F528C4BC1464E152058F84E?doi=10.1.1.278.7779&amp;rank=5</link><title>accountability? A field experiment in Mali</title><description>accountability? A field experiment in Mali

by Jessica Gottlieb, Jessica Gottlieb , 2012

"... ﻿Does Raising Vote Expectations Improve Accountability? A Field Experiment in Mali Jessica Gottlieb ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

large-scale experiment across 95 localities in &lt;em&gt;Mali&lt;/em&gt; in which some voters received information about</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7430-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7430_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:50:08">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=97CFBC6E2F528C4BC1464E152058F84E?doi=10.1.1.202.146&amp;rank=6</link><title>Experiences of the GDRN5 Network in Mali</title><description>Experiences of the GDRN5 Network in Mali

by Aly Bacha Konaté

"... Network in Mali Aly Bacha Konaté April 2003About the authors Aly Bacha Konaté gained a Masters in Forestry ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Securing the commons No.6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7430-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7430_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:51:12">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=97CFBC6E2F528C4BC1464E152058F84E?doi=10.1.1.152.8108&amp;rank=7</link><title>IDENTIFYING THE DETERMINANTS AND CHARACTERISTICS OF MOTHERS’ INCOME IN RURAL MALI By</title><description>IDENTIFYING THE DETERMINANTS AND CHARACTERISTICS OF MOTHERS’ INCOME IN RURAL MALI By

by Megan Elizabeth Mcglinchy, Megan E. Mcglinchy

"... ﻿IDENTIFYING THE DETERMINANTS AND CHARACTERISTICS OF MOTHERS’ INCOME IN RURAL MALI By Megan ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This study investigates the determinants and characteristics of women’s income in &lt;em&gt;Mali&lt;/em&gt;. Malian men</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7430-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7430_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:52:26">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=97CFBC6E2F528C4BC1464E152058F84E?doi=10.1.1.367.7362&amp;rank=8</link><title>Mali: The Case for a Permanent UN Intervention Force?</title><description>Mali: The Case for a Permanent UN Intervention Force?

by Matthew Willis, Matthew Willis, Ashlee Godwin

"... ﻿Mali: The case for a Permanent UN Intervention force? Matthew Willis Royal United Services ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

The Royal United Services Institute (RUSI) is an independent think tank engaged in cutting edge defence and security research. A unique institution, founded in 1831 by the Duke of Wellington, RUSI embodies nearly two centuries of forward thinking, free discussion and careful reflection on defence and security matters.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7430-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7430_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:54:57">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=97CFBC6E2F528C4BC1464E152058F84E?doi=10.1.1.296.5425&amp;rank=9</link><title>MALI: FLOOD MANAGEMENT- NIGER RIVER INLAND DELTA</title><description>MALI: FLOOD MANAGEMENT- NIGER RIVER INLAND DELTA

by Samuel Diarra, Marcel Kuper, Gil Mahé

"... MANAGEMENT CASE STUDY 1 MALI: FLOOD MANAGEMENT - NIGER RIVER INLAND DELTA January 2004 Edited by TECHNICAL ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Opinions expressed in the case study are those of author(s) and do not necessarily reflect those of the WMO/GWP</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7430-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7430_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:56:12">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=97CFBC6E2F528C4BC1464E152058F84E?doi=10.1.1.365.8385&amp;rank=10</link><title>Agricultural privitisation and reform of farmer organisations in Mali</title><description>Agricultural privitisation and reform of farmer organisations in Mali

by Isaïe Dougnon, Siaka Sanogo, Bakary Coulibaly, Abdoul Karim Diamoutene, John Morton , 2010

"... in Mali Isaïe Dougnon¹, Siaka Sanogo², Bakary Coulibaly¹, Abdoul Karim Diamoutene¹ and John Morton ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

“Leaving farmers as orphans”:</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>