<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7434">wellness hotel Maastricht</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:40:01" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7434-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7434_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:40:07">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=697F37CFA5C6171A948BFBD4A3D790C8?doi=10.1.1.177.461&amp;rank=1</link><title>Increasing Returns and Economic Geography</title><description>Increasing Returns and Economic Geography

by Paul Krugman \- Journal of Political Economy , 1991

"... as dimensionless points (and frequently assumes zero transportation costs between countries as well). Admittedly ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 577 (5 self) \- Add to MetaCart

as dimensionless points (and frequently assumes zero transportation costs between countries as &lt;em&gt;well&lt;/em&gt;). Admittedly</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7434-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7434_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:42:42">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=697F37CFA5C6171A948BFBD4A3D790C8?doi=10.1.1.107.3613&amp;rank=2</link><title>Independent Component Analysis</title><description>Independent Component Analysis

by Aapo Hyvärinen \- Neural Computing Surveys , 2001

"... . Well-known linear transformation methods include, for example, principal component analysis, factor ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1492 (93 self) \- Add to MetaCart

. &lt;em&gt;Well&lt;/em&gt;-known linear transformation methods include, for example, principal component analysis, factor</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7434-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7434_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:44:04">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=697F37CFA5C6171A948BFBD4A3D790C8?doi=10.1.1.131.9807&amp;rank=3</link><title>Shape and motion from image streams under orthography: a factorization method</title><description>Shape and motion from image streams under orthography: a factorization method

by Carlo Tomasi \- International Journal of Computer Vision , 1992

"... of the vi- sion community over the last decade. Yet it is common knowledge that existing solutions work well ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 894 (37 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Inferring scene geometry and camera motion from a stream of images is possible in principle, but is an ill-conditioned problem when the objects are distant with respect to their size. We have developed a factorization method that can overcome this difficulty by recovering shape and motion under orthography without computing depth as an intermediate step. An image stream can be represented by the 2FxP measurement matrix of the image coordinates of P points tracked through F frames. We show that under orthographic projection this matrix is of rank 3. Based on this observation, the factorization method uses the singular-value decomposition technique to factor the measurement matrix into two matrices which represent object shape and camera rotation respectively. Two of the three translation components are computed in a preprocessing stage. The method can also handle and obtain a full solution from a partially filled-in measurement matrix that may result from occlusions or tracking failures. The method gives accurate results, and does not introduce smoothing in either shape or motion. We demonstrate this with a series of experiments on laboratory and outdoor image streams, with and without occlusions. 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7434-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7434_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:47:28">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=697F37CFA5C6171A948BFBD4A3D790C8?doi=10.1.1.399.6138&amp;rank=4</link><title>Monopolistic competition and optimum product diversity</title><description>Monopolistic competition and optimum product diversity

by K. Dixit, Joseph E. Stiglitz, K. Dixit, Joseph, E. Stiglitz \- American Economic Review , 1977

"... is whether a market solution will yield the socially optimum kinds and quantities of commodities. It is well ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 767 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

you have obtained prior permission, you may not download an entire issue of a journal or multiple copies of articles, and you may use content in the JSTOR archive only for your personal, non-commercial use. Please contact the publisher regarding any further use of this work. Publisher contact information may be obtained at</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7434-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7434_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:51:58">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=697F37CFA5C6171A948BFBD4A3D790C8?doi=10.1.1.29.5833&amp;rank=5</link><title>Context-Aware Computing Applications</title><description>Context-Aware Computing Applications

by Bill N. Schilit , Norman Adams, Roy Want \- IN PROCEEDINGS OF THE WORKSHOP ON MOBILE COMPUTING SYSTEMS AND APPLICATIONS , 1994

"... and locations covering the office, meeting room, home, airport, hotel, classroom, market, bus, etc. Users might ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 659 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper describes software that examines and reacts to an individual's changing context. Such software can promote and mediate people's interactions with devices, computers, and other people, and it can help navigate unfamiliar places. We believe that a limited amount of information covering a person's proximate environment is most important for this form of computing since the interesting part of the world around us is what we can see, hear, and touch. In this paper we define context-aware computing, and describe four categories of context-aware applications: proximate selection, automatic contextual reconfiguration, contextual information and commands, and context-triggered actions. Instances of these application types have been prototyped on the PARCTAB, a wireless, palm-sized computer.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7434-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7434_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:52:31">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=697F37CFA5C6171A948BFBD4A3D790C8?doi=10.1.1.99.8377&amp;rank=6</link><title>The interdisciplinary study of coordination</title><description>The interdisciplinary study of coordination

by Thomas W. Malone, Kevin Crowston \- ACM Computing Surveys , 1994

"... desirable? What is necessary for them to work well? To some extent, we can answer these questions ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 535 (14 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This survey characterizes an emerging research area, sometimes called coordination theory, that focuses on the interdisciplinary study of coordination. Research in this area uses and extends ideas about coordination from disciplines such as computer science, organization theory, operations research, economics, linguistics, and psychology. A key insight of the framework presented here is that coordination can be seen as the process of managing dependencies among activities. Further progress, therefore, should be possible by characterizing different kinds of dependencies and identifying the coordination processes that can be used to manage them. A variety of processes are analyzed from this perspective, and commonalities across disciplines are identified. Processes analyzed include those for managing shared resources, producer/consumer relationships, simultaneity constraints, and tank/subtask dependencies. Section 3 summarizes ways of applying a coordination perspective in three different domains: (1) understanding the effects of information technology on human organizations and markets, (2) designing cooperative work tools, and (3) designing distributed and parallel computer systems. In the final section, elements of a research</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7434-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7434_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:56:25">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=697F37CFA5C6171A948BFBD4A3D790C8?doi=10.1.1.48.6641&amp;rank=7</link><title>Region Competition: Unifying Snakes, Region Growing, and Bayes/MDL for Multi-band Image Segmentation</title><description>Region Competition: Unifying Snakes, Region Growing, and Bayes/MDL for Multi-band Image Segmentation

by Song Chun Zhu, Alan Yuille \- IEEE Transactions on Pattern Analysis and Machine Intelligence , 1996

"... generalization to the multi-dimensional case is called Hotelling's test [17]). If this statistic is below a ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 633 (20 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We present a novel statistical and variational approach to image segmentation based on a new algorithm named region competition. This algorithm is derived by minimizing a generalized Bayes/MDL criterion using the variational principle. The algorithm is guaranteed to converge to a local minimum and combines aspects of snakes/balloons and region growing. Indeed the classic snakes/balloons and region growing algorithms can be directly derived from our approach. We provide theoretical analysis of region competition including accuracy of boundary location, criteria for initial conditions, and the relationship to edge detection using filters. It is straightforward to generalize the algorithm to multiband segmentation and we demonstrate it on grey level images, color images and texture images. The novel color model allows us to eliminate intensity gradients and shadows, thereby obtaining segmentation based on the albedos of objects. It also helps detect highlight regions. 1 Division of Appli...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7434-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7434_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:59:26">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=697F37CFA5C6171A948BFBD4A3D790C8?doi=10.1.1.22.8990&amp;rank=8</link><title>Stochastic Perturbation Theory</title><description>Stochastic Perturbation Theory

by G. W. Stewart , 1988

"... , it is well known that if A is nonsingular, then (A + E) \Gamma1 = A \Gamma1 \Gamma A \Gamma1 EA \Gamma ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 617 (31 self) \- Add to MetaCart

. In this paper classical matrix perturbation theory is approached from a probabilistic point of view. The perturbed quantity is approximated by a first-order perturbation expansion, in which the perturbation is assumed to be random. This permits the computation of statistics estimating the variation in the perturbed quantity. Up to the higher-order terms that are ignored in the expansion, these statistics tend to be more realistic than perturbation bounds obtained in terms of norms. The technique is applied to a number of problems in matrix perturbation theory, including least squares and the eigenvalue problem. Key words. perturbation theory, random matrix, linear system, least squares, eigenvalue, eigenvector, invariant subspace, singular value AMS(MOS) subject classifications. 15A06, 15A12, 15A18, 15A52, 15A60 1. Introduction. Let A be a matrix and let F be a matrix valued function of A. Two principal problems of matrix perturbation theory are the following. Given a matrix E, pr...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7434-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7434_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:03:27">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=697F37CFA5C6171A948BFBD4A3D790C8?doi=10.1.1.33.4726&amp;rank=9</link><title>Probabilistic Principal Component Analysis</title><description>Probabilistic Principal Component Analysis

by Michael E. Tipping, Chris M. Bishop \- Journal of the Royal Statistical Society, Series B , 1999

"... (PCA) (Jolliffe 1986) is a well-established technique for dimensionality reduction, and a chapter ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 476 (5 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Principal component analysis (PCA) is a ubiquitous technique for data analysis and processing, but one which is not based upon a probability model. In this paper we demonstrate how the principal axes of a set of observed data vectors may be determined through maximum-likelihood estimation of parameters in a latent variable model closely related to factor analysis. We consider the properties of the associated likelihood function, giving an EM algorithm for estimating the principal subspace iteratively, and discuss, with illustrative examples, the advantages conveyed by this probabilistic approach to PCA. Keywords: Principal component analysis</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7434-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7434_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:05:36">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=697F37CFA5C6171A948BFBD4A3D790C8?doi=10.1.1.202.2386&amp;rank=10</link><title>A Survey of active network Research</title><description>A Survey of active network Research

by David L. Tennenhouse, Jonathan M. Smith \- IEEE Communications , 1997

"... wellSource Active Router Legacy Router Active Router Destination active client active server user ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 460 (20 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Active networks are a novel approach to network architecture in which the switches of the network perform customized computations on the messages flowing through them. This approach is motivated by both lead user applications, which perform user-driven computation at nodes within the network today, and the emergence of mobile code technologies that make dynamic network service innovation attainable. In this paper, we discuss two approaches to the realization of active networks and provide a snapshot of the current research issues and activities. Introduction – What Are Active Networks? In an active network, the routers or switches of the network perform customized computations on the messages flowing through them. For example, a user of an active network could send a “trace ” program to each router and arrange for the program to be executed when their packets are processed. Figure 1 illustrates how the routers of an IP</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>