<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7435">trendy bar Berlin</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:09:17" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7435-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7435_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:09:19">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=4A85B849D611B6B948102AF90A818713?doi=10.1.1.94.7224&amp;rank=1</link><title>Ant Colony Optimization</title><description>Ant Colony Optimization

by Christian Blum, Marco Dorigo , 2004

"... 3172, pp. 118–129, 2004. c○ Springer-Verlag Berlin Heidelberg 2004 Deception in Ant Colony Optimization ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 591 (60 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract. The search process of a metaheuristic is sometimes misled. This may be caused by features of the tackled problem instance, by features of the algorithm, or by the chosen solution representation. In the field of evolutionary computation, the first case is called deception and the second case is referred to as bias. In this work we formalize the notions of deception and bias for ant colony optimization. We formally define first order deception in ant colony optimization, which corresponds to deception as being described in evolutionary computation. Furthermore, we formally define second order deception in ant colony optimization, which corresponds to the bias introduced by components of the algorithm in evolutionary computation. We show by means of an example that second order deception is a potential problem in ant colony optimization algorithms. 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7435-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7435_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:13:24">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=4A85B849D611B6B948102AF90A818713?doi=10.1.1.224.3197&amp;rank=2</link><title>The eyes have it: A task by data type taxonomy for information visualizations</title><description>The eyes have it: A task by data type taxonomy for information visualizations

by Ben Shneiderman \- In IEEE Symposium on Visual Languages , 1996

"... psychologists, statisticians, and graphic designers (Berlin, 1983; Cleveland, 1993; Tufte, 1983, 1990) offer ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 748 (23 self) \- Add to MetaCart

ben @ cs.umd.edu A useful starting point for designing advanced graphical user interjaces is the Visual lnformation-Seeking Mantra: overview first, zoom and filter, then details on demand. But this is only a starting point in trying to understand the rich and varied set of information visualizations that have been proposed in recent years. This paper offers a task by data type taxonomy with seven data types (one-, two-, three-dimensional datu, temporal and multi-dimensional data, and tree and network data) and seven tasks (overview, Zoom, filter, details-on-demand, relate, history, and extracts). Everything points to the conclusion that the phrase 'the language of art ' is more</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7435-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7435_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:15:03">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=4A85B849D611B6B948102AF90A818713?doi=10.1.1.130.151&amp;rank=3</link><title>Applied Nonparametric Regression</title><description>Applied Nonparametric Regression

by Wolfgang Härdle , 1994

"... ﻿Applied Nonparametric Regression Wolfgang Härdle Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 467 (9 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7435-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7435_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:18:31">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=4A85B849D611B6B948102AF90A818713?doi=10.1.1.109.6628&amp;rank=4</link><title>An algorithm for pronominal anaphora resolution</title><description>An algorithm for pronominal anaphora resolution

by Herbert J Leass \- Computational Linguistics , 1994

"... Research Center † Sietec Systemtechnik (Siemens AG), D-13623 Berlin, Germany. E-mail: leass ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 325 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper presents an algorithm for identifying the noun phrase antecedents of third person pronouns and lexical anaphors (reflexives and reciprocals). The algorithm applies to the syntactic representations generated by McCord's Slot Grammar parser, and relies on salience measures derived from syntactic structure and a simple dynamic model of attentional state. Like the parser, the algorithm is implemented in Prolog. The authors have tested it extensively on computer manual texts, and conducted a blind test on manual text containing 360 pronoun occurrences. The algorithm successfully identifies the antecedent of the pronoun for 86 % of these pronoun occurrences. The relative contributions of the algorithm's components to its overall success rate in this blind test are examined. Experiments were conducted with an enhancement of the algorithm which contributes statistically modelled information concerning semantic and real world relations to the algorithm's decision procedure. Interestingly, this enhancement only marginally improves the algorithm's performance (by 2%). The algorithm is compared with other approaches to anaphora resolution which have been proposed in the literature. In particular, the search procedure of Hobbs ' algorithm was implemented in the Slot Grammar framework and applied to the sentences in the blind test set. The authors ' algorithm achieves a higher rate of success (4%) than Hobbs ' algorithm. The relation of the algorithm to the centering approach is discussed, as well as to models of anaphora resolution which invoke a variety of informational factors in ranking antecedent candidates. 1.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7435-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7435_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:21:42">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=4A85B849D611B6B948102AF90A818713?doi=10.1.1.1.5374&amp;rank=5</link><title>Short Signatures without Random Oracles</title><description>Short Signatures without Random Oracles

by Dan Boneh, Xavier Boyen , 2004

"... --- EUROCRYPT 2004, volume 3027 of Lecture Notes in Computer Science, pages 56--73, Berlin: SpringerVerlag, 2004 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 265 (14 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We describe a short signature scheme which is existentially unforgeable under a chosen message attack without using random oracles. The security of our scheme depends on a new complexity assumption we call the Strong Di#e-Hellman assumption. This assumption has similar properties to the Strong RSA assumption, hence the name. Strong RSA was previously used to construct signature schemes without random oracles. However, signatures generated by our scheme are much shorter and simpler than signatures from schemes based on Strong RSA.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7435-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7435_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:25:24">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=4A85B849D611B6B948102AF90A818713?doi=10.1.1.205.3511&amp;rank=6</link><title>ESP: Path-Sensitive Program Verification in Polynomial Time</title><description>ESP: Path-Sensitive Program Verification in Polynomial Time

by Manuvir Das, Sorin Lerner, Mark Seigle , 2002

"... and/or a fee. PLDI’02, June 17-19, 2002, Berlin, Germany. Copyright 2002 ACM 1 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 250 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

In this paper, we present a new algorithm for partial program verification that runs in polynomial time and space. We are interested in checking that a program satisfies a given temporal safety property. Our insight is that by accurately modeling only those branches in a program for which the property-related behavior differs along the arms of the branch, we can design an algorithm that is accurate enough to verify the program with respect to the given property, without paying the potentially exponential cost of full pathsensitive analysis. We have implemented this “property simulation ” algorithm as part of a partial verification tool called ESP. We present the results of applying ESP to the problem of verifying the file I/O behavior of a version of the GNU C compiler (gcc, 140,000 LOC). We are able to prove that all of the 646 calls to fprintf in the source code of gcc are guaranteed to print to valid, open files. Our results show that property simulation scales to large programs and is accurate enough to verify meaningful properties.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7435-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7435_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:26:16">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=4A85B849D611B6B948102AF90A818713?doi=10.1.1.111.2041&amp;rank=7</link><title>Authenticated encryption: Relations among notions and analysis of the generic composition paradigm</title><description>Authenticated encryption: Relations among notions and analysis of the generic composition paradigm

by Mihir Bellare, Chanathip Namprempre , 2000

"... -7, 2000. Springer-Verlag, Berlin, Germany. This is the full version. Authenticated Encryption: Relations ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 222 (22 self) \- Add to MetaCart

and analysis of the generic composition paradigm</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7435-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7435_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:27:38">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=4A85B849D611B6B948102AF90A818713?doi=10.1.1.28.9219&amp;rank=8</link><title>The Great Reversals: The Politics of Financial Development in the 20th Century</title><description>The Great Reversals: The Politics of Financial Development in the 20th Century

by Raghuram G. Rajan, Luigi Zingales, Roger Laeven, Galina Ovtcharova, Nahid Rahman, Sofia Ramos, Ruy Ribeiro, Amir Sasson , 2001

"... benefited from comments by Oren Bar-Gill, Lucian Bebchuk, Charles Borden, Peter Hogfeldt, Louis Kaplow, Fred ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 210 (7 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Indicators of the development of the financial sector do not improve monotonically over time. In particular, we find that by most measures, countries were more financially developed in 1913 than in 1980 and only recently have they surpassed their 1913 levels. This pattern cannot be explained by structural theories that attribute cross-country differences in financial development to time-invariant factors, such as a country's legal origin or culture. We propose an "interest group" theory of financial development where incumbents oppose financial development because it breeds competition. The theory predicts that incumbents' opposition will be weaker when an economy allows both cross-border trade and capital flows. This theory can go some way in accounting for the cross-country differences and the time series variation of financial development. When we recognize that different kinds of institutional heritages afford different scope for private interests to express themselves, we obtain a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7435-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7435_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:29:12">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=4A85B849D611B6B948102AF90A818713?doi=10.1.1.11.3056&amp;rank=9</link><title>Efficient and Precise Datarace Detection for Multithreaded Object-Oriented Programs</title><description>Efficient and Precise Datarace Detection for Multithreaded Object-Oriented Programs

by Jong-deok Choi, Keunwoo Lee, Alexey Loginov, Robert O'Callahan, Vivek Sarkar, Manu Sridharan , 2002

"... and/or a fee. To Appear: PLDI’02, June 17-19, 2002, Berlin, Germany. Copyright 2002 ACM 1 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 181 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We present a novel approach to dynamic datarace detection for multithreaded object-oriented programs. Past techniques for onthe -fly datarace detection either sacrificed precision for performance, leading to many false positive datarace reports, or maintained precision but incurred significant overheads in the range of 3# to 30#. In contrast, our approach results in very few false positives and runtime overhead in the 13% to 42% range, making it both efficient and precise. This performance improvement is the result of a unique combination of complementary static and dynamic optimization techniques.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7435-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7435_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:32:46">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=4A85B849D611B6B948102AF90A818713?doi=10.1.1.255.9295&amp;rank=10</link><title>Hot Stars: Old-Fashioned or Trendy?</title><description>Hot Stars: Old-Fashioned or Trendy?

by A. W. A. Pauldrach , 2003

"... ﻿Hot Stars: Old-Fashioned or Trendy? A. W. A. Pauldrach Institut für Astronomie und Astrophysik der ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Spectroscopic analyses with the intention of the interpretation of the UV-spectra of the brightest stars as individuals – supernovae – or as components of starforming regions – massive O stars – provide a powerful tool with great astrophysical potential for the determination of extragalactic distances and of the chemical composition of star-forming galaxies even at high redshifts. The perspectives of already initiated work with the new generation of tools for quantitative UV-spectroscopy of Hot Stars that have been developed during the last two decades are presented and the status of the continuing effort to construct corresponding models for Hot Star atmospheres is reviewed. Since the physics of the atmospheres of Hot Stars are strongly affected by velocity expansion dominating the spectra at all wavelength ranges, hydrodynamic model atmospheres for O-type stars and explosion models for Supernovae of Type Ia are necessary as basis for the synthesis and analysis of the spectra. It is shown that stellar parameters, abundances, and stellar wind properties can</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>