<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7437">free aldi meyola songs</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:57:40" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7437-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7437_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:57:42">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=7F5D9301B542774C45C2A9353C11EB06?doi=10.1.1.154.1828&amp;rank=1</link><title>Global Environmental Policy and Global Trade Policy</title><description>Global Environmental Policy and Global Trade Policy

by Jeffrey Frankel , 2008

"... University, and Joseph E. Aldy, Fellow, Resources for the Future. For more information, see the Project ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 7 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7437-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7437_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:03:22">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=7F5D9301B542774C45C2A9353C11EB06?doi=10.1.1.177.6679&amp;rank=2</link><title>Global Environment and . . .</title><description>Global Environment and . . .

by Jeffrey Frankel

"... For the Harvard Project on International Climate Agreements, Directed by Joe Aldy and Rob Stavins Forthcoming ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

be a disaster for supporters of the WTO and &lt;em&gt;free&lt;/em&gt; trade as much as for supporters of the Kyoto Protocol</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7437-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7437_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:05:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=7F5D9301B542774C45C2A9353C11EB06?doi=10.1.1.152.1982&amp;rank=3</link><title>16 Global environment and trade</title><description>16 Global environment and trade

by Jeffrey Frankel

"... of the WTO and free trade as much as for supporters of the Kyoto Protocol and environmental protection ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7437-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7437_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:07:15">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=7F5D9301B542774C45C2A9353C11EB06?doi=10.1.1.152.2690&amp;rank=4</link><title>ORDER The Globalisation Council</title><description>ORDER The Globalisation Council

by Harpel Professor, Input From Joseph Aldy, Globalisation Council, Original Susan Berg

"... capable research assistance by Danxia Xie; valuable input from Joseph Aldy, Scott Barrett, Jagdish ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

www.sweden.gov.se/globalisation Preface Is globalization bad for the environment? Trade has some of its effects through the channel of accelerating economic growth, because trade contributes to growth analogously to investment, technological progress, and so on. Although growth is bad for air and water pollution at the initial stages of industrialization, later on it reduces pollution as countries become rich enough to pay to clean up their environments. The report Environmental Effects of International Trade considers whether globalisation has damaged environmental goals. Empirical studies of cross-country data generally find no detrimental effects of trade on some measures of environmental degradation such as local SO2 (sulphur dioxide) air pollution, controlling for income. The evidence does suggest that trade and growth can exacerbate other</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7437-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7437_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:08:48">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=7F5D9301B542774C45C2A9353C11EB06?doi=10.1.1.218.1414&amp;rank=5</link><title>Environmental Effects of . . .</title><description>Environmental Effects of . . .

by Jeffrey Frankel , 2009

"... by the observation that CO2 is a global externality, which cannot be addressed at the national level due to the free ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>