<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7445">marathon training</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:57:00" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7445-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7445_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:57:02">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A3D5FEBCBDE9897A3C25D1601001A56F?doi=10.1.1.226.1424&amp;rank=1</link><title>Marathon County</title><description>Marathon County

by Amber M. Ruff-brei , 2011

"... the Marathon County Sheriff’s Department. The officers are trained to work at both the adult jail and the JDC ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

An EEO/AA employer, University of Wisconsin-Extension provides equal opportunities in employment and programming, including Title IX and ADA requirements. POSITIVE YOUTH DEVELOPMENT JUVENILE JUSTICE ii Even though juvenile delinquency rates have gone down over the past decade, delinquency is still a problem that affects families, communities, government, and society. This paper examines the facilities, education, and the treatment aspects of the juvenile justice system. The traditional approach to working with juvenile delinquents is to increase punishment; this paper looks at ways of incorporating positive youth development principles into the juvenile justice system. POSITIVE YOUTH DEVELOPMENT JUVENILE JUSTICE iii</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7445-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7445_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:00:16">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A3D5FEBCBDE9897A3C25D1601001A56F?doi=10.1.1.130.9869&amp;rank=2</link><title>Running The Marathon</title><description>Running The Marathon

by William Cowan, Robin Cowan, Patrick Llerena, William Cowan, Robin Cowan, Patrick Llerena, Université Louis Pasteur, Jel O, William Cowan, Robin Cowan, Patrick Llerena

"... ﻿#2008-014 Running The Marathon William Cowan, Robin Cowan and Patrick Llerena Working Paper Series ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

This paper also circulates as a working paper of BETA, Université Louis Pasteur,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7445-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7445_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:01:29">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A3D5FEBCBDE9897A3C25D1601001A56F?doi=10.1.1.358.2991&amp;rank=3</link><title>the 10-km marathon swim</title><description>the 10-km marathon swim

by Renata R. T. Castro, Ii Fern, A Sns Mendes

"... marathon swim Renata R. T. Castro, I,II Fernanda SNS Mendes, II Antonio Claudio L. Nobrega II doi: 10 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Risk of hypothermia in a new olympic event:</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7445-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7445_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:03:20">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A3D5FEBCBDE9897A3C25D1601001A56F?doi=10.1.1.384.1331&amp;rank=4</link><title>• Applications: Suggestions for the MT Marathon week.</title><description>• Applications: Suggestions for the MT Marathon week.

by unknown authors , 2009

"... ’s code. • Applications: Suggestions for the MT Marathon week. Jan 26, 2009 TectoMT for Plaintext Freaks 1 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

• Debugging someone else’s code.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7445-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7445_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:05:37">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A3D5FEBCBDE9897A3C25D1601001A56F?doi=10.1.1.358.3866&amp;rank=5</link><title>Creatine Kinase Elevations in Marathon Runners: Relationship to Training and Competition</title><description>Creatine Kinase Elevations in Marathon Runners: Relationship to Training and Competition

by Arthur J, Robert E. Lopez , 1980

"... in Marathon Runners: Relationship to Training and Competition ARTHUR J. SIEGEL, M.D., LAWRENCE M. SILVERMAN ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

injury. Limited data exist on CK levels in conditioned athletes after endurance &lt;em&gt;training&lt;/em&gt; and competition</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7445-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7445_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:07:28">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A3D5FEBCBDE9897A3C25D1601001A56F?doi=10.1.1.27.8570&amp;rank=6</link><title>An Experimental Comparison of Range Image Segmentation Algorithms</title><description>An Experimental Comparison of Range Image Segmentation Algorithms

by Adam Hoover, Gillian Jean-Baptiste, Xiaoyi Jiang, Patrick J. Flynn, Horst Bunke, Dmitry Goldgof, Kevin Bowyer, David Eggert, Andrew Fitzgibbon, Robert Fisher , 1996

"... as the code for the comparison tool and the segmentation algorithms presented herein, are available via http://marathon ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 228 (15 self) \- Add to MetaCart

A methodology for evaluating range image segmentation algorithms is proposed. This methodology involves (a) a common set of 40 laser range finder images and 40 structured light scanner images that have manually specified ground truth and (b) a set of defined performance metrics for instances of correctly segmented, missed and noise regions, over- and under-segmentation, and accuracy of the recovered geometry. A tool is used to objectively compare a machine generated segmentation against the specified ground truth. Four research groups have contributed to evaluate their own algorithm for segmenting a range image into planar patches.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7445-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7445_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:09:52">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A3D5FEBCBDE9897A3C25D1601001A56F?doi=10.1.1.350.4698&amp;rank=7</link><title>Metabolic Factors Limiting Performance in Marathon Runners</title><description>Metabolic Factors Limiting Performance in Marathon Runners

by Benjamin I. Rapoport , 2010

"... ﻿Metabolic Factors Limiting Performance in Marathon Runners Benjamin I. Rapoport 1,2 * 1 M.D.– Ph ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

major &lt;em&gt;marathon&lt;/em&gt;. Of those who attempt to race over the &lt;em&gt;marathon&lt;/em&gt; distance of 26 miles and 385 yards (42</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7445-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7445_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:12:07">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A3D5FEBCBDE9897A3C25D1601001A56F?doi=10.1.1.169.9712&amp;rank=8</link><title>The role of deliberate practice in the acquisition of expert performance</title><description>The role of deliberate practice in the acquisition of expert performance

by K. Anders Ericsson, Ralf Th. Krampe, Clemens Tesch-romer \- Psychological Review , 1993

"... , intensity, and structure of training appear to play a major role. The fastest time for the marathon ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 178 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The theoretical framework presented in this article explains expert performance as the end result of individuals ' prolonged efforts to improve performance while negotiating motivational and external constraints. In most domains of expertise, individuals begin in their childhood a regimen of effortful activities (deliberate practice) designed to optimize improvement. Individual differences, even among elite performers, are closely related to assessed amounts of deliberate practice. Many characteristics once believed to reflect innate talent are actually the result of intense practice extended for a minimum of 10 years. Analysis of expert performance provides unique evidence on the potential and limits of extreme environmental adaptation and learning. Our civilization has always recognized exceptional individuals, whose performance in sports, the arts, and science is vastly superior to that of the rest of the population. Speculations on the causes of these individuals ' extraordinary abilities and performance are as old as the first records of their achievements. Early accounts commonly attribute these individuals' outstanding performance to divine intervention, such as the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7445-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7445_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:15:18">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A3D5FEBCBDE9897A3C25D1601001A56F?doi=10.1.1.41.4403&amp;rank=9</link><title>Adaptive Statistical Language Modeling: A Maximum Entropy Approach</title><description>Adaptive Statistical Language Modeling: A Maximum Entropy Approach

by Ronald Rosenfeld, Jaime Carbonell, Alexander Rudnicky , 1994

"... language model based on the ME approach was trained on the Wall Street Journal corpus, and showed 32 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 177 (5 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Language modeling is the attempt to characterize, capture and exploit regularities in natural language. In statistical language modeling, large amounts of text are used to automatically determine the model's parameters. Language modeling is useful in automatic speech recognition, machine translation, and any other application that processes natural language with incomplete knowledge. In this thesis, I view language as an information source which emits a stream of symbols from a finite alphabet (the vocabulary). The goal of language modeling is then to identify and exploit sources of information in the language stream, so as to minimize its perceived entropy. Most existing statistical language models exploit the immediate past only. To extract information from further back in the document's history, I use trigger pairs as the basic information bearing elements. This allows the model to adapt its expectations to the topic of discourse. Next, statistical evidence from many sources must...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7445-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7445_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:19:45">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A3D5FEBCBDE9897A3C25D1601001A56F?doi=10.1.1.379.4588&amp;rank=10</link><title>Monitoring The Segment Parameters During Long Term Physical Training From Motion Capture Data</title><description>Monitoring The Segment Parameters During Long Term Physical Training From Motion Capture Data

by unknown authors

"... marathon training before running the 2009 Tokyo Marathon. The motion data is recorded on a weekly basis ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

which the candidate followed a 16-week &lt;em&gt;marathon&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;training&lt;/em&gt; before running the 2009 Tokyo &lt;em&gt;Marathon&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>