<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7450">thailand individual travel</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:28:41" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7450-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7450_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:28:43">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A1698E5E31E3E496C43BFD72520D5FBB?doi=10.1.1.145.8411&amp;rank=1</link><title>Ant Colony System: A cooperative learning approach to the traveling salesman problem</title><description>Ant Colony System: A cooperative learning approach to the traveling salesman problem

by Marco Dorigo, Luca Maria Gambardella \- IEEE TRANSACTIONS ON EVOLUTIONARY COMPUTATION , 1997

"... Cooperative Learning Approach to the Traveling Salesman Problem Marco Dorigo, Senior Member, IEEE, and Luca ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 624 (49 self) \- Add to MetaCart

to the &lt;em&gt;traveling&lt;/em&gt; salesman problem (TSP). In the ACS, a set of cooperating agents called ants cooperate to find good</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7450-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7450_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:32:34">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A1698E5E31E3E496C43BFD72520D5FBB?doi=10.1.1.26.1865&amp;rank=2</link><title>The Ant System: Optimization by a colony of cooperating agents</title><description>The Ant System: Optimization by a colony of cooperating agents

by Marco Dorigo, Vittorio Maniezzo, Alberto Colorni \- IEEE TRANSACTIONS ON SYSTEMS, MAN, AND CYBERNETICS-PART B , 1996

"... of the search process. We apply the proposed methodology to the classical Traveling Salesman Problem (TSP ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 802 (47 self) \- Add to MetaCart

to the classical &lt;em&gt;Traveling&lt;/em&gt; Salesman Problem (TSP), and report simulation results. We also discuss parameter</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7450-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7450_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:36:31">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A1698E5E31E3E496C43BFD72520D5FBB?doi=10.1.1.103.8926&amp;rank=3</link><title>How bad is selfish routing?</title><description>How bad is selfish routing?

by Tim Roughgarden, Éva Tardos \- JOURNAL OF THE ACM , 2002

"... such that the sum of all travel times—the total latency—is minimized. In many settings, it may be expensive ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 516 (27 self) \- Add to MetaCart

such that the sum of all &lt;em&gt;travel&lt;/em&gt; times—the total latency—is minimized. In many settings, it may be expensive</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7450-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7450_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:40:02">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A1698E5E31E3E496C43BFD72520D5FBB?doi=10.1.1.110.9916&amp;rank=4</link><title>The click modular router</title><description>The click modular router

by Eddie Kohler , 2001

"... elements. Individual elements implement simple router functions like packet classification, queueing ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 873 (26 self) \- Add to MetaCart

router is assembled from packet processing modules called elements. &lt;em&gt;Individual&lt;/em&gt; elements implement simple</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7450-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7450_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:46:14">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A1698E5E31E3E496C43BFD72520D5FBB?doi=10.1.1.117.7097&amp;rank=5</link><title>The Small-World Phenomenon: An Algorithmic Perspective</title><description>The Small-World Phenomenon: An Algorithmic Perspective

by Jon Kleinberg \- in Proceedings of the 32nd ACM Symposium on Theory of Computing , 2000

"... of Milgram’s original findings: that individuals using local information are collectively very effective ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 621 (6 self) \- Add to MetaCart

of Milgram’s original findings: that &lt;em&gt;individuals&lt;/em&gt; using local information are collectively very effective</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7450-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7450_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:51:51">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A1698E5E31E3E496C43BFD72520D5FBB?doi=10.1.1.132.970&amp;rank=6</link><title>Search and replication in unstructured peer-to-peer networks</title><description>Search and replication in unstructured peer-to-peer networks

by Qin Lv, Pei Cao, Edith Cohen, Kai Li, Scott Shenker , 2002

"... in Gnutella does not scale; each individual query gener-ates a large amount of traffic and, as it grows ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 515 (6 self) \- Add to MetaCart

; each &lt;em&gt;individual&lt;/em&gt; query gener-ates a large amount of traffic and, as it grows, the system quickly becomes</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7450-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7450_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:55:46">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A1698E5E31E3E496C43BFD72520D5FBB?doi=10.1.1.13.268&amp;rank=7</link><title>A Survey of Mobility Models for Ad Hoc Network Research</title><description>A Survey of Mobility Models for Ad Hoc Network Research

by Tracy Camp , Jeff Boleng, Vanessa Davies \- WIRELESS COMMUNICATIONS &amp; MOBILE COMPUTING (WCMC): SPECIAL ISSUE ON MOBILE AD HOC NETWORKING: RESEARCH, TRENDS AND APPLICATIONS , 2002

"... and they must occur in reasonable time slots. For example, we would not want MNs to travel in straight lines ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 731 (7 self) \- Add to MetaCart

In the performance evaluation of a protocol for an ad hoc network, the protocol should be tested under realistic conditions including, but not limited to, a sensible transmission range, limited buffer space for the storage of messages, representative data traffic models, and realistic movements of the mobile users (i.e., a mobility model). This paper is a survey of mobility models that are used in the simulations of ad hoc networks. We describe several mobility models that represent mobile nodes whose movements are independent of each other (i.e., entity mobility models) and several mobility models that represent mobile nodes whose movements are dependent on each other (i.e., group mobility models). The goal of this paper is to present a number of mobility models in order to offer researchers more informed choices when they are deciding upon a mobility model to use in their performance evaluations. Lastly, we present simulation results that illustrate the importance of choosing a mobility model in the simulation of an ad hoc network protocol. Specifically, we illustrate how the performance results of an ad hoc network protocol drastically change as a result of changing the mobility model simulated.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7450-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7450_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:59:21">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A1698E5E31E3E496C43BFD72520D5FBB?doi=10.1.1.228.3906&amp;rank=8</link><title>The Hungarian method for the assignment problem</title><description>The Hungarian method for the assignment problem

by H. W. Kuhn, Bryn Yaw \- Naval Res. Logist. Quart , 1955

"... regarded it as a relative of the travelling salesman problem; her work is available only in the form ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 758 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Assuming that numerical scores are available for the performance of each of n persons on each of n jobs, the "assignment problem" is the quest for an assignment of persons to jobs so that the sum of the n scores so obtained is as large as possible. It is shown that ideas latent in the work of two Hungarian mathematicians may be exploited to yield a new method of solving this problem. 1.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7450-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7450_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:02:34">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A1698E5E31E3E496C43BFD72520D5FBB?doi=10.1.1.21.61&amp;rank=9</link><title>Semantic Web Services</title><description>Semantic Web Services

by Sheila A. Mcilraith, Tran Cao Son, Honglei Zeng \- IEEE Intelligent Systems , 2001

"... some task, given a high-level description of the task’s objective. A user might say, “Make the travel ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 517 (20 self) \- Add to MetaCart

hose properties, capabilities, interfaces, and effects are encoded in an unambiguous, machine-understandable form. The realization of the Semantic Web is underway with the development of new AI-inspired content markup languages, such as OIL, 3 DAML+OIL (www.daml.org/2000/10/daml-oil), and DAML-L (the last two are members of the DARPA Agent Markup Language (DAML) family of languages). 4 These languages have a well-defined semantics and enable the markup and manipulation of complex taxonomic and logical relations between entities on the Web. A fundamental component of the Semantic Web will be the markup of Web services to make them computer-interpretable, use-apparent, and agent-ready. This article addresses precisely this component. We present an approach to Web service markup that provides an agent-independent declarative API capturing the data and metadata associated with a service together with specifications of its pro</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7450-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7450_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:03:20">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A1698E5E31E3E496C43BFD72520D5FBB?doi=10.1.1.31.9786&amp;rank=10</link><title>Understanding and Using Context</title><description>Understanding and Using Context

by Anind K. Dey \- Personal and Ubiquitous Computing , 2001

"... , however, can be used to characterize the user's situation. If a user is traveling with other people ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 506 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Context is a poorly used source of information in our computing environments. As a result, we have an impoverished understanding of what context is and how it can be used. In this paper, we provide an operational definition of context and discuss the different ways that context can be used by context-aware applications. We also present the Context Toolkit, an architecture that supports the building of these context-aware applications. We discuss the features and abstractions in the toolkit that make the task of building applications easier. Finally, we introduce a new abstraction, a situation, which we believe will provide additional support to application designers. 1. Introduction Humans are quite successful at conveying ideas to each other and reacting appropriately. This is due to many factors: the richness of the language they share, the common understanding of how the world works, and an implicit understanding of everyday situations. When humans talk with humans, they are able...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>