<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7451">buy animal farm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:07:58" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7451-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7451_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:07:59">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1C56BC725447DABAFFE48D506B64906E?doi=10.1.1.201.9742&amp;rank=1</link><title>Capitalism, Socialism and Democracy</title><description>Capitalism, Socialism and Democracy

by Joseph A. Schumpeter, In The S, Joseph A. Schumpeter , 1942

"... increase sales, and they add jobs. On the downside of the churn, losers find their customers aren’t buying ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 676 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

or method of economic change and not only never is but never can be stationary.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7451-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7451_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:08:36">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1C56BC725447DABAFFE48D506B64906E?doi=10.1.1.320.2401&amp;rank=2</link><title>Credit Cycles</title><description>Credit Cycles

by Nobuhiro Kiyotaki, John Moore \- Journal of Political Economy , 1997

"... that in equilibrium the farmer will not want to consume more than the bruised fruit: the overall return from farming ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 768 (13 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We construct a model of a dynamic economy in which lenders cannot force borrowers to repay their debts unless the debts are secured. In such an economy, durable assets play a dual role: not only are they factors of production, but they also serve as collateral for loans. The dynamic interaction between credit limits and asset prices turns out to be a powerful transmission mechanism by which the effects of shocks persist, amplify, and spill over to other sectors. We show that small, temporary shocks to technology or income distribution can generate large, persistent fluctuations in output and asset prices. I.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7451-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7451_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:12:26">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1C56BC725447DABAFFE48D506B64906E?doi=10.1.1.11.6264&amp;rank=3</link><title>Agents and the Semantic Web</title><description>Agents and the Semantic Web

by James Hendler \- IEEE INTELLIGENT SYSTEMS , 2001

"... , for example, a cow and a donkey would be linked to barnyard animals, mammals, animals, and so forth. While ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1638 (12 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Many challenges of bringing communicating multiagent systems to the Web require ontologies. The integration of agent technology and ontologies could significantly affect the use of Web services and the ability to extend programs to perform tasks for users more efficiently and with less human intervention.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7451-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7451_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:14:10">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1C56BC725447DABAFFE48D506B64906E?doi=10.1.1.119.2204&amp;rank=4</link><title>Intelligent agents: Theory and practice</title><description>Intelligent agents: Theory and practice

by Michael Wooldridge, Nicholas R. Jennings \- The Knowledge Engineering Review , 1995

"... -like graphical icon or an animated face (Maes, 1994a, p36) — for obvious reasons, such agents are of particular ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1084 (80 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The concept of an agent has become important in both Artificial Intelligence (AI) and mainstream computer science. Our aim in this paper is to point the reader at what we perceive to be the most important theoretical and practical issues associated with the design and construction of intelligent agents. For convenience, we divide these issues into three areas (though as the reader will see, the divisions are at times somewhat arbitrary). Agent theory is concerned with the question of what an agent is, and the use of mathematical formalisms for representing and reasoning about the properties of agents. Agent architectures can be thought of as software engineering models of agents; researchers in this area are primarily concerned with the problem of designing software or hardware systems that will satisfy the prop-erties specified by agent theorists. Finally, agent languages are software systems for programming and experimenting with agents; these languages may embody principles proposed by theorists. The paper is not intended to serve as a tutorial introduction to all the issues mentioned; we hope instead simply to identify the most important issues, and point to work that elaborates on them. The article includes a short review of current and potential applications of agent technology.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7451-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7451_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:17:04">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1C56BC725447DABAFFE48D506B64906E?doi=10.1.1.2.7039&amp;rank=5</link><title>From SHIQ and RDF to OWL: The Making of a Web Ontology Language</title><description>From SHIQ and RDF to OWL: The Making of a Web Ontology Language

by Ian Horrocks, Peter F. Patel-Schneider, Frank Van Harmelen \- Journal of Web Semantics , 2003

"... they can facilitate communication between buying and selling agents by providing a common vocabulary ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 468 (45 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The OWL Web Ontology Language is a new formal language for representing ontologies in the Semantic Web. OWL has features from several families of representation languages, including primarily Description Logics and frames. OWL also shares many characteristics with RDF, the W3C base of the Semantic Web. In this paper we discuss how the philosophy and features of OWL can be traced back to these older formalisms, with modifications driven by several other constraints on OWL. Several interesting problems...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7451-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7451_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:18:29">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1C56BC725447DABAFFE48D506B64906E?doi=10.1.1.21.988&amp;rank=6</link><title>Hierarchically Classifying Documents Using Very Few Words</title><description>Hierarchically Classifying Documents Using Very Few Words

by Daphne Koller, Mehran Sahami , 1997

"... to documents about agriculture, which distinguishes animal husbandry from crop farming. Each of these subtasks ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 421 (9 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The proliferation of topic hierarchies for text documents has resulted in a need for tools that automatically classify new documents within such hierarchies. Existing classification schemes which ignore the hierarchical structure and treat the topics as separate classes are often inadequate in text classification where the there is a large number of classes and a huge number of relevant features needed to distinguish between them. We propose an approach that utilizes the hierarchical topic structure to decompose the classification task into a set of simpler problems, one at each node in the classification tree. As we show, each of these smaller problems can be solved accurately by focusing only on a very small set of features, those relevant to the task at hand. This set of relevant features varies widely throughout the hierarchy, so that, while the overall relevant feature set may be large, each classifier only examines a small subset. The use of reduced feature sets allows us to util...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7451-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7451_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:20:37">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1C56BC725447DABAFFE48D506B64906E?doi=10.1.1.177.4643&amp;rank=7</link><title>Games and decisions</title><description>Games and decisions

by Debra Edwards Ph. D , 1957

"... for registered resmethrin products. • Products labeled for use on Livestock, Farm Animals, and Pets (Direct ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 416 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7451-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7451_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:22:32">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1C56BC725447DABAFFE48D506B64906E?doi=10.1.1.178.6588&amp;rank=8</link><title>The Theory of Economic Regulation</title><description>The Theory of Economic Regulation

by George J. Stigler \- The Bell Journal of Economics and Management Science , 1971

"... in states with a substantial number of trucks on farms: the powerful agricultural interests would insist ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 405 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The potential usex of public resources and powers to improve the economic stuius of economic groups (such as industries and occupations) are analyzed to provide a scheme of the demand for regulation. The characteristics of the political process which allow relatively small groups to obtain such regulation is then sketched lo provide elemenls of a theory of supply of regulation. A variety of empirical evidence and illustration is also presented. W The state—the machinery and power of the state—is a potential resource or threat to every industry in the society. With its power to prohibit or compel, to take or give money, the state can and does selectively help or hurt a vast number of industries. That political juggernaut, the petroleum industry, is an immense consumer of political benefits, and simultaneously the underwriters of marine insurance have their more modest repast. The central tasks of the theory of economic regulation are to explain who will receive the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7451-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7451_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:23:56">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1C56BC725447DABAFFE48D506B64906E?doi=10.1.1.154.5491&amp;rank=9</link><title>Organizations</title><description>Organizations

by North Carolina A, Colin R. W, Earl O. Heady, Harvey J. Gold, Leonard W. Aur, Joseph C. Burns, Donald G. Davenport, Charles E. Main, Larry A. Nelson, Robert S. Sowell, Ronald E. Stinner , 1958

"... State UniversitySmall Farm Systems. • • \- Earl O. Heady University of Iowa ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 396 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Proceedings Editor:</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7451-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7451_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:27:54">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=1C56BC725447DABAFFE48D506B64906E?doi=10.1.1.147.1344&amp;rank=10</link><title>Opinion Mining and Sentiment Analysis</title><description>Opinion Mining and Sentiment Analysis

by Bo Pang, Lillian Lee , 2008

"... applicants from colleagues, or consulted Consumer Reports to decide what dishwasher to buy. But the Internet ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 367 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

An important part of our information-gathering behavior has always been to find out what other people think. With the growing availability and popularity of opinion-rich resources such as online review sites and personal blogs, new opportunities and challenges arise as people now can, and do, actively use information technologies to seek out and understand the opinions of others. The sudden eruption of activity in the area of opinion mining and sentiment analysis, which deals with the computational treatment of opinion, sentiment, and subjectivity in text, has thus occurred at least in part as a direct response to the surge of interest in new systems that deal directly with opinions as a first-class object. This survey covers techniques and approaches that promise to directly enable opinion-oriented information-seeking systems. Our focus is on methods that seek to address the new challenges raised by sentiment-aware applications, as compared to those that are already present in more traditional fact-based analysis. We include materialon summarization of evaluative text and on broader issues regarding privacy, manipulation, and economic impact that the development of opinion-oriented information-access services gives rise to. To facilitate future work, a discussion of available resources, benchmark datasets, and evaluation campaigns is also provided.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>