<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7457">the music man lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:12:11" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7457-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7457_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:12:12">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8BC1149BCFBE728C3F38F3121BD8515C?doi=10.1.1.30.6583&amp;rank=1</link><title>Social Information Filtering: Algorithms for Automating "Word of Mouth"</title><description>Social Information Filtering: Algorithms for Automating "Word of Mouth"

by Upendra Shardanand, Pattie Maes , 1995

"... recommendations for music albums and artists. Ringo's database of users and artists grows dynamically as more ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 871 (17 self) \- Add to MetaCart

recommendations for &lt;em&gt;music&lt;/em&gt; albums and artists. Ringo's database of users and artists grows dynamically as more</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7457-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7457_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:12:47">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8BC1149BCFBE728C3F38F3121BD8515C?doi=10.1.1.153.8488&amp;rank=2</link><title>Affective Computing</title><description>Affective Computing

by R. W. Picard , 1995

"... , or see colors as they hear music. Synesthetic experiences behave as if the senses are cross ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1200 (37 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Recent neurological studies indicate that the role of emotion in human cognition is essential; emotions are not a luxury. Instead, emotions play a critical role in rational decision-making, in perception, in human interaction, and in human intelligence. These facts, combined with abilities computers are acquiring in expressing and recognizing affect, open new areas for research. This paper defines key issues in "affective computing," computing that relates to, arises from, or deliberately influences emotions. New models are suggested for computer recognition of human emotion, and both theoretical and practical applications are described for learning, human-computer interaction, perceptual information retrieval, creative arts and entertainment, human health, and machine intelligence. Significant potential advances in emotion and cognition theory hinge on the development of affective computing, especially in the form of wearable computers. This paper establishes challenges and future directions for this emerging field.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7457-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7457_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:16:52">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8BC1149BCFBE728C3F38F3121BD8515C?doi=10.1.1.149.3392&amp;rank=3</link><title>Basic objects in natural categories</title><description>Basic objects in natural categories

by Eleanor Rosch, Carolyn B. Mervis, Wayne D. Gray, David M, Penny Boyes-braem \- Cognitive Psychology , 1976

"... -occurrence of attributes in the most common taxonomies of man-made and biological objects in our own culture. Experiment 2 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 487 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Categorizations which humans make of the concrete world are not arbitrary but highly determined. In taxonomies of concrete objects, there is one level of abstraction at which the most basic category cuts are made. Basic categories are those which carry the most information, possess the highest category cue validity, and are, thus, the most differentiated from one another. The four experiments of Part I define basic objects by demonstrating that in taxonomies of common concrete nouns in English based on class inclusion, basic objects are the most inclusive categories whose members: (a) possess significant numbers of attributes in common, (b) have motor programs which are similar to one another, (c) have similar shapes, and (d) can be identified from averaged shapes of members of the class. The eight experiments of Part II explore implications of the structure of categories. Basic objects are shown to be the most inclusive categories for which a concrete image of the category as a whole can be formed, to be the first categorizations made during perception of the environment, to be the earliest categories sorted and earliest named by children, and to be the categories</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7457-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7457_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:21:17">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8BC1149BCFBE728C3F38F3121BD8515C?doi=10.1.1.110.961&amp;rank=4</link><title>The architecture of complexity</title><description>The architecture of complexity

by Herbert A. Simon \- Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society , 1962

"... of music, based on such units as movements, parts, themes, phrases, is well known. The hierarchic structure ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 382 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

A number of proposals have been advanced in recent years for the development of “general systems theory ” that, abstracting from properties peculiar to physical, biological, or social systems, would be applicable to all of them. 1 We might well feel that, while the goal is laudable, systems of such diverse kinds could hardly be expected to have any nontrivial properties in common. Metaphor and analogy can be helpful, or they can be misleading. All depends on whether the similarities the metaphor captures are significant or superficial. It may not be entirely vain, however, to search for common properties among diverse kinds of complex systems. The ideas that go by the name of cybernetics constitute, if not a theory, at least a point of view that has been proving fruitful over a wide range of applications. 2 It has been useful to look at the behavior of adaptive systems in terms of the concepts of feedback and homeostasis, and to analyze adaptiveness in terms of the theory of selective information. 3 The ideas of feedback and information provide a frame of reference for viewing a wide range of situations, just as do the ideas of evolution, of relativism, of axiomatic method, and of</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7457-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7457_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:21:58">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8BC1149BCFBE728C3F38F3121BD8515C?doi=10.1.1.101.3197&amp;rank=5</link><title>Extracting patterns and relations from the world wide web</title><description>Extracting patterns and relations from the world wide web

by Sergey Brin \- In WebDB Workshop at 6th International Conference on Extending Database Technology, EDBT’98 , 1998

"... The Invisible Man H. G. Wells The Island of Dr. Moreau H. G. Wells The Science Fiction Volume 1 H. G. Wells ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 340 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract. The World Wide Web is a vast resource for information. At the same time it is extremely distributed. A particular type of data such as restaurant lists may be scattered across thousands of independent information sources in many di erent formats. In this paper, we consider the problem of extracting a relation for such a data type from all of these sources automatically. We present a technique which exploits the duality between sets of patterns and relations to grow the target relation starting from a small sample. To test our technique we use it to extract a relation of (author,title) pairs from the World Wide Web. 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7457-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7457_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:23:12">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8BC1149BCFBE728C3F38F3121BD8515C?doi=10.1.1.310.2508&amp;rank=6</link><title>Automatical Composition of Lyrical Songs</title><description>Automatical Composition of Lyrical Songs

by Jukka M. Toivanen, Hannu Toivonen, Ro Valitutti

"... the challenging task of automatically composing lyrical songs with matching musical and lyrical features, and we ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

We address the challenging task of automatically composing &lt;em&gt;lyrical&lt;/em&gt; songs with matching &lt;em&gt;musical&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7457-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7457_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:25:24">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8BC1149BCFBE728C3F38F3121BD8515C?doi=10.1.1.205.8487&amp;rank=7</link><title>Lyric text mining in music mood classification</title><description>Lyric text mining in music mood classification

by Xiao Hu, J. Stephen, Downie Andreas, F. Ehmann \- Proceedings of the International Society for Music Information Retrieval Conference , 2009

"... ﻿10th International Society for Music Information Retrieval Conference (ISMIR 2009) LYRIC TEXT ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 11 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This research examines the role &lt;em&gt;lyric&lt;/em&gt; text can play in improving audio &lt;em&gt;music&lt;/em&gt; mood classification. A</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7457-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7457_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:27:44">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8BC1149BCFBE728C3F38F3121BD8515C?doi=10.1.1.116.3382&amp;rank=8</link><title>From data mining to knowledge discovery in databases</title><description>From data mining to knowledge discovery in databases

by Usama Fayyad, Gregory Piatetsky-shapiro, Padhraic Smyth \- AI Magazine , 1996

"... -domain and proprietary sources. For example, FIREFLY is a personal music-recommendation agent: It asks a user his ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 295 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

■ Data mining and knowledge discovery in databases have been attracting a significant amount of research, industry, and media attention of late. What is all the excitement about? This article provides an overview of this emerging field, clarifying how data mining and knowledge discovery in databases are related both to each other and to related fields, such as machine learning, statistics, and databases. The article mentions particular real-world applications, specific data-mining techniques, challenges involved in real-world applications of knowledge discovery, and current and future research directions in the field. Across a wide variety of fields, data are</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7457-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7457_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:29:18">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8BC1149BCFBE728C3F38F3121BD8515C?doi=10.1.1.11.9216&amp;rank=9</link><title>Mel Frequency Cepstral Coefficients for Music Modeling</title><description>Mel Frequency Cepstral Coefficients for Music Modeling

by Beth Logan \- In International Symposium on Music Information Retrieval , 2000

"... Of all the man-made sounds which influence our lives, speech and music are arguably the most prolific ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 226 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

for speech recognition - and investigate their applicability to modeling &lt;em&gt;music&lt;/em&gt;. In particular, we examine two</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7457-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7457_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:32:02">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=8BC1149BCFBE728C3F38F3121BD8515C?doi=10.1.1.51.6538&amp;rank=10</link><title>Visual Recognition of American Sign Language Using Hidden Markov Models</title><description>Visual Recognition of American Sign Language Using Hidden Markov Models

by Thad E. Starner, Alex Pentland , 1995

"... to "see" its user allows for richer and more varied paradigms of man-machine interaction. Recently ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 281 (14 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Using hidden Markov models (HMM's), an unobstrusive single view camera system is developed that can recognize hand gestures, namely, a subset of American Sign Language (ASL). Previous systems have concentrated on finger spelling or isolated word recognition, often using tethered electronic gloves for input. We achieve high recognition rates for full sentence ASL using only visual cues. A forty word lexicon consisting of personal pronouns, verbs, nouns, and adjectives is used to create 494 randomly constructed five word sentences that are signed by the subject to the computer. The data is separated into a 395 sentence training set and an independent 99 sentence test set. While signing, the 2D position, orientation, and eccentricity of bounding ellipses of the hands are tracked in real time with the assistance of solidly colored gloves. Simultaneous recognition and segmentation of the resultant stream of feature vectors occurs five times faster than real time on an HP 735. With a strong ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>