<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7459">little johnny jokes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:02:13" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7459-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7459_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:02:14">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B787E51A4E6590ABF8A72FE671666A92?doi=10.1.1.109.6332&amp;rank=1</link><title>Grouplens: Applying collaborative filtering to usenet news</title><description>Grouplens: Applying collaborative filtering to usenet news

by Joseph A. Konstan, Bradley N. Miller, David Maltz, Jonathan L. Herlocker, Lee R. Gordon, John Riedl, High Volume \- Communications of the ACM , 1997

"... .humor newsgroup, a group designed for jokes and other humorous postings, value articles based on whether ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 590 (15 self) \- Add to MetaCart

, readers of the rec.humor newsgroup, a group designed for &lt;em&gt;jokes&lt;/em&gt; and other humorous postings, value articles</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7459-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7459_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:04:45">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B787E51A4E6590ABF8A72FE671666A92?doi=10.1.1.152.6298&amp;rank=2</link><title>Why Johnny can’t encrypt: A usability evaluation of PGP</title><description>Why Johnny can’t encrypt: A usability evaluation of PGP

by Alma Whitten, J. D. Tygar

"... ﻿In Proceedings of the 8th USENIX Security Symposium, August 1999, pp. 169-183 Why Johnny Can ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 341 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

User errors cause or contribute to most computer security failures, yet user interfaces for security still tend to be clumsy, confusing, or near-nonexistent. Is this simply due to a failure to apply standard user interface design techniques to security? We argue that, on the contrary, effective security requires a different usability standard, and that it will not be achieved through the user interface design techniques appropriate to other types of consumer software. To test this hypothesis, we performed a case study of a security program which does have a good user interface by general standards: PGP 5.0. Our case study used a cognitive walkthrough analysis together with a laboratory user test to evaluate whether PGP 5.0 can be successfully used by cryptography novices to achieve effective electronic mail security. The analysis found a number of user interface design flaws that may contribute to security failures, and the user test demonstrated that when our test participants were given 90 minutes in which to sign and encrypt a message using PGP 5.0, the majority of them were unable to do so successfully. We conclude that PGP 5.0 is not usable enough to provide effective security for most computer users, despite its attractive graphical user interface, supporting our hypothesis that user interface design for effective security remains an open problem. We close with a brief description of our continuing work on the development and application of user interface design principles and techniques for security. 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7459-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7459_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:05:59">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B787E51A4E6590ABF8A72FE671666A92?doi=10.1.1.17.8065&amp;rank=3</link><title>A Perspective on Psychology and Economics</title><description>A Perspective on Psychology and Economics

by Matthew Rabin , 2001

"... , Switzerland, September 1, 2001, but with the underwear joke removed. I thank Lorenz Goette, Steve Pischke ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 455 (7 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This essay provides a perspective on the trend towards integrating psychology into economics. Some topics are discussed, and arguments are provided for why movement towards greater psychological realism in economics will improve mainstream economics.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7459-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7459_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:08:50">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B787E51A4E6590ABF8A72FE671666A92?doi=10.1.1.13.2424&amp;rank=4</link><title>Mining the Peanut Gallery: Opinion Extraction and Semantic Classification of Product Reviews</title><description>Mining the Peanut Gallery: Opinion Extraction and Semantic Classification of Product Reviews

by Kushal Dave, Steve Lawrence, David M. Pennock , 2003

"... weights (as little as a quarter of the weight of the larger features). Experiments using lower ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 281 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The web contains a wealth of product reviews, but sifting through them is a daunting task. Ideally, an opinion mining tool would process a set of search results for a given item, generating a list of product attributes (quality, features, etc.) and aggregating opinions about each of them (poor, mixed, good). We begin by identifying the unique properties of this problem and develop a method for automatically distinguishing between positive and negative reviews. Our classifier draws on information retrieval techniques for feature extraction and scoring, and the results for various metrics and heuristics vary depending on the testing situation. The best methods work as well as or better than traditional machine learning. When operating on individual sentences collected from web searches, performance is limited due to noise and ambiguity. But in the context of a complete web-based tool and aided by a simple method for grouping sentences into attributes, the results are qualitatively quite useful.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7459-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7459_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:11:36">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B787E51A4E6590ABF8A72FE671666A92?doi=10.1.1.305.1417&amp;rank=5</link><title>A-morphous morphology</title><description>A-morphous morphology

by Stephen R. Anderson, D. Meyer, D. Platt, D. Ridley , 1992

"... left little if any distinctive content to such a field in either of these two domains. In phonology ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 264 (7 self) \- Add to MetaCart

developments in phonology and syntax left &lt;em&gt;little&lt;/em&gt; if any distinctive content to such a field in either</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7459-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7459_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:14:37">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B787E51A4E6590ABF8A72FE671666A92?doi=10.1.1.206.5718&amp;rank=6</link><title>Teaching Johnny not to fall for phish</title><description>Teaching Johnny not to fall for phish

by Ponnurangam Kumaraguru, Steve Sheng, Alessandro Acquisti, Lorrie Faith Cranor, Jason Hong \- ACM Trans. Internet Technol , 2010

"... ﻿Teaching Johnny Not to Fall for Phish PONNURANGAM KUMARAGURU, STEVE SHENG, ALESSANDRO ACQUISTI ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 21 (10 self) \- Add to MetaCart

and phishing websites, &lt;em&gt;little&lt;/em&gt; research has been done in the area of training users to recognize those attacks</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7459-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7459_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:15:22">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B787E51A4E6590ABF8A72FE671666A92?doi=10.1.1.283.8067&amp;rank=7</link><title>Joke Fleer</title><description>Joke Fleer

by Marrit A. Tuinman, Harald J. Hoekstra, Dirk Th. Sleijfer, Damon J. Vidrine, Ellen R. Gritz, Josette E. H. M. Hoekstra-weebers, M. A. Tuinman, H. J. Hoekstra, J. Fleer, D. T. Sleijfer, D. J. Vidrine, E. R. Gritz, J. E. H. M. Hoekstra-weebers, J. E. H. M. Hoekstra-weebers , 2006

"... . Tuinman Harald J. Hoekstra Dirk Th. Sleijfer Joke Fleer Damon J. Vidrine Ellen R. Gritz Josette E. H. M ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Testicular cancer: a longitudinal pilot study on stress response symptoms and quality of life in couples before and after chemotherapy</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7459-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7459_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:15:56">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B787E51A4E6590ABF8A72FE671666A92?doi=10.1.1.29.6454&amp;rank=8</link><title>Bridging Physical and Virtual Worlds with Electronic Tags</title><description>Bridging Physical and Virtual Worlds with Electronic Tags

by Roy Want, Kenneth P. Fishkin, Anuj Gujar, Beverly L. Harrison , 1999

"... , unlike this previous work, we have tried to build invisible interfaces that have little reliance ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 227 (6 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The role of computers in the modern office has tended to split our activities between virtual interactions in the realm of the computer and physical interactions with real objects that have been part of the traditional office infrastructure. This paper discusses a variety of scenarios we have implemented in which the physical world can be invisibly and seamlessly augmented with electronic tags in order to connect physical objects with virtual representations or computational functionality. We demonstrate the utility of linking physical objects to electronic services and actions that are naturally associated with their form (e.g., a dictionary and a web-based translation service). Unlike previous work in this area, we have focused on uniquely combining four inexpensive technologies with off-the-shelf applications, everyday objects, and computational devices. KEYWORDS: RFID tag, ubiquitous computing, tangible interface, physical UI, phicon, augmented reality. INTRODUCTION Six years ag...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7459-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7459_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:17:34">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B787E51A4E6590ABF8A72FE671666A92?doi=10.1.1.135.6808&amp;rank=9</link><title>How do people organize their desks? Implications for the design of office information systems</title><description>How do people organize their desks? Implications for the design of office information systems

by Thomas W. Malone \- ACM Transactions on Office Information Systems , 1983

"... research scientist, Kenneth has very little routine paper flow. Most of the information in his office ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 224 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper describes a series of interviews focusing on the way professional and clerical office workers organize the information in their desks and offices. A number of implications for designing &amp;quot;natural&amp;quot; and convenient computer-based information systems are discussed. Two principal claims are made: (1) A very important function of desk organization is to remind the user of things to do, not just to help the user find desired information. Failing to support this function may seriously impair the usefulness of electronic office systems, and explicitly facilitating it may provide an important advantage for automated office systems over their nonautomated predecessors. (2) The cognitive difficulty of categorizing information is an important factor in explaining how people organize their desks. Computer-based systems may help with this difficulty by (a) doing as much automatic classification as possible (e.g., based on access dates}, and (b) including untitled &amp;quot;piles &amp;quot; of information arranged by physical location as well as explicitly titled and logically arranged &amp;quot;files.&amp;quot; Several other implications for the design of electronic office systems are discussed, and some differences in how people organize their desks are described. Categories and Subject Descriptors: H.1.2 [Models and Principles]: User/Machine Systems--</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7459-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7459_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:18:22">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=B787E51A4E6590ABF8A72FE671666A92?doi=10.1.1.77.9349&amp;rank=10</link><title>Defaults in Update Semantics</title><description>Defaults in Update Semantics

by Frank Veltman \- JOURNAL OF PHILOSOPHICAL LOGIC , 1996

"... looking for a referent: ‘He is just joking.’ If it is not clear to whom the speaker is referring ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 217 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

ABSTRACT. The aim of this paper is twofold: (i) to introduce the framework of update semantics and to explain what kind of phenomena may successfully be analysed in it; (ii) to give a detailed analysis of one such phenomenon: default reasoning. KEY WORDS: dynamic semantics, defaults, epistemic modalities.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>