<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7477">china bird flu</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:57:26" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7477-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7477_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:57:37">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=59CE4C1A467DD38A7201ACE2D359473A?doi=10.1.1.398.2045&amp;rank=1</link><title>• West Nile • Avian FluBird Flu: The next major epidemic?</title><description>• West Nile • Avian FluBird Flu: The next major epidemic?

by Wayne F. Peate, L. Nied, Jonathan Sexton Bs, Person To Person, Hepatitis A

"... /AIDS • Tuberculosis • Vancomycin/methicillin resistance (MRSA, VRE) • SARS • West Nile • Avian FluBird Flu: The next ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

• Be aware of communicable diseases that firefighters are susceptible to • Take home SOPs for the above • Practice what learned in case studies • Disseminate best practices: Code 90 • Be knowledgeable about the latest on MRSA and firefighters</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7477-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7477_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:58:27">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=59CE4C1A467DD38A7201ACE2D359473A?doi=10.1.1.115.2861&amp;rank=2</link><title>A survey on visual surveillance of object motion and behaviors</title><description>A survey on visual surveillance of object motion and behaviors

by Weiming Hu, Tieniu Tan, Liang Wang, Steve Maybank \- IEEE Transactions on Systems, Man and Cybernetics , 2004

"... . This work was supported in part by the National Science Foundation of China (NSFC) under Grants 60105002 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 244 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract—Visual surveillance in dynamic scenes, especially for humans and vehicles, is currently one of the most active research topics in computer vision. It has a wide spectrum of promising applications, including access control in special areas, human identification at a distance, crowd flux statistics and congestion analysis, detection of anomalous behaviors, and interactive surveillance using multiple cameras, etc. In general, the processing framework of visual surveillance in dynamic scenes includes the following stages: modeling of environments, detection of motion, classification of moving objects, tracking, understanding and description of behaviors, human identification, and fusion of data from multiple cameras. We review recent developments and general strategies of all these stages. Finally, we analyze possible research directions, e.g., occlusion handling, a combination of twoand three-dimensional tracking, a combination of motion analysis and biometrics, anomaly detection and behavior prediction, content-based retrieval of surveillance videos, behavior understanding and natural language description, fusion of information from multiple sensors, and remote surveillance. Index Terms—Behavior understanding and description, fusion of data from multiple cameras, motion detection, personal identification, tracking, visual surveillance.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7477-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7477_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:59:42">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=59CE4C1A467DD38A7201ACE2D359473A?doi=10.1.1.225.150&amp;rank=3</link><title>Avian Flu: Modeling and Implications for Control</title><description>Avian Flu: Modeling and Implications for Control

by Maia Martcheva , 2011

"... the current situation where avian flu infects humans through bird-to-human infection and human flu is endemic ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

infected domestic &lt;em&gt;birds&lt;/em&gt;. Since 2003 more than 500 people have been infected and nearly 60 % of them have</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7477-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7477_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:02:07">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=59CE4C1A467DD38A7201ACE2D359473A?doi=10.1.1.369.5696&amp;rank=4</link><title>“Decoding the Flu”</title><description>“Decoding the Flu”

by Norris Armstrong

"... ﻿NATIONAL CENTER FOR CASE STUDY TEACHING IN SCIENCE CASE TEACHING NOTES for “Decoding the Flu ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7477-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7477_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:05:44">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=59CE4C1A467DD38A7201ACE2D359473A?doi=10.1.1.224.1423&amp;rank=5</link><title>AVIAN INFLUENZA: KNOW WHEN THE SKY IS FALLING MEDIA AND scientific engrossment</title><description>AVIAN INFLUENZA: KNOW WHEN THE SKY IS FALLING MEDIA AND scientific engrossment

by Phylum Chordata Class , 2005

"... over flu in Phylum Chordata, Class Aves represents yet another diversion by this wily virus to distract ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

over &lt;em&gt;flu&lt;/em&gt; in</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7477-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7477_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:09:01">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=59CE4C1A467DD38A7201ACE2D359473A?doi=10.1.1.134.7190&amp;rank=6</link><title>Recent Developments in Human Motion Analysis</title><description>Recent Developments in Human Motion Analysis

by Liang Wang, Weiming Hu, Tieniu Tan

"... , Chinese Academy of Sciences, Beijing, P. R. China, 100080 Visual analysis of human motion is currently one ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 169 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Visual analysis of human motion is currently one of the most active research topics in computer vision. This strong interest is driven by a wide spectrum of promising applications in many areas such as virtual reality, smart surveillance, perceptual interface, etc. Human motion analysis concerns the detection, tracking and recognition of people, and more generally, the understanding of human behaviors, from image sequences involving humans. This paper provides a comprehensive survey of research on computer vision based human motion analysis. The emphasis is on three major issues involved in a general human motion analysis system, namely human detection, tracking and activity understanding. Various methods for each issue are discussed in order to examine the state of the art. Finally, some research challenges and future directions are discussed.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7477-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7477_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:12:17">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=59CE4C1A467DD38A7201ACE2D359473A?doi=10.1.1.226.6217&amp;rank=7</link><title>Implications of Avian Flu for Economic Development in Kenya</title><description>Implications of Avian Flu for Economic Development in Kenya

by James Thurlow , 2010

"... to avian flu given its position along migratory bird routes and proximity to other high-risk countries ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

agricultural research centers that receive principal funding from governments, private foundations, and international and regional organizations, most of which are members of the Consultative Group on International Agricultural Research (CGIAR). FINANCIAL CONTRIBUTORS AND PARTNERS IFPRI’s research, capacity strengthening, and communications work is made possible by its financial contributors and partners. IFPRI receives its principal funding from governments, private foundations, and international and regional organizations, most of which are members of the Consultative Group on</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7477-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7477_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:15:41">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=59CE4C1A467DD38A7201ACE2D359473A?doi=10.1.1.322.2244&amp;rank=8</link><title>Rare Disasters and Asset Markets in the Twentieth Century,” Quarterly</title><description>Rare Disasters and Asset Markets in the Twentieth Century,” Quarterly

by Robert J. Barro, Marios Angeletos, John Campbell, Gene Fama, Xavier Gabaix, Hans Genberg, Mike Golosov, Bob Lucas, Greg Mankiw, Raj Mehra, Sergio Rebelo, Aleh Tsyvinski, Marty Weitzman, Marc Weidenmier, Ivan Werning \- Journal of Economics , 2006

"... (tsunamis, hurricanes, earthquakes, asteroid collisions), and epidemics of disease (Black Death, avian flu ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 157 (5 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The potential for rare economic disasters explains a lot of asset-pricing puzzles. I calibrate disaster probabilities from the twentieth century global history, especially the sharp contractions associated with World War I, the Great Depression, and World War II. The puzzles that can be explained include the high equity premium, low risk-free rate, and volatile stock returns. Another mystery that may be resolved is why expected real interest rates were low in the United States during major wars, such as World War II. The model, an extension of Rietz [1988], maintains the tractable framework of a representative agent, time-additive and iso-elastic preferences, and complete markets. The results hold with i.i.d. shocks to productivity growth in a Lucas-tree type economy and also with the inclusion of capital formation.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7477-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7477_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:17:42">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=59CE4C1A467DD38A7201ACE2D359473A?doi=10.1.1.194.8670&amp;rank=9</link><title>Swine Flu HUMAN INFLUENZA VIRUSES AND THE POTENTIAL FOR INTER-SPECIES TRANSMISSION</title><description>Swine Flu HUMAN INFLUENZA VIRUSES AND THE POTENTIAL FOR INTER-SPECIES TRANSMISSION

by Carolyn Buxton, Bridges Md, I Ntroduction

"... detection. Outbreaks of the Asian Flu were first reported in late February 1957 in China and spread to Hong ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

person to person. The most infamous of pandemics was the 1918-1919 Spanish &lt;em&gt;Flu&lt;/em&gt; pandemic, which resulted</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7477-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7477_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:18:42">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=59CE4C1A467DD38A7201ACE2D359473A?doi=10.1.1.413.3058&amp;rank=10</link><title>The Ins and Outs of Biosecurity: Bird ’flu in East Anglia and the Spatial Representation of Risk</title><description>The Ins and Outs of Biosecurity: Bird ’flu in East Anglia and the Spatial Representation of Risk

by Brigitte Nerlich, Brian Brown, Nick Wright

"... ﻿The Ins and Outs of Biosecurity: Bird ’flu in East Anglia and the Spatial Representation of Risk ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 2 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Avian influenza, or &lt;em&gt;‘bird&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;’flu&lt;/em&gt; ’ arrived in Norfolk in April 2006 in the form of the low pathogenic</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>