<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7480">phd comics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:06:42" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7480-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7480_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:06:46">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=16674279D2D7295455D2B61947147545?doi=10.1.1.4.7642&amp;rank=1</link><title>An Experimental Implementation of the Spatial Model, Comic working paper COMIC-NOTT-4-15, available</title><description>An Experimental Implementation of the Spatial Model, Comic working paper COMIC-NOTT-4-15, available

by Chris Greenhalgh \- Department of Computer Science, The University of Nottingham , 1994

"... of Computer Science and others within the COMIC project [2.,5.,6.]. Some aspects of this model have been ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 7 (3 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This paper describes an experimental implementation of the spatial model of interaction in virtual environments 1 . This implementation is intended to allow assessment of the scalability of the spatial model, in particular the use of auras, and the usefulness of focus, nimbus and awareness in controlling spatial interaction. The spatial model yields a natural and readily extensible system, but the current networking technology prevents very large-scale testing of the system. 1.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7480-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7480_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:08:12">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=16674279D2D7295455D2B61947147545?doi=10.1.1.188.7188&amp;rank=2</link><title>Automating the Multidimensional Design of Data Warehouses PhD. Thesis PhD. Student: Oscar Romero</title><description>Automating the Multidimensional Design of Data Warehouses PhD. Thesis PhD. Student: Oscar Romero

by Advisor Alberto, Abelló Gamazo, Programa De Doctorat En Software, Departament Llenguatges, Sistemes Informàtics

"... .Acknowledgements “Every thesis begins with a single keystroke.” PhD Comics, 2009 My foremost thank goes to Alberto Abelló ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

is, somehow, also yours. Acknowledgements “Every thesis begins with a single keystroke.” &lt;em&gt;PhD&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Comics&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7480-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7480_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:09:54">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=16674279D2D7295455D2B61947147545?doi=10.1.1.134.3474&amp;rank=3</link><title>Science Institutes for Continuing Education</title><description>Science Institutes for Continuing Education

by unknown authors , 2007

"... collections comics communities css DACS database design digital dreamweaver evaluation gaming imaging index ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

architecture archives bibliography blogging bookmaking cataloging children collections &lt;em&gt;comics&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7480-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7480_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:12:16">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=16674279D2D7295455D2B61947147545?doi=10.1.1.117.4040&amp;rank=4</link><title>Harvesting Image Databases from the Web</title><description>Harvesting Image Databases from the Web

by F. Schroff \- In ICCV , 2007

"... through the European PhD Scholarship Programme and by EU project CLASS. A. Criminisi Microsoft Research ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 73 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The objective of this work 1 is to automatically generate a large number of images for a specified object class (for example, penguin). A multi-modal approach employing both text, meta data and visual features is used to gather many, high-quality images from the web. Candidate images are obtained by a text based web search querying on the object identifier (the word penguin). The web pages and the images they contain are downloaded. The task is then to remove irrelevant images and re-rank the remainder. First, the images are re-ranked using a Bayes posterior estimator trained on the text surrounding the image and meta data features (such as the image alternative tag, image title tag, and image filename). No visual information is used at this stage. Second, the top-ranked images are used as (noisy) training data and a SVM visual classifier is learnt to improve the ranking further. The principal novelty is in combining text/meta-data and visual features in order to achieve a completely automatic ranking of the images. Examples are given for a selection of animals (e.g. camels, sharks, penguins), vehicles (cars, airplanes, bikes) and other classes (guitar, wristwatch), totalling 18 classes. The results are assessed by precision/recall curves on ground truth annotated data and by comparison to previous approaches including those of Berg et al. [5] (on an additional six classes) and Fergus et al. [9]. 1.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7480-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7480_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:13:42">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=16674279D2D7295455D2B61947147545?doi=10.1.1.395.1928&amp;rank=5</link><title>Media Politics ‒ Political Media, The NECS 2013 Conference Kateryna</title><description>Media Politics ‒ Political Media, The NECS 2013 Conference Kateryna

by unknown authors , 2013

"... Lobodenko, PhD student in arts and media in the University of Sorbonne, Paris III (France) When animation ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

&lt;em&gt;PhD&lt;/em&gt; student in arts and media</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7480-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7480_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:16:38">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=16674279D2D7295455D2B61947147545?doi=10.1.1.402.6774&amp;rank=6</link><title>3.3.4 Discrete Random Variables in the StoEx-framework.......... 91</title><description>3.3.4 Discrete Random Variables in the StoEx-framework.......... 91

by Dipl. -inform Heiko Koziolek, Prof Dr, Ralf Reussner, Prof Dr, Wilhelm Hasselbring

"... , the author of PhD-comics, for letting PhD students all over the world bear grad school life with a smile ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

&lt;em&gt;PhD&lt;/em&gt; thesis to gain the degree of</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7480-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7480_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:18:18">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=16674279D2D7295455D2B61947147545?doi=10.1.1.360.9574&amp;rank=7</link><title>A mini-thesis submitted to upgrade from MPhil to PhD</title><description>A mini-thesis submitted to upgrade from MPhil to PhD

by Donia Badawood, Supervisors Prof, Jo Wood, Prof Jason, Dykes Donia Badawood , 2012

"... ﻿Badawood, D. (2012). Evaluation of storytelling in information visualization (MPhil to PhD ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Copyright &amp; reuse City University London has developed City Research Online so that its users may access the research outputs of City University London's staff. Copyright © and Moral Rights for this paper are retained by the individual author(s) and / or other copyright holders. All material in City Research Online is checked for eligibility for copyright before being made available in the live archive. URLs from City Research Online may be freely distributed and linked to from other web pages. Versions of research The version in City Research Online may differ from the final published version. Users are advised to check the Permanent City Research Online URL above for the status of the paper. Enquiries If you have any enquiries about any aspect of City Research Online, or if you wish to make contact with the author(s) of this paper, please email the team at publications@city.ac.uk.giCentre- School of Informatics</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7480-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7480_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:20:58">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=16674279D2D7295455D2B61947147545?doi=10.1.1.251.2765&amp;rank=8</link><title>Real-time Illustrative Visualization of Cardiovascular HemodynamicsColophon The thesis cover was designed by the author (Roy van Pelt).</title><description>Real-time Illustrative Visualization of Cardiovascular HemodynamicsColophon The thesis cover was designed by the author (Roy van Pelt).

by Roy Franciscus, Petrus Pelt

"... was designed by the author (Roy van Pelt). The comic was drawn by Koert Stavenuiter (www ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

The &lt;em&gt;comic&lt;/em&gt; was digitally inked by the author. This contents were typeset by the author using L ATEX2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7480-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7480_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:22:27">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=16674279D2D7295455D2B61947147545?doi=10.1.1.211.6229&amp;rank=9</link><title>Theory as Game: Designing the Gamegame</title><description>Theory as Game: Designing the Gamegame

by Aki Järvinen

"... studies. The approach presented in the paper is similar to Scott McCloud’s Understanding Comics: a theory ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

to Scott McCloud’s Understanding &lt;em&gt;Comics&lt;/em&gt;: a theory of &lt;em&gt;comics&lt;/em&gt; in the form of a &lt;em&gt;comic&lt;/em&gt; book. Respectively</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7480-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7480_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:26:12">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=16674279D2D7295455D2B61947147545?doi=10.1.1.130.2940&amp;rank=10</link><title>A TEACHER’S GUIDE TO THE SIGNET CLASSIC EDITION OF WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE’S THE TAMING OF THE SHREW</title><description>A TEACHER’S GUIDE TO THE SIGNET CLASSIC EDITION OF WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE’S THE TAMING OF THE SHREW

by J. Luther, Laura A. Mccammon

"... , EMERITUS and ARTHEA J. S. REED, PH.D., UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA, RETIRED A Teacher’s Guide ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

courses, the lively &lt;em&gt;comic&lt;/em&gt; plot and appealing characters make it an excellent introduction to the Bard</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>