<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7483">facebook paying?</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:11:30" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7483-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7483_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:11:32">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CD1F5ED0F3A10FEE34CECAE8164CE193?doi=10.1.1.149.7163&amp;rank=1</link><title>Above the Clouds: A Berkeley View of Cloud Computing</title><description>Above the Clouds: A Berkeley View of Cloud Computing

by Michael Armbrust, Armando Fox, Rean Griffith, Anthony D. Joseph, Randy H. Katz, Andrew Konwinski, Gunho Lee, David A. Patterson, Ariel Rabkin, Matei Zaharia , 2009

"... members Amazon Web Services, Cisco Systems, Facebook, Hewlett- Packard, IBM, NEC, Network Appliance ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 360 (10 self) \- Add to MetaCart

, &lt;em&gt;Facebook&lt;/em&gt;, Hewlett-</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7483-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7483_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:13:07">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CD1F5ED0F3A10FEE34CECAE8164CE193?doi=10.1.1.372.4524&amp;rank=2</link><title>FUNDRAISING WITH FACEBOOK</title><description>FUNDRAISING WITH FACEBOOK

by Fundraising Facebook

"... ﻿JANUARY 2013 ARTEZ INTERACTIVE WHITE PAPER FUNDRAISING WITH FACEBOOK ARTEZ.COM | FACEBOOK ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

&lt;em&gt;FACEBOOK&lt;/em&gt;... If you feel it’s been a tough nut to crack for fundraising, you’re not alone! Many</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7483-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7483_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:15:20">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CD1F5ED0F3A10FEE34CECAE8164CE193?doi=10.1.1.411.7977&amp;rank=3</link><title>Privacy and Facebook</title><description>Privacy and Facebook

by Ronan Comer, Nigel Mc Kelvey, Kevin Curran

"... reduced. From an alternative viewpoint, Facebook have to pay a staff of over 1700 people in order ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Social Networking is continually growing and showing more possibilities. &lt;em&gt;Facebook&lt;/em&gt; the leading</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7483-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7483_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:15:45">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CD1F5ED0F3A10FEE34CECAE8164CE193?doi=10.1.1.178.5784&amp;rank=4</link><title>Student Socialization in the Age of Facebook</title><description>Student Socialization in the Age of Facebook

by Louise Barkhuus, Juliana Tashiro

"... ﻿Student Socialization in the Age of Facebook Louise Barkhuus University of California, San Diego ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 8 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Most research regarding online social networks such as &lt;em&gt;Facebook&lt;/em&gt;, MySpace, Linked-In and Friendster</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7483-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7483_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:17:46">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CD1F5ED0F3A10FEE34CECAE8164CE193?doi=10.1.1.294.6240&amp;rank=5</link><title>The Personality of Popular Facebook Users</title><description>The Personality of Popular Facebook Users

by Daniele Quercia, Renaud Lambiotte, David Stillwell, Michal Kosinski, Jon Crowcroft

"... Facebook Users Daniele Quercia § , Renaud Lambiotte ‡ , David Stillwell ∗ , Michal Kosinski † , Jon ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 4 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We study the relationship between &lt;em&gt;Facebook&lt;/em&gt; popularity (number of contacts) and personality traits</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7483-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7483_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:18:58">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CD1F5ED0F3A10FEE34CECAE8164CE193?doi=10.1.1.379.7417&amp;rank=6</link><title>Follow Education Review on Facebook</title><description>Follow Education Review on Facebook

by Reviewed Serena Johnson , 2011

"... Policy Center http://nepc.colorado.edu Follow Education Review on Facebook a multi-lingual journal ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Few topics have been more researched in deaf education than literacy. However, despite the decades of research that have been devoted to improving the reading and writing rates of deaf students, there exist relatively few syntheses of the information. When meta-analytic research has been undertaken, it has found that there are significant gaps in the research that has been conducted (Luckner &amp; Handley, 2008). Despite the difficulty of such metaanalytic research, Trezek and her colleagues do their best to complete it. As textbooks go, it is difficult to find one that you enjoy. By their nature, textbooks are functional, not frivolous and are solely used to gain information about a subject. Professors assign them, students purchase them, curse</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7483-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7483_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:21:38">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CD1F5ED0F3A10FEE34CECAE8164CE193?doi=10.1.1.227.657&amp;rank=7</link><title>Facebook Goes to the Doctor</title><description>Facebook Goes to the Doctor

by Matt Bishop, Peter Yellowlees, Carrie Gates, Gabriel Silberman

"... ﻿Facebook Goes to the Doctor Matt Bishop Dept. of Computer Science University of California ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

The use of computer-based social networks for health care changes the privacy paradigm of face-to-face treatment. For example, in an office, a patient can be reasonably sure that the physician or therapist is the only one present, and is who has been providing treatment. On a computer-based social network, communications travel over the World Wide Web, raising the possibility of eavesdropping, delay, and other problems. Further, verification of the party with whom the patient is communicating is more difficult, and to many less credible, than in-person verification. This paper describes the privacy paradigm, presents a set of requirements for effective use of computer-based social networks in health care, discusses what current technology can provide, and what gaps must be closed to meet the rest of the requirements. 1.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7483-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7483_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:22:35">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CD1F5ED0F3A10FEE34CECAE8164CE193?doi=10.1.1.363.1770&amp;rank=8</link><title>Poster: Privacy Attitudes of Facebook Users</title><description>Poster: Privacy Attitudes of Facebook Users

by Gregory Norcie

"... ﻿Poster: Privacy Attitudes of Facebook Users Gregory Norcie University of Pittsburgh School ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

“Bits Blog ” for short) offered &lt;em&gt;Facebook&lt;/em&gt; users the chance to ask questions of Elliot Schrage, Vice</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7483-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7483_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:23:08">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CD1F5ED0F3A10FEE34CECAE8164CE193?doi=10.1.1.167.1166&amp;rank=9</link><title>THE FACEBOOK PROJECT THE MISSING BOX: THE RACIAL POLITICS BEHIND THE FACEBOOK INTERFACE</title><description>THE FACEBOOK PROJECT THE MISSING BOX: THE RACIAL POLITICS BEHIND THE FACEBOOK INTERFACE

by Jeff Ginger, University Of, Illinois At Urbana-champaign

"... ﻿THE FACEBOOK PROJECT THE MISSING BOX: THE RACIAL POLITICS BEHIND THE FACEBOOK INTERFACE JEFF ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

the fact that &lt;em&gt;Facebook&lt;/em&gt; is a visually-driven website, suggests that &lt;em&gt;Facebook&lt;/em&gt; serves to inadvertently</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7483-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7483_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:26:52">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CD1F5ED0F3A10FEE34CECAE8164CE193?doi=10.1.1.302.1092&amp;rank=10</link><title>Facebook YouTube Corporate</title><description>Facebook YouTube Corporate

by unknown authors

"... -Marsteller Evidence-Based Communications Group, 2010. Figure 1 65% Twitter 54% 50% 33% Facebook YouTube Corporate Blog ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Social media has changed the way organizations interact with their customers. The communication has become bi-directional — customers are using these new media to talk about their preferences, while organizations are leveraging these channels to interface with their customers like never before.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>