<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7488">DIY shops london open sunday</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:14:31" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7488-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7488_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:14:33">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=5D3C1F63D17E298E89324B9063629F93?doi=10.1.1.33.2176&amp;rank=1</link><title>Wrapper Induction for Information Extraction</title><description>Wrapper Induction for Information Extraction

by Nicholas Kushmerick , 1997

"... repositories, recipe collections, and many more. With widespread adoption of open standards such as http ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 519 (30 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The Internet presents numerous sources of useful information---telephone directories, product catalogs, stock quotes, weather forecasts, etc. Recently, many systems have been built that automatically gather and manipulate such information on a user's behalf. However, these resources are usually formatted for use by people (e.g., the relevant content is embedded in HTML pages), so extracting their content is difficult. Wrappers are often used for this purpose. A wrapper is a procedure for extracting a particular resource's content. Unfortunately, hand-coding wrappers is tedious. We introduce wrapper induction, a technique for automatically constructing wrappers. Our techniques can be described in terms of three main contributions. First, we pose the problem of wrapper construction as one of inductive learn...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7488-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7488_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:17:15">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=5D3C1F63D17E298E89324B9063629F93?doi=10.1.1.23.7883&amp;rank=2</link><title>Supporting Trust in Virtual Communities</title><description>Supporting Trust in Virtual Communities

by Alfarez Abdul-Rahman , Stephen Hailes , 2000

"... -Rahman Department of Computer Science, University College London, Gower Street, London WC1E 6BT, United Kingdom F ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 306 (8 self) \- Add to MetaCart

At any given time, the stability of a community depends on the right balance of trust and distrust. Furthermore, we face information overload, increased uncertainty and risk taking as a prominent feature of modern living. As members of society, we cope with these complexities and uncertainties by relying trust, which is the basis of all social interactions. Although a small number of trust models have been proposed for the virtual medium, we find that they are largely impractical and artificial. In this paper we provide and discuss a trust model that is grounded in real-world social trust characteristics, and based on a reputation mechanism, or word-of-mouth. Our proposed model allows agents to decide which other agents' opinions they trust more and allows agents to progressively tune their understanding of another agent's subjective recommendations.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7488-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7488_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:19:46">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=5D3C1F63D17E298E89324B9063629F93?doi=10.1.1.200.7967&amp;rank=3</link><title>WORKERS ' ATTITUDES TO SUNDAY TRADING: AN EXAMINATION OF THE DIY AND GROCERY MARKETS IN SCOTLAND</title><description>WORKERS ' ATTITUDES TO SUNDAY TRADING: AN EXAMINATION OF THE DIY AND GROCERY MARKETS IN SCOTLAND

by Wales

"... the merits and highlighting the disadvantages of seven day opening exists. One of the anomalies of Sunday ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7488-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7488_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:23:20">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=5D3C1F63D17E298E89324B9063629F93?doi=10.1.1.140.3395&amp;rank=4</link><title>Why Cryptosystems Fail</title><description>Why Cryptosystems Fail

by Ross Anderson , 2005

"... large class action got underway in the High Court in London [MB], in which hundreds of plainti s seek ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 274 (35 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Designers of cryptographic systems are at a disadvantage to most other engineers, in that information on how their systems fail is hard to get: their major users have traditionally been government agencies, which are very secretive about their mistakes. In this article, we present the results of a survey of the failure modes of retail banking systems, which constitute the next largest application of cryptology. It turns out that the threat model commonly used by cryptosystem designers was wrong: most frauds were not caused by cryptanalysis or other technical attacks, but by implementation errors and management failures. This suggests that a paradigm shift is overdue in computer security; we look at some of the alternatives, and see some signs that this shift may begetting under way.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7488-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7488_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:23:55">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=5D3C1F63D17E298E89324B9063629F93?doi=10.1.1.28.9219&amp;rank=5</link><title>The Great Reversals: The Politics of Financial Development in the 20th Century</title><description>The Great Reversals: The Politics of Financial Development in the 20th Century

by Raghuram G. Rajan, Luigi Zingales, Roger Laeven, Galina Ovtcharova, Nahid Rahman, Sofia Ramos, Ruy Ribeiro, Amir Sasson , 2001

"... ’s openness as a proxy for the strength of incumbents’ opposition to financial development. While crude ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 210 (7 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Indicators of the development of the financial sector do not improve monotonically over time. In particular, we find that by most measures, countries were more financially developed in 1913 than in 1980 and only recently have they surpassed their 1913 levels. This pattern cannot be explained by structural theories that attribute cross-country differences in financial development to time-invariant factors, such as a country's legal origin or culture. We propose an "interest group" theory of financial development where incumbents oppose financial development because it breeds competition. The theory predicts that incumbents' opposition will be weaker when an economy allows both cross-border trade and capital flows. This theory can go some way in accounting for the cross-country differences and the time series variation of financial development. When we recognize that different kinds of institutional heritages afford different scope for private interests to express themselves, we obtain a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7488-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7488_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:27:37">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=5D3C1F63D17E298E89324B9063629F93?doi=10.1.1.197.5345&amp;rank=6</link><title>LONDON</title><description>LONDON

by Stirling Fk La, Leigh Sparks, George Nicholson , 265

"... other material changes over the period of their studies, most notably the extension of Sunday opening ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

citation without the express permission of the authors.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7488-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7488_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:30:08">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=5D3C1F63D17E298E89324B9063629F93?doi=10.1.1.390.8380&amp;rank=7</link><title>SMSlingshot: An Expert Amateur DIY Case Study</title><description>SMSlingshot: An Expert Amateur DIY Case Study

by Patrick Tobias Fischer, Eva Hornecker, Christian Zoellner

"... graphics rendering code from the spread.gun. The main DIY support consisted of Open Source libraries ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

of this ‘product ’ has many &lt;em&gt;DIY&lt;/em&gt; aspects, with professional industrial designers and technologists becoming expert</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7488-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7488_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:32:48">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=5D3C1F63D17E298E89324B9063629F93?doi=10.1.1.199.9567&amp;rank=8</link><title>The Distribution of Realized Exchange Rate Volatility</title><description>The Distribution of Realized Exchange Rate Volatility

by Torben G. Andersen, Tim Bollerslev, Francis X. Diebold, Paul Labys \- Journal of the American Statistical Association , 2001

"... , and London School of Economics (LSE), as well as the editor, associate editor, two anonymous referees, Dave ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 150 (17 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Using high-frequency data on deutschemark and yen returns against the dollar, we construct model-free estimates of daily exchange rate volatility and correlation that cover an entire decade. Our estimates, termed realized volatilities and correlations, are not only model-free, but also approximately free of measurement error under general conditions, which we discuss in detail. Hence, for practical purposes, we may treat the exchange rate volatilities and correlations as observed rather than latent. We do so, and we characterize their joint distribution, both unconditionally and conditionally. Noteworthy results include a simple normality-inducing volatility transformation, high contemporaneous correlation across volatilities, high correlation between correlation and volatilities, pronounced and persistent dynamics in volatilities and correlations, evidence of long-memory dynamics in volatilities and correlations, and remarkably precise scaling laws under temporal aggregation.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7488-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7488_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:35:44">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=5D3C1F63D17E298E89324B9063629F93?doi=10.1.1.364.3512&amp;rank=9</link><title>London</title><description>London

by Mark Bevan, Karen Croucher, Bressenden Place , 2011

"... -use this information (not including logos) free of charge in any format or medium, under the terms of the Open ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Department for Communities and Local GovernmentThe findings in this report are those of the authors and do not necessarily represent</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7488-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7488_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:36:38">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=5D3C1F63D17E298E89324B9063629F93?doi=10.1.1.412.7069&amp;rank=10</link><title>London</title><description>London

by N. Beech, G. Greig, H. Patrick, North Haugh, D. Sims, Ecy Tz, Ky St

"... . Sims Cass Business School City University 106 Bunhill Row London EC1Y 8TZ KY16 9ST UK UK Tel: 01334 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Improvisation, mistakes, learning, activity theory</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>