<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7492">oldest jokes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:43:50" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7492-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7492_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:43:51">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=0453D78F2225F7127408ACAF7398AB18?doi=10.1.1.137.6019&amp;rank=1</link><title>Computationally recognizing wordplay in jokes</title><description>Computationally recognizing wordplay in jokes

by Julia M. Taylor, Lawrence J. Mazlack \- In Proceedings of CogSci 2004 , 2004

"... ﻿Computationally Recognizing Wordplay in Jokes Julia M. Taylor (tayloj8@(email omitted);) Lawrence J ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 3 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

, it may be possible to recognize &lt;em&gt;jokes&lt;/em&gt; based on statistical language recognition techniques</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7492-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7492_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:45:10">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=0453D78F2225F7127408ACAF7398AB18?doi=10.1.1.113.3822&amp;rank=2</link><title>Socially translucent systems: social proxies, persistent conversation, and the design of “Babble</title><description>Socially translucent systems: social proxies, persistent conversation, and the design of “Babble

by Thomas Erickson, David N, Wendy A. Kellogg, Mark Laff, John T. Richards, Erin Bradner , 1999

"... with the oldest items first (e.g., Figure 1). Each comment is preceded by a header which has a time stamp ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 99 (11 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We take as our premise that it is possible and desirable to design systems that support social processes. We describe Loops, a project which takes this approach to supporting computer-mediated communication (CMC) through structural and intemctive properties such as persistence and a minimalist graphical representation of users and their activities that we call a social proxy. We discuss a prototype called “Babble ” that has been used by our group for over a year, and has been deployed to six other groups at the Watson labs for about two months. We describe usage experiences, lessons learned, and next steps.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7492-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7492_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:46:48">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=0453D78F2225F7127408ACAF7398AB18?doi=10.1.1.92.9852&amp;rank=3</link><title>Humorous Wordplay Recognition *</title><description>Humorous Wordplay Recognition *

by Julia M. Taylor

"... humor, it may be possible to recognize jokes based on statistical language recognition techniques ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

be possible to recognize &lt;em&gt;jokes&lt;/em&gt; based on statistical language recognition techniques. Computational humor</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7492-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7492_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:47:18">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=0453D78F2225F7127408ACAF7398AB18?doi=10.1.1.50.5059&amp;rank=4</link><title>Comparing Information Without Leaking It</title><description>Comparing Information Without Leaking It

by Ronald Fagin, Moni Naor, Peter Winkler \- Communications of the ACM , 1996

"... their numerical worths. Similarly, a group of friends may wish to determine who among them is the oldest, or has ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 63 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We consider simple means by which two people may determine whether they possess the same information, without revealing anything else to each other in case that they do not. Incumbent of the Morris and Rose Goldman Career Development Chair. Research supported by an Alon Fellowship and a grant from the Israel Science Foundation administered by the Israeli Academy of Sciences. Most of this work was done while the author was at the IBM Almaden Research Center. y Most of this work was done while the author was with Bellcore. 1 Introduction Consider the following problem, which actually arose in real life (we have masked the problem somewhat to protect confidentiality). Bob comes to Ron, a manager at his company, with a complaint about a sensitive matter; he asks Ron to keep his identity confidential. A few months later, Moshe (another manager) tells Ron that someone has complained to him, also with a confidentiality request, about the same matter. Ron and Moshe would like to determi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7492-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7492_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:49:25">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=0453D78F2225F7127408ACAF7398AB18?doi=10.1.1.272.1970&amp;rank=5</link><title>RESEARCH ARTICLE Open Access</title><description>RESEARCH ARTICLE Open Access

by Claire Goodman, Elspeth Mathie, Marion Cowe, Alex Mendoza, Daphne Westwood, Diane Munday, Patricia M Wilson, Clare Crang, Katherine Froggatt, Steve Iliffe, Jill Manthorpe, Heather Gage, Stephen Barclay

"... /20 RESEARCH ARTICLE Open Access Talking about living and dying with the oldest old: public involvement in a ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Talking about living and dying with the &lt;em&gt;oldest&lt;/em&gt; old: public involvement in a study on end of life</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7492-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7492_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:50:55">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=0453D78F2225F7127408ACAF7398AB18?doi=10.1.1.77.9136&amp;rank=6</link><title>Reducing noise in gossip-based reliable broadcast</title><description>Reducing noise in gossip-based reliable broadcast

by P. Kouznetsov, R. Guerraoui, S. B. Handurukande, A. -m. Kermarrec \- In Proceedings of the 20th International Symposium on Reliable Distributed Systems , 2001

"... of times the message has been retransmitted. Roughly speaking, if you have to choose among a set of jokes ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 17 (6 self) \- Add to MetaCart

among a set of &lt;em&gt;jokes&lt;/em&gt; to memorize, you might probably not choose the one you have heard the most often</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7492-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7492_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:51:32">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=0453D78F2225F7127408ACAF7398AB18?doi=10.1.1.160.4178&amp;rank=7</link><title>ABOUT THE COVER Henri de Toulouse-Lautrec (1864–1901). At the Moulin Rouge: The Dance (1890). Oil on canvas (115.6 cm x 149.9 cm). Philadelphia Museum of Art: The Henry P. Mcllhenny Collection in memory of Frances P. Mcllhenny, 1986</title><description>ABOUT THE COVER Henri de Toulouse-Lautrec (1864–1901). At the Moulin Rouge: The Dance (1890). Oil on canvas (115.6 cm x 149.9 cm). Philadelphia Museum of Art: The Henry P. Mcllhenny Collection in memory of Frances P. Mcllhenny, 1986

by Hygeia As Muse, Polyxeni Potter

"... sketches, photographs, and studies from life, he sang and joked during the brief execution of the work ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

from life, he sang and &lt;em&gt;joked&lt;/em&gt; during the brief execution of the work. Lautrec’s remarkable legacy seems</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7492-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7492_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:52:12">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=0453D78F2225F7127408ACAF7398AB18?doi=10.1.1.104.3839&amp;rank=8</link><title>Strangers and friends: Collaborative play in World of Warcraft</title><description>Strangers and friends: Collaborative play in World of Warcraft

by Bonnie Nardi, Justin Harris \- In Proc. CSCW 2006 , 2006

"... come together to flirt, dance, drink, hug, joke, smile, laugh, and cheer. These actions, and many ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 38 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We analyze collaborative play in an online video game, World of Warcraft, the most popular personal computer game in the United States, with significant markets in Asia and Europe. Based on an immersive ethnographic study, we describe how the social organization of the game and player culture affect players ’ enjoyment and learning of the game. We discovered that play is characterized by a multiplicity of collaborations from brief informal encounters to highly organized play in structured groups. The variety of collaborations makes the game more fun and provides rich learning opportunities. We contrast these varied collaborations, including those with strangers, to the “gold standard ” of Gemeinschaft-like communities of close relations in tightknit groups. We suggest populations for whom similar games could be designed.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7492-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7492_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:52:53">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=0453D78F2225F7127408ACAF7398AB18?doi=10.1.1.294.9758&amp;rank=9</link><title>Tweets from Justin Bieber’s Heart: The Dynamics of the “Location ” Field in User Profiles</title><description>Tweets from Justin Bieber’s Heart: The Dynamics of the “Location ” Field in User Profiles

by Brent Hecht, Lichan Hong, Bongwon Suh, H. Chi

"... and Computer Science brent@(email omitted); ABSTRACT Little research exists on one of the most common, oldest ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 20 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Little research exists on one of the most common, &lt;em&gt;oldest&lt;/em&gt;, and most utilized forms of online social</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7492-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7492_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:54:05">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=0453D78F2225F7127408ACAF7398AB18?doi=10.1.1.74.167&amp;rank=10</link><title>CoMedia: Mobile Group Media for Active Spectatorship</title><description>CoMedia: Mobile Group Media for Active Spectatorship

by Giulio Jacucci, Antti Oulasvirta, Tommi Ilmonen, John Evans, Antti Salovaara \- In Proc. CHI 2007, ACM Press , 2007

"... members, coordination of group action, keeping up to date with others, spectating remotely, and joking ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 10 (7 self) \- Add to MetaCart

members, coordination of group action, keeping up to date with others, spectating remotely, and &lt;em&gt;joking&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>