<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7493">islam discussions social media</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:56:57" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7493-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7493_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:56:58">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CA559C25CF9406F96964F5BFFF007F82?doi=10.1.1.30.6583&amp;rank=1</link><title>Social Information Filtering: Algorithms for Automating "Word of Mouth"</title><description>Social Information Filtering: Algorithms for Automating "Word of Mouth"

by Upendra Shardanand, Pattie Maes , 1995

"... Social Information Filtering: Algorithms for Automating "Word of Mouth" Upendra Shardanand MIT ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 871 (17 self) \- Add to MetaCart

. In particular, we &lt;em&gt;discuss&lt;/em&gt; the implementation of a networked system called Ringo, which makes personalized</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7493-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7493_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:58:24">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CA559C25CF9406F96964F5BFFF007F82?doi=10.1.1.334.378&amp;rank=2</link><title>Is it an Agent, or just a Program?: A Taxonomy for Autonomous Agents</title><description>Is it an Agent, or just a Program?: A Taxonomy for Autonomous Agents

by Stan Franklin, Art Graesser \- In Intelligent Agents III , 1997

"... of software agents gave rise to much discussion of just what such an agent is, and of how they differ from ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 558 (26 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The advent of software agents gave rise to much &lt;em&gt;discussion&lt;/em&gt; of just what such an agent is</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7493-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7493_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:00:27">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CA559C25CF9406F96964F5BFFF007F82?doi=10.1.1.153.8488&amp;rank=3</link><title>Affective Computing</title><description>Affective Computing

by R. W. Picard , 1995

"... ﻿M.I.T Media Laboratory Perceptual Computing Section Technical Report No. 321 Revised November 26 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1200 (37 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Recent neurological studies indicate that the role of emotion in human cognition is essential; emotions are not a luxury. Instead, emotions play a critical role in rational decision-making, in perception, in human interaction, and in human intelligence. These facts, combined with abilities computers are acquiring in expressing and recognizing affect, open new areas for research. This paper defines key issues in "affective computing," computing that relates to, arises from, or deliberately influences emotions. New models are suggested for computer recognition of human emotion, and both theoretical and practical applications are described for learning, human-computer interaction, perceptual information retrieval, creative arts and entertainment, human health, and machine intelligence. Significant potential advances in emotion and cognition theory hinge on the development of affective computing, especially in the form of wearable computers. This paper establishes challenges and future directions for this emerging field.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7493-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7493_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:02:23">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CA559C25CF9406F96964F5BFFF007F82?doi=10.1.1.317.3619&amp;rank=4</link><title>Flocks, herds, and schools: a distributed behavioral model</title><description>Flocks, herds, and schools: a distributed behavioral model

by Craig W. Reynolds \- Computer Graphics , 1987

"... of animals; for a charming and literate discussion of such words see An Exultation of Larks. [16] **This ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 796 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

The aggregate motion of a flock of birds, a herd of land animals, or a school of fish is a beautiful and familiar part of the natural world. But this type of complex motion is rarely seen in computer animation. This paper explores an approach based on simulation as an alternative to scripting the paths of each bird individually. The simulated flock is an elaboration of a particle system, with the simulated birds being the particles. The aggregate motion of the simulated flock is created by a distributed behavioral model much like that at work in a natural flock; the birds choose their own course. Each simulated bird is implemented as an independent actor that navigates according to its local perception of the dynamic environment, the laws of simulated physics that rule its motion, and a set of behaviors programmed into it by the "animator. " The aggregate motion of the simulated flock is the result of the dense interaction of the relatively simple behaviors of the individual simulated birds.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7493-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7493_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:05:40">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CA559C25CF9406F96964F5BFFF007F82?doi=10.1.1.108.4092&amp;rank=5</link><title>Fab: Content-based, collaborative recommendation</title><description>Fab: Content-based, collaborative recommendation

by Marko Balabanovic, Yoav Shoham \- Communications of the ACM , 1997

"... on the World-Wide Web. In traditional media, readers are provided assistance in making selections ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 474 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

available on the World-Wide Web. In traditional &lt;em&gt;media&lt;/em&gt;, readers are provided assistance in making selections</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7493-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7493_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:09:18">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CA559C25CF9406F96964F5BFFF007F82?doi=10.1.1.117.4330&amp;rank=6</link><title>A survey of context-aware mobile computing research</title><description>A survey of context-aware mobile computing research

by Guanling Chen, David Kotz , 2000

"... literature in this area. In Section 2 we discuss various definitions of “context”. Section 3 summarizes ways ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 468 (2 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Context-aware computing is a mobile computing paradigm in which applications can discover and take advantage of contextual information (such as user location, time of day, nearby people and devices, and user activity). Since it was proposed about a decade ago, many researchers have studied this topic and built several context-aware applications to demonstrate the usefulness of this new technology. Context-aware applications (or the system infrastructure to support them), however, have never been widely available to everyday users. In this survey of research on context-aware systems and applications, we looked in depth at the types of context used and models of context information, at systems that support collecting and disseminating context, and at applications that adapt to the changing context. Through this survey, it is clear that context-aware research is an old but rich area for research. The difficulties and possible solutions we outline serve as guidance for researchers hoping to make context-aware computing a reality. 1.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7493-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7493_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:12:16">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CA559C25CF9406F96964F5BFFF007F82?doi=10.1.1.153.6476&amp;rank=7</link><title>What is Twitter, a Social Network or a News Media?</title><description>What is Twitter, a Social Network or a News Media?

by Haewoon Kwak, Changhyun Lee, Hosung Park, Sue Moon

"... ﻿What is Twitter, a Social Network or a News Media? Haewoon Kwak, Changhyun Lee, Hosung Park ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 358 (7 self) \- Add to MetaCart

and obtained 41.7 million user profiles, 1.47 billion &lt;em&gt;social&lt;/em&gt; relations, 4, 262 trending topics, and 106 million</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7493-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7493_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:13:55">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CA559C25CF9406F96964F5BFFF007F82?doi=10.1.1.133.6957&amp;rank=8</link><title>RCV1: A new benchmark collection for text categorization research</title><description>RCV1: A new benchmark collection for text categorization research

by David D. Lewis, Yiming Yang, Tony G. Rose, Fan Li, G. Dietterich, Fan Li \- Journal of Machine Learning Research , 2004

"... identification, language identification), and to mixtures of text with other data (multimedia and cross-media ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 430 (10 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Reuters Corpus Volume I (RCV1) is an archive of over 800,000 manually categorized newswire stories recently made available by Reuters, Ltd. for research purposes. Use of this data for research on text categorization requires a detailed understanding of the real world constraints under which the data was produced. Drawing on interviews with Reuters personnel and access to Reuters documentation, we describe the coding policy and quality control procedures used in producing the RCV1 data, the intended semantics of the hierarchical category taxonomies, and the corrections necessary to remove errorful data. We refer to the original data as RCV1-v1, and the corrected data as RCV1-v2. We benchmark several widely used supervised learning methods on RCV1-v2, illustrating the collection’s properties, suggesting new directions for research, and providing baseline results for future studies. We make available detailed, per-category experimental results, as well as</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7493-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7493_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:14:37">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CA559C25CF9406F96964F5BFFF007F82?doi=10.1.1.24.5437&amp;rank=9</link><title>A Set Of Principles For Conducting And Evaluating Interpretive Field Studies In Information Systems</title><description>A Set Of Principles For Conducting And Evaluating Interpretive Field Studies In Information Systems

by Heinz K. Klein, Michael D. Myers , 1999

"... understanding and social action. Example: Monteiro and Hanseth’s (1996) findings are discussed in relation ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 416 (4 self) \- Add to MetaCart

This article &lt;em&gt;discusses&lt;/em&gt; the conduct and evaluation of interpretive research in information systems</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7493-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7493_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:15:20">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=CA559C25CF9406F96964F5BFFF007F82?doi=10.1.1.85.9752&amp;rank=10</link><title>Reality Mining: Sensing Complex Social Systems</title><description>Reality Mining: Sensing Complex Social Systems

by Nathan Eagle, Alex Pentland \- J. OF PERSONAL AND UBIQUITOUS COMPUTING , 2005

"... ﻿Eagle, N., and Pentland, A., "Reality Mining: Sensing Complex Social Systems"', J. of Personal ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 387 (22 self) \- Add to MetaCart

We introduce a system for sensing complex &lt;em&gt;social&lt;/em&gt; systems with data collected from one hundred</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>