<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7496">why IEEE member</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:00:27" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7496-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7496_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:00:28">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A15F5BBEBACE7A0BB3620BFD7B553F92?doi=10.1.1.21.61&amp;rank=1</link><title>Semantic Web Services</title><description>Semantic Web Services

by Sheila A. Mcilraith, Tran Cao Son, Honglei Zeng \- IEEE Intelligent Systems , 2001

"... are members of the DARPA Agent Markup Language (DAML) family of languages). 4 These languages have a well ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 517 (20 self) \- Add to MetaCart

are &lt;em&gt;members&lt;/em&gt; of the DARPA Agent Markup Language (DAML) family of languages). 4 These languages have a well</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7496-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7496_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:04:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A15F5BBEBACE7A0BB3620BFD7B553F92?doi=10.1.1.194.8080&amp;rank=2</link><title>Theory of the Firm: Managerial Behavior, Agency Costs and Ownership Structure</title><description>Theory of the Firm: Managerial Behavior, Agency Costs and Ownership Structure

by Michael C. Jensen, William H. Meckling , 1976

"... by the existence of debt and outside equity, demonstrate who bears costs and why, and investigate the Pareto ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 898 (5 self) \- Add to MetaCart

of the agency costs generated by the existence of debt and outside equity, demonstrate who bears costs and &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7496-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7496_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:05:05">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A15F5BBEBACE7A0BB3620BFD7B553F92?doi=10.1.1.131.2084&amp;rank=3</link><title>A tutorial on hidden markov models and selected applications in speech recognition</title><description>A tutorial on hidden markov models and selected applications in speech recognition

by Lawrence R. Rabiner \- Proceedings of the IEEE , 1989

"... . RABINER, FELLOW, IEEE Although initially introduced and studied in the late 1960s and early 1970s ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 4251 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

. There are two strong reasons &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; this has occurred. First the models are very rich in mathematical structure</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7496-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7496_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:06:19">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A15F5BBEBACE7A0BB3620BFD7B553F92?doi=10.1.1.13.8919&amp;rank=4</link><title>The Mathematics of Statistical Machine Translation: Parameter Estimation</title><description>The Mathematics of Statistical Machine Translation: Parameter Estimation

by Peter F. Brown, Vincent J.Della Pietra, Stephen A. Della Pietra, Robert. L. Mercer \- Computational Linguistics , 1993

"... be a concern to some readers: Why do we estimate Pr(e) and Pr(fle ) rather than estimate Pr ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 1176 (1 self) \- Add to MetaCart

, we should address an issue that may be a concern to some readers: &lt;em&gt;Why&lt;/em&gt; do we estimate Pr(e) and Pr</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7496-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7496_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:09:11">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A15F5BBEBACE7A0BB3620BFD7B553F92?doi=10.1.1.117.315&amp;rank=5</link><title>No Silver Bullet: Essence and Accidents of Software Engineering</title><description>No Silver Bullet: Essence and Accidents of Software Engineering

by Frederick P. Brooks \- IEEE Computer , 1987

"... , in reliability, in simplicity. In this article, I shall try to show why, by examining both the nature ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 546 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

-of-magnitude improvement in productivity, in reliability, in simplicity. In this article, I shall try to show &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7496-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7496_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:12:06">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A15F5BBEBACE7A0BB3620BFD7B553F92?doi=10.1.1.20.299&amp;rank=6</link><title>SCRIBE: A large-scale and decentralized application-level multicast infrastructure</title><description>SCRIBE: A large-scale and decentralized application-level multicast infrastructure

by Miguel Castro, Peter Druschel, Anne-Marie Kermarrec, Antony Rowstron \- IEEE Journal on Selected Areas in Communications (JSAC , 2002

"... ﻿IEEE JOURNAL ON SELECTED AREAS IN COMMUNICATIONS, VOL. XX, NO. Y, MONTH 2002 100 Scribe: A large ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 499 (29 self) \- Add to MetaCart

large numbers of groups, with a potentially large number of &lt;em&gt;members&lt;/em&gt; per group. Scribe is built on top</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7496-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7496_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:14:54">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A15F5BBEBACE7A0BB3620BFD7B553F92?doi=10.1.1.17.9507&amp;rank=7</link><title>Gapped Blast and PsiBlast: a new generation of protein database search programs</title><description>Gapped Blast and PsiBlast: a new generation of protein database search programs

by Stephen F. Altschul, Thomas L. Madden, Alejandro A. Schäffer, Jinghui Zhang, Zheng Zhang, Webb Miller, David J. Lipman \- NUCLEIC ACIDS RESEARCH , 1997

"... -BLAST is used to uncover several new and interesting members of the BRCT superfamily. INTRODUCTION Variations ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 3822 (55 self) \- Add to MetaCart

and interesting &lt;em&gt;members&lt;/em&gt; of the BRCT superfamily.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7496-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7496_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:16:24">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A15F5BBEBACE7A0BB3620BFD7B553F92?doi=10.1.1.112.463&amp;rank=8</link><title>Myrinet: A Gigabit-per-Second Local Area Network</title><description>Myrinet: A Gigabit-per-Second Local Area Network

by Nanette J. Boden, Danny Cohen, Robert E. Felderman, Alan E. Kulawik, Charles L. Seitz, Jakov N. Seizovic, Wen-king Su \- IEEE Micro , 1995

"... by members of these two research projects. Multicomputer Message-Passing Networks. A multicomputer [4, 5 ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 901 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

company founded by &lt;em&gt;members&lt;/em&gt; of these two research projects. Multicomputer Message-Passing Networks. A</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7496-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7496_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:17:43">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A15F5BBEBACE7A0BB3620BFD7B553F92?doi=10.1.1.26.1865&amp;rank=9</link><title>The Ant System: Optimization by a colony of cooperating agents</title><description>The Ant System: Optimization by a colony of cooperating agents

by Marco Dorigo, Vittorio Maniezzo, Alberto Colorni \- IEEE TRANSACTIONS ON SYSTEMS, MAN, AND CYBERNETICS-PART B , 1996

"... System: Optimization by a colony of cooperating agents Marco Dorigo *,^ , Member, IEEE, Vittorio Maniezzo ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 802 (47 self) \- Add to MetaCart

An analogy with the way ant colonies function has suggested the definition of a new computational paradigm, which we call Ant System. We propose it as a viable new approach to stochastic combinatorial optimization. The main characteristics of this model are positive feedback, distributed computation, and the use of a constructive greedy heuristic. Positive feedback accounts for rapid discovery of good solutions, distributed computation avoids premature convergence, and the greedy heuristic helps find acceptable solutions in the early stages of the search process. We apply the proposed methodology to the classical Traveling Salesman Problem (TSP), and report simulation results. We also discuss parameter selection and the early setups of the model, and compare it with tabu search and simulated annealing using TSP. To demonstrate the robustness of the approach, we show how the Ant System (AS) can be applied to other optimization problems like the asymmetric traveling salesman, the quadrat...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7496-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7496_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:21:10">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=A15F5BBEBACE7A0BB3620BFD7B553F92?doi=10.1.1.11.2477&amp;rank=10</link><title>Image Quality Assessment: From Error Visibility to Structural Similarity</title><description>Image Quality Assessment: From Error Visibility to Structural Similarity

by Zhou Wang, Alan C. Bovik, Hamid R. Sheikh, Eero P. Simoncelli \- IEEE TRANSACTIONS ON IMAGE PROCESSING , 2004

"... Error Visibility to Structural Similarity Zhou Wang, Member, IEEE, Alan C. Bovik, Fellow, IEEE Hamid R ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 577 (40 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Objective methods for assessing perceptual image quality have traditionally attempted to quantify the visibility of errors between a distorted image and a reference image using a variety of known properties of the human visual system. Under the assumption that human visual perception is highly adapted for extracting structural information from a scene, we introduce an alternative framework for quality assessment based on the degradation of structural information. As a specific example of this concept, we develop a Structural Similarity Index and demonstrate its promise through a set of intuitive examples, as well as comparison to both subjective ratings and state-of-the-art objective methods on a database of images compressed with JPEG and JPEG2000.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>