<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7497">shostakovich life</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:21:55" name="CiteSeerX" id="FW14-e004"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e004-7497-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7497_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:22:01">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E56BC2CBE3B51D0AEC1536D284479143?doi=10.1.1.399.3965&amp;rank=1</link><title>Edward PearsallThe Film Music of Dmitri Shostakovich in</title><description>Edward PearsallThe Film Music of Dmitri Shostakovich in

by Erik James Heine, The Gadfly, King Lear, The Gadfly, King Lear, Erik James Heine

"... music appear, from the perspective of a non-Russian. John Riley’s Shostakovich: A Life in Film ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

A task of this magnitude cannot be completed without outside assistance, so there are a few people that I need to thank. First, I’d like to thank my parents, Rick and Deb Heine, for instilling a sense of drive in me. Without their approval and encouragement, I would still be in the chemistry department, languishing in a field where I did not want to be. There are a couple of colleagues of mine that I need to thank. The first is John Loughlin. His laughter is infectious and we always had a good time, even if the work was difficult. I also need to thank Karen Ernst. We both arrived at Texas at the same time, and basically had the same schedule our first year as doctoral students. She has been a wonderful friend throughout these three years. Without these two people, my doctoral work would not have been nearly as enjoyable. I need to thank all of my professors, particularly the ones with whom I taught, Drs. Almen, Pearsall, and Wheeldon. I’ve had a wonderful experience teaching at Texas, primarily because I had terrific models. Special thanks to my advisor, Dr. David Neumeyer, for putting up with me during the writing and editing period, and</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7497-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7497_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:25:03">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E56BC2CBE3B51D0AEC1536D284479143?doi=10.1.1.391.9910&amp;rank=2</link><title>E. Ward CheneyShostakovich’s Cello Sonata: Its Genesis Related to Socialist Realism by</title><description>E. Ward CheneyShostakovich’s Cello Sonata: Its Genesis Related to Socialist Realism by

by Miranda Clare Wilson, Elliott Antokoletz Supervisor, Phyllis Young Co-supervisor, A Clare Wilson, Mus. B M. Mus , 1919

"... , and functions like the scherzo and trio movement in a Classical 1 Laurel Fay, Shostakovich: A Life (New York ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Abstract not found</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7497-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7497_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:25:49">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E56BC2CBE3B51D0AEC1536D284479143?doi=10.1.1.410.6347&amp;rank=3</link><title>A Transcription for Band</title><description>A Transcription for Band

by Jeffrey David Gershman, Jerry F. Junkin, Donald Grantham Co-supervisor, Hanns-bertold Dietz, Kevin L. Sedatole, Dan E. Welcher, Jeffrey David Gershman

"... and gratitude indebted to all of the people who have helped shape my musical and personal life. While ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

and gratitude indebted to all of the people who have helped shape my musical and personal &lt;em&gt;life&lt;/em&gt;. While</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7497-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7497_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:27:26">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E56BC2CBE3B51D0AEC1536D284479143?doi=10.1.1.188.6579&amp;rank=4</link><title>Proceedings of the International Symposium on Music Acoustics (Associated Meeting of the International Congress on Acoustics)</title><description>Proceedings of the International Symposium on Music Acoustics (Associated Meeting of the International Congress on Acoustics)

by John Smith, Joe Wolfe

"... need less adjustment by the singer to be tuned to f0, which would not only make life easier ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Wagner’s music is even better than it sounds: resonance tuning produced by matching vowels with pitch</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7497-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7497_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:30:13">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E56BC2CBE3B51D0AEC1536D284479143?doi=10.1.1.156.8868&amp;rank=5</link><title>of Australia</title><description>of Australia

by Catherine Fraser

"... most memorable musical moment in my life was probably the very first rehearsal piece of ADO ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

bows to the audience, and then turns, raising his baton, to face more than 100 musicians with their instruments poised, it can feel as if time has stopped. The anticipation of a whole concert of magical music to follow, the culmination of much concentrated</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7497-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7497_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:30:44">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E56BC2CBE3B51D0AEC1536D284479143?doi=10.1.1.385.7350&amp;rank=6</link><title>The rewarding aspects of music listening are related to degree of emotional arousal</title><description>The rewarding aspects of music listening are related to degree of emotional arousal

by Valorie N. Salimpoor, Mitchel Benovoy, Gregory Longo, Jeremy R. Cooperstock, Robert J \- PloS One , 2009

"... life event (e.g., prom, a memorable concert, etc.) or a period of time (e.g., summer of 2004, high ..."

Abstract \- Cited by 2 (0 self) \- Add to MetaCart

Background: Listening to music is amongst the most rewarding experiences for humans. Music has no functional resemblance to other rewarding stimuli, and has no demonstrated biological value, yet individuals continue listening to music for pleasure. It has been suggested that the pleasurable aspects of music listening are related to a change in emotional arousal, although this link has not been directly investigated. In this study, using methods of high temporal sensitivity we investigated whether there is a systematic relationship between dynamic increases in pleasure states and physiological indicators of emotional arousal, including changes in heart rate, respiration, electrodermal activity, body temperature, and blood volume pulse. Methodology: Twenty-six participants listened to self-selected intensely pleasurable music and ‘‘neutral’ ’ music that was individually selected for them based on low pleasure ratings they provided on other participants ’ music. The ‘‘chills’’ phenomenon was used to index intensely pleasurable responses to music. During music listening, continuous real-time recordings of subjective pleasure states and simultaneous recordings of sympathetic nervous system activity, an objective measure of emotional arousal, were obtained. Principal Findings: Results revealed a strong positive correlation between ratings of pleasure and emotional arousal. Importantly, a dissociation was revealed as individuals who did not experience pleasure also showed no significant increases</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7497-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7497_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:31:25">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E56BC2CBE3B51D0AEC1536D284479143?doi=10.1.1.368.1508&amp;rank=7</link><title>Is It Worth It? Lintott and Ethically Evaluating Environmental Art</title><description>Is It Worth It? Lintott and Ethically Evaluating Environmental Art

by John Andrew Fisher

"... not only acknowledging the site but actually incorporating some of its original features and life forms. 7 ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

The question ‘Is it worth it?’, as originally applied to artworks by Tolstoy and here reintroduced by Sheila Lintott, opens a fruitful avenue for understanding land art. It is, however, a question with many facets in need of analysis. I will try to sketch that analysis here. Although the target of Lintott’s discussion is the category of land art, the Tolstoyan question does not come up only in the case of land art. It frequently arises in cases of controversial or extravagant types of art of many sorts, and understanding its application to various types of art illuminates their artistic content as well as their artistic value. I take the is-it-worth-it question to be a question of overall value—i.e., the sum of positive and negative values the generation of a work necessarily or contingently brings into existence. Although Tolstoy may appear to pose primarily a resource question, in actuality he pursues the issue in more complex ways that apply to land art as well as to his example of an opera. Tolstoy usefully reminds us of the multiple locations for moral and value assessment in the calculation of the overall worth of any artwork. He worries about the opportunity costs of the labor and the materials</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7497-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7497_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:33:24">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E56BC2CBE3B51D0AEC1536D284479143?doi=10.1.1.420.8693&amp;rank=8</link><title>Design</title><description>Design

by David Raymond, Juliet Grabowski, Bobbi Lonobile, Kurt Brownell, Walter Colley, Nathan Martel, Nathan Martel, Jamal J. Rossi , 2006

"... September 15–17, 2006 • Shostakovich \+ Weinberg: An Artistic Dialog: Festival honoring the centenary ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

Transition and change provide the opportunity to celebrate past achievements and to chart a course for future accomplishments. Our heartiest congratulations and hopes for great success go forth with Jim Undercofler as he assumes his new responsibilities as the President and CEO of the Philadelphia Orchestra. As you will read in the pages ahead, Jim’s tenure as Director and Dean of Eastman has been marked by innovative accomplishments, which have strengthened the School’s commitment to leadership. As we look to the future, and to the coming academic year in particular, there exist three important initiatives that will have historic implications for the Eastman School of Music. The first is the search for our next Dean. President Seligman has appointed a search committee, which will be chaired by University Vice-President and General Secretary Paul Burgett. Information about the search can be found on President Seligman’s web page on the University’s web site: www.rochester.edu/president.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7497-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7497_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:36:29">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E56BC2CBE3B51D0AEC1536D284479143?doi=10.1.1.178.6011&amp;rank=9</link><title>Two RECENT NOVELS,powerful evocations of</title><description>Two RECENT NOVELS,powerful evocations of

by Jane Manthorne, Of Books, Duke Custis

"... of wonder to his brief, violent lifee2 Duke Custis and Johnny are characters in fiction who find their way ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

youth almost trapped in a rough-tough society, show the influence</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e004-7497-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e004/7497_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:38:11">http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary;jsessionid=E56BC2CBE3B51D0AEC1536D284479143?doi=10.1.1.303.9925&amp;rank=10</link><title>the streets of São Paulo, Brazil.</title><description>the streets of São Paulo, Brazil.

by Loschiavo Santos, Maria Cecilia, Loschiavo Santos, Maria Cecilia The Ephemeral, Robert Harl , 2008

"... to what could be interpreted as matters of life and death, is graphic design. Graphic design depicts ..."

Abstract \- Add to MetaCart

This document is the author deposited version. You are advised to consult the publisher's version if you wish to cite from it.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>