<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7037">how to write journalistic review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:39:47" name="CERN Documents" id="FW14-e003"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e003-7037-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7037_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:39:50">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1564182?ln=en</link><title>CERN Webfest: A weekend for science on the web 
Webfest du CERN : un weekend consacré à la science sur le web</title><description>CERN Webfest: A weekend for science on the web 
Webfest du CERN : un weekend consacré à la science sur le web / CERN Bulletin 
Are you passionate about science? Do you like communicating that passion to the general public? Then come along to the CERN Summer Student Webfest on the weekend of 3-4 August! It is a grassroots initiative by the summer students, open to all staff and users, and aims to spark new ideas that could innovate the future of web-based education about CERN, the LHC and particle physics.   The CERN Summer Student Webfest is a weekend of online web-based creativity modelled on the gatherings (sometimes called hackfests or hackathons) that energize many open-source communities. [...] 
BUL-EV-2013-050.- 2013 \- Published in : CERN Bulletin 31/2013 32/2013 Fulltext: JPG;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7037-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7037_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:41:04">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1554541?ln=en</link><title>Why can't I sue my software provider? 
Pourquoi ne puis-je pas poursuivre en justice mon fournisseur de logiciels ?</title><description>Why can't I sue my software provider? 
Pourquoi ne puis-je pas poursuivre en justice mon fournisseur de logiciels ? / Computer Security Team 
Imagine buying a new car, fixing its number plates on and driving it off to the autobahn in order to test whether the 250km/h top speed on the speed meter is genuine. However, there's too much traffic,and  you have to slow down. [...] 
BUL-NA-2013-132.- 2013 \- Published in : CERN Bulletin 27/2013 28/2013</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7037-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7037_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:42:11">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1462256?ln=en</link><title>No app for that? Make it yourself! 
Pas d'appli pour ça ? Créez-la !</title><description>No app for that? Make it yourself! 
Pas d'appli pour ça ? Créez-la ! / CERN Bulletin 
Are you passionate about science? Do you like communicating that passion to the general public? Then come along to the very first CERN Summer Student Webfest kicking off on Friday 3 August! The Webfest is a grassroots initiative by the summer students, seeking to spark new ideas that could innovate the future of web-based education about CERN, the LHC and particle physics.   The CERN Summer Student Webfest is a weekend of online web-based creativity modelled on the gatherings (sometimes called hackfests or hackathons) that energize many open source communities. [...] 
BUL-NA-2012-239.- 2012 \- Published in : CERN Bulletin 30/2012 31/2012</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>