<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7078">count in korean</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:41:10" name="CERN Documents" id="FW14-e003"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e003-7078-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7078_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:41:15">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1299809?ln=en</link><title>How to evaluate universities in terms of their relative citation impacts: Fractional counting of citations and the normalization of differences among disciplines</title><description>How to evaluate universities in terms of their relative citation impacts: Fractional counting of citations and the normalization of differences among disciplines / Leydesdorff, Loet ; Shin, Jung C 
Fractional counting of citations can improve on ranking of multi-disciplinary research units (such as universities) by normalizing the differences among fields of science in terms of differences in citation behavior. [...] 
arXiv:1010.2465. \- 2010\. 
Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7078-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7078_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:42:16">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1262705?ln=en</link><title>Neutron Stars with Bose-Einstein Condensation of Antikaons as MIT Bags</title><description>Neutron Stars with Bose-Einstein Condensation of Antikaons as MIT Bags / Ryu, C Y ; Hyun, C H ; Hong, S W 
We investigate the properties of an antikaon in medium, regarding itas a MIT bag. We first construct the MIT bag model for a kaon with$\sigma^*$ and $\phi$ in order to describe the interaction of$s$-quarks in hyperonic matter in the framework of the modifiedquark-meson coupling model. [...] 
arXiv:1004.5198.- 2010 \- Published in : J. Korean Phys.Soc. 54 (2009) 1448 External link: Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7078-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7078_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:43:28">http://cds.cern.ch/record/836450?ln=en</link><title>Superconformal Quantum Mechanics of Small Black Holes</title><description>Superconformal Quantum Mechanics of Small Black Holes / Kim, S ; Raeymaekers, J 
Recently, Gaiotto, Strominger and Yin have proposed a holographic dual description for the near-horizon physics of certain N=2 black holes in terms of the superconformal quantum mechanics on D0-branes in the attractor geometry. We provide further evidence for their proposal by applying it to the case of `small' black holes which have vanishing horizon area in the leading supergravity approximation. [...] 
hep-th/0505176; KIAS-P-2005-033.- Seoul, S Korea : Korean Inst. Adv. Study, 2005 - 16 p. \- Published in : J. High Energy Phys. 08 (2005) 082 Access to fulltext document: PDF; External link: hep-th/0505176 PDF</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7078-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7078_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:44:42">http://cds.cern.ch/record/776461?ln=en</link><title>In-beam gamma-ray coincidence spectroscopy for low-lying states of tellurium isotopes by using a sup n sup a sup t Sn(alpha,2n gamma) reaction</title><description>In-beam gamma-ray coincidence spectroscopy for low-lying states of tellurium isotopes by using a sup n sup a sup t Sn(alpha,2n gamma) reaction / Ha, J H ; Choi, B H ; Kim, J C ; Park, S H ; Lee, C S ; Lee, J H ; Kwon, Y K ; Kim, J H ; Chai, J S 
Low-lying states of sup 1 sup 1 sup 8 sup , sup 1 sup 2 sup 0 sup , sup 1 sup 2 sup 2 Te isotopes were studied through the sup n sup a sup t Sn(alpha,2n gamma) fusion-evaporation reaction. The experiment was performed at a new beam line recently attached to the MC-50 cyclotron of the Korea Cancer Center Hospital. [...] 
2000 \- Published in : J. Korean Phys. Soc.: 36 (2000) , no. 4, pp. 199-205</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7078-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7078_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:45:50">http://cds.cern.ch/record/623632?ln=en</link><title>Operation of a RPC with low resistivity bakelite for the endcap region of CMS in a high-rate environment</title><description>Operation of a RPC with low resistivity bakelite for the endcap region of CMS in a high-rate environment / Ahn, S H ; Choi, E J ; Hong, B ; Hong, S J ; Kang, D H ; Kim, T J ; Lee, K S ; Park, S ; Park, W J ; Ryu, M S et al. 
We present the beam-test results for a real-size prototype resistive plate chamber (RPC) for the endcap region of the Compact Muon Solenoid (CMS) experiment at CERN Large Hadron Collider (LHC). The chamber built with relatively low resistivity bakelite was tested at the Gamma Irradiation Facility (GIF) at CERN under a high photon-flux environment with an effective cluster rate up to about 1.2 kHz/cm/sup 2/. [...] 
2002 \- Published in : J. Korean Phys. Soc.: 41 (2002) , no. 5, pp. 667-73</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>