<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7106">active learning survey</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:48:41" name="CERN Documents" id="FW14-e003"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e003-7106-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7106_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:48:44">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1693428?ln=en</link><title></title><description>Third International Conference on Soft Computing for Problem Solving \- SocProS 2013 SocProS 13   26 - 28 Dec 2013  \- Roorkee, India  / Pant, Millie (ed.); Deep, Kusum (ed.); Nagar, Atulya (ed.); Bansal, Jagdish (ed.) 
The present book is based on the research papers presented in the 3rd International Conference on Soft Computing for Problem Solving (SocProS 2013), held as a part of the golden jubilee celebrations of the Saharanpur Campus of IIT Roorkee, at the Noida Campus of Indian Institute of Technology Roorkee, India. This book is divided into two volumes and covers a variety of topics including mathematical modelling, image processing, optimization, swarm intelligence, evolutionary algorithms, fuzzy logic, neural networks, forecasting, medical and health care, data mining etc. [...] 
New Delhi : Springer, 2014 
e-proceedings (v.1) 
e-proceedings (v.2)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7106-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7106_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:49:47">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1668356?ln=en</link><title>Embedding librarianship in learning management systems : a how-to-do-it manual for librarians</title><description>Embedding librarianship in learning management systems : a how-to-do-it manual for librarians / Tumbleson, Beth E 
Information literacy instruction is best when it is integrated into actual research, and in higher education that means embedding librarianship into the learning management system (LMS) [...] 
Chicago, IL : American Library Association, 2014. - 185 p.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7106-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7106_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:50:58">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1646894?ln=en</link><title>Deformations of surface singularities</title><description>Deformations of surface singularities / Némethi, András (ed.) ; Szilárd, ágnes (ed.) 
The present publication contains a special collection of research and review articles on deformations of surface singularities, that put together serve as an introductory survey of results and methods of the theory, as well as open problems, important examples and connections to other areas of mathe [...] 
Berlin : Springer, 2013. (Bolyai Society Mathematical Studies ; 23)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7106-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7106_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:52:09">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1638438?ln=en</link><title>Search for gamma-ray-emitting active galactic nuclei in the Fermi-LAT unassociated sample using machine learning</title><description>Search for gamma-ray-emitting active galactic nuclei in the Fermi-LAT unassociated sample using machine learning / Doert, M ; Errando, M 
The second Fermi-LAT source catalog (2FGL) is the deepest all-sky survey available in the gamma-ray band. [...] 
arXiv:1312.5726. \- 2013\. - 7 p. 
Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7106-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7106_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:53:17">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1637552?ln=en</link><title>AGN Absorption Linked to Host Galaxies</title><description>AGN Absorption Linked to Host Galaxies / Juneau, Stéphanie 
Multiwavelength identification of AGN is crucial not only to obtain a more complete census, but also to learn about the physical state of the nuclear activity (obscuration, efficiency, etc.). [...] 
arXiv:1312.4563. \- 2013\. - 3 p. 
Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7106-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7106_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:54:29">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1635225?ln=en</link><title></title><description>Computational Intelligence, Cyber Security and Computational Models \- ICC3 2013   19–21 Dec 2013  \- Coimbatore, India  / Krishnan, G (ed.); Anitha, R (ed.); Lekshmi, R (ed.); Kumar, M (ed.); Bonato, Anthony (ed.); Graña, Manuel (ed.) 
This book contains cutting-edge research material presented by researchers, engineers, developers, and practitioners from academia and industry at the International Conference on Computational Intelligence, Cyber Security and Computational Models (ICC3) organized by PSG College of Technology, Coimbatore, India during December 19–21, 2013. The materials in the book include theory and applications for design, analysis, and modeling of computational intelligence and security. [...] 
New Delhi : Springer, 2014 
e-proceedings</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7106-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7106_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:55:28">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1625554?ln=en</link><title>Towards an intelligent learning management system under blended learning : trends, profiles and modeling perspectives</title><description>Towards an intelligent learning management system under blended learning : trends, profiles and modeling perspectives / Dias, Sofia B 
This book offers useful information that evokes initiatives towards rethinking of the value, efficiency, inclusiveness, effectiveness and personalization of the intelligent learning management systems-based blended-learning environment.. 
Dordrecht : Springer, 2013. - 243 p. (Intelligent Systems Reference Library ; 59)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7106-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7106_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:56:28">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1625432?ln=en</link><title>Coverbal synchrony in human-machine interaction</title><description>Coverbal synchrony in human-machine interaction / Rojc, Matej 
Embodied conversational agents (ECA) and speech-based human-machine interfaces can together represent more advanced and more natural human-machine interaction [...] 
Hoboken, NJ : Taylor and Francis, 2013. - 432 p.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7106-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7106_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:57:28">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1616251?ln=en</link><title>Real-life marketing and promotion strategies in college libraries : connecting with campus and community</title><description>Real-life marketing and promotion strategies in college libraries : connecting with campus and community / Petruzzelli, Barbara W 
Practical advice on how to promote your library and how to better understand and serve library usersReal-Life Marketing and Promotion Strategies in College Libraries is a ?how-to? guide to marketing and promotional activities that will raise your library's visibility in the face of increased competition from other information providers [...] 
Hoboken, NJ : Taylor and Francis, 2012. - 205 p.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7106-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7106_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:58:26">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1615759?ln=en</link><title>Microwave radio transmission design guide</title><description>Microwave radio transmission design guide . \- 2nd ed. / Manning, Trevor 
This newly revised second edition provides a current, comprehensive treatment of the subject with a focus on applying practical knowledge to real-world networks [...] 
Norwood : Artech House, 2009. - 296 p.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>