<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7111">what is the starting salary for a recruiter</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:03:49" name="CERN Documents" id="FW14-e003"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e003-7111-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7111_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:03:52">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1609878?ln=en</link><title>Hiring, training, and supervising library shelvers</title><description>Hiring, training, and supervising library shelvers / Tunstall, Patricia 
How do you find good library shelvers and keep them for more than a few months? Tunstall gives practical advice to help you do just that with a complete overview on how to hire, test, train, and retain shelvers.. 
Chicago : ALA Editions, 2009. - 121 p.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7111-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7111_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:04:49">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1275543?ln=en</link><title>Five-Yearly Review 2010 : Confirmation that our salaries are going downhill 
Five-Yearly Review 2010 : Confirmation that our salaries are going downhill</title><description>Five-Yearly Review 2010 : Confirmation that our salaries are going downhill 
Five-Yearly Review 2010 : Confirmation that our salaries are going downhill / Staff Association 
A general review of our financial and social conditions takes place every five years: “the five-yearly review”, whose principles and procedures are described in Annex A1 of the Staff Rules and Regulations. The purpose of the five-yearly review is to ensure that the financial and social conditions offered by the Organization allow it to recruit and retain from all its Member States staff members of the highest competence and integrity required for the execution of its mission [...] 
BUL-SA-2010-136.- 2010 \- Published in : CERN Bulletin 27/2010 28/2010 Fulltext: Graphique_1(1)_image \- JPG; Graphique_2(2)_image \- JPG; Graphique_5(1)_image \- JPG; Graphique_3(1)_image \- JPG; Graphique_4(1)_image \- JPG;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7111-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7111_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:06:04">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1255862?ln=en</link><title>EUTELSAT is not answering anymore, the ILOAT has cut them off 
EUTELSAT ne répond plus, le TAOIT a coupé la ligne !</title><description>EUTELSAT is not answering anymore, the ILOAT has cut them off 
EUTELSAT ne répond plus, le TAOIT a coupé la ligne ! / Association du personnel 
On 3rd February, the ILOAT (International Labour Organization Administrative Tribunal, which is also our tribunal) delivered a judgement which has had us thinking ever since. This decision could, in certain circumstances, infringe upon the pension rights of international civil servants [...] 
BUL-SA-2010-068.- 2010 \- Published in : CERN Bulletin 14/2010 15/2010</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>