<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7131">golf games</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:48:58" name="CERN Documents" id="FW14-e003"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e003-7131-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7131_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:49:00">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1690092?ln=en</link><title>Play Golf with the CERN Golf Club 
Jouez au golf avec le Club de golf du CERN</title><description>Play Golf with the CERN Golf Club 
Jouez au golf avec le Club de golf du CERN / Golf Club 
The snow has gone, the grass is getting greener and the golf courses open up to hibernating golfers; The CERN golf club committee has been busy organising the program for the coming golf season, with many attractive outings to nearby courses. Are you new to CERN? And you play golf? or would like to learn ? then join us, playing golf and having fun [...] 
BUL-SA-2014-044.- 2014 \- Published in : , no. 14/2014, pp. 5 
\- Published in : , no. 15/2014, pp. 5 Fulltext: tableau-3-francais_image \- GIF; tableau 3_2_image \- JPG;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7131-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7131_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:49:54">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1663674?ln=en</link><title>The physics of golf</title><description>The physics of golf . \- 2nd ed. / Jorgensen, Theodore P 
Improve your golf game by learning the underlying fundamentals of the golf swing in this acclaimed, unique contribution to the sport Finally, you’ll understand why shortening your backswing doesn’t substantially decrease clubhead velocity what components contribute to the optimal swing and what variations are acceptable how and why properly shifting your weight adds to distance why a golf ball behaves and spins as it does and much more Written by a physicist after some twenty years of research, Physics of Golf is the only book devoted exclusively to explaining the science behind a successful golf game Technical appendices offer details for the so inclined The revised and expanded second now offers you -new material on high-tech club designs -a complete new chapter on short putts -additional applications of physics to the problems every player faces "Jorgensen tells golfers what they ought to be doing and why, the correct technique according to the principles of physics" -Golf Weekly "…gives new insights and precise views into the forces and torques developed in the downswing…Thank you, Dr Jorgensen…We will all treasure your book" -American Golf Pro "The heart of golfer Ted Jorgensen’s delightful book lies in his analysis of the swing of the golf club and how, armed with insights from that analysis, you, he and I might all swing the club better and play better golf…[The book] is designed to be accessible to the casual reader while satisfying the critical student But first word or last, for anyone who has swung a golf club, the book is fun to read" -Physics Today "This very enjoyable book covers most aspects of golf from the swing, to club selection, golf balls, and human motion" -Applied Mechanics Review 
New York : Springer, 1999.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7131-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7131_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:51:11">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1615771?ln=en</link><title>On the efficient determination of most near neighbors : horseshoes, hand grenades, web search and other situations when close is close enough</title><description>On the efficient determination of most near neighbors : horseshoes, hand grenades, web search and other situations when close is close enough / Manasse, Mark S 
The time-worn aphorism ""close only counts in horseshoes and hand-grenades"" is clearly inadequate. [...] 
San Rafael : Morgan &amp; Claypool Publishers, 2012. - 90 p.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7131-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7131_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:52:22">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1609824?ln=en</link><title>Incredible iPhone apps for dummies</title><description>Incredible iPhone apps for dummies / LeVitus, Bob 
A full-color directory of must-have iPhone and iPod touch apps! The App Store allows you to browse and download thousands of applications that were developed with the iPhone SDK and published through Apple [...] 
Hoboken, NJ : Wiley, 2010. - 243 p.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7131-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7131_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:53:30">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1567059?ln=en</link><title>Croquet Club 
Croquet Club</title><description>Croquet Club 
Croquet Club / Croquet Club 
On the weekend of 13/14 July, the club hosted the 18th Swiss golf croquet championship. Alongside  club members,  10 members of the Zürich Croquet Club took part. [...] 
BUL-SA-2013-130.- 2013 \- Published in : CERN Bulletin 33/2013 34/2013 35/2013</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7131-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7131_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:54:45">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1564623?ln=en</link><title>CROQUET CLUB 
CROQUET CLUB</title><description>CROQUET CLUB 
CROQUET CLUB / Croquet Club 
On the weekend of 13/14 July, the club hosted the 18th Swiss golf croquet championship. Alongside club members, 10 members of the Zürich Croquet Club took part. [...] 
BUL-SA-2013-120.- 2013 \- Published in : CERN Bulletin 31/2013 32/2013</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7131-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7131_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:55:53">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1537847?ln=en</link><title>RUGBY 
RUGBY</title><description>RUGBY 
RUGBY / Rugby Club 
Women's rugby has been gaining popularity for some years now. The ‘’Wildcats’’, the women's rugby Club of CERN Meyrin St-Genis (RC CMSG), is the only women's team currently present in Geneva area [...] 
BUL-SA-2013-050.- 2013 \- Published in : CERN Bulletin 15/2013 16/2013 Fulltext: JPG;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7131-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7131_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:57:00">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1487882?ln=en</link><title>Divided Spheres : Geodesics and the Orderly Subdivision of the Sphere</title><description>Divided Spheres : Geodesics and the Orderly Subdivision of the Sphere / Popko, Edward S 
This well-illustrated book-in color throughout-presents a thorough introduction to the mathematics of Buckminster Fuller's invention of the geodesic dome, which paved the way for a flood of practical applications as diverse as weather forecasting and fish farms. [...] 
Hoboken, NJ : CRC Press, 2012. - 525 p.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7131-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7131_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:58:11">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1438720?ln=en</link><title>Mathematical Snippets : Exploring mathematical ideas in small bites</title><description>Mathematical Snippets : Exploring mathematical ideas in small bites / Pappas, Theoni 
From nutritional labels and box office statistics to terabytes and megapixels, the 21st century world is awash in numbers. [...] 
New York : Wide World Publishing, Tetra, 2008. - 209 p.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7131-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7131_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:59:17">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1391846?ln=en</link><title>Probabilistic divide-and-conquer: a new exact simulation method, with integer partitions as an example</title><description>Probabilistic divide-and-conquer: a new exact simulation method, with integer partitions as an example / Arratia, Richard ; DeSalvo, Stephen 
Many natural simulation tasks, such as generating a partition of a large integer $n$, choosing uniformly over the $p_n$ conceivable choices, might be done by proposing a random object from a larger set, and then checking for membership in the desired target set. [...] 
arXiv:1110.3856. \- 2011\. 
Preprint</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>