<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7141">Cambridge must do</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:51:05" name="CERN Documents" id="FW14-e003"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e003-7141-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7141_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:51:07">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1628178?ln=en</link><title>Resolved Imaging of the HR 8799 Debris Disk with Herschel</title><description>Resolved Imaging of the HR 8799 Debris Disk with Herschel / Matthews, Brenda C (National Research Council of Canada Herzberg Astronomy and Astrophsyics, BC, Canada ; University of Victoria, BC, Canada) ; Kennedy, Grant (Institute of Astronomy, University of Cambridge, United Kingdom) ; Sibthorpe, Bruce (SRON Netherlands Institute for Space Research, Groningen, the Netherlands) ; Booth, Mark (Instituto de Astrofísica, Pontificia Universidad Católica de Chile, Santiago, Chile ; University of Victoria, BC, Canada ; National Research Council of Canada Herzberg Astronomy and Astrophsyics, BC, Canada) ; Wyatt, Mark (Institute of Astronomy, University of Cambridge, United Kingdom) ; Broekhoven-Fiene, Hannah (University of Victoria, BC, Canada ; National Research Council of Canada Herzberg Astronomy and Astrophsyics, BC, Canada) ; Macintosh, Bruce (Lawrence Livermore National Labs, CA, U.S.A ; Stanford University, CA, U.S.A) ; Marois, Christian (National Research Council of Canada Herzberg Astronomy and Astrophsyics, BC, Canada ; University of Victoria, BC, Canada) 
We present Herschel far-infrared and submillimeter maps of the debris disk associated with the HR 8799 planetary system. [...] 
arXiv:1311.2977. \- 2013\. - 13 p. 
Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7141-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7141_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:52:13">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1455503?ln=en</link><title>Feedback from the IR Background in the Early Universe</title><description>Feedback from the IR Background in the Early Universe / Wolcott-Green, Jemma (Cambridge University) ; Haiman, Zoltán (Columbia University) 
It is commonly believed that the earliest stages of star-formation in the Universe were self-regulated by global radiation backgrounds - either by the ultraviolet Lyman-Werner (LW) photons emitted by the first stars (directly photodissociating H_2), or by the X-rays produced by accretion onto the black hole (BH) remnants of these stars (heating the gas but catalyzing H_2 formation). [...] 
arXiv:1206.1861. \- 2012\. 
Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7141-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7141_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:53:27">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1447457?ln=en</link><title>Measurement of the top quark pair cross section with ATLAS in pp collisions at $\sqrt{s}$ = 7 TeV using final states with an electron or a muon and a hadronically decaying $\tau$ lepton</title><description>Measurement of the top quark pair cross section with ATLAS in pp collisions at $\sqrt{s}$ = 7 TeV using final states with an electron or a muon and a hadronically decaying $\tau$ lepton / ATLAS Collaboration 
A measurement of the cross section of top quark pair production in proton-proton collisions recorded with the ATLAS detector at the LHC at a centre-of-mass energy of 7 TeV is reported. The data sample used corresponds to an integrated luminosity of 2.05 fb$^{-1}$. [...] 
arXiv:1205.2067; CERN-PH-EP-2012-102.- Geneva : CERN, 2012 - 22 p. \- Published in : Phys. Lett. B 717 (2012) 89-108 Elsevier Open Access article: PDF; External links: Previous draft version; Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7141-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7141_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:54:44">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1390844?ln=en</link><title>Biological Computation as the Revolution of Complex Engineered Systems</title><description>Biological Computation as the Revolution of Complex Engineered Systems / Gómez-Cruz, Nelson Alfonso ; Maldonado, Carlos Eduardo 
Provided that there is no theoretical frame for complex engineered systems (CES) as yet, this paper claims that bio-inspired engineering can help provide such a frame. Within CES bio-inspired systems play a key role. [...] 
arXiv:1110.3316.- 2011 External link: Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7141-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7141_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:55:53">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1380893?ln=en</link><title>Measurement of the cross section for the production of a W boson in association with b-jets in pp collisions at $\sqrt{s}$ = 7 TeV with the ATLAS detector</title><description>Measurement of the cross section for the production of a W boson in association with b-jets in pp collisions at $\sqrt{s}$ = 7 TeV with the ATLAS detector / ATLAS Collaboration 
A measurement is presented of the cross section for the production of a W boson with one or two jets, of which at least one must be a b-jet, in pp collisions at sqrt(s)=7 TeV. Production via top decay is not included in the signal definition. [...] 
arXiv:1109.1470; CERN-PH-EP-2011-132.- Geneva : CERN, 2012 - 24 p. \- Published in : Phys. Lett. B 707 (2012) 418-437 Elsevier Open Access article: PDF; External links: Previous draft version; Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7141-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7141_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:57:20">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1172915?ln=en</link><title>Black-hole masses of distant quasars</title><description>Black-hole masses of distant quasars / Vestergaard, M (Steward Observatory, University of Arizona, current address: Tufts University) 
A brief overview of the methods commonly used to determine or estimate the black hole mass in quiescent or active galaxies is presented and it is argued that the use of mass-scaling relations is both a reliable and the preferred method to apply to large samples of distant quasars. [...] 
arXiv:0904.2615. \- 2009\. 
Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7141-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7141_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:58:22">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1081414?ln=en</link><title>Modelling the dynamical evolution of the Bootes dwarf spheroidal galaxy</title><description>Modelling the dynamical evolution of the Bootes dwarf spheroidal galaxy / Fellhauer, M (Institute of Astronomy, University of Cambridge, UK;) ; Wilkinson, M I (Dept. of Physics and Astronomy, University of Leicester, UK;) ; Evans, N W (Institute of Astronomy, University of Cambridge, UK;) ; Belokurov, V (Institute of Astronomy, University of Cambridge, UK;) ; Irwin, M J (Institute of Astronomy, University of Cambridge, UK;) ; Gilmore, G (Institute of Astronomy, University of Cambridge, UK;) ; Zucker, D B (Institute of Astronomy, University of Cambridge, UK;) ; Kleyna, J T (Institute for Astronomy, Honolulu, Hawaii, USA) 
We investigate a wide range of possible evolutionary histories for the recently discovered Bootes dwarf spheroidal galaxy, a Milky Way satellite. [...] 
arXiv:0801.2657. \- 2008\. - 10 p. 
Full text</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7141-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7141_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:59:29">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1023752?ln=en</link><title>The stellar initial mass function of metal-rich populations</title><description>The stellar initial mass function of metal-rich populations / Kroupa, P 
Does the IMF vary? Is it significantly different in metal-rich environments than in metal-poor ones? Theoretical work predicts this to be the case. [...] 
astro-ph/0703282. \- 2007\. - 17 p. 
Access to fulltext document \- Access to fulltext document</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7141-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7141_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:00:49">http://cds.cern.ch/record/940193?ln=en</link><title>Unmanaged Internet Protocol: Taming the Edge Network Management Crisis</title><description>Unmanaged Internet Protocol: Taming the Edge Network Management Crisis / Ford, B 
Though appropriate for core Internet infrastructure, the Internet Protocol is unsuited to routing within and between emerging ad-hoc edge networks due to its dependence on hierarchical, administratively assigned addresses. [...] 
cs.NI/0603075. \- 2006\. - 7 p. 
Access to fulltext document</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7141-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7141_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:01:58">http://cds.cern.ch/record/815528?ln=en</link><title>Gluon Distributions and Fits using Dipole Cross-Sections</title><description>Gluon Distributions and Fits using Dipole Cross-Sections / Thorne, R S 
I investigate the relationship between the gluon distribution obtained using a dipole model fit to low-x data on F_2(x,Q^2) and standard gluons obtained from global fits with the collinear factorization theorem at fixed order. I stress the necessity to do fits of this type carefully, and in particular to include the contribution from heavy flavours to the inclusive structure function. [...] 
hep-ph/0501124; CAVENDISH-HEP-2005-01.- Cambridge : Cavendish Lab. High Energy Phys. Group, 2005 - 24 p. \- Published in : Phys. Rev. D 71 (2005) 054024 
\- Published in : AIP Conf. Proc.: 792 (2005) , pp. 324-327 Access to fulltext document: PDF; External links: hep-ph/0501124 PDF; Published version from AIP 
In : 13th International Workshop on Deep Inelastic Scattering, Madison, WI, USA, 27 Apr - 1 May 2005, pp.324-327</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>