<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7147">breast cancer review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:10:58" name="CERN Documents" id="FW14-e003"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e003-7147-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7147_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:11:00">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1693422?ln=en</link><title>Advances in medical diagnostic technology</title><description>Advances in medical diagnostic technology / Lai, Khin Wee 
This book provides the most recent findings and knowledge in advanced diagnostics technology, covering a wide spectrum including brain activity analysis, breast and lung cancer detection, echocardiography, computer aided skeletal assessment to mitochondrial biology imaging at the cellular level [...] 
Singapore : Springer, 2014.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7147-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7147_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:12:00">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1633681?ln=en</link><title>Machine learning with R</title><description>Machine learning with R / Lantz, Brett 
Written as a tutorial to explore and understand the power of R for machine learning [...] 
Birmingham : Packt Publ., 2013. - 396 p.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7147-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7147_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:13:07">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1626900?ln=en</link><title></title><description>International Conference on Frontiers of Intelligent Computing : Theory and Applications \- FICTA 2013   14 - 16 Nov 2013  \- Bhubaneswar, India  / Satapathy, Suresh (ed.); Udgata, Siba (ed.); Biswal, Bhabendra (ed.) 
This volume contains the papers presented at the Second International Conference on Frontiers in Intelligent Computing: Theory and Applications (FICTA-2013) held during 14-16 November 2013 organized by Bhubaneswar Engineering College (BEC), Bhubaneswar, Odisha, India. It contains 63 papers focusing on application of intelligent techniques which includes evolutionary computation techniques like genetic algorithm, particle swarm optimization techniques, teaching-learning based optimization etc  for various engineering applications such as data mining, Fuzzy systems, Machine Intelligence and ANN, Web technologies and Multimedia applications and Intelligent computing and Networking etc.. 
Cham : Springer, 2014 
e-proceedings</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7147-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7147_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:14:07">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1601320?ln=en</link><title>Nuclear medicine board review : questions and answers for self-assessment</title><description>Nuclear medicine board review : questions and answers for self-assessment . \- 3rd ed. / Goldfarb, C 
Complete with more than 2,000 questions and answers, the third edition of Nuclear Medicine Board Review: Questions and Answers for Self-Assessment fully prepares readers for certification or re-certification exams administered by the American Board of Radiology, the American Board of Nuclear Medicine, the Certification Board of Nuclear Cardiology, and the Nuclear Medicine Technology Certification Board [...] 
New York, NY : Thieme, 2011. - 221 p.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7147-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7147_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:15:03">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1513969?ln=en</link><title>Test Sensitivity in the Computer-Aided Detection of Breast Cancer from Clinical Mammographic Screening: a Meta-analysis</title><description>Test Sensitivity in the Computer-Aided Detection of Breast Cancer from Clinical Mammographic Screening: a Meta-analysis / Levman, Jacob 
Objectives: To assess evaluative methodologies for comparative measurements of test sensitivity in clinical mammographic screening trials of computer-aided detection (CAD) technologies. [...] 
arXiv:1302.1382. \- 2013\. 
Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7147-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7147_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:16:04">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1501664?ln=en</link><title>Sodium Magnetic Resonance Imaging: Biomedical Applications</title><description>Sodium Magnetic Resonance Imaging: Biomedical Applications / Madelin, Guillaume 
In this article, we present an up-to-date overview of the potential biomedical applications of sodium MRI in vivo. [...] 
arXiv:1212.4400. \- 2012\. 
Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7147-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7147_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:17:14">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1488773?ln=en</link><title>Optimization and Data Analysis in Biomedical Informatics</title><description>Optimization and Data Analysis in Biomedical Informatics / Pardalos, Panos M 
This volume covers some of the topics that are related to the rapidly growing field of biomedical informatics [...] 
Dordrecht : Springer, 2012. - 199 p. (Fields Institute Communications ; 63) 
ebook</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7147-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7147_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:18:26">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1486524?ln=en</link><title>Modeling and Analysis of Shape with Applications in Computer-aided Diagnosis of Breast Cancer</title><description>Modeling and Analysis of Shape with Applications in Computer-aided Diagnosis of Breast Cancer / Guliato, Denise 
Malignant tumors due to breast cancer and masses due to benign disease appear in mammograms with different shape characteristics: the former usually have rough, spiculated, or microlobulated contours, whereas the latter commonly have smooth, round, oval, or macrolobulated contours [...] 
San Rafael : Morgan &amp; Claypool Publishers, 2011. - 95 p. 
ebook</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7147-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7147_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:19:35">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1447611?ln=en</link><title>Using data mining techniques for diagnosis and prognosis of cancer disease</title><description>Using data mining techniques for diagnosis and prognosis of cancer disease / Kharya, Shweta 
Breast cancer is one of the leading cancers for women in developed countries including India. [...] 
arXiv:1205.1923. \- 2012\. 
Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7147-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7147_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:20:43">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1413733?ln=en</link><title>Machine Interpretation of Patterns : Image Analysis and Data Mining</title><description>Machine Interpretation of Patterns : Image Analysis and Data Mining / De, Rajat K 
This review volume provides from both theoretical and application points of views, recent developments and state-of-the-art reviews in various areas of pattern recognition, image processing, machine learning, soft computing, data mining and web intelligence [...] 
Singapore : World Scientific, 2010. - 316 p. 
ebook</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>