<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7165">vice president residence</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:53:58" name="CERN Documents" id="FW14-e003"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e003-7165-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7165_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:54:00">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1492100?ln=en</link><title>Gilles Jobin Final residency lecture - Collision between dance and physics</title><description>Gilles Jobin Final residency lecture - Collision between dance and physics / Koek, Ariane (speaker) (CERN) ; Doser, Michael (speaker) (CERN) ; Dimou, Maria (speaker) (CERN) ; Jobin, Gilles (speaker) 
CERN, the Republic and Canton of Geneva, and the City of Geneva are delighted to invite you to the final public lecture about collisions between dance and physics by the first winner of Collide@CERN Geneva, the choreographer Gilles Jobin. The event marks the end of his residency and will be held at the CERN Globe of Science and Innovation on 6th November at 1800 [...] 
2012 - Streaming video. Conferences External link: Event details In : Gilles Jobin Final residency lecture - Collision between dance and physics</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7165-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7165_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:55:06">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1201649?ln=en</link><title>Analyzing petabytes of data with Hadoop</title><description>Analyzing petabytes of data with Hadoop / Jeff Hammerbacher (speaker) (Cloudera) 
Abstract The open source Apache Hadoop project provides a powerful suite of tools for storing and analyzing petabytes of data using commodity hardware. After several years of production use inside of web companies like Yahoo! and Facebook and nearly a year of commercial support and development by Cloudera, the technology is spreading rapidly through other disciplines, from financial services and government to life sciences and high energy physics. The talk will motivate the design of Hadoop and discuss some key implementation details in depth. [...] 
2009 - Streaming video. CERN Computing Colloquium External link: Event details In : Analyzing petabytes of data with Hadoop</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>