<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7174">seal team 6</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:56:12" name="CERN Documents" id="FW14-e003"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e003-7174-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7174_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:56:22">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1635678?ln=en</link><title>TRACKER</title><description>TRACKER / Bora Akgun ; Tomas Hreus 
Pixel Tracker Maintenance of the Pixel Tracker has been ongoing since it was extracted from inside CMS and safely stored at low temperatures in Pixel laboratory at Point 5 (see previous Bulletin).    All four half cylinders of the forward Pixel detector (FPIX) have been repaired and the failures have been understood. In October, a team of technicians from Fermilab replaced a total of three panels that were not repairable in place [...] 
CMSBUL-ARTICLE-2013-040.- 2013 \- Published in : , no. 3/2013, pp. 4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7174-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7174_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:57:42">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1613990?ln=en</link><title>Handbook of wafer bonding</title><description>Handbook of wafer bonding / Ramm, Peter 
Written by an author and editor team from microsystems companies and industry-near research organizations, this handbook and reference presents dependable, first-hand information on bonding technologies.In the first part, researchers from companies and institutions around the world discuss the most reliable and reproducible technologies for the production of bonded wafers. [...] 
Hoboken, NJ : Wiley, 2011. - 430 p.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7174-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7174_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:58:49">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1561185?ln=en</link><title>TRACKER</title><description>TRACKER / M. Dinardo and G. Benelli 
Pixel Tracker At the beginning of May, the Pixel detector was successfully extracted from inside CMS. The operation lasted one and a half days each for the forward and barrel Pixel detectors [...] 
CMSBUL-ARTICLE-2013-022.- 2013 \- Published in : , no. 2/2013, pp. 4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7174-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7174_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:00:08">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1544475?ln=en</link><title>TRACKER</title><description>TRACKER / R. Yohay and E. Butz 
  Pixel Tracker Preparation of the newly built Pixel clean room in the radioprotection (RP) zone of SX5 has been proceeding at a steady clip since the beginning of 2013. The clean room is designed to provide a cold, dry, dust-free laboratory environment for storage and repairs of the CMS Pixel detector during LS1 and future LHC shutdown periods. [...] 
CMSBUL-ARTICLE-2013-004.- 2013 \- Published in : , no. 1/2013, pp. 4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7174-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7174_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:01:08">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1542491?ln=en</link><title>LS1 Report: working night and day 
Dernières nouvelles du LS1 : au travail, jour et nuit</title><description>LS1 Report: working night and day 
Dernières nouvelles du LS1 : au travail, jour et nuit / Simon Baird 
In the LHC tunnel, the first underground activities of the SMACC (Superconducting Magnet And Circuit Consolidation) project have begun. In sector 5-6, the opening of the W bellows, which form the outer shell around the circuit connections between each of the cryo-magnets, is underway. [...] 
BUL-NA-2013-077.- 2013 \- Published in : CERN Bulletin 17/2013 18/2013 Fulltext: JPG;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7174-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7174_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:02:10">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1478709?ln=en</link><title>A Siberian delivery 
Colis de Sibérie</title><description>A Siberian delivery 
Colis de Sibérie / Caroline Duc 
On Friday, 14 September, a truck transporting the parts for two new components of Linac4, the linear accelerator that will replace Linac2 in a couple of years' time, arrived at CERN from Siberia.   Preparation of the seal used to obtain a vacuum between the half-cells making up the module elements [...] 
BUL-NA-2012-297.- 2012 \- Published in : CERN Bulletin 39/2012 40/2012 Fulltext: linac4_image \- JPG; Truck_from_Siberia_image \- JPG JPG; Truck_from_Siberia_image.jpg?subformat= \- ASC; stoackage des modules au batiment 152_image \- JPG JPG; stoackage des modules au batiment 152_image.jpg?subformat= \- ASC;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7174-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7174_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:03:11">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1428082?ln=en</link><title>TRACKER</title><description>TRACKER / C. Barth 
  Strip Tracker In the end of 2011, the Silicon Strip Tracker participated in the very successful heavy-ion collision data-taking. With zero downtime attributed to the Strip Tracker, CMS could achieve the excellent efficiency of 96%. [...] 
CMSBUL-ARTICLE-2012-004.- 2012 \- Published in : , no. 1/2012, pp. 5</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7174-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7174_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:04:13">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1402025?ln=en</link><title>TECHNICAL COORDINATION</title><description>TECHNICAL COORDINATION / A. Ball and W. Zeuner 
  Operational experience 2011 CMS is approaching the end of a very successful year of operation. Proton- proton running ended in the late afternoon of 30th October with a stunning 5.73 fb–1 delivered by LHC, of which CMS recorded 5.22 fb–1. [...] 
CMSBUL-ARTICLE-2011-054.- 2011 \- Published in : , no. 3/2011, pp. 2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7174-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7174_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:05:16">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1248687?ln=en</link><title>TRACKER</title><description>TRACKER / K. Gill and G. Bolla 
Silicon strips During the first collisions the strip-Tracker operated with excellent performance and stability. The results obtained were very impressive and this exciting experience marked a fine end to another intense year [...] 
CMSBUL-ARTICLE-2010-006.- 2010 \- Published in : , no. 1/2010, pp. 6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7174-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7174_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:06:27">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1227013?ln=en</link><title>TECHNICAL COORDINATION</title><description>TECHNICAL COORDINATION / A. Ball ; W. Zeuner. 
Overview From a technical perspective, CMS has been in “beam operation” state since 6th November. The detector is fully closed with all components operational and the magnetic field is normally at the nominal 3.8T [...] 
CMSBUL-ARTICLE-2009-199.- \- Published in : , no. 3/2009, pp. 2</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>