<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7239">roundabout safety</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:24:07" name="CERN Documents" id="FW14-e003"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e003-7239-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7239_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:24:09">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1477550?ln=en</link><title>Accidents can happen to any of us, whether we are on foot, cycling or driving 
À pied, à vélo ou en auto - Tous vulnérables !</title><description>Accidents can happen to any of us, whether we are on foot, cycling or driving 
À pied, à vélo ou en auto - Tous vulnérables ! / 
Excessive speeding, STOP signs not respected, a cyclist on the wrong side of the road, a pedestrian not paying attention, someone on a mobile phone while driving - are you familiar with any of these situations? The HSE Unit would like to express its opinion in light of the road accident statistics involving personnel at CERN.   In 2011, the HSE Unit's Accident/Incident Prevention and Follow-up Service recorded 28 motoring accidents involving personnel either on the CERN site or on journeys to and from work - double the 2010 statistics! These include accidents that could have been avoided by reducing speed or not using a mobile phone while driving [...] 
BUL-AN-2012-058.- 2012 \- Published in : CERN Bulletin 37/2012 38/2012 39/2012 40/2012</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7239-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7239_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:25:21">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1325620?ln=en</link><title>Tram works (TCMC) 
Travaux du Tram (TCMC)</title><description>Tram works (TCMC) 
Travaux du Tram (TCMC) / GS Department 
In order to allow the final switchover of traffic, as part of the on-going Tram works (TCMC), please note that the traffic lights at Entrance B will be out of service from 7 to 14 February. In order to ensure traffic safety and allow CERN employees to exit the site, a temporary roundabout will be installed during this week [...] 
BUL-GI-2011-007.- 2011 \- Published in : CERN Bulletin 06/2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7239-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7239_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:26:32">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1167719?ln=en</link><title>Car park by the flag poles closed at Gate B end 
Parking des Drapeaux fermé du côté de la Porte B</title><description>Car park by the flag poles closed at Gate B end 
Parking des Drapeaux fermé du côté de la Porte B / GS Department 
In the framework of the work for the new tramline, the car park by the flag poles is being reorganised, partly with a view to improving safety for pedestrians and motorists. As a consequence, it will no longer be possible to enter and leave the car park at the Gate B end (except in the case of TPG buses, which will continue to use the same route as before). [...] 
BUL-GI-2009-033; 13/2009; 14/2009.- 2009 \- Published in : CERN Bulletin 13/2009 14/2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7239-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7239_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:27:49">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1159931?ln=en</link><title>The worksite for the tram-line reaches CERN 
Les travaux du tramway atteignent le CERN</title><description>The worksite for the tram-line reaches CERN 
Les travaux du tramway atteignent le CERN / 

The civil-engineering work for the tram-line outside CERN starts on 16 February. The zones affected by the work [...] 
BUL-NA-2009-024; 7/2009; 8/2009.- 2009 \- Published in : CERN Bulletin 7/2009 8/2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7239-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7239_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:29:08">http://cds.cern.ch/record/45833?ln=en</link><title>« I respect other road users. Do you? » 
« Je roule courtois, et vous ? »</title><description>« I respect other road users. Do you? » 
« Je roule courtois, et vous ? » 
[BUL-NA-2002-074]; [26/2002].- 
Published in CERN Bulletin 26/2002

Detailed record \- Similar records</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>