<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7326">volcanoe eruption</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:57:33" name="CERN Documents" id="FW14-e003"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e003-7326-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7326_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:57:35">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1646357?ln=en</link><title>The controversial early brightening in the first half of 20th century: a contribution from pyrheliometer measurements in Madrid (Spain)</title><description>The controversial early brightening in the first half of 20th century: a contribution from pyrheliometer measurements in Madrid (Spain) / Antón, M ; Vaquero, J M ; Aparicio, A J P 
A long-term decrease in downward surface solar radiation from the 1950s to the 1980s ("global dimming") followed by a multi-decadal increase up to the present ("brightening") have been detected in many regions worldwide. [...] 
arXiv:1402.0131. \- 2014\. - 19 p. 
Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7326-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7326_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:58:22">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1608401?ln=en</link><title>Volcanic and tectonic hazard assessment for nuclear facilities</title><description>Volcanic and tectonic hazard assessment for nuclear facilities / Connor, Charles B 
A summary of the current state-of-the-art in volcanic and tectonic hazard assessment of nuclear facilities for researchers, geologists and engineers.. 
Cambridge : Cambridge University Press, 2009. - 638 p.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7326-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7326_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:59:11">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1493288?ln=en</link><title>Bubble Dynamics and Shock Waves</title><description>Bubble Dynamics and Shock Waves / Delale, Can (ed.) 
This volume of the Shock Wave Science and Technology Reference Library is concerned with the interplay between bubble dynamics and shock waves [...] 
Berlin : Springer, 2013. (Shock Wave Science and Technology Reference Library ; 8)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7326-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7326_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:00:02">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1470889?ln=en</link><title>Electrical properties of volcanic ash samples from Eyjafjallaj\"okull and Gr\'imsv\"otn</title><description>Electrical properties of volcanic ash samples from Eyjafjallaj\"okull and Gr\'imsv\"otn / Houghton, I M (nee Piper) ; Aplin, K L ; Nicoll, K A 
Volcanic ash is known to charge electrically, producing some of the most spectacular displays of lightning in nature. [...] 
arXiv:1207.6733. \- 2012\. 
Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7326-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7326_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:00:46">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1458422?ln=en</link><title>Solid-Liquid Phase Transition As a Mechanism of Volcano Eruption</title><description>Solid-Liquid Phase Transition As a Mechanism of Volcano Eruption / Ivanchin, Alexander ; Vikulin, Alexander 
This paper considers the formation of the magma volcano chamber and its eruption due to melting of the matter within the earth crust because of heating caused by plastic deformation occurring during tectonic movement. [...] 
arXiv:1206.5992. \- 2012\. 
Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7326-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7326_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:01:41">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1367657?ln=en</link><title>Influence of Non-Newtonian rheology on magma degassing</title><description>Influence of Non-Newtonian rheology on magma degassing / Divoux, Thibaut ; Vidal, Valérie ; Ripepe, Maurizio ; Géminard, Jean-Christophe 
Many volcanoes exhibit temporal changes in their degassing process, from rapid gas puffing to lava fountaining and long-lasting quiescent passive degassing periods. This range of behaviors has been explained in terms of changes in gas flux and/or magma input rate. [...] 
arXiv:1107.2555.- 2011 - 5 p. \- Published in : Geophys. Res. Lett.: 38 (2011) , pp. L12301 External link: Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7326-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7326_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:02:40">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1359599?ln=en</link><title>The impact of the Kasatochi eruption on the Moon's illumination during the August 2008 lunar eclipse</title><description>The impact of the Kasatochi eruption on the Moon's illumination during the August 2008 lunar eclipse / Muñoz, A García (IAC) ; Pallé, E (IAC) ; Osorio, M R Zapatero (CAB, CSIC-INTA) ; Martín, E L (CAB, CSIC-INTA) 
The Moon's changeable aspect during a lunar eclipse is largely attributable to variations in the refracted unscattered sunlight absorbed by the terrestrial atmosphere that occur as the satellite crosses the Earth's shadow. [...] 
arXiv:1106.3050. \- 2011\. 
Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7326-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7326_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:03:37">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1312698?ln=en</link><title>Muons reveal the interior of volcanoes 
Des muons pour sonder les volcans</title><description>Muons reveal the interior of volcanoes 
Des muons pour sonder les volcans / Francesco Poppi 
The MU-RAY project has the very challenging aim of providing a “muon X-ray” of the Vesuvius volcano (Italy) using a detector that records the muons hitting it after traversing the rock structures of the volcano. This technique was used for the first time in 1971 by the Nobel Prize-winner Louis Alvarez, who was searching for unknown burial chambers in the Chephren pyramid [...] 
BUL-NA-2010-348.- 2010 \- Published in : CERN Bulletin 50/2010 51/2010 Fulltext: Vesuvio_image \- JPG; Asama_image \- BMP; Schema_image \- BMP;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7326-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7326_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:04:44">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1301774?ln=en</link><title>Modeling volcanic ash dispersal</title><description>Modeling volcanic ash dispersal / Macedonio, Giovanni (speaker) (Istituto Nazionale di Geofisica e Vulcanologia, Ossservatorio) 
Explosive volcanic eruptions inject into the atmosphere large amounts of volcanic material (ash, blocks and lapilli). Blocks and larger lapilli follow ballistic and non-ballistic trajectories and fall rapidly close to the volcano [...] 
2010 - Streaming video. CERN Colloquium External link: Event details In : Modeling volcanic ash dispersal</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7326-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7326_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:05:43">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1293807?ln=en</link><title>Atmosphere Extinction at the ORM on La Palma: A 20 yr Statistical Database Gathered at the Carlsberg Meridian Telescope</title><description>Atmosphere Extinction at the ORM on La Palma: A 20 yr Statistical Database Gathered at the Carlsberg Meridian Telescope / Garcia-Gil, A ; Munoz-Tunon, C ; Varela, A M 
The Observatorio del Roque de los Muchachos (ORM), in the Canary Islands (Spain), was one of the candidates to host the future European Extremely Large Telescope (E-ELT) and is the site of the Gran Telescopio Canarias (GTC), the largest optical infrared facility to date. Sky transparency is a key parameter as it defines the quality of the photometry to be acquired in the astronomical observations. [...] 
arXiv:1009.4056.- 2010 External link: Preprint</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>