<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7412">when queen elisabeth</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 18:55:38" name="CERN Documents" id="FW14-e003"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e003-7412-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7412_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 18:55:40">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1547747?ln=en</link><title>Measurement of the distributions of event-by-event flow harmonics in lead--lead collisions at $\sqrt{s_{NN}}$=2.76 TeV with the ATLAS detector at the LHC</title><description>Measurement of the distributions of event-by-event flow harmonics in lead--lead collisions at $\sqrt{s_{NN}}$=2.76 TeV with the ATLAS detector at the LHC / ATLAS Collaboration 
The distributions of event-by-event harmonic flow coefficients $v_n$ for n=2-4 are measured in $\sqrt{s_{NN}}$=2.76 TeV Pb+Pb collisions using the ATLAS detector at the LHC. The measurements are performed using charged particles with transverse momentum $p_T$ &gt; 0.5 GeV and in the pseudorapidity range |$\eta$| &lt; 2.5 in a dataset of approximately 7 $\mu b^{-1}$ recorded in 2010. [...] 
arXiv:1305.2942; CERN-PH-EP-2013-044.- Geneva : CERN, 2013 - 62 p. \- Published in : J. High Energy Phys. 11 (2013) 183 Springer Open Access article: PDF; External links: Previous draft version; Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7412-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7412_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 18:56:27">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1492197?ln=en</link><title>Searches for heavy long-lived sleptons and R-Hadrons with the ATLAS detector in pp collisions at $\sqrt{s}$ = 7 TeV</title><description>Searches for heavy long-lived sleptons and R-Hadrons with the ATLAS detector in pp collisions at $\sqrt{s}$ = 7 TeV / ATLAS Collaboration 
A search for long-lived particles is performed using a data sample of 4.7 fb-1 from proton-proton collisions at a centre-of-mass energy $\sqrt{s}$ = 7 TeV collected by the ATLAS detector at the LHC. No excess is observed above the estimated background and lower limits, at 95% confidence level, are set on the mass of the long-lived particles in different scenarios, based on their possible interactions in the inner detector, the calorimeters and the muon spectrometer. [...] 
arXiv:1211.1597; CERN-PH-EP-2012-236.- Geneva : CERN, 2013 - 33 p. \- Published in : Phys. Lett. B 720 (2013) 277-308 Elsevier Open Access article: PDF; External links: Previous draft version; Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7412-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7412_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 18:57:23">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1488925?ln=en</link><title>Search for pair production of heavy top-like quarks decaying to a high-$p_T$ W boson and a b quark in the lepton plus jets final state at $\sqrt{s}$=7 TeV with the ATLAS detector</title><description>Search for pair production of heavy top-like quarks decaying to a high-$p_T$ W boson and a b quark in the lepton plus jets final state at $\sqrt{s}$=7 TeV with the ATLAS detector / ATLAS Collaboration 
A search is presented for production of a heavy up-type quark (t') together with its antiparticle, assuming a significant branching ratio for subsequent decay into a W boson and a b quark. The search is based on 4.7 fb$^{-1}$ of pp collisions at $\sqrt{s}$=7 TeV recorded in 2011 with the ATLAS detector at the CERN Large Hadron Collider. [...] 
arXiv:1210.5468; CERN-PH-EP-2012-258.- Geneva : CERN, 2013 - 27 p. \- Published in : Phys. Lett. B 718 (2013) 1284-1302 Elsevier Open Access article: PDF; External links: Previous draft version; Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7412-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7412_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 18:58:12">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1436105?ln=en</link><title>Search for a fermiophobic Higgs boson in the diphoton decay channel with the ATLAS detector</title><description>Search for a fermiophobic Higgs boson in the diphoton decay channel with the ATLAS detector / ATLAS Collaboration 
A search for a fermiophobic Higgs boson with diphoton events produced in proton-proton collisions at a centre-of-mass energy of sqrt(s) = 7 TeV is performed using data corresponding to an integrated luminosity of 4.9 fb-1 collected by the ATLAS experiment. A specic benchmark model is considered where all the fermion couplings to the Higgs boson are set to zero and the bosonic couplings are kept at the Standard Model values. [...] 
arXiv:1205.0701; CERN-PH-EP-2012-105.- Geneva : CERN, 2012 - 21 p. \- Published in : Eur. Phys. J. C 72 (2012) 2157 Springer Open Access article: PDF; External links: Previous draft version; Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7412-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7412_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 18:58:59">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1408771?ln=en</link><title>Search for first generation scalar leptoquarks in pp collisions at $\sqrt{s}$=7 TeV with the ATLAS detector</title><description>Search for first generation scalar leptoquarks in pp collisions at $\sqrt{s}$=7 TeV with the ATLAS detector / ATLAS Collaboration 
We report a search for first generation scalar leptoquarks using 1.03 fb^-1 of proton-proton collisions data produced by the Large Hadron Collider at sqrt{s}=7 TeV and recorded by the ATLAS experiment. Leptoquarks are sought via their decay into an electron or neutrino and a quark, producing events with two oppositely charged electrons and at least two jets, or events with an electron, missing transverse momentum and at least two jets. [...] 
arXiv:1112.4828; CERN-PH-EP-2011-202.- Geneva : CERN, 2012 - 20 p. \- Published in : Phys. Lett. B 709 (2012) 158-176 
\- Published in : Phys. Lett. B 711 (2012) 442-455 (Erratum) Elsevier Open Access article: PDF; Elsevier Open Access article (Erratum): PDF; External links: Previous draft version; Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7412-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7412_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 18:59:43">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1389814?ln=en</link><title>Search for Massive Colored Scalars in Four-Jet Final States in $\sqrt{s}$=7 TeV proton-proton collisions with the ATLAS Detector</title><description>Search for Massive Colored Scalars in Four-Jet Final States in $\sqrt{s}$=7 TeV proton-proton collisions with the ATLAS Detector / ATLAS Collaboration 
A search for pair-produced scalar particles decaying to a four-jet final state is presented. The analysis is performed using an integrated luminosity of 34 pb^-1 recorded by the ATLAS detector in 2010. [...] 
arXiv:1110.2693; CERN-PH-EP-2011-154.- Geneva : CERN, 2011 - 18 p. \- Published in : Eur. Phys. J. C 71 (2011) 1828 Springer Open Access article: PDF; External links: Previous draft version; Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7412-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7412_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 19:00:36">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1347253?ln=en</link><title>Search for pair production of first or second generation leptoquarks in proton-proton collisions at $\sqrt{s}$=7 TeV using the ATLAS detector at the LHC</title><description>Search for pair production of first or second generation leptoquarks in proton-proton collisions at $\sqrt{s}$=7 TeV using the ATLAS detector at the LHC / ATLAS Collaboration 
This paper describes searches for the pair production of first or second generation scalar leptoquarks using 35/pb of proton-proton collision data recorded by the ATLAS detector at sqrt(s)=7 TeV. Leptoquarks are seached in events with two oppositely charged muons or electrons and at least two jets, and in events with one muon or electron, missing transverse momentum and at least two jets [...] 
arXiv:1104.4481; CERN-PH-EP-2011-050.- Geneva : CERN, 2011 - 26 p. \- Published in : Phys. Rev. D 83 (2011) 112006 APS Open Access article: PDF; External links: Previous draft version; Fulltext</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>