<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7447">running shoes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:32:16" name="CERN Documents" id="FW14-e003"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e003-7447-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7447_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:32:18">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1694090?ln=en</link><title>Behind the scenes of GS: Open Sesame! 
Dans les coulisses de GS : Sésame, ouvre-toi !</title><description>Behind the scenes of GS: Open Sesame! 
Dans les coulisses de GS : Sésame, ouvre-toi ! / Anaïs Schaeffer 
The section in the GS-IS Group responsible for running the CERN Stores processes hundreds of orders per day, checks the quality of each and every product and is responsible for warehousing thousands of items available in a richly-stocked catalogue.   Sprawling across several buildings (73, 128 and 129), a total surface area of 3640 m2, and providing 28,300 cubic metres of storage space, the equivalent of 330 semi-trailers, the CERN stores are a veritable treasure trove! The products on offer range from office stationery and computer hardware to fire extinguishers, cables, steel and chemicals. [...] 
BUL-NA-2014-077.- 2014 \- Published in : , no. 16/2014, pp. 12 
\- Published in : , no. 17/2014, pp. 12 Fulltext: IMG_7394_image \- JPG; IMG_7388_image \- JPG; Machine_image \- JPG; MachinesStockage_image \- JPG; IMG_7388-2_image \- JPG;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7447-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7447_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:32:35">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1614051?ln=en</link><title>Pipe drafting and design</title><description>Pipe drafting and design . \- 3rd ed. / Parisher, Roy A 
Pipe Drafting and Design, Third Edition provides step-by-step instructions to walk pipe designers, drafters, and students through the creation of piping arrangement and isometric drawings [...] 
Burlington, MA : Elsevier, 2011. - 475 p.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7447-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7447_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:32:54">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1608311?ln=en</link><title>Pipe drafting and design</title><description>Pipe drafting and design . \- 2nd ed. / Parisher, Roy A 
Pipe designers and drafters provide thousands of piping drawings used in the layout of industrial and other facilities [...] 
Burlington, MA : Elsevier, 2001. - 325 p.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7447-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7447_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:33:16">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1416960?ln=en</link><title>The Art of Readable Code</title><description>The Art of Readable Code / Boswell, Dustin 
As programmers, we've all seen source code that's so ugly and buggy it makes our brain ache [...] 
Sebastopol : O'Reilly Media, 2011. - 204 p.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7447-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7447_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:33:42">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1379213?ln=en</link><title>CERN firefighters win medals in New York 
Les pompiers du CERN médaillés à New York</title><description>CERN firefighters win medals in New York 
Les pompiers du CERN médaillés à New York / Joannah Caborn Wengler 
This year CERN's firefighters have taken part for the first time in the World Police and Fire Games,held in New York at the end of August. After an intensive training programme and some glorious achievements, the members of the CERN Fire Brigade taking part in the event enthusiastically share their experience with us. [...] 
BUL-NA-2011-226.- 2011 \- Published in : CERN Bulletin 37/2011 38/2011 Fulltext: Pompiers1_image \- JPG; Pompiers2_image \- JPG;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7447-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7447_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:33:59">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1311852?ln=en</link><title>TECHNICAL COORDINATION</title><description>TECHNICAL COORDINATION / A. Ball ; W. Zeuner 
Operational Experience At the end of the first full-year running period of LHC, CMS is established as a reliable, robust and mature experiment. In particular common systems and infrastructure faults accounted for &lt;0.6 % CMS downtime during LHC pp physics [...] 
CMSBUL-ARTICLE-2010-044.- 2010 \- Published in : , no. 3/2010, pp. 2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7447-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7447_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:34:25">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1253375?ln=en</link><title>The front line guide to creating a winning management style</title><description>The front line guide to creating a winning management style / Sears, Woodrow H 
Amherst : HRD Press, 2007. - 128 p. 
ebook</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7447-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7447_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:34:44">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1095905?ln=en</link><title>Open Days – The final countdown 
Portes ouvertes le compte à rebours est lancé</title><description>Open Days – The final countdown 
Portes ouvertes le compte à rebours est lancé / 
In only a few days CERN will open its doors to everyone! Thousands of volunteers are working very hard so that your visit will be both mind-boggling and fun. Where is the coldest place in the Universe? How can you move 30 tonne magnets with sub-millimetre precision? Why do you need huge detectors to look at the infinitely small? There’s only one way to find the answers: Come to CERN! 
In only a few days CERN will open its doors to everyone! Thousands of volunteers are working very hard so that your visit will be both mind-boggling and fun [...] 
BUL-NA-2008-039; 14/2008; 15/2008.- 2008 \- Published in : CERN Bulletin 14/2008 15/2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7447-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7447_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:34:46">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1062432?ln=en</link><title>Particle physics and the anthropology of right and left</title><description>Particle physics and the anthropology of right and left- We have all looked at ants at some point and wondered where they go about with so much dash and drive. Likewise I ask what drives so many competent and specialized people in this gigantic collaborative enterprise on the LHC at CERN [...] [ATL-ENEWS-2007-060]-

Detailed record \- Similar records</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7447-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7447_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:37:03">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1038086?ln=en</link><title>ATLAS people can run!</title><description>ATLAS people can run!- It must be all the training we are getting every day, running around trying to get everything ready for the start of the LHC next year. This year, the ATLAS runners were in fine form and came in force [...] [ATL-ENEWS-2007-028]-

Detailed record \- Similar records</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>