<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7504">leiden schools</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:13:33" name="CERN Documents" id="FW14-e003"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e003-7504-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7504_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:13:37">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1666302?ln=en</link><title>Complex organic molecules in protoplanetary disks</title><description>Complex organic molecules in protoplanetary disks / Walsh, Catherine (Leiden Observatory, The Netherlands ; School of Mathematics and Physics, Queen's University Belfast, UK) ; Millar, T J (School of Mathematics and Physics, Queen's University Belfast, UK) ; Nomura, Hideko (Department of Earth and Planetary Sciences, Tokyo Institute of Technology, Japan) ; Herbst, Eric (Departments of Chemistry, Astronomy, and Physics, University of Virginia, USA) ; Weaver, Susanna L Widicus (Department of Chemistry, Emory University, USA) ; Aikawa, Yuri (Department of Earth and Planetary Sciences, Kobe University, Japan) ; Laas, Jake C (Department of Chemistry, Emory University, USA) ; Vasyunin, Anton I (Department of Chemistry, University of Virginia, USA) 
(Abridged) Protoplanetary disks are vital objects in star and planet formation, possessing all the material which may form a planetary system orbiting the new star. We investigate the synthesis of complex organic molecules (COMs) in disks to constrain the achievable chemical complexity and predict species and transitions which may be observable with ALMA. [...] 
arXiv:1403.0390.- 2014 - 34 p. \- Published in : Walsh et al. 2014, A&amp;A, 536, A33 (available here: http://www.aanda.org/articles/aa/abs/2014/03/aa22446-13/aa22446-13.html) External link: Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7504-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7504_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:14:39">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1648341?ln=en</link><title>Physical and chemical structure of planet-forming disks probed by millimeter observations and modeling</title><description>Physical and chemical structure of planet-forming disks probed by millimeter observations and modeling / Dutrey, Anne (- Laboratoire d'Astrophysique de Bordeaux, CNRS, University of Bordeaux, France) ; Semenov, Dmitry (- Max-Planck-Institut für Astronomie, Königstuhl, Heidelberg, Germany) ; Chapillon, Edwige (- Institute of Astronomy and Astrophysics, Academia Sinica, Taiwan, Republic of China) ; Gorti, Uma (- SETI Institute, 189 Bernardo Ave, Mountain View USA - NASA Ames Research Center, USA) ; Guilloteau, Stéphane (- Laboratoire d'Astrophysique de Bordeaux, CNRS, University of Bordeaux, France) ; Hersant, Franck (- Laboratoire d'Astrophysique de Bordeaux, CNRS, University of Bordeaux, France) ; Hogerheijde, Michiel (- Leiden Observatory, Leiden University, The Netherlands) ; Hughes, Meredith (- Wesleyan University, Department of Astronomy, Van Vleck Observatory, USA) ; Meeus, Gwendolyn (- UAM, Dpto. Fisica Teurica, Mud.15, Fac. de Ciencias, Madrid, Spain) ; Nomura, Hideko (- Department of Astronomy, Graduate School of Science, Kyoto University, Japan) et al. 
Protoplanetary disks composed of dust and gas are ubiquitous around young stars and are commonly recognized as nurseries of planetary systems. [...] 
arXiv:1402.3503. \- 2014\. - 24 p. 
Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7504-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7504_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:17:51">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1559410?ln=en</link><title></title><description>EVOLVE : International Conference \- A Bridge between Probability, Set Oriented Numerics, and Evolutionary Computation IV   10 - 13 Jul 2013  \- Leiden, Netherlands  / Emmerich, Michael (ed.); Deutz, Andre (ed.); Schuetze, Oliver (ed.); Bäck, Thomas (ed.); Tantar, Emilia (ed.); Tantar, Alexandru-Adrian (ed.); Moral, Pierre (ed.); Legrand, Pierrick (ed.); Bouvry, Pascal (ed.); Coello, Carlos (ed.) 
Numerical and computational methods are nowadays used in a wide range of contexts in complex systems research, biology, physics, and engineering.  Over the last decades different methodological schools have emerged with emphasis on different aspects of computation, such as nature-inspired algorithms, set oriented numerics, probabilistic systems and Monte Carlo methods. Due to the use of different terminologies and emphasis on different aspects of algorithmic performance there is a strong need for a more integrated view and opportunities for cross-fertilization across particular disciplines. [...] 
Heidelberg : Springer, 2013 
e-proceedings</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7504-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7504_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:20:46">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1530190?ln=en</link><title>Molecular line emission from a protoplanetary disk irradiated externally by a nearby massive star</title><description>Molecular line emission from a protoplanetary disk irradiated externally by a nearby massive star / Walsh, Catherine (Astrophysics Research Centre, School of Mathematics and Physics, Queen's University Belfast, UK ; Leiden Observatory, Leiden University, The Netherlands) ; Millar, T J (Astrophysics Research Centre, School of Mathematics and Physics, Queen's University Belfast, UK) ; Nomura, Hideko (Department of Astronomy, Graduate School of Science, Kyoto University, Japan) 
Star formation often occurs within or nearby stellar clusters. Irradiation by nearby massive stars can photoevaporate protoplanetary disks around young stars (so-called proplyds) which raises questions regarding the ability of planet formation to take place in these environments. [...] 
arXiv:1303.4903.- 2013 \- Published in : Walsh, Millar, &amp; Nomura 2013, ApJL, 766, L23 External link: Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7504-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7504_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:22:39">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1516597?ln=en</link><title>LOFAR detections of low-frequency radio recombination lines towards Cassiopeia A</title><description>LOFAR detections of low-frequency radio recombination lines towards Cassiopeia A / Asgekar, Ashish (ASTRON, The Netherlands) ; Oonk, J B R (ASTRON, The Netherlands) ; Yatawatta, S (ASTRON, The Netherlands ; Kapteyn Astronomical Institute, Groningen) ; van Weeren, R J (Leiden Observatory, The Netherlands ; ASTRON, The Netherlands ; Harvard-Smithsonian CfA, Cambridge, USA) ; McKean, J P (ASTRON, The Netherlands) ; White, G (STFC Rutherford Appleton Laboratory, UK ; Department of Physics &amp; Astronomy, The Open University, UK) ; Jackson, N (Jodrell Bank Center for Astrophysics, UK) ; Anderson, J (MPIfR, Bonn) ; Avruch, I M (SRON Netherlands Insitute for Space Research ; Kapteyn Astronomical Institute, Groningen ; ASTRON, The Netherlands) ; Batejat, F (Onsala Space Observatory, Chalmers University of Technology, Sweden) et al. 
Cassiopeia A was observed using the Low-Band Antennas of the LOw Frequency ARray (LOFAR) with high spectral resolution. [...] 
arXiv:1302.3128. \- 2013\. 
Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7504-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7504_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:25:00">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1458097?ln=en</link><title>Strategic Plan for Astronomy in the Netherlands 2011-2020</title><description>Strategic Plan for Astronomy in the Netherlands 2011-2020 / Groot, P J ; Kuijken, K ; Stark, R 
Strategic Plan for Astronomy in the Netherlands 2011 - 2020, written by the Netherlands Committee for Astronomy (NCA), on behalf of the excellence research school in astronomy NOVA, (combining the university astronomy institutes of the universities of Amsterdam, Groningen, Leiden and Nijmegen), the NWO division of Physical Sciences, the Netherlands Institute for Radio Astronomy ASTRON and the Netherlands Institute for Space Research SRON. [...] 
arXiv:1206.5497. \- 2012\. 
Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7504-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7504_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:27:53">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1457700?ln=en</link><title>The First ALMA view of IRAS 16293-2422: Direct detection of infall onto source B and high-resolution kinematics of source A</title><description>The First ALMA view of IRAS 16293-2422: Direct detection of infall onto source B and high-resolution kinematics of source A / Pineda, Jaime E (European Southern Observatory ; UK ARC Node, Jodrell Bank Centre for Astrophysics, School of Physics and Astronomy, University of Manchester, Manchester, UK) ; Maury, Anaëlle J (European Southern Observatory) ; Fuller, Gary A (UK ARC Node, Jodrell Bank Centre for Astrophysics, School of Physics and Astronomy, University of Manchester, Manchester, UK) ; Testi, Leonardo (European Southern Observatory ; INAF-Osservatorio Astrofisico di Arcetri, Firenze, Italy) ; García-Appadoo, Diego (European Southern Observatory, Vitacura, Santiago, Chile ; Joint ALMA Observatory, Vitacura, Santiago, Chile) ; Peck, Alison B (Joint ALMA Observatory, Vitacura, Santiago, Chile ; North American ALMA Science Center, National Radio Astronomy Observatory, Charlottesville, VA, USA) ; Villard, Eric (Joint ALMA Observatory, Vitacura, Santiago, Chile) ; Corder, Stuartt A (North American ALMA Science Center, National Radio Astronomy Observatory, Charlottesville, VA, USA) ; van Kempen, Tim A (Joint ALMA Observatory, Vitacura, Santiago, Chile ; Leiden Observatory, Leiden University, Leiden, The Netherlands) ; Turner, Jean L (Department of Physics and Astronomy, UCLA, Los Angeles, CA, USA) et al. 
Aims: In this paper, we focus on the kinematical properties of a proto-binary to study the infall and rotation of gas towards its two protostellar components. [...] 
arXiv:1206.5215. \- 2012\. 
Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7504-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7504_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:30:16">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1451985?ln=en</link><title>Beyond citations: Scholars' visibility on the social Web</title><description>Beyond citations: Scholars' visibility on the social Web / Bar-Ilan, Judit (Department of Information Science, Bar-Ilan University) ; Haustein, Stefanie (Central Library, Forschungszentrum Jülich) ; Peters, Isabella (Department of Information Science, Heinrich-Heine-University) ; Priem, Jason (School of Information and Library Science, University of North Carolina-Chapel Hill) ; Shema, Hadas (Department of Information Science, Bar-Ilan University) ; Terliesner, Jens (Department of Information Science, Heinrich-Heine-University) 
Traditionally, scholarly impact and visibility have been measured by counting publications and citations in the scholarly literature. [...] 
arXiv:1205.5611. \- 2012\. 
Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7504-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7504_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:32:32">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1427345?ln=en</link><title>Multi-line detection of O2 toward rho Oph A</title><description>Multi-line detection of O2 toward rho Oph A / Liseau, R (Chalmers University of Technology, Sweden) ; Goldsmith, P F (Jet Propulsion Laboratory, USA) ; Larsson, B (Department of Astronomy, Stockholm University, Sweden) ; Pagani, L (LERMA &amp; UMR8112 du CNRS, France) ; Bergman, P (Onsala Space Observatory, Sweden) ; Bourlot, J Le (Observatoire de Paris, France) ; Bell, T A (Centro de Astrobiología, Madrid, Spain) ; Benz, A O (Institute of Astronomy, Zurich, Switzerland) ; Bergin, E A (Department of Astronomy, University of Michigan, USA) ; Bjerkeli, P (Chalmers University of Technology, Sweden) et al. 
Models of pure gas-phase chemistry in well-shielded regions of molecular clouds predict relatively high levels of molecular oxygen, O2, and water, H2O. [...] 
arXiv:1202.5637. \- 2012\. 
Preprint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e003-7504-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e003/7504_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:34:55">http://cds.cern.ch/record/1342159?ln=en</link><title>Centenary of the discovery of superconductivity 
La supraconductivité fête ses 100 ans</title><description>Centenary of the discovery of superconductivity 
La supraconductivité fête ses 100 ans / Anaïs Vernède 
To mark the centenary of the discovery of the phenomenon of superconductivity, MANEP and the University of Geneva are organising open days at the PhysiScope between 8 and 15 April 2011. On 13 April CERN will make a contribution to the series of events with a lecture on superconductivity followed by a demonstration of the phenomenon at the Globe   Historic graph showing the superconducting transition of mercury, measured in Leiden in 1911 by H [...] 
BUL-NA-2011-091.- 2011 \- Published in : CERN Bulletin 15/2011 16/2011 Fulltext: supraconductivit&amp;eacute_image. \- JPG; supraconductivit&amp;eacute_image.(1) \- JPG; supra_image \- JPG; supra(1)_image \- JPG;</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>