<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7468">car change radiator fluid</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:00:30" name="Yahoo Answers" id="FW14-e132"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e132-7468-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e132/7468_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:00:30">https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20120715124333AAEmyyt</link><title>Changed out radiator coolant/fluids, now the car makes a hissing noise when its turned on and running?</title><description>... my system a little didn't see much of any bubbles pop up from the radiator. My car makes a hissing noise when I start it and when its running...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e132-7468-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e132/7468_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:01:02">https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20080928170405AA3B9Ym</link><title>Changing the fluids in my car ?!?!?</title><description>...) oil since 2006. What would you recommend I do to my car ? what should be replaced or changed. Thanks Roxy</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e132-7468-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e132/7468_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:01:43">https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20110224172910AAPqZb9</link><title>Does my car need more radiator fluid.?</title><description>I put radiator fluid in after changing out a hose. Now when I have the heater on inside my car and I come to a complete stop with the car on, the heater ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e132-7468-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e132/7468_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:02:14">https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20090721065814AACSOy8</link><title>Should I use a purified water when changing my radiator fluid?</title><description>I am going to change my radiator fluid soon (the green stuff) and I was wondering if I...50/50 mix? This is my first time doing it on my own car but have seen it done multiple times</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e132-7468-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e132/7468_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:02:55">https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20110919211726AAg8FRQ</link><title>Flushing all the fluids in my car wondering what the cost will be?</title><description>I want to flush all the fuilds in my car. My car is a 1999 honda civic -brake fluid -power steering -radiator -engine coolant - i want to do tranny but i heard you have to go to honda...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e132-7468-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e132/7468_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:03:12">https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20090612212808AAdPEkQ</link><title>2005 Honda Civic Transmission and Radiator Fluid Change?</title><description>... told I needed Transmission Fluid and Radiator Fluid change.. How much would both of the cost ? and if I had to pick one...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e132-7468-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e132/7468_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:03:38">https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20120806112150AA7o8Pt</link><title>How do I know when to change transmission fluid for my 1992 Ford Escort GT?</title><description>...color. I notice when I shift the car from maybe drive, to reverse, the car shakes a bit. I know some people say to not change the fluid of a tranny, but to just add it. Should I get the fluid ch...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e132-7468-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e132/7468_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:04:01">https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20120829095219AA2TGpD</link><title>Which of these car repairs should i do first?</title><description>Upper radiator hose blowed. Needs to be replaced. Trasmission oil dark...day will not getting this done for 3 more months mess up my car?</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e132-7468-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e132/7468_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:04:33">https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20130716080148AA3jOVR</link><title>How to prep a car for a long drive.?</title><description>...again a couple days later. I recently had my radiator fluids flushed and refilled and plan on taking the trip at night when it's cooler out. The car runs pretty good. Any problems I might ex...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e132-7468-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e132/7468_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:05:06">https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20070425145559AAlg2Qc</link><title>Changing radiator fluid in a 1997 Ford Escort LX?</title><description>Hi, I have all of the stuff to change my fluid but I don't know how to get to the underneath part to drain my old fluid...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>