<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7003">Male circumcision</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:41:47" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7003-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7003_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:41:47">http://www.howstuffworks.com/circumcision.htm</link><title>How Circumcision Works</title><description>Circumcision is a common medical practice in many places, but where did the tradition of circumcision even come from? Should we rethink circumcisions?.. not all) Jews and Muslims circumcise their male children. Throughout Africa, some tribes uniformly circumcise and others uniformly do not. If you were born...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7003_01_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/circumcision-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7003-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7003_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:43:25">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/infectious/circum-aids-female.htm</link><title>Does male circumcision up the risk of male-to-female HIV transmission?</title><description>The giddiness over studies showing that circumcision reduces a man's risk of contracting AIDS from an infected woman has died down a bit in the wake.. that measured the effect of male circumcision on HIV transmission from female to male. The findings were incredible and consistent: Circumcision appeared...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7003_02_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/circum-aids-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7003-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7003_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:44:55">http://www.howstuffworks.com/circumcision.htm</link><title>How Circumcision Works: Lots More Information</title><description>For more circumcision information and other health issues, try this page... Does male circumcision up the risk of male-to-female HIV transmission? The Newborn After Delivery Are we on the brink of an AIDS vaccine? 10 Instances...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7003-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7003_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:46:41">http://www.howstuffworks.com/sexual-health/male-reproductive-system/circumcision-necessary.htm</link><title>Are circumcisions really necessary?: Lots More Information</title><description>For more information on whether circumcision is necessary and other health articles, try this page...Rel­ated Articles How Circumcision Works Why would circumcision decrease a man's risk of contracting AIDS? How AIDS Works Does male circumcision up...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7003_04_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/circumcision-necessary-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7003-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7003_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:49:04">http://www.howstuffworks.com/circumcision.htm</link><title>How Circumcision Works: Why Circumcise?</title><description>Why circumcise? There are plenty of arguments for circumcision, like the link between circumcision and HIV rates. Why circumcise? Find out...: If you're raised in a culture or religion in which the majority of males are cut, then it may seem like a natural decision to circumcise. Many times...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7003-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7003_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:51:17">http://www.howstuffworks.com/circumcision.htm</link><title>How Circumcision Works: The Case for the Uncircumcised</title><description>for himself what he wants to do with his own genitals. Female genital mutilation is banned in many nations around the world, and male circumcision should...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7003-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7003_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:53:01">http://health.howstuffworks.com/sexual-health/male-reproductive-system/circumcision-definition.htm</link><title>Circumcision</title><description>What is the definition of circumcision? Learn about the origins, risks and benefits of circumcision... birth. Not all males undergo circumcision. Today, it is done primarily for religious and cultural reasons. Another reason for circumcision is related...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7003-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7003_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:55:26">http://health.howstuffworks.com/sexual-health/male-reproductive-system/circumcision-preferences-dictionary.htm</link><title>Circumcision or Not? A Matter of Personal Preference</title><description>Circumcision benefits are based on personal preference. Learn about the reasons to reconsider your circumcision preferences... of the foreskin that covers its tip. Called a prepuce, the foreskin is removed in some males during circumcision. Over time, however, the circumcised penis loses...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7003-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7003_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:56:17">http://www.howstuffworks.com/sexual-health/male-reproductive-system/circumcision-necessary.htm</link><title>Are circumcisions really necessary?</title><description>Is circumcision necessary? Signs point to no, although there are valid reasons for circumcision. Learn why some think circumcision isn't necessary... with a kingdom on Earth. But circumcision predated this supposed event, and ancient hieroglyphs show that Egyptians circumcised their males long before Abraham...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7003-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7003_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:59:01">http://www.howstuffworks.com/circumcision.htm</link><title>How Circumcision Works: Other Issues in the Circumcision Debate</title><description>The circumcision debate has brought up issues from foreskin restoration to female genital mutilation. Dive into the circumcision debate... of the same reasons as male circumcision -- cultural norms and the belief that FGM promotes marital fidelity later in life. Several health and human...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>