<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7051">dinosaur names</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:05:29" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7051-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7051_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:05:30">http://www.howstuffworks.com/environmental/earth/geology/dinosaur-leonardo.htm</link><title>What's so special about a dinosaur named Leonardo?</title><description>What's so special about a dinosaur named Leonardo? It's a fully preserved dinosaur mummy. Learn what's so special about a dinosaur named Leonardo. ..In 2000, members of a Judith River Dinosaur Institute expedition found a fossil -- a 77-million-year-old duckbill dinosaur, more officially known...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7051_01_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/dinosaur-leonardo-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7051-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7051_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:06:42">http://www.howstuffworks.com/environmental/earth/geology/dinosaur.htm</link><title>How Dinosaurs Work: Dinosaur Facts</title><description>These dinosaur facts and characteristics explain what makes a dinosaur a dinosaur. Get dinosaur facts learn how many named species of dinosaurs exist... many types of dinosaurs inhabited the planet. There are currently about 700 named species, but this probably represents a fraction of the dinosaurs...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7051_02_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/dinosaur-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7051-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7051_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:08:06">http://www.howstuffworks.com/terms-and-associations/naming-continent.htm</link><title>How Naming the Continents Works: How Naming the Continents Works: Author's Note</title><description>The names of the continents are well known but their origins are rather hazy. Learn about the names of the continents and where they come from... the days before seven (or six or five) named continents, but it turns out it's tough to read them at just 400 pixels wide. If you do a Google search...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7051_03_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/naming-continent-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7051-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7051_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:09:32">http://www.howstuffworks.com/dinosaurs/dinosaur-discoveries.htm</link><title>Dinosaur Discoveries: Dinosaur Discoveries in 19th Century England</title><description>In England, in 1824, William Buckland described the first dinosaur - Megalosaurus. Learn more about early dinosaur discoveries in 19th c. England... dinosaur name was Megalosaurus, meaning "giant lizard." In 1824, William Buckland, a clergyman, published the first scientific dinosaur account. He...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7051_04_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/dinosaur-discoveries-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7051-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7051_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:10:54">http://www.howstuffworks.com/dinosaurs/dinosaur-discoveries.htm</link><title>Dinosaur Discoveries: Opening Asia to Paleontology</title><description>During the 20th century in Asia, dinosaur discoveries were being made over extensive lands. Learn more about dinosaur discoveries in Asia. .. to roam between these areas. These duckbilled dinosaurs, named Saurolophus, enjoy the shade and water on a warm Late Cretaceous day. Canadian Museum...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7051-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7051_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:12:16">http://www.howstuffworks.com/dinosaurs/dinosaur-evolution.htm</link><title>Dinosaur Evolution: The Linnaean System of Classification</title><description>The Linnaean system of dinosaur classification was developed in the 1750s by Carl von Linné. Learn about the history of the Linnaean system.... Since Linnaeus began using this system, over a million species have been named. Classification Chart of Dinosaurs Collection of Publications International...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7051_06_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/dinosaur-evolution-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7051-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7051_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:13:41">http://www.howstuffworks.com/dinosaurs/recent-dinosaur-discoveries.htm</link><title>Recent Dinosaur Discoveries</title><description>Dinosaur interest soared in the 1990s, mostly due to the film Jurassic Park and new dinosaur discoveries. Learn about more recent dinosaur... Since 1990, more than 100 new dinosaur genera have been described and named. Dinosaur Image Gallery Building a dinosaur for Jurassic Park. See more...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7051_07_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/recent-dinosaur-discoveries-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7051-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7051_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:15:44">http://www.howstuffworks.com/dinosaurs/dinosaur-discoveries.htm</link><title>Dinosaur Discoveries: Dinosaur Discoveries in Canada</title><description>During the 19th century in Canada, dinosaur discoveries were being made over extensive lands. Learn more about dinosaur discoveries in Canada. .., unearthed a large partial skull of a meat-eating dinosaur, which was later named Albertosaurus sarcophagus, in Alberta. Albertosaurus with a juvenile Ann...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7051-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7051_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:17:36">http://www.howstuffworks.com/dinosaurs/dinosaur-discoveries.htm</link><title>Dinosaur Discoveries: The Great American Dinosaur Rush</title><description>During the 19th century in America, dinosaur discoveries were being made over extensive lands. Learn more about dinosaur discoveries in America. ..) that Holland named Apatosaurus louisae, in honor of Carnegie's wife. That skeleton proved to be the "tip of the iceberg" of dinosaur fossils...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7051-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7051_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:19:12">http://www.howstuffworks.com/dinosaurs/dinosaur-discoveries.htm</link><title>Dinosaur Discoveries: Early Dinosaur Discoveries</title><description>Early dinosaur discoveries were made on almost every continent during the 17th and 18th centuries. Learn more about these early dinosaur discoveries... dinosaur bones and there are many in the Connecticut Valley in New England. In the early 1800s, a farm boy named Pliny Moody described birdlike tracks...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>