<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7067">used kindle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:45:46" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7067-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7067_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:45:47">http://www.howstuffworks.com/gadgets/travel/amazon-kindle.htm</link><title>How the Amazon Kindle Works</title><description>Amazon Kindle is the first e-book reader to allow users to download new books directly to the machine itself. Learn more about the Amazon Kindle... on the competition. Why would you want to use an e-book reader in the first place? One reason is that a single e-book reader can hold many titles. The $69 Kindle...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7067_01_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/amazon-kindle-100x60a.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7067-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7067_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:46:48">http://www.howstuffworks.com/gadgets/travel/amazon-kindle.htm</link><title>How the Amazon Kindle Works: The E-book Reader Display</title><description>Amazon Kindle is the first ebook reader to allow users to download new books directly to the machine itself. Learn more about the Amazon Kindle...The Kindle's form factor makes it easy to use and to carry around with you. Courtesy Amazon One complaint some people had about early e-book readers...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7067-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7067_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:47:50">http://www.howstuffworks.com/tablets/kindle-fire.htm</link><title>How the Kindle Fire Works</title><description>Amazon's Kindle Fire is more than just an e-book reader. Find out what sets the Kindle Fire apart from the rest of the tablet crowd..., the Kindle used electronic ink from a company named eInk to display text and images. Because the device only consumed power when connected to a network or when...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7067_03_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/kindle-fire-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7067-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7067_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:49:14">http://www.howstuffworks.com/gadgets/travel/amazon-kindle.htm</link><title>How the Amazon Kindle Works: Amazon's E-book Store</title><description>For more information about the Amazon Kindle and related topics, please take a look at the links on this page at HowStuffWorks... to your Amazon profile and deregister your Kindle as soon as possible. Otherwise, the thief may use your Kindle to download a library of books on your dime...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7067-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7067_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:50:46">http://www.howstuffworks.com/gadgets/travel/amazon-kindle.htm</link><title>How the Amazon Kindle Works: Inside the Amazon Kindle</title><description>Amazon Kindle is the first ebook reader to allow users to download new books directly to the machine itself. Learn more about the Amazon Kindle... of the Kindle -- with the exception of the Kindle Fire -- use a Linux-based operating system. According to hardware hacker Igor Skochinsky, it uses the Das U...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7067-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7067_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:51:57">http://www.howstuffworks.com/tablets/kindle-fire.htm</link><title>How the Kindle Fire Works: The Kindle Fire OS and Amazon's Cloud</title><description>Amazon's Kindle Fire is more than just an e-book reader. Find out what sets the Kindle Fire apart from the rest of the tablet crowd... that the Kindle Fire doesn't need to do too much work. In theory, this speeds up page-loading times. Amazon also supports the Kindle Fire through the use of cloud...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7067-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7067_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:52:53">http://www.howstuffworks.com/gadgets/travel/amazon-kindle.htm</link><title>How the Amazon Kindle Works: Amazon Kindle Layout</title><description>The Amazon Kindle layout shows its ergonomic design and a rubberized back that makes it easy to grip. Read about the Amazon Kindle layout... the base model for Amazon, uses a five-way controller and doesn't have a physical keyboard. It's the smallest Kindle yet, measuring in at 6.5 inches (17...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7067-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7067_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:53:42">http://www.howstuffworks.com/gadgets/travel/amazon-kindle.htm</link><title>How the Amazon Kindle Works: Features of the Kindle Keyboard</title><description>Amazon Kindle is the first ebook reader to allow users to download new books directly to the machine itself. Learn more about the Amazon Kindle...The Kindle Keyboard, released in 2011, looks a lot like the Kindle 2. Courtesy Amazon On either side of the Kindle Keyboard's screen you'll find two...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7067-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7067_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:54:54">http://www.howstuffworks.com/tablets/kindle-paperwhite.htm</link><title>How the Kindle Paperwhite Works: Kindle Paperwhite Specs</title><description>Amazon's Kindle Paperwhite delivers a new screen display that is supposed to cut down on eye strain. Read about this multi-layered screen technology... previous Kindles, Paperwhite uses E Ink technology, which employs microscopic black and white particles to draw text and images onto the screen...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7067_09_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/kindle-paperwhite-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7067-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7067_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:56:03">http://www.howstuffworks.com/tablets/kindle-paperwhite.htm</link><title>How the Kindle Paperwhite Works: The Front-lit Screen</title><description>Amazon's Kindle Paperwhite delivers a new screen display that is supposed to cut down on eye strain. Read about this multi-layered screen technology... are still on. The LEDs only go off when you turn the device off. This illumination allows you to use the Kindle Paperwhite in a number of settings, from...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>