<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7070">compact flash memory card</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:06:32" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7070-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7070_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:06:33">http://www.howstuffworks.com/flash-memory.htm</link><title>How Flash Memory Works: Removable Flash Memory Cards</title><description>Removable flash memory cards come in different types and provide flexible, compact storage. Learn about the types and uses of removable flash memory..SmartMedia card There are a few reasons to use flash memory instead of a hard disk: It has no moving parts, so it's noiseless. It allows faster...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7070_01_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/flash-memory-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7070-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7070_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:07:39">http://www.howstuffworks.com/flash-memory.htm</link><title>Introduction to How Flash Memory Works</title><description>Flash memory is a compact, flexible type of storage. Learn about types of flash memory, removable flash memory and uses of flash memory... examples of flash memory: Your computer's BIOS chip CompactFlash (most often found in digital cameras) SmartMedia (most often found in digital cameras...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7070-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7070_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:09:20">http://www.howstuffworks.com/flash-memory.htm</link><title>How Flash Memory Works: Lots More Information</title><description>For more information on flash memory and good prices on the top selling flash memory, check out these great links... Works More Great Links CompactFlash Association PCMCIA Home Page Kingston: The Ultimate Memory Guide Transtronics: How EPROMs Work A Brief History...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7070-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7070_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:10:50">http://www.howstuffworks.com/flash-memory.htm</link><title>How Flash Memory Works: Flash Memory Standards</title><description>Flash memory standards adhere to standards developed by the PCMIA. Learn about flash memory standards and new developments like PRAM...Media and CompactFlash, as well as PCMCIA Type I and Type II memory cards, adhere to standards developed by the Personal Computer Memory Card International...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7070-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7070_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:12:14">http://www.howstuffworks.com/computer-memory-pictures.htm</link><title>Computer Memory Pictures</title><description>The computer memory pictures at HowStuffWorks explore flash, RAM, ROM and more. Learn about the types of computer memory with computer memory..-ROM can store up to 1GB of data, equal to about 700 floppy disks and a DVD-ROM can store between 4 and 16GB. Flash memory cards are another popular...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7070_05_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/computer-memory-quiz-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7070-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7070_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:13:19">http://www.howstuffworks.com/computer-memory.htm</link><title>How Computer Memory Works: Cache and Registers</title><description>is turned off. A number of types of memory fall into this category. The most familiar is ROM, but Flash memory storage devices such as CompactFlash or Smart...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7070_06_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/computer-memory-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7070-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7070_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:14:15">http://www.howstuffworks.com/wireless-internet-card.htm</link><title>How Wireless Internet Cards Work: Wireless Internet Cards for Laptops, Desktops and PDAs</title><description>Wireless Internet cards for laptops usually come preinstalled. Learn how wireless Internet cards for laptops work and how your cell phone might help.... Wireless CompactFlash cards, like PC Cards, fit into a slot on the side or back of a PDA and enable it to communicate with the Internet. WWW.hat? Even though...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7070_07_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/wireless-internet-card-100x.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7070-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7070_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:15:25">http://www.howstuffworks.com/removable-storage.htm</link><title>How Removable Storage Works: Portable Memory</title><description>Removable memory has unchained us from our PCs -- we can now carry gigabytes of data wherever we go, in a device the size of a matchbox. Learn about...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7070_08_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/removable-storage-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7070-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7070_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:16:12">http://www.howstuffworks.com/removable-storage.htm</link><title>How Removable Storage Works: Solid-State: Cards</title><description>Removable memory has unchained us from our PCs -- we can now carry gigabytes of data wherever we go, in a device the size of a matchbox. Learn about..Flash-memory storage devices such as CompactFlash or SmartMedia cards are today's most common form of electronic nonvolatile memory. CompactFlash...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7070-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7070_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:17:04">http://www.howstuffworks.com/removable-storage.htm</link><title>How Removable Storage Works: How Small Can It Get?</title><description>Removable memory has unchained us from our PCs -- we can now carry gigabytes of data wherever we go, in a device the size of a matchbox. Learn about..Media and CompactFlash cards continue to increase in capacity while maintaining their tiny size. Other solid-state memory devices, such as Sony's Memory Stick...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>