<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7103">cystic fibrosis treatment</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:37:22" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7103-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7103_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:37:24">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/respiratory/are-there-current-reports-about-cystic-fibrosis-treatment.htm</link><title>Are there current reports about cystic fibrosis treatment?</title><description>Learn if there are current reports about cystic fibrosis treatment from this article. Visit Discovery Health to learn more about current reports..Well-founded and ongoing cystic fibrosis research means that there are always new and exciting treatments on the horizon. The plethora of current...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7103-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7103_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:38:43">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/respiratory/cystic-fibrosis-treated.htm</link><title>How is cystic fibrosis treated?</title><description>How is cystic fibrosis treated? Visit Discovery Health to learn more about the treatment of cystic fibrosis from his article..., social workers, and perhaps psychologists. Most cystic fibrosis treatment clinics are located in major hospitals. A comprehensive treatment plan early...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7103-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7103_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:39:35">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/respiratory/cystic-fibrosis-foundation.htm</link><title>Is there a cystic fibrosis foundation?</title><description>Is there a cystic fibrosis foundation? Visit Discovery Fit &amp; Health to learn if there is a cystic fibrosis foundation.... The Cystic Fibrosis Foundation has several mandates. It encourages cystic fibrosis research in terms of finding a cure and improving treatment. The foundation...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7103-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7103_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:40:36">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/respiratory/common-cystic-fibrosis.htm</link><title>How common is cystic fibrosis?</title><description>How common is cystic fibrosis? Visit Discovery Health to learn about the prevalence of cystic fibrosis from this article.... Historically, people would die from cystic fibrosis symptoms in their teens. Modern technology and research, however, has greatly improved treatment for cystic...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7103-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7103_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:41:28">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/respiratory/cystic-fibrosis-statistics.htm</link><title>What are some cystic fibrosis statistics?</title><description>What are some cystic fibrosis statistics? Please visit Discovery Fit &amp; Health to learn more about cystic fibrosis and some cystic fibrosis statistics... in the 1980s, people with cystic fibrosis had an average life expectancy of 14 years. With modern technology and treatment, however, people with this condition...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7103-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7103_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:42:44">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/respiratory/cystic-fibrosis.htm</link><title>Cystic Fibrosis: Treating Cystic Fibrosis</title><description>Cystic fibrosis impacts the lungs and the digestive tract, leading to significant nutritional deficiencies. Learn about nutrition and cystic fibrosis...There are two other exciting treatments available now for cystic fibrosis patients that may dramatically improve the condition and function...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7103-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7103_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:43:32">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/respiratory/cystic-fibrosis.htm</link><title>Cystic Fibrosis: Lots More Information</title><description>Cystic fibrosis impacts the lungs and the digestive tract, leading to significant nutritional deficiencies. Learn about nutrition and cystic fibrosis..., August 5, 2004;351(6):606-608. Glutathione: A Radical Treatment for Cystic Fibrosis Lung Disease? Day BJ, Chest, January 2005;127(1):12-14. Erythrocyte...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7103-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7103_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:44:47">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/respiratory/cystic-fibrosis.htm</link><title>Cystic Fibrosis</title><description>Cystic fibrosis impacts the lungs and the digestive tract, leading to significant nutritional deficiencies. Learn about nutrition and cystic fibrosis...Cystic fibrosis (CF) may be one of the most common genetic diseases to go unnoticed by many. It is actually quite common because nearly 1 in 31...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7103-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7103_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:45:54">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/respiratory/cystic-fibrosis.htm</link><title>Cystic Fibrosis: Goals of Nutritional Supplementation</title><description>Cystic fibrosis impacts the lungs and the digestive tract, leading to significant nutritional deficiencies. Learn about nutrition and cystic fibrosis... the cystic fibrosis will limit how many vitamins and nutrients are absorbed. Large quantities of fruits, vegetables, proteins and healthy fats are encouraged...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7103-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7103_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:46:43">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/respiratory/life-expectancy-cystic-fibrosis.htm</link><title>What is the average life expectancy for people with cystic fibrosis?</title><description>The average life expectancy for people with cystic fibrosis is adulthood. Learn more about the average life expectancy for people with cystic.. or adolescence, as treatment options were limited. In fact, as recently as the 1960s, most children with cystic fibrosis did not live past preschool age [source...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>