<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7106">active learning survey</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:01:19" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7106-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7106_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:01:20">http://health.howstuffworks.com/wellness/aging/baby-boomers/10-popular-baby-boomer-activities.htm</link><title>10 Popular Baby Boomer Activities: 9: Career Changes</title><description>Baby boomer activities range from skydiving to going to concerts. Take a look at 10 popular baby boomer activities to learn more about.. to continue working well after 65. Of the group staying in the work force, two-thirds plan to make a career change [source: Merrill Lynch]. Activities...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7106_01_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/10-baby-boomer-activities-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7106-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7106_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:02:25">http://health.howstuffworks.com/wellness/aging/baby-boomers/10-popular-baby-boomer-activities.htm</link><title>10 Popular Baby Boomer Activities: 1: Spiritual and Social Experiences</title><description>Baby boomer activities range from skydiving to going to concerts. Take a look at 10 popular baby boomer activities to learn more about..Though their approaches in life may vary, most boomers strive to participate in activities spiritually and socially meaningful. Maintaining a level...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7106-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7106_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:03:14">http://www.howstuffworks.com/green-living/9-human-activities-threaten-birds.htm</link><title>9 Human Activities That Threaten Birds and Why We Need to Effect Change Now</title><description>9 human activities that threaten birds are explained in this article. Learn about 9 human activites that threaten birds...Related Posts All species?flora or fauna?live in a delicate balance within our eco-system. This balance is often upset by the activities of one...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7106-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7106_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:03:50">http://www.howstuffworks.com/business-communications/how-online-surveys-work.htm</link><title>How Online Surveys Work: Dangers of Paid Online Surveys</title><description>The dangers of paid online surveys are numerous and serious. Learn how to protect yourself from the dangers of paid online surveys at HowStuffWorks..., it probably is. [source: About.com] The biggest danger of paid online survey sites is simply spending a lot of time on an activity that pays very little...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7106_04_thumb.gif">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/online-surveys.gif</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7106-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7106_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:04:40">http://www.howstuffworks.com/engineering/structural/earthquake-resistant-buildings.htm</link><title>How Earthquake-resistant Buildings Work: Earthquake-resistant Building Designs: U.S. Geological Survey to the Rescue</title><description>Earthquake-resistant buildings are able to withstand seismic waves. Learn how earthquake-resistant buildings work at HowStuffWorks...A sample hazard map that an engineer might use Image courtesy U.S. Geological Survey Before a major construction project begins, engineers must first...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7106_05_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/earthquake-resistant-building-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7106-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7106_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:05:26">http://www.howstuffworks.com/economics/volunteer/opportunities/volunteer-african-scientific-research.htm</link><title>How to Volunteer at the African Scientific Research Institute: Activities of the African Scientific Research Institute</title><description>The African Scientific Research Institute performs a variety of activities to help communities founded by former slaves. Read about the ASRI.. of the area and implement surveys to collect data that can be used in the planning process. Volunteers may participate in any or all of these activities...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7106_06_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/volunteer-asri-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7106-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7106_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:06:16">http://www.howstuffworks.com/green-living/good-call-mobile-phone.htm</link><title>Good Call! Using Your Mobile Phone for Green Activism</title><description>Eco-friendly book options are availabl, so green your book buying. Learn more about greening your book buying... day. Over half of the world's population has quick, easy access to cell phones and wireless technology. For example, 97% of people surveyed in Tanzania...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7106-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7106_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:07:11">http://www.howstuffworks.com/agritourism.htm</link><title>How Agritourism Works: Who are the agritourists?</title><description>Agritourists often feel nostalgic about agricultural activities. Learn who the agritourists are and why they are willing to pay money to do chores... citizens who may feel nostalgic about local farm life. And if they can trace their family tree back to agricultural activities, many even feel that they...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7106_08_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/agritourism-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7106-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7106_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:08:00">http://www.howstuffworks.com/green-living/draft-for-kids-play-is-life.htm</link><title>For Kids, Play Is Life (with video)</title><description>The Playreport releases the results from their global survey on child development and play. Learn more about play is life..., movement and being social are such natural urges. Children learn about their world through play, and as they grow their play becomes more intricate...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7106-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7106_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:09:05">http://www.howstuffworks.com/culture-traditions/tv-and-culture/advent-of-television-impact-politics.htm</link><title>How did the advent of television impact politics?: Television's Impact on Government's Roles</title><description>, and Reagan got his package through [source: Foote]. According to a survey from the 1990s, the average network newscast spent 20 percent of its time throughout...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7106_10_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/tv-politics-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>