<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7111">what is the starting salary for a recruiter</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:17:43" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7111-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7111_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:17:44">http://www.howstuffworks.com/how-to-start-group-home-business.htm</link><title>How to Start a Group Home Business</title><description>Do you know how to start a group home business? Find out how to start a group home business in this article from HowStuffWorks... want to start a group home: Choose a location. Check your city's zoning requirements [source: Home Business Center]. Try to get the neighbors on board so...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7111-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7111_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:18:37">http://www.howstuffworks.com/business-communications/sales-hiring.htm</link><title>How Building a Sales Team Works: Recruiting Your Sales Team</title><description>Recruiting your sales team can be a daunting task. Recruiting events, recruiting firms and outsourcing are some of the common methods for sales... Recruiting Firms Recruiting firms screen and place sales representatives with companies, managing the entire process from start to finish. They even offer...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7111_02_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/sales-hiring-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7111-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7111_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:19:27">http://www.howstuffworks.com/business/professional-development/highest-paying-mba-careers.htm</link><title>What are the highest paying MBA careers?: Which MBAs do recruiters want most?</title><description>Recruiters look for certain qualities in MBA graduates. Find out what recruiters want the most when looking at recent MBA grads.... Stanford University is also a good place to get started, counting Nike founder Philip Knight, Yahoo co-founder Jerry Yang, and Google founders Sergey Brin...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7111_03_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/rich-mbas1-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7111-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7111_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:20:38">http://www.howstuffworks.com/business-hiring.htm</link><title>How Hiring Works: Your hiring needs</title><description>Business hiring is an important step when starting your new business. Learn about the steps in the business hiring process and new employee hiring... of the costs. Can you afford to pay someone? Remember you'll not only have the salary to pay, you'll also have benefits and tax issues to deal with. Do you need...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7111-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7111_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:21:28">http://www.howstuffworks.com/police-academy.htm</link><title>How Police Academies Work: Life After the Police Academy</title><description>hires in 2007 [source: Associated Press]. The combination of a diverse economy, low starting salaries and the war in Iraq has negatively affected...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7111_05_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/police-academies-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7111-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7111_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:22:23">http://www.howstuffworks.com/military/army-careers/how-to-become-army-pharmacy-technician.htm</link><title>How to Become an Army Pharmacy Technician: Tips for Becoming an Army Pharmacy Technician</title><description>and time of service increases. New recruits start at around $17,611 per year, but keep in mind that the military gives you bonuses (including a signing bonus...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7111_06_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/army-pharm-tech-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7111-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7111_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:23:15">http://www.howstuffworks.com/business/professional-development/highest-paying-mba-careers.htm</link><title>What are the highest-paying MBA careers?</title><description>have typically recruited the most MBA students. According to the Graduate Management Admission Council (GMAC), salaries for MBAs vary according...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7111-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7111_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:24:03">http://www.howstuffworks.com/economics/volunteer/information/professional-volunteer.htm</link><title>Can you be a professional volunteer?: Programs for the Unspecialized Professional Volunteer</title><description>of the big ones. Started in 1960 by John F. Kennedy, the Peace Corps furthers the cause of world peace by sending volunteers to live and work in developing...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7111_08_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/professional-volunteer-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7111-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7111_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:24:52">http://www.howstuffworks.com/bomb-sniffing-dog.htm</link><title>How Bomb-sniffing Dogs Work: Sniff, Sit, Repeat</title><description>Base in Texas. Dogs usually start training when they are between 1 and 3 years old. In this window, dogs are the most playful and willing to learn, which...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7111_09_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/bomb-sniffing-dog-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7111-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7111_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:25:48">http://www.howstuffworks.com/economics/volunteer/organizations/office-of-civil-defense.htm</link><title>How the Office of Civilian Defense Worked: Organization and Leadership of the OCD</title><description>15 minutes to ready emergency shelters and extinguish all lights in the area. After 15 minutes, the "blue" warning officially started...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7111_10_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/office-civilian-defense-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>