<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7112">facebook icons</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:26:43" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7112-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7112_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:26:44">http://www.howstuffworks.com/internet/social-networking/networks/facebook.htm</link><title>How Facebook Works: Facebook Applications</title><description>Facebook applications include everything from photo applications to video applications that are available to all members. Learn about Facebook.. Facebook applications. Image courtesy Facebook's applications set it apart from other social networking sites. Facebook's first-party applications include...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7112_01_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/top-10-things-not-to-share-on-social-networks-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7112-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7112_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:27:49">http://www.howstuffworks.com/internet/social-networking/networks/facebook.htm</link><title>How Facebook Works: Third-Party Facebook Applications</title><description>Third-party Facebook applications include map features that are made from a variety of programming languages. Learn about third-party Facebook..Facebook members can choose to use third-party applications like this map feature to enhance their profiles. Image courtesy Applying Yourself...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7112-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7112_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:28:44">http://www.howstuffworks.com/internet/social-networking/information/facebook-timeline.htm</link><title>How Facebook Timeline Works: Living With Timeline</title><description>In early 2012, Facebook Timeline replaced the personal wall format that users had been accustomed to. See what Facebook Timeline is all about...Facebook's strategy for getting users on board with the Timeline layout is to pitch it as an opportunity to "tell your story." Screenshot...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7112_03_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/facebook-timeline-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7112-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7112_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:30:09">http://www.howstuffworks.com/internet/social-networking/networks/add-blog-facebook-page.htm</link><title>How do you add a blog to your Facebook page?</title><description>Use the Facebook application, Notes, to add a blog to your Facebook page. Learn how to add a blog to your Facebook page from this article...You have a number of options, including plug-ins and free or paid apps, which will let you share your blog on your Facebook page. Facebook also comes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7112-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7112_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:30:59">http://www.howstuffworks.com/internet/social-networking/information/hide-friends-on-facebook.htm</link><title>How do you hide friends on Facebook?</title><description>How do you hide friends on Facebook? Visit HowStuffWorks.com to read more about how to hide friends on Facebook...The default setting on Facebook enables everyone to see your list of friends. You can change and customize this setting in different ways. First you...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7112-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7112_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:31:56">http://www.howstuffworks.com/cell-phone-apps/facebook-mobile-app.htm</link><title>How the Facebook Mobile App Works: Facebook Mobile App Features</title><description>The Facebook mobile app lets you update your status and more on the go. Learn what you can do the Facebook mobile app...The Facebook app's home page puts links to all of the web site's features on one small, convenient screen. Rebecca van Ommen/Paper Boat Creative...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7112_06_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/facebook-mobile-app-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7112-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7112_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:33:00">http://www.howstuffworks.com/internet/tips/how-to-use-facebook.htm</link><title>How to Use Facebook: Facebook Posts and Shares</title><description>Wondering how to use Facebook? If you are new to Facebook, check out these guidelines on how to use Facebook to get started... to share content on Facebook directly from their sites. Especially on news sites, you might notice the Facebook icon (along with other icons, usually...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7112_07_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/how-to-use-facebook-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7112-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7112_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:33:50">http://www.howstuffworks.com/internet/tips/how-to-use-facebook.htm</link><title>How to Use Facebook: Create a Facebook Profile</title><description>Wondering how to use Facebook? If you are new to Facebook, check out these guidelines on how to use Facebook to get started... think is fun (click the pencil-shaped "edit profile" icon on the upper right). In this and in everything on Facebook, most people enjoy letting...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7112-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7112_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:34:46">http://www.howstuffworks.com/internet/tips/how-to-update-your-facebook-privacy-settings.htm</link><title>How to Update Your Facebook Privacy Settings: Facebook Privacy Issues</title><description>Updating your Facebook privacy settings can help you control who sees your profile and your status updates. Learn how to update your Facebook privacy..Use the lock icon when you make a status update to override your Facebook privacy settings for that single post. Stephanie Crawford for How...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7112_09_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/facebook-privacy-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7112-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7112_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:35:29">http://www.howstuffworks.com/internet/tips/how-to-cull-facebook-friends-list.htm</link><title>How to Artfully Cull Your Facebook Friends List: Tips for Managing Your Facebook Friends List</title><description>Looking to trim down your Facebook friends list or make more of your posts visible to certain people? See how to artfully cull your Facebook friend.. or any other content. You'll also find the icon when editing settings for each photo album. To other users, Facebook doesn't indicate whether certain...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7112_10_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/facebook-cull-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>