<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7137">Cat movies</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:34:45" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7137-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7137_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:34:46">http://www.howstuffworks.com/elvis-presley-movies.htm</link><title>Elvis Presley Movies: Live a Little, Love a Little</title><description>, who earns his living by working for two very distinct clients. Mike Landsdown, played by Don Porter, owns and operates Classic Cat Magazine, a girlie...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7137-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7137_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:35:51">http://www.howstuffworks.com/13-notable-movies-directed-by-ron-howard.htm</link><title>13 Notable Movies Directed by Ron Howard: 5\. Backdraft (1991)</title><description>Ron Howard has directed many blockbusters and charming comedies, from Splash to A Beautiful Mind. Read this list of Ron Howard movies... as they work and toil in the Chicago Fire Department. Kurt Russell and William Baldwin star as the brothers who play cat and mouse with a mysterious arsonist...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7137_02_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/13-notable-movies-directed-by-ron-howard-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7137-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7137_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:37:02">http://www.howstuffworks.com/culture-traditions/holidays-christmas/5-tips-survive-holidays-movie-lovers.htm</link><title>5 Ways to Survive the Holidays With Your Family: A Movie Lover's Guide: 4: Don't Let Family Members Visit With Their Pets</title><description>Who knew the keys to surviving the holidays were in your favorite movies? Read about how to survive the holidays with lessons from family movies... their slobbering pooches or long-haired, allergy-inducing cats when they visit. Besides the unavoidable disruption the interloping visitors will cause to your home...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7137_03_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/survive-holidays-with-family-movies-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7137-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7137_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:37:46">http://www.howstuffworks.com/culture-traditions/holidays-halloween/halloween-games.htm</link><title>Halloween Games: Macabre Movie</title><description>Make your Halloween party guests movie stars in your own homemade Macabre Movie. Learn more in this article. ..Haul out the video camera and film a homemade horror movie. As you already know from watching them through the years, a plot is second fiddle to cool...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7137_04_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/halloween-games-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7137-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7137_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:39:10">http://www.howstuffworks.com/pets/8-famous-felines.htm</link><title>8 Famous Felines: 5\. The Cat in The Hat</title><description>Cats can be a bit snooty, but some felines have 'purr-fected' the art of charming the boots off the public. Learn about 8 famous felines...The Cat in the Hat is a troublemaker of the most lovable sort. A creation of whimsical children's author Dr. Seuss, the cat attempts to entertain two...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7137_05_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/8-famous-felines-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7137-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7137_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:40:13">http://www.howstuffworks.com/steadicam.htm</link><title>How Steadicams Work</title><description>Some of the greatest movie scenes of all time were filmed using Steadicams. They allow moviemakers to produce moving, hand-held shots that have.. to keep it level. But in TV shows and professional movies (read: not that one you shot of your cat playing the keyboard), you see lots of long, moving hand...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7137_06_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/steadicam-a-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7137-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7137_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:41:11">http://www.howstuffworks.com/10000-bc.htm</link><title>Inside '10,000 BC': Lots More Information</title><description>Compass" Inside "Bee Movie" Inside "I Am Legend" How Saber-Tooth Cats Worked How Dinosaurs Worked How Fossils Work How Pyramids...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7137_07_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/10000-bc-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7137-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7137_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:41:54">http://www.howstuffworks.com/pets/8-famous-felines.htm</link><title>8 Famous Felines: 7\. Orangey</title><description>Cats can be a bit snooty, but some felines have 'purr-fected' the art of charming the boots off the public. Learn about 8 famous felines... Rhubarb, a movie about an eccentric millionaire who adopts a feral cat. Orangey won his first Patsy (Picture Animal Top Star of the Year) for the Rhubarb...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7137-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7137_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:42:49">http://www.howstuffworks.com/10000-bc.htm</link><title>Introduction to Inside "10,000 BC"</title><description>'10,000 BC' is a new prehistoric movie from famed director Roland Emmerich. Learn about the making of the movie '10,000 BC.' .. on location in Africa and New Zealand. Movies Image Gallery A documentary about mammoth hunters was the inspiration for Roland Emmerich's "10,000 BC...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7137-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7137_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:43:55">http://www.howstuffworks.com/kranks.htm</link><title>Creating the Kranks Neighborhood: Inside and on the Roof</title><description>Sometimes, reality just doesn't do the trick. To get the right feel for the movie "Christmas with the Kranks," filmmakers had to build a fake wintry.. house very densely decorated--a lot of kid stuff. Mrs. Scheel likes cats, so there are a lot of cat motifs in the house. Frohmeyer has an elk's head over...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7137_10_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/kranks-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>