<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7144">can headphones cause hearing loss</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:30:28" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7144-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7144_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:30:29">http://www.howstuffworks.com/gadgets/audio-music/bone-conducting-headphones.htm</link><title>How Bone-conducting Headphones Work: How Bone Conduction Works</title><description>Using bone-conducting headphones instead of ear buds may be a lot better for your ears. How do these bone-conducting headphones do their job?..-century composer Ludwig Van Beethoven, who suffered hearing loss apparently caused by thickening of the structures in his middle ear, may have been one of the first...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7144_01_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/bonephones-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7144-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7144_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:31:32">http://health.howstuffworks.com/medicine/modern-technology/7-health-problems-for-the-modern-age.htm</link><title>7 Health Problems for the Modern Age: Earbud-related Hearing Loss</title><description>While your iPod may bring you hours of enjoyment, it could also cause health problems. Read our list of seven health problems for the modern age... noise, requiring users to turn up the volume, often to 110 to 120 decibels -- loud enough to cause hearing loss after only an hour and 15 minutes...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7144_02_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/cubicle-2-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7144-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7144_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:32:26">http://health.howstuffworks.com/wellness/hygiene-tips/how-to-care-for-your-ears.htm</link><title>How to Care for Your Ears: Protecting Your Ears</title><description>Protecting your ears from injury is a simple matter of knowing what to avoid. Learn what sounds can damage your ears and the proper way to clean them... of entering college freshmen already display some hearing loss. Much of that may be due to what's come to be commonly called noise pollution. Loud noise can...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7144_03_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/how-to-care-for-your-ears-1-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7144-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7144_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:33:26">http://www.howstuffworks.com/ipod.htm</link><title>How iPods Work: iPod Accessories</title><description>that repeated exposure to this volume, especially via in-ear headphones ("ear buds") can cause "tinnitus and loss of hearing in later life...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7144_04_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/ipod-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7144-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7144_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:34:13">http://health.howstuffworks.com/human-body/systems/ear/tinnitus.htm</link><title>Tinnitus</title><description>Tinnitus analgesics, a ringing in the ears, is a common problem. Learn about the causes and treatment of tinnitus... in the body and believed to be beneficial for this type of hearing loss, is an easy addition to any treatment regimen at 250 mg daily, with food. Minerals...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7144-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7144_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:35:07">http://health.howstuffworks.com/wellness/natural-medicine/home-remedies/home-remedies-for-ringing-in-the-ears.htm</link><title>9 Home Remedies for Ringing in the Ears</title><description>Our home remedies for ringing in the ears can help people escape those sounds inside their heads... the headphones. Worse, you could end up with temporary or even permanent hearing loss. Every additional exposure to loud noise damages the tiny hair cells...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>