<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7146">why do leaves fall</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:48:33" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7146-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7146_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:48:35">http://www.howstuffworks.com/green-living/use-fall-leaves.htm</link><title>Don't Throw Leaves Away This Fall: 3 Ways to Use Them!</title><description>Use fall leaves instead of throwing them away with these great tips. Learn how to use fall leaves...Nathan Blaney/Getty Images DCL With Fall beginning, the leaves will soon be off the trees and on your lawn. Granted, I don't have a lawn these days...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7146-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7146_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:49:55">http://www.howstuffworks.com/life/botany/leaves-turn-red.htm</link><title>Why do leaves change color and turn red?: Lots More Information</title><description>To get more information on leaves turning red and related topics, follow these links. ..://scifun.chem.wisc.edu/CHEMWEEK/fallcolr/fallcolr.html "Why Do Autumn Leaves Turn Red? Soil May Dictate Fall Colors." Science Daily. Oct. 29, 2007. (Sept. 8, 2008)http...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7146_02_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/leaves-turn-red-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7146-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7146_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:50:42">http://www.howstuffworks.com/life/botany/leaves-turn-red.htm</link><title>Why do leaves change color and turn red?: Anthocyanins: Painting the Town Red</title><description>Anthocyanins are pigments that allow some trees to recover the last nutrients before winter hits. Learn how anthocyanins change leaves from green.., the leaves fall off in the tree's attempt to conserve energy. But before the leaves fall off and the tree closes up shop, it wants to pull in as much sugar...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7146-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7146_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:51:41">http://www.howstuffworks.com/green-living/garden-fall.htm</link><title>How to Get the Most Out of Your Garden This Fall</title><description>Don't come up short this harvest, plan ahead. Learn more about getting the most out of your garden this fall... do you get the most bang for your buck when it comes to gardening for fall? According to Mother Nature News, a few tips can truly improve this harvest...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7146-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7146_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:52:38">http://www.howstuffworks.com/fall-overboard.htm</link><title>What do I do if I fall overboard?: Man Overboard Rescue Procedures, Steps 1-5</title><description>thing to do if you see someone go overboard is shout "MAN OVERBOARD" as loud as you can along with a port (left) or starboard (right) location...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7146_05_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/fall-overboard-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7146-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7146_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:53:34">http://health.howstuffworks.com/wellness/oral-care/problems/decaying-tooth-falls-out.htm</link><title>What should you do if a decaying tooth falls out?</title><description>If a decaying tooth falls out, what happens next? Find out what you should do if a decaying tooth falls out... and floss just as regularly, sometimes you just get a bum tooth. Whether it's bad genes or just bad luck, what do you do if a decaying tooth finally comes out...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7146_06_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/lose-decaying-tooth-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7146-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7146_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:54:31">http://www.howstuffworks.com/family/parenting/maternity-paternity-leave/sleep-on-maternity-leave-pictures.htm</link><title>You Know You're Not Getting Enough Sleep on Maternity Leave When ...</title><description>You know you're not getting enough sleep on maternity when you recognize yourself in this gallery. See pictures of sleep on maternity leave... are coming out the wrong way, but you can't stop them before they do and have trouble communicating with the finesse you used to. Pixland/Thinkstock When you...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7146_07_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/not-getting-enough-sleep-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7146-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7146_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:55:15">http://www.howstuffworks.com/green-living/minimal-impact-enjoy-fall.htm</link><title>14 Low Impact Ways to Enjoy the Fall Season</title><description>Reduce the impact of your favorite fall activities. Learn more about 14 low impact ways to enjoy the fall season...: Break a sweat in the garden this fall. 1. Make mulch from fall leaves. You can reuse those leaves to nourish the supple blades of springtime grass. Read...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7146-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7146_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:56:33">http://health.howstuffworks.com/wellness/food-nutrition/facts/10-fall-foods.htm</link><title>10 Delicious Fall Foods at Their Peak: 1: Kale</title><description>Fall foods are often savory and delicious. See these 10 fall foods at their peak in autumn... gives kale its toughness). Here's how to do it: First remove the leaves from the stem and give them a wash and dry. Now rub them -- you can do...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7146_09_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/fall-foods-peak-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7146-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7146_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:57:44">http://www.howstuffworks.com/green-living/essential-change-carbon-fall.htm</link><title>5 Essential Changes to Make for a Low-Carbon Fall</title><description>Take steps to keep your impact low during the seasonal shift. Learn more about the five essential changes to make for a low-carbon fall...More on Staying Green in the Fall Fall is here, the time when leaves change color, weather cools, feasts are cooked...and carbon footprints rise...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>