<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7147">breast cancer review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:58:44" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7147-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7147_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:58:44">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/cancer/breast/surviving-breast-cancer.htm</link><title>Surviving Breast Cancer — What Happens Next?</title><description>Surviving breast cancer takes strength and courage. Learn more about surviving breast cancer at Discovery Health...Somewhere in the middle of breast cancer treatment, a woman might begin to ask herself: Is there life after breast cancer? What does that life look...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7147-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7147_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 07:59:51">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/cancer/breast/breast-cancer-team.htm</link><title>The Breast Cancer Team</title><description>A breast cancer team can help diagnose and treat this disease. Learn more about a breast cancer team at Discovery Health....net) Written by Madeline Roberts Vann, MPH Reviewed by Susan L. Luedke, MD St. Louis Cancer &amp; Breast Institute St. Louis University Medical Center Last...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7147-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7147_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:00:46">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/cancer/breast/talking-about-breast-cancer.htm</link><title>Talking About Breast Cancer</title><description>Talking about breast cancer can be helpful to anyone. Learn more about talking about breast cancer at Discovery Health... Reviewed by Susan L. Luedke, MD St. Louis Cancer &amp; Breast Institute St. Louis University Medical Center Last updated September 2008...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7147-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7147_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:01:36">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/cancer/breast/smoking-and-breast-cancer.htm</link><title>Smoking and Breast Cancer</title><description>Smoking and breast cancer are commonly linked to one another. Learn more about smoking and breast cancer at Discovery Health...Day News; American Cancer Society (www.cancer.org) Written by Madeline Roberts Vann, MPH Reviewed by Susan L. Luedke, MD St. Louis Cancer &amp; Breast...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7147-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7147_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:02:55">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/cancer/breast/preventing-breast-cancer.htm</link><title>Preventing Breast Cancer: Lots More Information</title><description>Preventing breast cancer hovers at the top of the list of concerns in female health. Read about measures for preventing breast cancer in women...Related Articles Surviving Breast Cancer Questions to Ask Breast Cancer Specialists Breast Cancer Myths Diagnosing and Treating Breast Cancer Sources...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7147-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7147_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:04:21">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/cancer/breast/breast-cancer-basic-overview.htm</link><title>Breast Cancer: An Overview with Basic Terms: Lots More Information</title><description>This breast cancer basic overview is loaded with helpful information. Check out this breast cancer basic overview at Discovery Health...Related Articles Breast Cancer: Everything You Need to Know Preventing Breast Cancer How to Administer Self-exams Top 10 Breast Cancer Myths Finding...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7147_06_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/how-breast-cancer-works-1-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7147-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7147_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:06:06">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/cancer/breast/diagnosing-and-treating-breast-cancer.htm</link><title>Diagnosing and Treating Breast Cancer: Lots More Information</title><description>Diagnosing and treating breast cancer can help prevent the disease from spreading. Learn more about diagnosing and treating breast cancer..Written by Madeline Roberts Vann, MPH Reviewed by Susan L. Luedke, MD St. Louis Cancer &amp; Breast Institute St. Louis University Medical Center Last updated September...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7147_07_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/diagnosing-breast-cancer-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7147-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7147_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:06:55">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/cancer/breast/signs-of-breast-cancer.htm</link><title>Signs of Breast Cancer: Lots More Information</title><description>Signs of breast cancer can be difficult to diagnose at first. Learn more about the signs of breast cancer at Discovery Health... by Madeline Roberts Vann, MPH Reviewed by Susan L. Luedke, MD St. Louis Cancer &amp; Breast Institute St. Louis University Medical Center Last updated...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7147_08_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/signs-breast-cancer-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7147-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7147_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:08:12">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/cancer/breast/choosing-a-breast-cancer-care-center.htm</link><title>How to Choose a Breast Cancer Care Center</title><description>Choosing a breast cancer care center is an important decision for your health. Find out how to choose a breast cancer care center at Discovery Health... Society (www.cancer.org) Written by Madeline Roberts Vann, MPH Reviewed by Susan L. Luedke, MD St. Louis Cancer &amp; Breast Institute St. Louis...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7147-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7147_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:09:27">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/cancer/breast/risk-factors-for-breast-cancer.htm</link><title>Risk Factors for Breast Cancer</title><description>Risk factors for breast cancer can increase due to types of lifestyles. Learn more about the risk factors for breast cancer at Discovery Health... Roberts Vann, MPH Reviewed by Susan L. Luedke, MD St. Louis Cancer &amp; Breast Institute St. Louis University Medical Center Last updated September 2008...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>