<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7166">pita recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:01:15" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7166-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7166_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:01:17">http://recipes.howstuffworks.com/fresh-ideas/easy-dinner-ideas/5-recipes-starring-your-steak-leftovers.htm</link><title>10 Recipes Starring Your Steak Leftovers: 3: Pita Pockets</title><description>Steak leftovers shouldn't go to waste in your fridge. Check out this article and get 5 recipes starring your steak leftovers...There's nothing wrong with a simple steak sandwich, but when you have such a great ingredient, show it off by packing it into a pita pocket...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7166_01_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/steak-leftovers-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7166-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7166_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:02:01">http://www.howstuffworks.com/fresh-ideas/easy-dinner-ideas/recipe-tips.htm</link><title>Recipe Tips</title><description>These recipe tips give details on adjusting quantities of ingredients to feed larger or smaller crowds. Healthy snack recipe tips are also provided...When adjusting recipe measurements, double or halve the quantities whenever possible. ©Photospin Q. How do I adjust the quantities of recipe...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7166_02_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/recipe-tips-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7166-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7166_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:02:50">http://recipes.howstuffworks.com/10-unleavened-breads.htm</link><title>More than Matzo: 10 Other Yummy Unleavened Breads: 1: Pita</title><description>Unleavened bread is one of man's first prepared foods, and it survives today in many forms. Get these 10 yummy unleavened breads recipes... be obvious. Careful, though. There are leavened and unleavened pita breads, so check the label or the recipe to know what you're getting. The secret...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7166_03_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/unleavened-breads-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7166-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7166_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:03:44">http://recipes.howstuffworks.com/thirtyone-recipes-cook-athomemay.htm</link><title>31 Recipes to Cook at Home During May: Meat and Meat Alternatives</title><description>Discover 31 Recipes to Cook at Home During May. Keep reading to learn 31 Recipes to Cook at Home During May... Organic Lamb Lamb Pita...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7166_04_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/asparagus-1-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7166-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7166_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:04:39">http://recipes.howstuffworks.com/thirtyone-recipes-cook-athomemay.htm</link><title>31 Recipes to Cook at Home During May: Week 3: May 15 - 21</title><description>Discover 31 Recipes to Cook at Home During May. Keep reading to learn 31 Recipes to Cook at Home During May...While you can still get wild leeks try this Wild Leek and Morel Quiche. If morels aren't in yet, you can used dried as I did for this recipe. I made...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7166-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7166_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:05:21">http://recipes.howstuffworks.com/fresh-ideas/low-sodium-dinners/5-easy-low-sodium-recipes-for-dinner.htm</link><title>10 Easy Low-sodium Recipes for Dinner: 4: Mallorca-style Vegetable Bake</title><description>Looking for easy low-sodium recipes for dinner? Visit TLC Cooking to see these 10 low-sodium recipes for dinner..., and they make a great side for a roasted pork loin, grilled seafood or sautéed fish. Tuck the leftovers inside a pita pocket for a hearty vegetarian sandwich....</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7166_06_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/low-sodium-recipes-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7166-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7166_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:06:10">http://recipes.howstuffworks.com/fresh-ideas/easy-dinner-ideas/5-healthy-easy-and-fun-kebob-recipes.htm</link><title>Kabobs: 5 Easy, Healthy and Fun Recipes: 5: Lamb with Tzatziki Sauce</title><description>Are you looking for healthy, easy and fun kabob recipes? Check out this article for 5 healthy, easy and fun kabob recipes... with tzatziki, a cool sauce made of yogurt, garlic, cucumber and dill. Round out the meal by serving couscous, hummus and pita bread. And if you want to make...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7166_07_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/5-easy-healthy-kabobs-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7166-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7166_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:06:56">http://www.howstuffworks.com/menus/10-easy-recipes-for-unexpected-guests.htm</link><title>10 Easy Recipes for Unexpected Guests: 7\. Bring on the Sandwiches</title><description>These 10 easy recipes for unexpected guests will save you from last-minute cooking panic. Learn 10 easy recipes for unexpected guests... meet your exacting standards. Use an unexpected bread choice, like a pita pocket, or layer on some guacamole, chopped olives, or hummus. Turkey gyros...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7166_08_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/recipes-for-unexpected-guests-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7166-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7166_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:07:47">http://recipes.howstuffworks.com/40-recipes-to-make-when-its-too-hot-to-cook.htm</link><title>40 Recipes to Make When It's Too Hot to Cook: Entertaining</title><description>Discover 40 Recipes to Make When It's Too Hot to Cook. Keep reading and learn 40 Recipes to Make When It's Too Hot to Cook...So much entertaining goes on during the summer months, and quick, easy recipes make it so much more fun for the host. Here's some general information...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7166_09_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/indoor-grilling-tips-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7166-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7166_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:08:51">http://recipes.howstuffworks.com/40-healthy-school-lunch-recipes-make-for-your-kids.htm</link><title>40 Healthy School Lunch Recipes to Make for Your Kids: For the Picky Eater</title><description>Learn 40 Healthy School Lunch Recipes to Make for Your Kids. Keep reading to learn Healthy School Lunch Recipes and discover some new, tasty treats!.. for lots of kids and you can stuff them with all sorts of things.Emeril has a recipe for egg salad in pita that sounds delicious. Lots of kids love baked...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7166_10_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/lunch-box-pictures-15-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>