<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7168">fabric glue</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:12:20" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7168-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7168_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:12:21">http://www.howstuffworks.com/home-improvement/household-hints-tips/cleaning-organizing/how-to-remove-glue-from-fabric.htm</link><title>How to Remove Glue From Fabric</title><description>How to remove glue from fabric. Visit TLC to learn more about how to remove glue from fabric..., and begins to harden [source: Elmers Glue]. We will now learn how to remove glue that is stuck to various types of fabric. Clothing Scrape off as much glue...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7168-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7168_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:13:05">http://www.howstuffworks.com/multipurpose-glues.htm</link><title>Multipurpose Glues</title><description>Multipurpose glues encompass everything from school glue to epoxy. Find out which glue to use for which home repair in this helpful article... common types of multipurpose adhesives. White glue (polyvinyl acetate, or PVA): PVA glue is a white liquid, usually sold in plastic bottles...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7168_02_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/multipurpose-glues-1-100x60-1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7168-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7168_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:14:09">http://www.howstuffworks.com/how-to-remove-glue-spots.htm</link><title>How to Remove Glue Spots: Washable Fabrics</title><description>Glue spots can stick you with a real mess. Learn stain removal tips to remove glue spots, clean glue stains, treat spots, and apply stain remover...Follow these steps to remove glue spots from washable fabrics such as Acrylic Fabric, Cotton, Linen, Modacrylic, Olefin, Polyester, Rayon, Spandex...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7168_03_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/question695-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7168-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7168_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:15:03">http://www.howstuffworks.com/how-to-remove-glue-spots.htm</link><title>How to Remove Glue Spots: Non-washable Fabrics</title><description>Glue spots can stick you with a real mess. Learn stain removal tips to remove glue spots, clean glue stains, treat spots, and apply stain remover...Follow these steps to remove glue spots from non-washable fabrics such as Acetate, Fiberglass, Rayon, Silk, Triacetate and Wool: Immediately sponge...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7168-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7168_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:16:04">http://www.howstuffworks.com/crafts/other-arts-crafts/fabric-crafts.htm</link><title>Fabric Crafts: Fancy Fabric Frame</title><description>This Fancy Fabric Frame craft transforms a boring frame into a work of art. Learn how to make this kids' fabric craft in this article... in their own customized design using this kids' art craft. What You'll Need: Wooden picture frame Paper towels and glass cleaner Printed fabric Craft glue Fancy...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7168_05_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/fabric-crafts-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7168-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7168_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:16:47">http://www.howstuffworks.com/crafts/other-arts-crafts/fabric-crafts.htm</link><title>Fabric Crafts: Sock Puppets</title><description>Sock puppets are a fun fabric craft that start with your old socks. Learn how to turn old socks into puppets with the instructions in this article... and thread Blunt scissors 2 buttons Fabric markers Felt Fabric glue Sock Puppets fabric craft How to Make Sock Puppets: Step 1: Make a dragon sock puppet. Sew...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7168-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7168_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:17:47">http://www.howstuffworks.com/crafts/other-arts-crafts/fabric-crafts.htm</link><title>Fabric Crafts: Fabric Flower Bookmark</title><description>A fabric flower bookmark is fun to make and is useful, too. Learn how to make a fabric flower bookmark for your or a friend in this article... vegetable garden as well in this art craft. What You'll Need: 2x6-inch piece of fabric Pressed flowers Craft glue Fabric markers 2x12-inch piece of iron...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7168-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7168_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:18:51">http://www.howstuffworks.com/under-the-hood/trends-innovations/glue-car-together.htm</link><title>Is it possible to assemble a car with glue?: Pros and Cons of Adhesives</title><description>You might be surprised to learn that automakers are using car glue to bond parts together on modern vehicles. Find out the advantages of using car..The Tata Nano uses automotive adhesives to attach body panels -- and to reduce weight. FABRICE COFFRINI/AFP/Getty Images Using adhesives has some...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7168_08_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/glue-car-together-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7168-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7168_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:19:36">http://www.howstuffworks.com/crafts/other-arts-crafts/fabric-crafts.htm</link><title>Fabric Crafts: Fabric Fruit</title><description>Fabric fruit is more attractive to display than the plastic variety. Learn how kids can make fabric fruit and other fabric crafts...: Red, yellow, orange, purple, and green felt or cotton cloth Ruler Blunt scissors Fabric glue Yarn Cotton batting Green construction paper Markers How...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7168-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7168_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:20:28">http://www.howstuffworks.com/home-improvement/home-diy/lighting/fabric-beaded-lampshades.htm</link><title>Fabric and Beaded Lampshades</title><description>This fabric and beaded lampshades lighting project adds a unique element to your home's decor. Learn to make a fabric and beaded lampshades at TLC.. these at a craft store) fabric (enough to cover your shade or multiple shades) scissors glue gun beads/trim (You can use the same beads as used on the bench...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7168_10_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/fabric-lamp-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>