<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7216">salmonella</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:56:10" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7216-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7216_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:56:11">http://health.howstuffworks.com/wellness/food-nutrition/facts/salmonella-scare.htm</link><title>Salmonella Scare</title><description>Salmonella scares happen when contaminated products become widely dispersed. Learn about the origins of salmonella scares...As I write this piece, America is undergoing the largest salmonella outbreak the CDC has ever tracked. To date, 810 people in 36 states have reported...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7216-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7216_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:56:57">http://health.howstuffworks.com/wellness/food-nutrition/facts/salmonella-scare.htm</link><title>Salmonella Scare: Go Local to Stop Salmonella</title><description>Salmonella scares happen when contaminated products become widely dispersed. Learn about the origins of salmonella scares....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7216-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7216_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:58:13">http://health.howstuffworks.com/wellness/food-nutrition/facts/salmonella-scare.htm</link><title>Salmonella Scare: Lots More Information</title><description>Salmonella scares happen when contaminated products become widely dispersed. Learn about the origins of salmonella scares... Poisoning Sources http://www.webmd.com/food-recipes/food-poisoning/news/20080627/salmonella-tomato-outbreak-biggest-ever http...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7216-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7216_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:59:12">http://health.howstuffworks.com/food-nutrition/salmonella-contaminated-pistachios-organic.htm</link><title>Salmonella Contaminated Pistachios were Certified Organic: Look Beyond the Label</title><description>There's more to Organic than a label—lower your risk of getting contaminated organic food. Learn more about salmonella contaminated pistachios...Paul Sakuma/AP DCL A million pounds of salmonella infected pistachios were just voluntarily recalled by the Setton Farms, one of the biggest...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7216-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7216_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:00:25">http://health.howstuffworks.com/food-nutrition/computer-program-forecasts-salmonella-in-pork.htm</link><title>Computer Program Forecasts Salmonella in Pork</title><description>Salmonella has presented a real problem to factory farms of late. From eggs to turkey and everywhere in between fears are deepening...Thinkstock DCL Salmonella has presented a real problem to factory farms of late. From eggs to turkey and everywhere in between fears are deepening...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7216-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7216_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:01:22">http://health.howstuffworks.com/food-nutrition/drug-resistant-salmonella-found-in-55000-pounds-of-turkey-burger.htm</link><title>Drug Resistant Salmonella Found in 55,000 Pounds of Turkey Burger</title><description>'s just what's happening. According to a story from CBS Los Angeles, a salmonella strain that caused the recall of nearly 55,000 pounds of frozen raw turkey...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7216-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7216_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:02:11">http://health.howstuffworks.com/food-nutrition/spots-salmonella-contaminated-pet-food-makes-humans-and-furry-friends-sick.htm</link><title>Spot's Salmonella: Contaminated Pet Food Makes Humans and Furry Friends Sick</title><description>this week's recall of 248 cases of iDoggie Wishbone pet treats because of salmonella contamination fears. Not only can your pets get sick, but you can too...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7216-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7216_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:03:04">http://health.howstuffworks.com/wellness/preventive-care/how-to-prevent-stomach-infections.htm</link><title>How to Prevent Stomach Infections: Preventing Salmonella</title><description>Learn how to avoid Salmonella bacteria, which is usually found in raw chicken and can cause a very unpleasant stomach infection, salmonellosis...Salmonellosis is caused by a number of Salmonella bacteria. According to the World Health Organization, more than 2,500 types of Salmonella bacteria...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7216-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7216_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:03:49">http://recipes.howstuffworks.com/tools-and-techniques/food-safety-tips.htm</link><title>Food Safety Tips: How to Prevent Salmonella</title><description>Salmonella can be avoided if you follow our food safety tips. Learn how to prevent salmonella here... contamination? Handle eggs with care, since they can carry salmonella. Photodisc A. Although salmonella bacteria is found on most chicken sold in this country...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7216_09_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/test-tube-meat-news-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7216-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7216_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:04:35">http://www.howstuffworks.com/science-vs-myth/everyday-myths/five-second-rule.htm</link><title>Does the five second rule really work?: Salmonella and the Five Second Rule</title><description>Does the five second rule keep you safe from salmonella? Learn how many salmonella viruses you could pick up by following the five second rule.... By applying a "salmonella soup" to tile, wood and nylon carpet, the researchers were able to not only see how long the germs lived in those...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7216_10_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/five-second-rule-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>