<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7230">council bluffs</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:33:52" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7230-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7230_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:33:53">http://geography.howstuffworks.com/united-states/geography-of-council-bluffs.htm</link><title>Geography of Council Bluffs</title><description>The geography of Council Bluffs adds greatly to the beauty and majesty of the United States. Learn more about the geography of Council Bluffs at HowStuffWorks...Council Bluffs, Iowa, the seat of Pottawattamie County. It is on the east bank of the Missouri River, opposite Omaha, Nebraska. Council Bluffs...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7230-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7230_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:34:49">http://geography.howstuffworks.com/united-states/geography-of-pine-bluff.htm</link><title>Geography of Pine Bluff</title><description>The geography of Pine Bluff adds greatly to the beauty and majesty of the United States. Learn more about the geography of Pine Bluff at HowStuffWorks... in 1832 and was incorporated in 1839. In 1863 part of the city was burned during a Civil War battle. Pine Bluff has the mayor-council form of government...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7230-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7230_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:35:31">http://www.howstuffworks.com/iowa-scenic-drive-loess-hills-scenic-byway.htm</link><title>Iowa Scenic Drives: Loess Hills Scenic Byway</title><description>to Allow: Seven hours States it runs through: Iowa Cities it runs through: Akron, Sioux City, Turin, Council Bluffs, Glenwood Considerations: Occasionally...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7230_03_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/iowa-scenic-drive-2-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7230-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7230_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:36:27">http://history.howstuffworks.com/american-history/pierre-jean-de-smet.htm</link><title>De Smet, Pierre Jean</title><description>missionary work among the Potawatomi Indians near present-day Council Bluffs, Iowa. In 1841 De Smet went to the Oregon country to begin mission work...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7230-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7230_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:37:16">http://www.howstuffworks.com/iowa-scenic-drive-loess-hills-scenic-byway.htm</link><title>Iowa Scenic Drives: Loess Hills Scenic Byway: Things to Do Along the Loess Hills Scenic Byway</title><description>in the communities along the byway. Cross the river from Council Bluffs to Omaha, Nebraska, to explore this busy city full of distractions. Or simply settle down...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7230-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7230_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:37:58">http://www.howstuffworks.com/iowa-scenic-drive-loess-hills-scenic-byway.htm</link><title>Iowa Scenic Drives: Loess Hills Scenic Byway: History of the Loess Hills Scenic Byway</title><description>to the West. ©2Byways.org This imposing white-trimmed brick mansion in Council Bluffs is a National Historic Landmark. It was built in 1869. The Oregon Trail...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7230-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7230_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:38:55">http://geography.howstuffworks.com/united-states/geography-of-omaha.htm</link><title>Geography of Omaha</title><description>Omaha, Nebraska, the largest city in the state and the seat of Douglas County. It lies on the west bank of the Missouri River, opposite Council...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7230-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7230_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:39:42">http://www.howstuffworks.com/iowa-scenic-drive-loess-hills-scenic-byway.htm</link><title>Iowa Scenic Drives: Loess Hills Scenic Byway: Highlights of the Loess Hills Scenic Byway</title><description>in Iowa. Check out all the Iowa Scenic Drives. Council Bluffs, Sioux City: Learn about these cities along the Loess Hill Scenic Byway....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7230-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7230_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:40:59">http://history.howstuffworks.com/american-history/history-of-iowa.htm</link><title>History of Iowa</title><description>railroad was completed across Iowa, from the Mississippi River to Council Bluffs.1873 Grange members opposed the practices of railroads serving farmers...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7230_09_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/history-of-iowa-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7230-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7230_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:41:45">http://geography.howstuffworks.com/united-states/geography-of-santa-monica.htm</link><title>Geography of Santa Monica</title><description>the oceanfront from high bluffs. Santa Monica's Civic Auditorium is the site of various conventions and trade shows. There is also a municipal airport. The city...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>