<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7242">hague convention</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:38:58" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7242-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7242_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:39:00">http://www.howstuffworks.com/rules-of-war.htm</link><title>How the Rules of War Work: Background</title><description>The Hague Conventions Conferences regarding the international rules of war were held in The Hague, the Netherlands, in 1899, 1907 and 1954. Dubbed...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7242_01_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/rules-of-war-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7242-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7242_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:39:47">http://www.howstuffworks.com/rules-of-war.htm</link><title>How the Rules of War Work: Cultural Property</title><description>each people makes its contribution to the culture of the world... (Hague Convention, 1954) Personal property is protected throughout the Hague...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7242-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7242_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:40:40">http://www.howstuffworks.com/rules-of-war.htm</link><title>Introduction to How the Rules of War Work</title><description>. But there are countless treaties that declare otherwise, signed by almost every nation in the world. ­The Hague laws and Geneva Conventions are some of the most widely...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7242-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7242_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:41:22">http://www.howstuffworks.com/rules-of-war.htm</link><title>How the Rules of War Work: Consequences of Violation</title><description>is adherence to the rules. So it seems that the conventions apply to the forces that follow the conventions. Both the Hague and Geneva Conventions address...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7242-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7242_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:42:15">http://www.howstuffworks.com/rules-of-war.htm</link><title>How the Rules of War Work: In the Field</title><description>the medical personnel of the opposing force until the medical crisis has passed. The Hague Conventions address not only armed conflict; the very first Hague law...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7242-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7242_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:43:09">http://www.howstuffworks.com/rules-of-war.htm</link><title>How the Rules of War Work: Prisoners of War</title><description>to captured Taliban combatants in the 2001-2002 war in Afghanistan, it was in violation of the third Geneva Convention. In the course of an armed conflict...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7242-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7242_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:44:06">http://www.howstuffworks.com/rules-of-war.htm</link><title>How the Rules of War Work: Civilians and Occupation</title><description>" to render a location protected from attack. The general purpose of the fourth Geneva Convention is to shield civilians, and children in particular, from...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7242-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7242_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:44:53">http://www.howstuffworks.com/rules-of-war.htm</link><title>How the Rules of War Work: Lots More Information</title><description>The Technology of War More Great Links The Avalon Project: Laws of War World Health Organization: International Treaties and Conventions Related to Health...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7242-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7242_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:45:43">http://www.howstuffworks.com/legal-torture.htm</link><title>When is torture legal?: The Legality of Torture</title><description>The legality of torture is negated by the Geneva Convention and the U.N. Convention Against Torture. Learn how a group of attorneys drafted..The Convention against Torture isn't the only document that forbids nations and individuals from practicing torture. In 1949, the Geneva Convention...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7242_09_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/legal-torture2-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7242-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7242_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:46:33">http://www.howstuffworks.com/family/parenting/adoption/tax-deductible-donation-for-an-international-adoption.htm</link><title>How do you give a tax-deductible donation for an international adoption?</title><description>. If you want to donate to international adoptions from countries that have signed The Hague Convention, the U.S Department of State has a list of Hague...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>