<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7303">what causes itchy feet</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:57:47" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7303-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7303_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:57:48">http://health.howstuffworks.com/skin-care/cleansing/products/cleansers-cause-itchiness.htm</link><title>Do certain cleansers cause itchiness?: Cleansers and Dry Skin</title><description>Certain cleansers cause dry skin. Learn more about cleansers and dry skin at HowStuffWorks. .. use could cause more harm than good if it dries out your skin to an uncomfortable, irritable level. Choosing the right cleanser will make all...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7303_01_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/cleansers-cause-itchiness-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7303-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7303_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:58:31">http://health.howstuffworks.com/wellness/hygiene-tips/how-to-care-for-your-feet.htm</link><title>How to Care for Your Feet: How to Buy Foot-Care Products</title><description>, and lanolin. You can also buy soaps or footbath products with ingredients that not only soften but also disinfect your feet. To treat scaly, itchy, dry skin...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7303_02_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/how-to-care-for-your-feet-100x60-1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7303-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7303_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:59:25">http://health.howstuffworks.com/skin-care/moisturizing/tips/how-to-get-rid-of-dry-skin-on-your-feet.htm</link><title>How to Get Rid of Dry Skin on Your Feet</title><description>Dry skin on your feet is a fashion faux pas, especially during sandal season. Remove dry skin on your feet with our moisturizing tips... unattractive and embarrassing, it can also be itchy, painful, and burning, too, especially in the case of conditions like athlete's foot. What causes dry skin...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7303-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7303_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:59:50">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/allergies/allergy-basics/can-anaphylaxis-cause-inflammation-in-my-joints.htm</link><title>Can anaphylaxis cause inflammation in your joints?</title><description>Visit Discovery Health to learn whether anaphylaxis can cause inflammation in your joints in this article... and itchy, red eyes. Anaphylaxis also causes the aforementioned drop in blood pressure, a change in heart rate and sometimes dizziness or loss...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7303-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7303_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:00:33">http://health.howstuffworks.com/skin-care/moisturizing/basics/how-to-smooth-out-rough-skin-on-your-face.htm</link><title>How to Smooth Out Rough Skin on Your Face</title><description>widespread problems include: Eczema: Also called dermatitis, eczema causes itchiness, redness, scaling and oozing. Flare-ups are often triggered by allergens...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7303_05_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/moisturize-face-cheap-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7303-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7303_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:01:18">http://health.howstuffworks.com/skin-care/problems/treating/identify-a-skin-rash.htm</link><title>How to Identify a Skin Rash: Skin Rash Causes</title><description>Skin rashes are caused by several different factors. Learn about skin rash causes at HowStuffWorks. .., covering large patches of skin, and are typically accompanied by fever, headache, aches, and pains. These nasty rashes can be caused by a virus, bacterial...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7303_06_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/identify-a-skin-rash-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7303-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7303_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:01:59">http://health.howstuffworks.com/wellness/preventive-care/how-to-prevent-childhood-infections.htm</link><title>How to Prevent Childhood Infections: Preventing Ringworm</title><description>Find out about ringworm, a fungal infection that causes itchy, red blotches and can be spread by infected animals and people...Despite its name, ringworm is not an infestation by a worm but a fungal infection of the skin. Different fungi cause ringworm on different parts...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7303-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7303_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:02:50">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/musculoskeletal/foot-injuries.htm</link><title>Foot Injuries: How to Treat Foot Rashes</title><description>Red, itchy feet can result from the touch of an irritating material or an overly moist environment. Learn how to treat foot rashes at HowStuffWorks... to the next section. To learn more about treating and avoiding problems with your feet, visit: Everyday Foot Problems: Discover what causes some of the most...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7303_08_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/foot-injuries-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7303-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7303_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:03:28">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/musculoskeletal/everyday-foot-problems.htm</link><title>Everyday Foot Problems: Dry Skin and Foot Pain</title><description>-skin conditions include eczema and psoriasis, both of which are rashes that are scabby and very itchy and that can show up all over the body, including on the feet...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7303_09_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/everyday-foot-problems-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7303-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7303_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:04:07">http://health.howstuffworks.com/wellness/preventive-care/how-to-prevent-traveling-infections.htm</link><title>How To Prevent Traveling Infections: Preventing Hookworms</title><description>Hookworm eggs found in animal feces hatch and form an itchy skin infection called cutaneous larva migrans, or CLM. Learn how to prevent hookworms...Hookworm eggs found in animal (usually dog or cat) feces hatch and form the larvae that cause CLM. These hookworms are not the same ones that cause...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>