<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7307">causes of the cold war</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:20:10" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7307-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7307_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:20:12">http://history.howstuffworks.com/cold-war/general-cold-war-history.htm</link><title>General Cold War History</title><description>The General Cold War History played an important part in history. Learn more about the General Cold War History at HowStuffWorks... that caused it. The Cold War ended with the collapse of the eastern European Communist regimes in the late 1980's and the breakup of the Soviet Union into 15...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7307_01_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/general-cold-war-history2-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7307-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7307_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:21:04">http://www.howstuffworks.com/history-vs-myth/who-won-cold-war.htm</link><title>Who won the Cold War?: Did the USSR die of natural causes?</title><description>The end of the Cold War came from many factors -- including Gorbachev's perestroika and glasnost. Learn about these initiatives and the end..-party communist system with a multi-party democratic system. So if the USSR died of natural causes or essentially killed itself, who deserves the title of Cold War...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7307_02_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/who-won-cold-war-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7307-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7307_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:21:55">http://www.howstuffworks.com/history-vs-myth/who-won-cold-war.htm</link><title>Who won the Cold War?: Who won the Cold War?: Author's Note</title><description>Who won the Cold War has long been debated by historians who study the Cold War and its proxy wars. Learn why who won the Cold War is a hard question..Josh Clark, Staff Writer hsw 2009 This article asked one of those seemingly easy questions: Who won the Cold War? Under "last man standing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7307-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7307_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:22:32">http://www.howstuffworks.com/the-cold-war-timeline.htm</link><title>The Cold War: October 1951-1991: The Continuing Impact of World War II</title><description>World War II was a devastating conflict, the echoes of which can still be felt today. Learn about the continuing impact of World War II... keeps alive the historical image of Adolf Hitler. Although World War II was comprised of many different wars, which between them had many causes...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7307_04_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/the-cold-war-timeline-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7307-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7307_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:23:11">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/cold-flu/wet-head-cold.htm</link><title>Will going out with wet hair really give you a cold?: Lots More Information</title><description>For more information about whether wet hair causes colds and for more health myths, see the links on this page.... Cause. http://www3.niaid.nih.gov/topics/commonCold/cause.htm O'Connor, Anahad. "The Claim: You Lose Most of Your Body Heat Through...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7307_05_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/wet-hair-cold-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7307-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7307_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:23:28">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/allergies/outdoor-allergies/pollen-allergies-cause-fever.htm</link><title>Can pollen allergies cause you to run a fever?</title><description>About 10 percent of Americans have a pollen allergy. Learn whether pollen allergies can cause you to run a fever in this article... an antibody called immunoglobulin E to neutralize the allergen. In turn, the antibody triggers a bunch of chemicals to wage the war on its behalf. You notice...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7307-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7307_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:24:19">http://health.howstuffworks.com/diseases-conditions/cold-flu/feed-a-cold.htm</link><title>Should you really feed a cold?: What is a cold, anyway?</title><description>What is a cold, exactly? Read up on the facts and find out whether it's best to feed a cold... Fielder's 2002 book "Cold Wars: The Fight Against the Common Cold," the ancient Egyptians had hieroglyphic symbols for colds and coughing...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7307_07_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/feed-a-cold-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7307-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7307_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:25:01">http://www.howstuffworks.com/biochem-war.htm</link><title>How Biological and Chemical Warfare Works: Feared Biological Agents</title><description>the Cold War [source: Britannica]. Anthrax -- A bacterium causes anthrax. It has a spore form that is very durable. If the spores or bacteria get into your...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7307_08_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/biochem-war-100x60a.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7307-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7307_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:25:39">http://www.howstuffworks.com/life/cellular-microscopic/10-flu-misconceptions.htm</link><title>10 Misconceptions About the Flu: 10: Getting the Flu Is Not That Different from a Bad Cold</title><description>vicious strain that emerged in 1918, killed between 20 and 50 million people worldwide, more than the number who died in World War I. Another strain...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7307_09_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/flu-miscon-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7307-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7307_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:26:27">http://history.howstuffworks.com/asian-history/history-of-afghanistan.htm</link><title>History of Afghanistan: After World War II</title><description>Afghanistan after World War II is a significant period in history. Learn all about Afghanistan after World War II at HowStuffWorks...The country was neutral in World War II and pursued a policy of non-alignment in the cold war. Both the United States and the Soviet Union provided...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>