<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7326">volcanoe eruption</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:35:23" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7326-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7326_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:35:25">http://www.howstuffworks.com/nature/natural-disasters/volcano.htm</link><title>How Volcanoes Work</title><description>Volcanoes are some of nature's most awe-inspiring displays, with everything from exploding mountaintops to rivers of lava. Learn how all.. the different types of volcanoes work. See more volcano pictures. Volcano Image Gallery Whenever there is a major volcanic eruption in the world, you'll­ see...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7326_01_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/volcano-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7326-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7326_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:36:11">http://www.howstuffworks.com/nature/natural-disasters/volcano.htm</link><title>How Volcanoes Work: Eruption Frequency</title><description>Eruption frequency is how scientists determine how active a given volcano is. Find out how scientists study eruption frequency and see pictures.. interesting structures, such as calderas and lava domes. Calderas, large crater-shaped basins, form when eruptions drain a magma chamber and the volcano edifice...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7326-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7326_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:36:49">http://www.howstuffworks.com/the-biggest-eruptions-on-earth-info.htm</link><title>Introduction to The Biggest Eruptions on Earth</title><description>When Mount Pinatubo in the Philippines began erupting in June 1991, the catastrophe made headlines around the world. Almost 300 people died during.. of rock and ash so huge that it completely blocked the sun for 600 kilometers (370 miles) around the volcano. Even larger eruptions occurred during...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7326-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7326_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:37:36">http://www.howstuffworks.com/nature/natural-disasters/volcano.htm</link><title>How Volcanoes Work: Types of Eruptions</title><description>Types of eruptions include fissure eruptions, hydrovolcanic eruptions, and Plinian eruptions. Find out how the types of eruptions differ from each..A tall Plinian plume erupts from Klyuchevskaya Volcano in Russia. Photo courtesy NASA Within these two broad eruption categories, there are several...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7326-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7326_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:38:16">http://www.howstuffworks.com/nature/natural-disasters/volcano.htm</link><title>How Volcanoes Work: Magma Eruptions</title><description>Magma eruptions are caused by internal gas pressure that forces the magma to the surface. Learn about magma eruptions and see pictures of magma.. they push a lot of the soda out with them. This is true for volcanoes as well. As the bubbles escape, they push the magma out, causing a spewing eruption...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7326-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7326_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:38:57">http://www.howstuffworks.com/nature/natural-disasters/volcano.htm</link><title>How Volcanoes Work: Other Types of Eruptions</title><description>Other types of eruptions include vulcanian eruptions, hydrovolcanic eruptions and fissure eruptions. Learn about these volcanic eruptions.... Vulcanian eruptions generally aren't associated with lava flow. A hydrovolcanic eruption from Ukinrek Volcano, off the coast of Alaska. Photo courtesy USGS...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7326-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7326_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:39:43">http://www.howstuffworks.com/the-biggest-eruptions-on-earth-info.htm</link><title>The Biggest Eruptions on Earth: Volcanoes and Ice Ages—cause and Effect?</title><description>When Mount Pinatubo in the Philippines began erupting in June 1991, the catastrophe made headlines around the world. Almost 300 people died during..A few geologists have even proposed that series of gigantic explosive eruptions may have triggered the ice ages (periods during which enormous sheets...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7326-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7326_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:40:27">http://www.howstuffworks.com/nature/natural-disasters/volcano.htm</link><title>How Volcanoes Work: Volcano Formation</title><description>Volcano formation is the result of an eruption at a hot spot at a particular point on the Earth. Learn about volcano formation and hot spot volcanism...Flowing lava on Kilauea Volcano in Hawaii Photo courtesy USGS Magma can also push up under the middle of a lithosphere plate, though this is much...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7326-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7326_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:41:08">http://www.howstuffworks.com/the-biggest-eruptions-on-earth-info.htm</link><title>The Biggest Eruptions on Earth: Evidence of Giant Eruptions</title><description>When Mount Pinatubo in the Philippines began erupting in June 1991, the catastrophe made headlines around the world. Almost 300 people died during.. for evidence of huge eruptions. Since then, they have identified about 80 volcanoes that at one time have erupted at least 100 cubic kilometers (24 cubic miles...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7326-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7326_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:41:47">http://www.howstuffworks.com/the-biggest-eruptions-on-earth-info.htm</link><title>The Biggest Eruptions on Earth: Clues to the Type of Eruption</title><description>When Mount Pinatubo in the Philippines began erupting in June 1991, the catastrophe made headlines around the world. Almost 300 people died during.. the magma reached the surface. Certain types of rock indicate the volcano erupted in an explosive blast, and other kinds show that the lava poured out more...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>