<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7328">reduce acne redness</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:44:34" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7328-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7328_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:44:36">http://health.howstuffworks.com/skin-care/problems/treating/acne-treatments.htm</link><title>Acne Treatments: Fast Facts</title><description>Get fast facts on acne treatments, and consider using these tips in your daily skincare routine to reduce acne breakouts... and reducing existing inflammation. Learn more about antibiotics for acne. Because high levels of hormones can increase oil production...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7328_01_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/pimples-quiz-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7328-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7328_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:45:05">http://health.howstuffworks.com/skin-care/problems/treating/acne-laser.htm</link><title>Can doctors treat acne with lasers?</title><description>Acne lasers are one treatment for bad acne. Find out if acne lasers are dangerous and if acne laser treatment is right for you... that have accumulated in the hair follicle to the point of damaging it. The drugs also calm the body's immune system response, reducing redness and swelling...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7328_02_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/acne-lasers-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7328-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7328_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:45:28">http://health.howstuffworks.com/skin-care/problems/treating/acne-laser.htm</link><title>Can doctors treat acne with lasers?: Acne Lasers and the War on Breakouts</title><description>Acne lasers can help treat breakouts. Learn about the pros and cons of using lasers on acne breakouts... of each. Diode lasers prevent future acne breakouts by reducing the skin's ability to produce sebum. This is accomplished by destroying some of the millions...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7328-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7328_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:45:56">http://health.howstuffworks.com/skin-care/problems/medical/adult-acne.htm</link><title>Adult Acne Overview: Skin Products for Adult Acne</title><description>There are several skin products that help with adult acne. Learn more about skin products for adult acne at HowStuffWorks...So which skin product is best suited for treating adult acne? The answer depends on the severity of the outbreak and whether a person is taking...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7328_04_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/adult-acne-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7328-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7328_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:46:43">http://health.howstuffworks.com/skin-care/problems/medical/acne.htm</link><title>All About Acne: Treating Acne</title><description>Treating acne can be done with creams and hygiene, though avoid picking and touching your face to prevent scarring. See options for treating acne... had success treating your acne with oral contraceptives, which reduce sebum production in women. Isotretinoin. This medication, which comes in drugs...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7328_05_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/acne-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7328-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7328_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:47:12">http://health.howstuffworks.com/skin-care/cleansing/tips/get-rid-of-body-acne.htm</link><title>How to Get Rid of Body Acne: Body Acne and Medication</title><description>Believe it or not, body acne is sometimes related to medication. Learn more about body acne and medication at HowStuffWorks. .. -- an ingredient in Accutane -- can be prescribed. This oral medication treats body acne by reducing the size of the sebaceous glands and preventing too much oil...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7328_06_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/get-rid-of-body-acne-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7328-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7328_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:47:32">http://health.howstuffworks.com/skin-care/men/cleansing-tips/mens-face-acne-cleansers.htm</link><title>What should men look for in face acne cleansers?: Men's Face Acne Cleanser Ingredients</title><description>Men's face acne cleansers sometimes include salicylic acid. Visit Discovery Health to learn more about men's face acne cleanser ingredients. ..The Jury is Still Out Many supposed acne remedies haven't been conclusively proven to work, and so have yet to reach FDA approval. As a result...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7328_07_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/face-acne-cleanser-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7328-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7328_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:48:02">http://health.howstuffworks.com/skin-care/problems/treating/5-surprising-acne-treatments.htm</link><title>5 Surprising Acne Treatments: 2: Heat</title><description>Try these surprising acne treatments to get rid of that pimple. Learn about 5 surprising acne treatments at HowStuffWorks...When combined with pulsed light treatments, heat therapy (as administered by a dermatologist) can destroy the bacteria responsible for acne as well...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7328_08_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/surprising-acne-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7328-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7328_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:48:34">http://health.howstuffworks.com/skin-care/problems/treating/get-rid-of-acne-scars.htm</link><title>How to Get Rid of Acne Scars: Do Acne Scars Ever Disappear?</title><description>Do acne scars ever disappear? Find out if acne scars ever disappear at HowStuffWorks. ..To Scar or Not to Scar? Not all acne causes scars. Some acne can leave behind temporary pseudo-scars -- the skin will appear red and inflamed when...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7328_09_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/get-rid-of-acne-scars-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7328-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7328_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:49:17">http://health.howstuffworks.com/skin-care/problems/treating/zeno-acne-treatment-device.htm</link><title>Zeno Acne Treatment Device: Does the Zeno Acne Device Really Work?</title><description>Does the Zeno acne treatment device really work? Find out if the Zeno acne treatment device really works at HowStuffWorks. .. or hard nodules that appear red and swollen due to the inflammation of the surrounding tissue [source: WebMD]. This type of acne can be especially difficult...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7328_10_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/zeno-acne-treatment-device-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>