<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7348">map of the united states</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:49:09" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7348-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7348_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:49:11">http://www.howstuffworks.com/crafts/recycled/projects/5-recycled-cereal-box-crafts.htm</link><title>10 Uses for Empty Cereal Boxes: 8\. Map of the United States</title><description>to make a colorful map of the United States. For this project, you'll need a sheet of poster board, lots of different kinds of cereal boxes, an Exacto knife...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7348_01_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/recycled-cereal-box-crafts-100x60a.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7348-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7348_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:49:48">http://www.howstuffworks.com/dictionary/geology-terms/united-states-geological-survey-info.htm</link><title>United States Geological Survey</title><description>United States Geological Survey is a term used to study and practice geology. Visit HowStuffWorks to learn all about the term United States..United States Geological Survey, an agency of the Department of the Interior. Its main functions are to appraise the nation's mineral and water...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7348-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7348_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:50:32">http://www.howstuffworks.com/environmental/earth/geophysics/map.htm</link><title>How Maps Work</title><description>Maps are a convenient method of illustrating a wide variety of data. Learn about the different types of maps and find out how maps are created... that can describe nearly anything about the world. A map of the United States足足. Check out more 足 o足n our Maps channel. You can also see maps of Canada...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7348_03_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/map-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7348-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7348_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:51:06">http://history.howstuffworks.com/revolutionary-war/early-years-of-the-united-states-government.htm</link><title>Early Years of New Government: Westward Expansion</title><description>Westward expansion was a key to the early years of the United States. Learn more about westward expansion at HowStuffWorks...Kentucky had been admitted as a state in 1792, Tennessee in 1796. United States territory was greatly enlarged during Jefferson's administration...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7348-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7348_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:51:53">http://www.howstuffworks.com/10-sprawliest-cities-in-united-states.htm</link><title>10 Sprawliest Cities in the United States: Lots More Information</title><description>What are the sprawliest cities in the United States? Learn about 10 of the sprawliest cities in the United States...Author's Note: 10 Sprawliest Cities in the United States The best way to gauge a city's sprawl, in my own humble opinion, is by looking for a hotel...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7348_05_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/sprawl-city-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7348-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7348_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:52:33">http://www.howstuffworks.com/environmental/earth/geophysics/map.htm</link><title>How Maps Work: Map Projections</title><description>Map projections are used to help translate a sphere into a flat surface. Learn about map projections and see pictures of different map projections... projections and their strengths and weaknesses from NASA, the National Atlas of the United States and the U.S. Geological Survey. Choosing the right projection...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7348-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7348_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:53:19">http://www.howstuffworks.com/environmental/earth/geophysics/map.htm</link><title>How Maps Work: Thematic Maps</title><description>Thematic maps require accurate, up-to-date information on a wide range of social and environmental topics. Find out how thematic maps are made.... Turner explains, "If we're doing a state map of Virginia, we might receive information from the state at one period, that was developed at one time...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7348-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7348_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:54:05">http://www.howstuffworks.com/environmental/earth/geophysics/map.htm</link><title>How Maps Work: Lots More Information</title><description>For more map information and information on related topics, check out these links...Nova. Personal interview. 4/10/2007. United States Geological Service. "Geographic Information Systems." (4/3/2007) http...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7348-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7348_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:54:41">http://www.howstuffworks.com/narco-state.htm</link><title>How Narco States Work</title><description>Narco states are places where illegal drugs are openly traded with governmental approval. Learn all about narco states. ... The United States has a particularly ravenous appetite for cocaine, consuming some 40 percent of the global supply each year [source: Glenny]. While...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7348_09_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/narco-states-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7348-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7348_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:55:27">http://www.howstuffworks.com/washington-state-scenic-drives.htm</link><title>Washington Scenic Drives</title><description>Washington scenic drives allow you to fully experience the state's varied terrain. See photos, highlights, and maps for three Washington scenic.. drive through the state, go to the links at the bottom of this page. They will connect you to articles that contain photos, highlights, and detailed maps...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7348_10_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/washington-state-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>