<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7428">rainy afternoon kids craft</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:31:56" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7428-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7428_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:31:58">http://www.howstuffworks.com/green-living/green-crafts-kids.htm</link><title>16 Top Green Crafts To Do With Your Kids</title><description>Eco-friendly crafts to do with kids of all ages and abilities. Learn more about the 16 top green crafts to do with your kids...Need more ideas for building your family quality time? Coming up with green crafts to do with your kids can make a rainy day more tolerable, build...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7428-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7428_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:32:43">http://www.howstuffworks.com/crafts/seasonal/winter/winter-crafts-for-kids.htm</link><title>Winter Crafts for Kids: Christmas Present Needlepoint Ornament</title><description>Make a Christmas present needlepoint ornament, a favorite winter craft for kids. Find out more about winter crafts for kids...Make a Christmas present needlepoint ornament, a wonderful craft project to make on rainy or snowy winter afternoons. It turns indoor time into fun...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7428_02_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/religious-christmas-crafts-10-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7428-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7428_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:33:29">http://www.howstuffworks.com/crafts/recycled/kids/recycled-juice-box-crafts.htm</link><title>Ultimate Guide to Recycled Juice Box Crafts</title><description>Recycled juice box crafts are fun and green. Visit HowStuffWorks to learn all about recycled juice box crafts... supplies will be enough to keep you and your kids entertained on a rainy afternoon. You can make everything from a doll to a miniature golf course...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7428_03_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/recycled-juice-box-crafts-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7428-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7428_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:34:05">http://www.howstuffworks.com/crafts/quick-easy-crafts/easy-indoor-activities-for-kids.htm</link><title>Easy Indoor Activities for Kids</title><description>Turn a dull afternoon into an adventure with easy indoor activities for kids. Learn about easy indoor activities for kids at HowStuffWorks... for Kids Easy Indoor Games for Kids Easy Indoor Crafts for Kids Rainy Day Activities...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7428_04_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/easy-indoor-activities-for-kids-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7428-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7428_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:34:41">http://www.howstuffworks.com/crafts/seasonal/winter/dance-activities-for-kids.htm</link><title>Dance Activities for Kids</title><description>Dance activities for kids break through boredom, and they're great exercise. Try everything from ballet to rain dances with dance activities... Find a style your kids like, and you'll be ready to dance through a rainy afternoon or even put on a show for the neighborhood. Ready to start tapping...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7428_05_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/dance-activities-for-kids-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7428-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7428_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:35:22">http://www.howstuffworks.com/crafts/quick-easy-crafts/easy-indoor-games-for-kids.htm</link><title>Easy Indoor Games for Kids</title><description>Easy indoor games for kids fight boredom by providing something fun to play. Learn about board games, math games and more that teach and entertain... activities and crafts, check out: Easy Crafts for Kids Easy Indoor Activities for Kids Easy Indoor Crafts for Kids Rainy Day Activities...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7428_06_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/easy-indoor-games-for-kids-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7428-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7428_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:36:04">http://www.howstuffworks.com/crafts/animal-crafts/dog-activities.htm</link><title>Dog Activities</title><description>Try your hand at dog activities for kids with puzzles, balloons, and even a dog parade. Learn more about dog activities for kids...On a sunny day or a rainy afternoon, there's always a way to celebrate canines with dog activities for kids. From quizzes and puzzles...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7428_07_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/dog-activities-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7428-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7428_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:36:44">http://www.howstuffworks.com/family/activities/after-school/tasty-after-school-activities.htm</link><title>Edible Crafts: Tasty After-School Activities: Candy Necklaces</title><description>Looking for some tasty after-school activities for the kids? Check out our article Edible Crafts: Tasty After-School Activities now!..-packaged candy necklace kits to keep on hand for a quick solution on a rainy afternoon....</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7428_08_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/edible-crafts-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>