<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7438">facebook privacy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:57:21" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7438-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7438_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:57:23">http://www.howstuffworks.com/internet/tips/how-to-update-your-facebook-privacy-settings.htm</link><title>How to Update Your Facebook Privacy Settings: Facebook Privacy Issues</title><description>Updating your Facebook privacy settings can help you control who sees your profile and your status updates. Learn how to update your Facebook privacy..Use the lock icon when you make a status update to override your Facebook privacy settings for that single post. Stephanie Crawford for How...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7438_01_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/facebook-privacy-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7438-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7438_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:57:38">http://www.howstuffworks.com/internet/tips/how-to-update-your-facebook-privacy-settings.htm</link><title>How to Update Your Facebook Privacy Settings: Important Facebook Privacy Settings</title><description>Updating your Facebook privacy settings can help you control who sees your profile and your status updates. Learn how to update your Facebook privacy..Using the "sharing in Facebook" section of your Facebook privacy settings, you can choose what you share and with whom. When you select any...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7438-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7438_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:58:15">http://www.howstuffworks.com/internet/tips/how-to-update-your-facebook-privacy-settings.htm</link><title>How to Update Your Facebook Privacy Settings</title><description>Updating your Facebook privacy settings can help you control who sees your profile and your status updates. Learn how to update your Facebook privacy..Concerned about your privacy on Facebook? Don't hide offline -- just adjust your settings. ©Jeffrey Coolidge/Getty Images Privacy is one...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7438-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7438_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:58:51">http://www.howstuffworks.com/internet/tips/how-to-update-your-facebook-privacy-settings.htm</link><title>How to Update Your Facebook Privacy Settings: Protect Privacy for Searches and Apps</title><description>Updating your Facebook privacy settings can help you control who sees your profile and your status updates. Learn how to update your Facebook privacy.. by the app itself. Stephanie Crawford for HowStuffWorks Regardless of any other privacy settings, Facebook makes your name, profile picture, gender...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7438-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7438_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:59:25">http://www.howstuffworks.com/internet/tips/how-to-update-your-facebook-privacy-settings.htm</link><title>How to Update Your Facebook Privacy Settings: Lots More Information</title><description>Updating your Facebook privacy settings can help you control who sees your profile and your status updates. Learn how to update your Facebook privacy..Related Articles How Facebook Works Facebook Quiz Top 5 Myths About Facebook How to Avoid Facebook Scams More Great Links 10 Privacy Settings Every...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7438-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7438_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:00:02">http://www.howstuffworks.com/facebook-tv.htm</link><title>How Facebook TV Will Work: Facebook, Media and Privacy</title><description>Could Facebook TV be the next big thing? Find out what Facebook TV is and how Facebook TV will work...For users, the core purpose of Facebook is to allow you to connect and share with friends online. It's a way to discover stuff that interests you...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7438_06_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/facebook-tv-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7438-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7438_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:00:41">http://www.howstuffworks.com/internet/social-networking/information/facebook-timeline.htm</link><title>How Facebook Timeline Works: Customizing Your Timeline and Privacy Settings</title><description>In early 2012, Facebook Timeline replaced the personal wall format that users had been accustomed to. See what Facebook Timeline is all about...Facebook's help center features a video to help you learn about your privacy settings. Screenshot by HowStuffWorks Timeline makes it easy to hide...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7438_07_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/facebook-timeline-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7438-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7438_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:01:22">http://www.howstuffworks.com/how-to-tech/how-to-avoid-facebook-scams.htm</link><title>How to Avoid Facebook Scams: Facebook Scams</title><description>Facebook scams often come from Facebook applications. Learn about Facebook scams and how they get into the framework of Facebook.... But not all apps are innocent. You should pay attention to what kind of information the app says it must be able to access to work properly. Facebook's privacy...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7438_08_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/avoid-facebook-scams-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7438-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7438_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:02:00">http://www.howstuffworks.com/internet/social-networking/networks/unhide-friends-facebook.htm</link><title>How do you unhide friends on Facebook?</title><description>You can change default Facebook settings to enable or block friends from sharing specific content, such as posts or pictures. Learn how to unhide..You can change your privacy settings by clicking on the Accounts tab in your Facebook account. Click on Privacy Settings to control what you share...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7438-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7438_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:02:42">http://www.howstuffworks.com/internet/tips/is-facebook-sharing-personal-information.htm</link><title>Is Facebook sharing your personal information?</title><description>Is Facebook sharing your personal information? Learn about Facebook privacy settings and if Facebook is sharing your personal information...How much personal information should you put on Facebook? Is it safe? Thomas Northcut/Photodisc/Thinkstock Popular Web Sites Image Gallery It...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7438_10_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/facebook-personal-info-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>