<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7445">marathon training</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:27:50" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7445-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7445_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:27:51">http://www.howstuffworks.com/outdoor-activities/running/training/advanced-marathon-training.htm</link><title>How Advanced Marathon Training Works</title><description>Advanced marathon training is for seasoned distance runners only. Visit HowStuffWorks to learn about Advanced marathon training...Training for advanced marathon running may bring you even further off the beaten path. iStockphoto/Thinkstock The day you slapped that "26...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7445_01_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/advanced-marathon-training100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7445-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7445_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:28:27">http://www.howstuffworks.com/outdoor-activities/running/training/intermediate-marathon-training.htm</link><title>How Intermediate Marathon Training Works</title><description>Intermediate marathon training is a great way to improve your running. Visit HowStuffWorks to learn about intermediate marathon training...Stockphoto/Thinkstock Intermediate marathon training is about taking your body to the next level of running. But how do you know if you're an intermediate runner? Specifically...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7445_02_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/intermediate-marathon-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7445-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7445_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:29:09">http://health.howstuffworks.com/wellness/diet-fitness/information/green-marathon-training.htm</link><title>6 Ways to Green Your Marathon Training</title><description>Training for a marathon is hard work but it can be a truly life changing accomplishment. Learn more about 6 ways to green your marathon training...Michael Rosenfeld/Getty Images DCL Training for a marathon is hard work but it can be a truly life changing accomplishment. The ability to train...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7445-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7445_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:29:42">http://www.howstuffworks.com/outdoor-activities/running/training/advanced-marathon-training.htm</link><title>How Advanced Marathon Training Works: Advanced Marathon Training Schedule</title><description>This advanced marathon training schedule will help runners lower their times. Visit HowStuffWorks to see this advanced marathon training schedule. .., a strategy called tapering is crucial to running your best marathon. He says three weeks before your race, you should reduce your training mileage...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7445-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7445_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:30:19">http://www.howstuffworks.com/outdoor-activities/running/training/intermediate-marathon-training.htm</link><title>How Intermediate Marathon Training Works: Intermediate Marathon Training Schedule</title><description>An intermediate marathon training schedule can help improve your race time. Visit HowStuffWorks to see this intermediate marathon training schedule... on Saturday; and the marathon on Sunday. Most intermediate training schedules can prepare an intermediate runner for a race-quality marathon within a 16- to 20...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7445-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7445_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:30:54">http://www.howstuffworks.com/outdoor-activities/running/training/advanced-marathon-training.htm</link><title>How Advanced Marathon Training Works: Tips for Advanced Marathon Training</title><description>These tips for Advanced marathon training can help seasoned runners race better. Visit HowStuffWorks to find tips for Advanced marathon training. ..Should you avoid caffeine and alcohol while you're training? According to lab studies, caffeine is likely to improve your marathon time anywhere...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7445-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7445_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:31:36">http://www.howstuffworks.com/outdoor-activities/running/training/10-marathon-training-tips.htm</link><title>Top 10 Marathon Training Tips</title><description>The top 10 training tips for a 10K can make your race a more enjoyable experience. Visit HowStuffWorks to see the top 10 training tips for a 10K...Now that you've signed up for a marathon, how should you train? Thomas Northcut/Photodisc/Getty Images You bit the bullet. You took the plunge. You...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7445_07_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/10-marathon-tips-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7445-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7445_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:32:20">http://www.howstuffworks.com/outdoor-activities/running/training/intermediate-marathon-training.htm</link><title>How Intermediate Marathon Training Works: Lots More Information</title><description>To learn more about intermediate marathon training and related topics, follow these links...Related HowStuffWorks Articles How a Marathon Works How Advanced Marathon Training Works How the Ironman Works How to Train for Your First Marathon...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7445-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7445_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:32:55">http://www.howstuffworks.com/outdoor-activities/running/training/advanced-marathon-training.htm</link><title>How Advanced Marathon Training Works: Lots More Information</title><description>To learn more about Advanced marathon training and related topics, follow these links. ..Related HowStuffWorks Articles How a Marathon Works How the Ironman Works How to Train for Your First Marathon What's a green marathon? Why can...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7445-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7445_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:33:29">http://www.howstuffworks.com/outdoor-activities/running/training/intermediate-marathon-training.htm</link><title>How Intermediate Marathon Training Works: Tips for Intermediate Marathon Runners</title><description>These tips for intermediate marathon runners can help lower race times. Visit HowStuffWorks to find tips for intermediate marathon runners. .. is to train your body to be used to marathon-day hydration levels by drinking marathon-day levels throughout the training period. So even if you're only running...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>