<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7451">buy animal farm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:51:11" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7451-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7451_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:51:12">http://www.howstuffworks.com/green-living/congress-prevent-farm-animal-cruelty.htm</link><title>Will Congress Actually Be Able to Prevent Farm Animal Cruelty?</title><description>Will Congress prevent farm animal cruelty? Find out if Congress can prevent farm animal cruelty...More on Farm Animals: It was certainly a step in the right direction when California's Farm Animal Cruelty Prevention Act, Proposition 2 passed...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7451-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7451_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:51:57">http://www.howstuffworks.com/environmental/conservation/issues/vertical-farming.htm</link><title>Will there be farms in New York City's skyscrapers?</title><description>Vertical farming is a method of large-scale farming in an urban environment. Learn about the benefits of a vertical farm and vertical farming.., unwanted strains of plants or wandering animals. These farms would also be located in the urban areas where most of the Earth's population will be living...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7451_02_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/vertical-farming-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7451-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7451_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:52:31">http://www.howstuffworks.com/environmental/conservation/issues/agroforestry-farming.htm</link><title>Agroforestry Farming</title><description>Agroforestry farming offers an alternative to mainstream food production methods that reduces your carbon footprint. Learn about agroforestry farming... ecological services to the planet. Living on the farm increased my awareness of the interdependence of people, plants and animals. The world is gaining...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7451-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7451_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:53:07">http://www.howstuffworks.com/environmental/green-science/organic-farming.htm</link><title>How Organic Farming Works: Genetically Modified Foods</title><description>' market, and depending on where you live, you may be able to join a local co-op or buy a share in a community-supported organic farm. Or, try ordering...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7451_04_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/organic-food-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7451-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7451_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:53:43">http://www.howstuffworks.com/environmental/green-science/organic-farming.htm</link><title>How Organic Farming Works: Organic Standards and Certifications</title><description>Organic standards make the process of organic farming more labor and management intensive. Learn more about the different organic standards..: Soil Association]. Researchers are continuing to look at ways to improve upon organic farming practices, including methods of animal health care (such...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7451-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7451_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:54:24">http://recipes.howstuffworks.com/safron-factory-farming-interview.htm</link><title>Jonathan Safran Foer on Factory Farming, Thanksgiving, and Birthday Cake (Interview)</title><description>Bestselling author of Eating Animals talks about animals, environment, and...what people are saying about his book... the most surprising? JSF:I think the most surprising thing is just the breadth of factory farming. It's in everything. It's 99 percent of all the animals...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7451-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7451_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:54:58">http://recipes.howstuffworks.com/england-largest-ever-dairy-farm-trouble.htm</link><title>Why the Plan for England's Newest, Largest-Ever Dairy Farm Is Trouble: What does that mean for the U.S.?</title><description>Discover Why the Plan for England's Newest, Largest-Ever Dairy Farm Is Trouble. Keep reading to learn about England's Newest, Largest Dairy Farm... can personally verify or talk with the producer about farming conditions, chances are it is coming from a factory farm with similar conditions—animals...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7451_07_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/dairy-oral-care-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7451-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7451_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:55:39">http://recipes.howstuffworks.com/dairy-calf-abuse-takes-place-on-federally-subsidized-farm.htm</link><title>Dairy Calf Abuse Takes Place on a Federally Subsidized Farm</title><description>You may have seen the horrible news (and video footage) yesterday about workers at Conklin Dairy Farms abusing calves—including punching them..—including punching them, kicking downed cows, using pitchforks... and more. The footage, filmed by undercover investigators with Mercy for Animals, is from a farm...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7451-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7451_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:56:21">http://recipes.howstuffworks.com/10-foods-you-should-buy-organic.htm</link><title>10 Foods You Should Buy Organic</title><description>The foods you should buy organic include those with thin skins and ones you eat frequently. Learn what foods you should buy organic... foods that meet the standards set by the U.S. Department of Agriculture. Animals can't be given antibiotics or growth hormone. Farmers can't use...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7451_09_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/10-foods-you-should-buy-organic-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7451-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7451_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:56:58">http://recipes.howstuffworks.com/10-foods-you-should-buy-organic.htm</link><title>10 Foods You Should Buy Organic: 10: Meat</title><description>The foods you should buy organic include those with thin skins and ones you eat frequently. Learn what foods you should buy organic..., but standards are the same for all animals raised to be sold as organic. Ranchers and farm owners cannot give their animals antibiotics to make them resistant...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>