<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7456">gps reviews</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:09:49" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7456-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7456_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:09:50">http://www.howstuffworks.com/gadgets/travel/gps.htm</link><title>How GPS Receivers Work</title><description>GPS can pinpoint your location anywhere on Earth. Find out how GPS works, learn about the amazing technology behind GPS and read reviews of GPS..Essential Gadgets Image Gallery A GPS receiver uses satellites to pinpoint locations. See more pictures of essential gadgets. Essential Gadgets Image...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7456_01_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/gps-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7456-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7456_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:10:28">http://www.howstuffworks.com/gadgets/travel/gps.htm</link><title>How GPS Receivers Work: Lots More Information</title><description>GPS can pinpoint your location anywhere on Earth. Find out how GPS works, learn about the amazing technology behind GPS and read reviews of GPS.. Reality Will Work How Atomic Clocks Work How Compasses Work How does an EPIRB distress radio work? How Urban Gaming Works How GPS Phones Work How Maps Work...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7456-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7456_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:11:06">http://www.howstuffworks.com/survival/gear/handheld-gps.htm</link><title>How to Use a Handheld GPS: Lots More Information</title><description>To learn more about handheld GPS and related topics, follow these links...." Geocaching.com. 2009.http://www.geocaching.com/about/ "Handheld GPS: Reviews." Consumerresearch.com. 2009.http://www.consumersearch.com/gps &amp;quot...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7456_03_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/handheld-gps-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7456-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7456_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:11:44">http://www.howstuffworks.com/gadgets/automotive/car-gps-accidents.htm</link><title>Do car GPS devices cause accidents?</title><description>Car GPS devices can be useful -- or distracting. Learn about car GPS devices, when to use your own judgment and how to used you car's GPS device.. Review]. GPS has hit the mainstream. ­GPS, which stands for Global Positioning System, is made up of a group of satellites. These satellites communicate...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7456_04_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/car-gps-accidents-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7456-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7456_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:12:22">http://www.howstuffworks.com/gps-phone.htm</link><title>How GPS Phones Work: Lots More Information</title><description>To learn more about GPS phones, GPS receivers, cell phones, satellites and other related topics, check out these links... Overview Cellular Telephone Basics Wireless-Assisted GPS GPS World Sources Aquino, Grace. "GPS Phone Leads the Way." PCWorld, June 2004. http://www.pcworld.com/reviews...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7456_05_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/gps-phone-1--100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7456-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7456_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:12:56">http://www.howstuffworks.com/gadgets/clocks-watches/gps-watch.htm</link><title>How GPS Watches Work: The Right GPS Tool for the Job</title><description>A GPS watch links to a net of synchronized computers orbiting Earth to provide you with highly accurate data. Learn what you can do with a GPS watch..., and don't be afraid to pester friends about their GPS watches. The first-hand tips and real-life reviews you'll get will leave you well prepared to make...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7456_06_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/gps-watch-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7456-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7456_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:13:31">http://www.howstuffworks.com/gps-phone.htm</link><title>Introduction to How GPS Phones Work</title><description>GPS phones can pinpoint a location, give directions and provide information about businesses. Learn about GPS phones and how GPS receivers determine... In this article, we'll review the basics of how cell phones and GPS receivers work. Then, we'll explore how phones combine these technologies. Cell Phone Basics...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7456-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7456_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:14:05">http://www.howstuffworks.com/gadgets/automotive/car-gps-system.htm</link><title>Is it more affordable to have a portable GPS system in your car or have the dealer install one?: Lots More Information</title><description>For more information about GPS systems and related car electronics, take a look at the links on this page....cnet.com/best-tech-cars/?tag=rightColumnArea1.0 Delany, John R. "GPS Buying Guide." CNET Reviews. (Jan. 27, 2009) http://reviews.cnet.com/gps-buying-guide/?tag=leftColumnArea1.0 Newman...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7456_08_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/car-gps-system-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7456-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7456_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:14:59">http://www.howstuffworks.com/gadgets/automotive/5-car-gps-devices.htm</link><title>Top 5 Car GPS Devices</title><description>Car GPS devices are loaded with features that make them enticing to motorists. Learn more about car GPS devices at HowStuffWorks... of the best GPS devices currently on the market and review some of the features that make these gadgets so irresistible, even if you aren't going on a long trip....</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7456_09_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/5-car-gps-devices-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7456-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7456_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:15:41">http://www.howstuffworks.com/gadgets/automotive/car-gps-accidents.htm</link><title>Do car GPS devices cause accidents?: Lots More Information</title><description>For more information on GPS accidents and information on related topics, check out these links...Related HowStuffWorks Articles Top 5 Car Gadgets 5 Extravagant Car Amenities How Dashboard Displays Work Are RFID ignition systems secure? Why do GPS...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>