<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7499">gold price</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:58:13" name="HowStuffWorks" id="FW14-e134"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e134-7499-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7499_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:58:14">http://www.howstuffworks.com/gold.htm</link><title>How Gold Works</title><description>The rarity of gold is just one reason why people value the precious metal. Learn why gold inspires men to wage war and how we find and refine gold...Forget those ruby red slippers, Dorothy. This gold shoe, made in China and yours for the low price of $41,000, will take you a lot farther than...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7499_01_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/gold-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7499-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7499_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:58:50">http://history.howstuffworks.com/american-history/gold-standard.htm</link><title>Gold Standard</title><description>The Gold Standard was a significant part of history associated with the New Deal in North America. Learn more about the Gold Standard at HowStuffWorks... increasingly difficult to maintain as the official price of gold ceased to reflect its rising value and scarcity. In 1971 the United States stopped redeeming...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7499-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7499_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:59:30">http://www.howstuffworks.com/gold.htm</link><title>How Gold Works: Gold and Money</title><description>Gold and money is a term related to gold. Learn about gold and money at HowStuffWorks... for gold and will buy and sell gold at a fixed price. In 1900, with the passage of the Gold Standard Act, the United States formally adopted the gold...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7499-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7499_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:00:03">http://www.howstuffworks.com/gold.htm</link><title>How Gold Works: History of Gold: The Middle Ages and the Mad Rushes</title><description>Gold rushes is a term related to gold. Learn about gold rushes at HowStuffWorks... of the Mint. In 1700, Newton fixed the price of gold, redefining the shilling, pound and pence so that 21 shillings and 6 pence would stay equivalent to one...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7499-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7499_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:00:40">http://www.howstuffworks.com/gold.htm</link><title>How Gold Works: Lots More Information</title><description>For more gold information and information on related topics, check out these links..., 2009) http://pubs.usgs.gov/gip/prospect2/prospectgip.html Larmer, Brook. "The Real Price of Gold." National Geographic...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7499-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7499_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:01:15">http://www.howstuffworks.com/medicine/modern-technology/gold-nanotech.htm</link><title>How could gold save my life?</title><description>Gold nanoparticles have the potential to change breast cancer detection radically, according to a recent study. Learn about the use of gold..Nanoparticles derived from gold hold tremendous possibilities for scientific and medical use. See more modern medicine pictures. Photographer: Jean...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7499_06_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/gold-nanotech-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7499-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7499_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:01:53">http://www.howstuffworks.com/personal-finance/financial-planning/how-do-you-invest-in-gold.htm</link><title>How do you invest in gold?</title><description>Do you know how to invest in gold? Find out the best ways to invest in gold in this article from howstuffworks.com... mitigate your losses when stocks and bonds begin to lose value, mainly because the price of gold tends to increase during bear markets and periods...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7499_07_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/invest-gold-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7499-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7499_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:02:32">http://www.howstuffworks.com/1975-honda-gl1000-gold-wing.htm</link><title>1975 Honda GL1000 Gold Wing</title><description>The 1975 Honda GL1000 Gold Wing motorcycle launched a touring-bike legend. Find out why and see pictures of the 1975 Honda GL1000 Gold Wing... for a lower center of gravity. The price to be paid for all these features was weight, as a bare-bones 1975 Honda GL1000 Gold Wing motorcycle tipped the scales...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7499_08_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/1975-honda-gl-1000-gold-wing-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7499-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7499_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:03:08">http://www.howstuffworks.com/destinations/summer-travel-families/alaska-panning-for-gold-pictures.htm</link><title>Everything I Need to Know I Learned ... Panning for Gold</title><description>You're sure to pick up some life lessons on summer vacation by panning for gold in Alaska. See pictures of panning for gold in Alaska...Convenience has its price: No need to trample through streams anymore! Most gold-panning tours in Alaska sell bags of gold-panning dirt, which comes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e134-7499-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7499_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:03:43">http://www.howstuffworks.com/wellness/spa-health/do-gold-facials-really-exist.htm</link><title>Do gold facials really exist?</title><description>Gold facials have been used as a way to preserve a youthful appearance for thousands of years -- but do gold facials really work?.. covered in 24-karat gold is an exclusive service that comes with a hefty price tag. You don't have to be the queen of Egypt to afford it, but a single...</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e134/7499_10_thumb.jpg">http://r.ddmcdn.com/u_0/w_100/gif/do-gold-facials-really-exist-100x60.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>