<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7009">linkedin engineering</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:04:12" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7009-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7009_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:04:13">http://news.slashdot.org/story/13/08/30/1525204/the-golden-gate-barrage-new-ideas-to-counter-sea-level-rise</link><title>The Golden Gate Barrage: New Ideas To Counter Sea Level Rise</title><description>waderoush writes "What do Google, Facebook, Yahoo, Oracle, LinkedIn, and Intuit have in common? They're just a few of the tech companies whose campuses alongside San Francisco Bay could be underwater by mid-century as sea levels rise. It's time for these organizations and other innovators to put some of their fabled brainpower into coming up with new ideas to counter the threat, Xconomy argues today. One idea: the Golden Gate Barrage, a massive system of dams, locks, and pumps located in the shadow of the iconic bridge. Taller than the Three Gorges Dam in China, it would be one of the largest and costliest projects in the history of civil engineering. But at least one Bay Area government official says might turn out to be the simplest way to save hundreds of square miles of land around the bay from inundation."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7009-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7009_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:05:36">http://science.slashdot.org/story/13/05/06/1813251/hivebio-is-working-to-become-seattles-first-community-biology-lab-video</link><title>HiveBio is Working to Become Seattle's First Community Biology Lab (Video)</title><description>HiveBio in Seattle is not the world's first community-based biology lab, but it may be the first one started by a high school student. Her name is Katriona Guthrie-Honea, and her co-founder is Bergen McMurray. They managed to get a lot of equipment and supplies donated to their new venture, along with a successful Microryza Campaign that raised $6425 even though their target was only $5100. They're renting space from a local hackerlab, and getting an insane amount of publicity for a venture that's just starting out. But why not? If Bergen's and Katriona's example can spur others to learn and create, whether in mechanical engineering, physics, electronics, computer science or biology, it's all good -- not only for the participants, but for anyone who might someday benefit from creations or discoveries made by people who got their first taste of hands-on science or engineering in a hackerspace or community biology lab.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7009-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7009_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:07:24">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/182945</link><title>Facebook Details the Software Engineering Behind Graph Search</title><description>Nerval's Lobster writes "Facebook's Graph Search, its new and powerful way of searching the social network for all manner of information, has drawn a lot of attention since its January unveiling. Some have praised its innovation; others have wondered openly whether its search abilities will end up threatening Google and LinkedIn. Still more have questioned what it all means for users' privacy—always a touchy subject in conjunction with Facebook. The social network previously revealed how it's adjusting its hardware infrastructure to deal with the spike in traffic that will come from interactions with Graph Search (short answer: the Disaggregated Rack, which will break up hardware resources and scale them independently of one another). Now, in a new blog posting, it's offering a bit more with regard to the software side of things, and how the company repurposed an existing system to solve Graph Search's enormous engineering challenge. Bottom line: Facebook's engineers and executives finally decided on Unicorn, an inverted-index system they'd had in development for quite some time."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7009-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7009_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:08:57">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/10/01/06/2155218/fake-bill-gates-message-dupes-top-tools</link><title>Fake "Bill Gates" Message Dupes Top Tools</title><description>yahoi writes with this excerpt from Dark Reading that might raise sysadmins' eyebrows about email security, in particular given the big names involved: "A researcher who conducted a successful spear-phishing experiment with a phony LinkedIn invitation from 'Bill Gates' is about to reveal the email products and services that failed to filter the spoofed message — and that list includes Microsoft Outlook 2007, Microsoft Exchange, Outlook Express, and Cisco IronPort. ... The experiment was aimed at measuring the effectiveness of email security controls in several major products and services. And the simplicity and success of the test demonstrated just how powerful social engineering can be and what little technology can actually do about it, security experts say."</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>