<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7024">reinforcement learning</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:50:46" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7024-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7024_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:50:47">http://news.slashdot.org/story/12/06/29/2355219/a-program-learns-oriental-ink-painting</link><title>A Program Learns Oriental Ink Painting</title><description>mikejuk writes about a neat use of machine learning. From the article: "Using reinforcement learning to make a computer paint like an oriental Sumi-e artist isn't just a matter of shouting 'well done' — and yet, when you look at the results, that's what you want to do. ... Three researchers at the Tokyo Institute of Technology have attempted to teach a computer how to do it [paint] using standard reinforcement learning. When the program used the brush to create a smooth stroke, it was rewarded. After it had learned to use the brush, it was set to rendering some photos and the results look very good."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7024-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7024_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:55:28">http://developers.slashdot.org/story/10/01/28/0052202/can-curiosity-be-programmed</link><title>Can Curiosity Be Programmed?</title><description>destinyland writes "AI researcher Jurgen Schmidhuber says his main scientific ambition 'is to build an optimal scientist, then retire.' The Cognitive Robotics professor has worked on problems including artificial ants and even robots that are taught how to tie shoelaces using reinforcement learning, but he believes algorithms can be written that allow the programming of curiosity itself. 'Curiosity is the desire to create or discover more non-random, non-arbitrary, regular data that is novel and surprising...' He's already created art using algorithmic information theory, and can describe the simple algorithmic principle that underlies subjective beauty, creativity, and curiosity itself. And he ultimately addresses the possibility that the entire Universe, including everyone in it, is in principle computable by a completely deterministic computer program."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7024-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7024_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:56:49">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/82767</link><title>PowerPoint Bad For Learning</title><description>cute-boy writes "This article in the Sydney Morning Herald reporting on research done at The University of NSW suggests the use of Microsoft PowerPoint (and similar products) in lectures and meetings actually makes it harder to absorb facts, rather than being a reinforcement of key points."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7024-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7024_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:00:11">http://developers.slashdot.org/story/04/02/10/1610229/practical-c</link><title>Practical C++</title><description>jsight writes with his review of Rob McGregor's Practical C++, published by QUE. He writes "Some books attempt to do one thing really well, and others attempt a little of everything. This book is clearly an example of the latter, in full force. Weighing in at a hefty 900 pages, you would expect this book to be crammed with chapters and details on every aspect of the STL and basic C++. In the following review, I am going to cover where it succeeds in doing this, and where it fails." (This book has been out for a few years; what books would make more sense today for a C++ learner's library?)</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>