<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7031">Thomas test</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:06:59" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7031-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7031_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:07:02">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/194559</link><title>CubeSat Launch Visible Around U.S. East Coast Tonight</title><description>Hugh Pickens DOT Com writes "Brad Lendon reports at CNN that 29 satellites, the most ever launched at one time, will be aboard a single Minotaur I rocket scheduled to lift off from NASA's Wallops Flight Facility in Virginia Tuesday night at 7:30 pm. The main payload will be the Air Force's Space Test Program Satellite-3, plus 28 tiny satellites called CubeSats about 4 inches on each side, weighing about 3 pounds and with a volume of about a quart. The cubesats will include Ho`oponopono-2 from the University of Hawaii to continue a long-existing radar calibration service for the 80 plus C-band radar tracking stations distributed around the world. It will also have CAPE-2 from the Cajun Advanced Picosatellite Experiment, to give students at the University of Louisiana at Lafayette the opportunity to research, design, develop, and maintain a low earth orbiting satellite, and SwampSat from the University of Florida to advance the TRL (Technology Readiness Level) of CMGs (Control Moment Gyroscopes) appropriate for smallsats. Among the CubeSats is the TJ3Sat, the first satellite made by high-schoolers to go into space, built by the students of Thomas Jefferson High School for Science and Technology in Alexandria, Virginia. It will give students and other amateur radio users the opportunity to send and receive data from the satellite. Approved text strings will be transmitted to the satellite, and the resulting voice interpretation will be relayed back to Earth over an amateur radio frequency using the onboard Stensat radio. Orbital says the 29 satellites should achieve orbit in a little less than 12½ minutes after the rocket ignites. NASA says the launch may be visible from northern Florida to southern Canada and as far west as Indiana. Live coverage of the launch is available via UStream beginning at 6:30 p.m. EST on launch day."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7031-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7031_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:08:43">http://yro.slashdot.org/story/13/06/13/1550225/supreme-court-no-patents-for-natural-dna-sequences</link><title>Supreme Court: No Patents For Natural DNA Sequences</title><description>ColdWetDog writes "The ongoing story of Myriad Genetics versus the rest of the world has come to an end. In a 9-0 decision, the US Supreme Court has decided that human genes cannot be patented. From a brief Bloomberg article: 'Writing for the court, Justice Clarence Thomas said isolated DNA is a "product of nature and not patent eligible merely because it has been isolated." At the same time, Thomas said synthetic molecules known as complementary DNA, or cDNA, can be patented because they require a significant amount of human manipulation to create.' Seems perfectly sane. Raw genes, the ones you find in nature are, wait for it — natural. Other bits of manipulated DNA / RNA / protein which take skill and time to create are potentially patentable. Oddly, Myriad Genetics stock actually rose on that information." Adds reader the eric conspiracy: "The result for Myriad is that they still have protection for their test, however the decision also allows researchers to work with the DNA sequences that are predecessors to the cDNA used in the test." Here's an AP report on the ruling, as carried by the Washington Post.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7031-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7031_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:10:37">http://science.slashdot.org/story/11/09/16/2010244/purdue-students-building-moon-lander-rocket</link><title>Purdue Students Building Moon Lander Rocket</title><description>tekgoblin sends words that a team of students at Purdue University are working on a project to build a rocket engine that could be used on a future Moon lander. Quoting: "Graduate students Thomas Feldman and Andrew Rettenmaier are part of a team developing a thrust chamber for NASA's Project Morpheus, which includes research to develop new technologies for future trips to the moon, Mars or asteroids. The rocket must meet stringent design and performance specifications related to factors including efficiency, size and weight limits, thrust and the ability to dynamically throttle the rocket from 1,300-4,200 pounds of thrust, Feldman said. ... A development test chamber has been designed and is ready for testing. This heavily instrumented chamber is far bulkier than the eventual flight chamber, and data from upcoming tests will be used to refine the flight engine's design."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7031-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7031_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:13:33">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/155632</link><title>Judge Blasts Prosecution of Alleged NSA Leaker</title><description>Hugh Pickens writes "The Washington Post reports that Judge Richard D. Bennett harshly criticized US prosecutor William M. Welch III for his treatment of a former spy agency official Thomas Drake, who was accused of leaking classified material. Bennett called the delays in the now-closed case 'unconscionable' and compared it to British tyranny in the colonial era. In 2007, FBI agents raided Drake's house, but it took over two years for officials to indict him. 'And then, over a year later, on the eve of trial, in June of 2011, the government says, "Whoops, we dropped the whole case,"' Bennett said. Drake was given a mild penalty for pleading guilty to the misdemeanor charge of exceeding authorized use of a computer: a year's probation and 240 hours of community service while all 10 felony counts were dropped. 'That's four years of hell that a citizen goes through,' Bennett said. 'It was not proper. It doesn't pass the smell test.' In contrast with his tough words for Welch, Bennett singled out for praise Drake's public defenders, James Wyda and Deborah L. Boardman, saying their work on behalf of Drake was 'at the highest level of professionalism.' Judge Welch said the matter was now closed and addressed Drake: 'I wish you the best of luck in the rest of your life.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7031-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7031_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:17:05">http://games.slashdot.org/story/11/07/01/1536255/court-on-video-games-less-cleavage-more-carnage</link><title>Court on Video Games: Less Cleavage, More Carnage</title><description>On Monday we discussed news of a Supreme Court ruling which held that violent video games deserved free speech protection under the First Amendment. Now, frequent Slashdot contributor Bennett Haselton writes with this followup that questions the Court's consistency in such matters. "I'm glad the Supreme Court struck down the California law against selling violent video games to minors, but reading over the decision, I had the odd feeling that the arguments by the dissenters made more sense than the majority — mainly because of the hypocrisy of continuing to ban sexuality while giving violence a pass." Read on for the rest of Bennett's thoughts.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7031-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7031_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:20:33">http://yro.slashdot.org/story/10/03/30/2352256/new-litigation-targets-20000-bittorrent-using-downloaders</link><title>New Litigation Targets 20,000 BitTorrent-Using Downloaders</title><description>Hugh Pickens writes "The Hollywood Reporter reports that more than 20,000 individual movie torrent downloaders have been sued in the past few weeks in Washington, DC, federal court for copyright infringement, and another lawsuit targeting 30,000 more torrent downloaders on five more films is forthcoming in what could be a test run that opens up the floodgates to massive litigation against the millions of individuals who use BitTorrent to download movies. The US Copyright Group, a company owned by intellectual property lawyers, is using a new proprietary technology by German-based Guardaley IT that allows for real-time monitoring of movie downloads on torrents. According to Thomas Dunlap, a lawyer at the firm, the program captures IP addresses based on the time stamp that a download has occurred and then checks against a spreadsheet to make sure the downloading content is the copyright protected film and not a misnamed film or trailer. 'We're creating a revenue stream and monetizing the equivalent of an alternative distribution channel,' says Jeffrey Weaver, another lawyer at the firm."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7031-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7031_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:22:05">http://books.slashdot.org/story/10/03/22/146235/metaprogramming-ruby</link><title>Metaprogramming Ruby</title><description>scottl writes "Metaprogramming Ruby is the first book to give an in-depth and readable explanation of how dynamic programming works in Ruby. It is both readable and accurate and will be a valuable resource to intermediate and probably advanced Ruby programmers for some time to come." Keep reading for the rest of scottl's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7031-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7031_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:23:57">http://idle.slashdot.org/story/09/12/30/1529232/test-new-diarrhea-drug-and-get-a-free-trip-to-mexico</link><title>Test New Diarrhea Drug and Get a Free Trip to Mexico</title><description>A pharmaceutical company is offering a free trip to Mexico to anyone willing to test their new diarrhea drug. Almost 1000 volunteers will be able to have some fun in the sun on Intercell's dime as long as they wear a patch that delivers the new drug, and they agree to regular testing should they fall ill. Nigel Thomas, clinical director of Intercell, said: "We are looking for people who have already planned to go to Mexico or Guatemala and think this would add another interesting aspect. We cover their expenses – flights and accommodation – nothing beyond that. It is almost like going on a package holiday. They will be met by a concierge who will take them to their hotel and arrange for them to give their first blood sample within 48 hours."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7031-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7031_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:26:15">http://features.slashdot.org/story/08/10/08/1345216/spammer-perjury-is-worth-prosecuting</link><title>Spammer Perjury is Worth Prosecuting</title><description>Slashdot regular Bennett Haselton summarizes his essay by saying "Spammers really do lie more often under oath than other parties in court (surprise). Judges and prosecutors could promote respect for the law by cracking down on it, and maybe make a dent in spam in the process." Read on to learn of his experiences with (shocking!) spammers who lie in court.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7031-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7031_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:26:53">http://ask.slashdot.org/story/08/08/25/1912205/should-companies-share-criminal-blame-in-id-theft</link><title>Should Companies Share Criminal Blame In ID Theft?</title><description>snydeq writes "Deep End's Paul Venezia criticizes the lack of criminal charges for corporate negligence in data breaches in the wake of last week's Best Western breach, which exposed the personal data of 8 million customers. 'The responsibilities attached to retaining sensitive personal identity information should include criminal charges against the company responsible for a leak, in addition to the party that receives the information,' Venezia writes. 'Until the penalties for giving away sensitive information in this manner include heavy fines and possibly even jail time for those responsible for securing that information, we'll see this problem occur again and again.' As data security lawyer Thomas J. Smedinghoff writes, data security law is already shifting the blame for data breaches onto IT, thanks to an emerging framework of complex regulations that could result in grave legal consequences should your organization suffer a breach. To date, however, IT's duty to provide security and its duty to disclose data breaches does not include criminal prosecution. Yet, with much of the data security framework being shaped by 'IT negligence' court cases over 'reasonable' security, that could very well be put to the test some day in court." It's a slippery slope to be sure, but where should the buck stop?</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>