<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7033">Porto</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:32:52" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7033-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7033_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:32:53">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/200385</link><title>To Reduce the Health Risk of Barbecuing Meat, Just Add Beer</title><description>PolygamousRanchKid (1290638) writes "Grilling meat gives it great flavour. This taste, though, comes at a price, since the process creates molecules called polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons (PAHs) which damage DNA and thus increase the eater's chances of developing colon cancer. But a group of researchers led by Isabel Ferreira of the University of Porto, in Portugal, think they have found a way around the problem. When barbecuing meat, they suggest, you should add beer. The PAHs created by grilling form from molecules called free radicals which, in turn, form from fat and protein in the intense heat of this type of cooking. One way of stopping PAH-formation, then, might be to apply chemicals called antioxidants that mop up free radicals. And beer is rich in these, in the shape of melanoidins, which form when barley is roasted." (The paper on which this report is based, sadly paywalled.)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7033-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7033_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:34:33">http://news.slashdot.org/story/13/09/14/184217/open-source-open-world</link><title>Open Source, Open World</title><description>New submitter Ian Grant writes "This article takes a brief look at open source software in Brazil and how it's transforming tech use in South America: Bringing free software to Brazil, however, is not just a matter of copying North American practices. The idea of free software has also been substantially transformed through contact with Brazilian politics. In the United States, the open source software community has long had libertarian leanings, which have only strengthened over time. The core tenet of free software, after all, is giving the users freedom to do what they want. ... And when free software was finally embraced by business, many members of the movement welcomed it as a validation of their ideas. The business-friendly side of free software is easily visible in Brazil, too. Many Brazilian companies, for example, use Linux. At the forum in Porto Alegre, commercial free software was well represented by large foreign companies, many of which appeared to be there primarily for recruiting. Yet the forum also showcased another side of Brazil’s place in the world of free software — a key meeting place of free software and leftist politics. "</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7033-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7033_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:37:25">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/67790</link><title>Stallman Selling Autographs</title><description>UltimaGuy writes "Sports stars, musicians, and other celebrities have been charging for autographs for years, but who would have thought Richard Stallman would be doing the same? Is this just for fun, or a clever, highly effective protest? Hackers, geeks and nerds gathered together at the 7th FISL - Internacional Free Software Forum, in Porto Alegre (Brazil) last week, were astounded when they got word that Richard Stallman, the founding father of the Free Software Foundation and creator of the GPL, was charging R$ 10 (about US$ 3) for an autograph and R$ 5 (less than US$ 2) to get his picture taken by free software enthusiasts at the event floor."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7033-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7033_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:38:14">http://slashdot.org/story/05/02/01/0037252/open-source-streaming-translations-in-porto-alegre</link><title>Open-Source Streaming Translations in Porto Alegre</title><description>Roland Piquepaille writes "The World Social Forum (WSF) (choose your language on the site), which ends today in Porto Alegre, Brazil, has less money to spend on computing than the World Economic Forum (WEF) held in Davos, Switzerland. But at both events, many different languages were spoken, meaning that simultaneous translations were an absolute necessity. If the WEF can afford professional translators and costly computers, in Porto Alegre, translators are volunteers, and the software to distribute the translations is open-source. The NIFT (Nomad Interpretation Free Tool) was already used for the 4th WSF held last year in Mumbai, India. The free software, which runs on a simple PC, collects and digitizes the translations from the interpreters before broadcasting them to a variety of devices. In fact, the technically-advanced NIFT allows for real-time streaming over the Internet of speeches in several different languages. This overview contains many links, references and illustrations about the NIFT project."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7033-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7033_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:42:00">http://developers.slashdot.org/story/05/01/25/2338214/international-free-software-forum-call-for-papers</link><title>International Free Software Forum Call For Papers</title><description>Pablo Lorenzzoni writes "On January 10th, the 6th International Free Software Forum - fisl6.0 [more info] issued a public call for papers. The conference will be held from June 1st to June 4th in Porto Alegre, a southern Brazilian capital already known by the World Social Forum. Proposals due on February 28th."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7033-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7033_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:42:49">http://developers.slashdot.org/story/04/02/04/1515245/international-free-software-forum-call-for-papers</link><title>International Free Software Forum Call For Papers</title><description>Anonymous Coward writes "On February 2nd, the 5th International Free Software Forum [more info] issued a Call For Papers to the public. Proposals due on March 7th, and no marketing lectures are allowed. The conference will be held from June 2nd to June 5th in Porto Alegre, a southern Brazilian capital already known by the World Social Forum."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7033-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7033_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:45:52">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/02/11/30/1738214/immobile-robots</link><title>Immobile Robots</title><description>Roland Piquepaille writes "Wade Roush wrote a long and well-documented article for the Technology Review about this new concept, the immobot, short for "immobile robot." He gives different industrial examples, from NASA to the water utility in Porto Alegre, and from Toyota cars to some new Xerox photocopiers. And he looks at the programming model behind the immobots. No "heuristic" programs here, but model-based programs instead. Check this column for details." The original article has more information.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7033-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7033_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:48:56">http://slashdot.org/story/02/02/05/1930246/rms-asks-miguel-to-explain-himself</link><title>RMS Asks Miguel to Explain Himself</title><description>phaze3000 writes "RMS, responding to questions from the audience at the World Social Forum in Porto Alegre, Brazil last week, has asked Miguel de Icaza to explain himself to the Free software community about comments made last week that Gnome should be based on .NET in the future. More details at Brazillian site Hotbits and in The Register." I find this amusing.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>