<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7044">song of ice and fire</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:01:11" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7044-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7044_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:01:12">http://news.slashdot.org/story/11/03/04/179210/george-rr-martin-finishes-a-dance-with-dragons</link><title>George RR Martin Finishes A Dance With Dragons</title><description>Lil'wombat writes "George RR Martin has completed his long awaited conclusion to the A Song of Ice and Fire series. A Dance with Dragons will be published on July 12, 2011. Let the celebrations begin! And everyone was worried that he was going to pull a Jordan."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7044-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7044_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:01:46">http://games.slashdot.org/story/09/05/14/050259/video-game-adaptation-in-the-works-for-a-song-of-fire-and-ice</link><title>Video Game Adaptation In the Works For A Song of Fire and Ice</title><description>On Wednesday, French game development studio Cyanide announced that they will be working with George R. R. Martin to bring his popular fantasy series, A Song of Fire and Ice, to the realm of video games. The press release implies that there will be more than one game, and the games will come out for PCs and "next-gen consoles." Apparently an HBO television series is in the works as well, in addition to board and card games related to the books.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7044-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7044_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:05:24">http://idle.slashdot.org/story/08/08/18/1320202/bottom-of-the-barrel-book-reviews-the-lost-blogs</link><title>Bottom of the Barrel Book Reviews — The Lost Blogs</title><description>We get a lot of books for review here at Slashdot. Most are sent out to users on our reviewer list within a few weeks. Others become part of an impressive wall of books on my desk before they find a home. There are a choice few however that are doomed to never see the inside of a Fedex box. This is mostly due to the complete and utter stupidity or absurdness of their subject matter. I've decided to give these failed intellectual endeavors a chance and explore just how big a waste of time a book can be. We start scraping the bottom of the barrel with a little number written by Paul Davidson called, The Lost Blogs. Read below to find out just how bad it got.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>