<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7046">tuning fork</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:10:49" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7046-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7046_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:10:50">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/13/07/01/1943218/microscopic-tuning-forks-help-determine-effectiveness-of-antibiotics</link><title>Microscopic "Tuning Forks" Help Determine Effectiveness of Antibiotics</title><description>sciencehabit writes "A patient admitted to a hospital with a serious bacterial infection may have only a few hours to live. Figuring out which antibiotic to administer, however, can take days. Doctors must grow the microbes in the presence of the drugs and see whether they reproduce. Rush the process, and they risk prescribing ineffective antibiotics, exposing the patient to unnecessary side effects, and spreading antibiotic resistance. Now, researchers have developed a microscopic 'tuning fork' that detects tiny vibrations in bacteria. The device might one day allow physicians to tell the difference between live and dead microbes—and enable them to recognize effective and ineffective antibiotics within minutes."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7046-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7046_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:12:15">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/109165</link><title>Setbacks Cast Doubt On NASA's Ares Project</title><description>stoolpigeon writes with this excerpt from an Orlando Sentinel article about the Ares program, which paints a bleak picture of the program's future: "Bit by bit, the new rocket ship that is supposed to blast America into the second Space Age and return astronauts to the moon appears to be coming undone. First was the discovery that it lacked sufficient power to lift astronauts in a state-of-the-art capsule into orbit. Then engineers found out that it might vibrate like a giant tuning fork, shaking its crew to death. Now, in the latest setback to the Ares I, computer models show the ship could crash into its launch tower during liftoff. "</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7046-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7046_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:16:44">http://science.slashdot.org/story/08/08/06/1521256/the-diy-dialysis-machine</link><title>The DIY Dialysis Machine</title><description>Millie Kelly was born with a condition that required an immediate operation. During this operation her kidneys started to fail and since she was too small for dialysis machines, doctors told her parents that she was unlikely to live. Luckily for Millie, Dr. Malcolm Coulthard and a colleague tried to build a much smaller kidney machine on their own and they were successful. Her mother said, "It was a green metal box with a few paint marks on it with quite a few wires coming out of it into my daughter - it didn't look like a normal NHS one." The girl was hooked up to the machine over a seven day period to allow her kidneys to recover. Two years later, her mother Rebecca says she is "fit as a fiddle." You should see what Dr. Coulthard can build using a postage stamp, a tuning fork, a lawn chair and a jellyfish.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7046-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7046_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:17:44">http://news.slashdot.org/story/04/05/24/0623247/vorbis-and-musepack-win-128kbps-multiformat-test</link><title>Vorbis And Musepack Win 128kbps Multiformat Test</title><description>technology is sexy writes "After 11 days of collecting results Roberto Amorim today announced the results of his 2nd Multi-Format listening test: Vorbis fork AoTuV scored the highest and ranks as the winner together with open source contender Musepack closely followed by Apple's AAC implementation and LAME MP3, which improved markably since last year thanks to further tunings of its VBR model done by Gabriel Bouvigne. Sony's ATRAC3 format ranks last after WMA on the third place. The suprising success of AoTuV (compared to last year's performance of Xiph.org's reference implementation) shows the potential of Vorbis and possible room for further tuning and improvments. Take a look at the detailed results and their discussion at Hydrogenaudio.org."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7046-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7046_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:21:44">http://news.slashdot.org/story/03/05/29/1546209/intrusion-detection-with-snort</link><title>Intrusion Detection with Snort</title><description>Eric Stats writes: "At one point in the not so distant past, Intrusion Detection Systems (IDSs) were network security applications reserved for Fortune 500 companies with enough IT budget to fork up the Big Dollar, or hard core packetheads willing to grep through tcpdump or shadow output. Over the past few years, a new pig on the block, Snort, has put that notion to rest. Instead of having to spring for hundreds of thousands of dollars for a feature-rich, state-of-the-art, IDS; open source fans now have an IDS that meets and beats most of the performance benchmarks and features of commercial, closed source IDSs. Jack Koziol's new book, Intrusion Detection with Snort, presents a comprehensive guide that those either novice to, or richly experienced with, the field of Intrusion Detection can use to get up to speed quickly on Snort." Read on for Eric's review.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>