<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7051">dinosaur names</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:27:39" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7051-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7051_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:27:40">http://books.slashdot.org/story/13/01/09/160246/book-review-the-nature-of-code</link><title>Book Review: The Nature of Code</title><description>eldavojohn writes "I kickstarted a project undertaken by Daniel Shiffman to write a book on what (at the time) seemed to be a very large knowledge space. What resulted is a good book (amazing by CC-BY-NC standards) available in both PDF and HTML versions. In addition to the book he maintains the source code for creating the book and of course the book examples. The Nature of Code starts off swimmingly but remains front heavy with a mere thirty five pages devoted to the final chapter on neural networks. This is an excellent book for Java and Processing developers that want to break into simulation and modeling of well, anything. It probably isn't a must-have title for very seasoned developers (unless you've never done simulation and modeling) but at zero cost why not?" Read below for the rest of eldavojohn's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7051-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7051_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:29:07">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/27323</link><title>Digital SFX Wizard Answers Slashdot Questions</title><description>Here are 10+ plus answers to Slashdot questions from motion picture digital effects expert Thad Beier. He chose the additional questions himself. (Yes, he's on Slashdot almost every day; we asked him to do the interview after reading many intelligent comments he's posted.) Anyway, there's some fine insight into the intersection of moviemaking, graphic arts, and computer science here, brought to you by an award-winning member of the film industry who just happens to be a fellow Slashdot reader.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>