<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7067">used kindle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:20:13" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7067-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7067_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:20:16">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/200269</link><title>Amazon's Fire TV: Is It Worth Game Developers' Time?</title><description>Nerval's Lobster (2598977) writes "Amazon is serious about conquering the living room: the online retailer has launched Fire TV, a set-top box that not only allows viewers to stream content, but also play games. That streaming-and-gaming capability makes Amazon a threat to Apple, which rumors suggest is hard at work on an Apple TV capable of doing the same things. In addition, Fire TV puts the screws to other streaming hardware, including Roku and Google's Chromecast, as well as smaller game consoles such as Ouya (a $99, Android-based device). Much of Amazon's competitive muscle comes from its willingness to sell hardware for cheap (the Fire TV retails for $99) on the expectation that owners will use it to stream and download digital content from Amazon, including television shows and apps. Those developers who've developed Android games have an advantage when it comes to migrating software to Amazon's new platform. "Porting You Don't Know Jack was really like developing for Android, with the exception of the store and the new controller library," Jackbox Games Designer/Director Steve Heinrich told Gamasutra after the Fire TV announcement. "The store itself is the same as the Kindle version, which we've used many times now, and the way the controller works is very close to what we did for Ouya." While Fire TV could represent yet another opportunity for game developers looking to make a buck, it also raises a pressing question: with so many platforms out there (iOS, PC, etc.), how's an indie developer or smaller firm supposed to allocate time and resources to best advantage?"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7067-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7067_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:22:21">http://news.slashdot.org/story/14/02/19/2342246/amazon-coins-and-how-the-definition-of-crypto-currency-is-getting-too-loose</link><title>Amazon Coins and How the Definition of 'Crypto-Currency' Is Getting Too Loose</title><description>Nerval's Lobster writes "Amazon has expanded support for its Amazon Coins from Kindle Fire tablets to Google Android mobile devices.In its press release, Amazon positioned its e-currency as the ultimate in convenience for customers who don't want their credit-card statements riddled with lots of micro-purchases from Amazon's App Store. Expanding the currency's reach is also a potential win for Amazon, which wants to create an end-to-end ecosystem for app developers. But Amazon Coins' existence could alienate the same demographic that made Bitcoin and other crypto-currencies such a hit. The company tethers the Coins to a user identity, and likely keeps significant records on its crypto-currency ecosystem: who buys what when. That concept is anathema to those online denizens who embraced Bitcoin as a way to make purchases without needing to reveal a real-world identity, or deal with a currency tethered to a central repository; genuine crypto-currency can be used to purchase pretty much anything from a purveyor willing to take it, including—in the case of Silk Road and other online bazaars—drugs and weapons. Indeed, Amazon Coins has more to do with a corporate 'currency' like the now-defunct Microsoft Points than an actual crypto-currency like Bitcoin. But that hasn't stopped some people from getting confused about it."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7067-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7067_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:24:43">http://ask.slashdot.org/story/14/02/15/0424242/ask-slashdot-e-ink-reader-for-academic-papers</link><title>Ask Slashdot: E-ink Reader For Academic Papers?</title><description>Albanach writes "Recently, I purchased an e-ink Kindle. I like real paper books, but I'm reading lots of academic papers. The Kindle is a nice way to carry and read them, and I went through several documents, highlighting important passages. Now I learn that there is no supported way to actually get a highlighted personal document back off of the Kindle with the highlights intact. I don't need lectures about DRM, proprietary software or anything else along those lines — there are other things the Kindle can and will be used for. What I would like to know is whether there's another e-ink reader that does let you add your own documents, then highlight them and export the altered document. Or does someone know of a way to achieve this using the Kindle itself?"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7067-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7067_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:26:36">http://books.slashdot.org/story/13/10/31/1637205/book-review-stay-awhile-and-listen</link><title>Book Review: Stay Awhile and Listen</title><description>Many of today's adult video gamers grew up with a gaming industry that was still trying to figure itself out. In the early-to-mid 1990s, most of the gaming genres we're familiar with today were still indistinct, half-formed concepts waiting for that one game necessary to define them. Thus, many players sat up and took notice when a relatively unknown company named Blizzard managed to exemplify not one, but two separate types of game in quick succession. Warcraft: Orcs and Humans put real-time strategy on the map, and Diablo set the standard for action RPGs. The two games immediately elevated Blizzard to the top of the industry, and many gamers wondered how one studio could put out two games like these so quickly. As it turns out, it wasn't one studio; it was a blending of two very different but extremely creative groups who had a passion for making video games. In Stay Awhile and Listen, author David Craddock lays out the history of the two groups, from how they first got into the gaming business to their eventual success launching now-legendary games. Read on for our review of the book.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7067-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7067_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:28:18">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/13/09/07/1432218/austrian-professor-creates-kindle-e-book-copier-with-lego-mindstorms</link><title>Austrian Professor Creates Kindle E-Book Copier With Lego Mindstorms</title><description>An anonymous reader writes "Using a Lego Mindstorms set, a Mac, and optical character recognition, Austrian professor Peter Purgathofer created a makeshift ebook copier. From the article: 'It's sort of a combination of high tech meets low. The scanning is done by way of the Mac's iSight camera. The Mindstorms set does two things: Hits the page-advance button on the Kindle (it appears to be an older model, like the one in the picture above), then mashes the space bar on the Mac, causing it to take a picture.' Purgathofer calls the creation a 'reflection on the loss of long established rights.' Check out the Vimeo video for a demonstration."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7067-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7067_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:30:43">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/13/03/23/044227/ibm-dipping-chips-in-ionic-liquid-to-save-power</link><title>IBM Dipping Chips In 'Ionic Liquid' To Save Power</title><description>Nerval's Lobster writes "IBM announced this week that it has developed a way to manufacture both logic and memory that relies on a small drop of 'ionic liquid' to flip oxides back and forth between an insulating and conductive state without the need to constantly draw power. In theory, that means both memory and logic built using those techniques could dramatically save power. IBM described the advance in the journal Science, and also published a summary of its results to its Website. The central idea is to eliminate as much power as possible as it moves through a semiconductor. IBM's solution is to use a bit of 'ionic liquid' to flip the state. IBM researchers applied a positively charged ionic liquid electrolyte to an insulating oxide material — vanadium dioxide — and successfully converted the material to a metallic state. The material held its metallic state until a negatively charged ionic liquid electrolyte was applied in order to convert it back to its original, insulating state. A loose analogy would be to compare IBM's technology to the sort of electronic ink used in the black-and-white versions of the Kindle and other e-readers. There, an electrical charge can be applied to the tiny microcapsules that contain the 'ink,' hiding or displaying them to render a page of text. Like IBM's solution, the e-ink doesn't require a constant charge; power only needs to be applied to re-render or 'flip' the page. In any event, IBM's technique could conceivably be applied to both mobile devices as well as power-hungry data centers."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7067-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7067_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:34:20">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/183077</link><title>U.S. ISBN Monopoly Denies Threat From Digital Self-Publishing</title><description>Ian Lamont writes "The Economist writes that self-publishing threatens the existence of the International Standard Book Number (ISBN) regimen, which is used to track and distribute printed books. Self-publishing of e-books has experienced triple-digit growth in recent years, and the most popular self-publishing platforms such as Amazon's Kindle Direct Publishing don't require ISBNs (Amazon assigns its own reference number to these titles). But Bowker, the sole distributor of ISBNs in the United States, sees an opportunity in self-publishing. The packages for independent authors are very expensive — Bowker charges $125 for a single ISBN, and $250 for ten. It also upsells other expensive services to new and naive authors, including $25 barcodes and a social widget that costs $120 for the first year. Laura Dawson, the product manager for identifiers at Bowker, insists that ISBNs are relevant and won't be replaced anytime soon: 'Given how hard it is to migrate database platforms and change standards, I wouldn't expect to replace the ISBN, simply because it is also an EAN, which is an ISO standard that forms the backbone of global trade of both physical and digital items. There are a lot of middlemen, even in self-publishing. They require standards in order to communicate with one another.'" It seems like a lot of programs/services just use ASINs (despite being controlled by a single private entity), probably indicating some deficiency with the current centralized registration regime. Back in 2005, Jimmy Wales suggested we needed something (culturally) similar to wikipedia for product identifiers. The O'Reilly interview indicates that the folks issuing ISBNs think DOIs are DOA too.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7067-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7067_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:37:41">http://features.slashdot.org/story/13/02/20/1657209/derek-khanna-answers-your-questions</link><title>Derek Khanna Answers Your Questions</title><description>Last week you had a chance to ask former Republican staffer Derek Khanna about his well publicized firing, copyright law, and the state of the government. Read below to see his answers to your questions.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7067-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7067_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:42:12">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/12/11/06/1440225/ipad-mini-costs-24-more-to-make-than-kindle-fire-hd</link><title>iPad Mini Costs $24 More To Make Than Kindle Fire HD</title><description>sweetpea86 writes "... but retails for $130 more. Teardowns of the Apple iPad Mini and the Amazon Kindle Fire HD have revealed that the two devices cost almost the same amount to manufacture, despite the retail prices being significantly different. Andrew Rassweiler, senior principal analyst of teardown services for IHS iSuppli, explains that Apple is sticking to the premium brand strategy it has always used for its media tablet and smartphone products, whereas Amazon is banking on content."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7067-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7067_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:47:18">http://news.slashdot.org/story/12/11/05/0122238/bruce-perens-answers-your-questions</link><title>Bruce Perens Answers Your Questions</title><description>A while ago you had the chance to ask Bruce Perens about how open source has changed in the past 15 years, what's happening now, and what's to come. Bruce has been busy traveling, but he's found some free time and sent in his answers. Read below to see what he has to say.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>