<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7070">compact flash memory card</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:53:43" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7070-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7070_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:53:45">http://slashdot.org/story/06/07/22/1246202/a-memory-card-torture-test</link><title>A Memory Card Torture Test</title><description>An anonymous reader writes "Would you buy a Ferrari and put regular gas into it? I don't think so. So why are most of us buying expensive digital cameras and using cheap memory cards? If you want to find out how much better a high speed memory card is, check out this group test of high capacity compact flash and SD cards."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7070-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7070_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:58:02">http://linux.slashdot.org/story/04/08/07/1243243/worlds-first-linux-computer-in-a-cf-card</link><title>World's First Linux Computer In A CF Card</title><description>An anonymous reader writes "LinuxDevices reports on the world's first Linux computer to fit inside a CompactFlash card. The 'Compact Flash Computer' (CFC) can be mixed and matched with third-party CF cards to instantly create minuscule Linux systems based entirely on CF cards. A wide variety of third-party CF peripheral cards can be used with the CFC, including RS232/485, Ethernet, Bluetooth, USB, 802.11, GSM, GPRS, GPS, and more. A combination power supply / bus expander module on a separate CF card, as well as a tiny 8-slot CF card backplane, are available as options." An anonymous reader adds "The card is based on a Freescale MPC5272 system-on-chip processor and contains 32MB of SDRAM and 8MB of Flash memory, and it comes with a uClinux based operating system and GNU development/debug tools."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7070-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7070_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:01:02">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/04/06/17/1621208/3d-linux-laptop-available</link><title>3D Linux Laptop Available</title><description>Anonymous Writer writes "EmperorLinux is distributing the Sharp Actius RD3D autostereo laptop with Linux pre-installed, dubbing it the 'Molecule'. Almost all the hardware features can be utilised under Linux; the autostereo 3D display (most importantly), CD-RW/DVD-RW combo drive, Ethernet port, audio hardware, PC Card slot, 4 USB 2.0 ports, FireWire port, Sony Memory Stick slot, Compact Flash slot, SD slot, and internal floppy dive. The only built-in feature unsupported is the internal 56 Kbps modem, however a supported 56 kbps PC Card modem is available as well as a WiFi PC Card."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7070-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7070_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:02:11">http://news.slashdot.org/story/03/01/16/021202/ferroelectric-storage-density-tops-20kdvdscubit2</link><title>Ferroelectric Storage Density Tops 20KDVDs/Cubit^2</title><description>DeAshcroft writes "As reported in Technology Research News, researchers from Tohoku University, the Japanese National Institute for Materials Science, and Pioneer Corporation have demonstrated a prototype ferroelectric (as opposed to ferromagnetic) storage mechanism with density of 1.5 trillion dots per square inch. No word on why Japanese researchers are using square inches, but the new storage benchmark is the DVD. This is 47 DVD's in a square inch, or over 20KiloDVD's per square cubit. Original paper appeared in the Applied Physics Letters."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7070-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7070_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:05:14">http://news.slashdot.org/story/02/01/20/0543250/review-nex-ii-cf-mp3-player</link><title>Review: Nex II CF MP3 Player</title><description>Music listener and Slashdot author chrisd has prepared a review of the new Nex II CF based mp3 player from Hong Kong based Frontier Labs. He declares it the best MP3 player he's owned, so read the whole review if you'd like to learn more.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>