<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7077">django django</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:14:11" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7077-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7077_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:14:13">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/196259</link><title>The Hobbit and Game of Thrones Top Most Pirated Lists of 2013</title><description>DavidGilbert99 writes "Fantasy fans are clearly among the most prevalent downloaders of pirated material if the 2013 lists of most pirated films and TV shows is anything to go by. The Hobbit beat Django Unchained and Fast and Furious 6 while on TV, Game of Thrones saw off competition from Breaking Bad and The Walking Dead as the most pirated TV show. While this is clearly losing money for both industries, the US box office doesn't seem to be suffering too much as it is about to record its best year ever."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7077-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7077_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:16:54">http://news.slashdot.org/story/13/03/02/1345249/propublicas-guide-to-news-app-tech</link><title>ProPublica's Guide To News App Tech</title><description>dstates writes "ProPublica, the award winning public interest journalism group and frequently cited Slashdot source, has published an interesting guide to app technology for journalism and a set of data and style guides. Journalism presents unique challenges with potentially enormous but highly variable site traffic, the need to serve a wide variety of information, and most importantly, the need to quickly develop and vet interesting content, and ProPublica serves lots of data sets in addition to the news. They are also doing some cool stuff like using AI to generate specific narratives from tens of thousands of database entries illustrating how school districts and states often don't distribute educational opportunities to rich and poor kids equally. The ProPublica team focuses on some basic practical issues for building a team, rapidly and flexibly deploying technology and insuring that what they serve is correct. A great news app developer needs three key skills: the ability to do journalism, design acumen and the ability to write code quickly — and the last is the easiest to teach. To build a team they look to their own staff rather than competing with Google for CS grads. Most news organizations use either Ruby on Rails or Python/Django, but more important than which specific technology you choose is to just pick a server-side programming language and stick to it. Cloud hosting provides news organizations with incredible flexibility (like increasing your capacity ten-fold for a few days around the election and then scaling back the day after), but they're not as fast as real servers, and cloud costs can scale quickly relative to real servers. Maybe a news app is not the most massive 'big data' application out there, but where else can you find the challenge of millions of users checking in several times a day for the latest news, and all you need to do is sort out which of your many and conflicting sources are providing you with straight information? Oh, and if you screw up, it will be very public."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7077-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7077_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:19:22">http://books.slashdot.org/story/12/07/30/1210224/book-review-core-python-applications-programming-3rd-ed</link><title>Book Review: Core Python Applications Programming, 3rd Ed.</title><description>thatpythonguy writes "Core Python Application Programming is the latest addition to a growing corpus of literature serving a growing number of Python programmers and engineers. This Prentice Hall book of 800+ pages covers some traditional areas and touches upon some new ones. I typically do not spend much time speaking about the author of the books that I review; however, this occasion warrants an exception. And it is not because Wesley Chun used Python over a decade ago to build the address book and spell-checker for Yahoo! Mail nor is it because he holds a minor degree in music from UC Berkeley in classical piano. Rather, it is because he is both an engineer and an instructor. In other words, he was not pulled from his geek duties and asked to become a pseudo-writer; he already does that for his consulting practice, authoring (or co-authoring) several books and articles on Python (including "Python Web Development with Django") as well as starring in his own training video (entitled "Python Fundamentals"). The result of that experience is a writing style that is technically sound, yet accessible." Keep reading for the rest of Ahmed's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7077-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7077_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:20:58">http://books.slashdot.org/story/12/07/06/0016210/book-review-head-first-python</link><title>Book Review: Head First Python</title><description>Michael J. Ross writes "Veteran computer programmers — adept with languages such as PHP, Perl, and JavaScript — typically have no trouble learning an additional language, often just by reading online tutorials and stepping through sample code. But for those new to programming, that approach can prove difficult and frustrating. Yet nowadays there appears to be growing interest among such people for learning how to write programs in Python, especially as it is seeing increasing use by Google and other organizations, and is often chosen as the primary teaching language in schools. For such budding programmers, one possible starting point is the book Head First Python." Read on for the rest of Michael's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7077-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7077_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:21:24">http://news.slashdot.org/story/12/05/26/1450228/barter-based-school-catching-on-globally</link><title>Barter-Based School Catching On Globally</title><description>sethopia writes "In 2010, three people had the crazy idea to start a school where the teachers teach whatever they want and the students pay for classes with whatever teachers need — cutlery, art, advice — but never with money. Trade Schools have been popping up around the world and are now active in 15 cities and 10 countries, with almost no prodding from its founders. Caroline Woolard, one of the founders, discusses the challenges and opportunities of adapting their idea to an international audience and making the Trade School software — based on Python and Django — great."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7077-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7077_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:23:56">http://ask.slashdot.org/story/11/12/04/2227209/ask-slashdot-one-framework-to-rule-them-all</link><title>Ask Slashdot: One Framework To Rule Them All?</title><description>New submitter ittybad writes "I work with a small web-based company, and, for some new web applications, we are looking to possibly change frameworks if it will be a benefit to our developers and our customers. We have experience with PHP's Symfony 1.4, and are not happy with what we are experiencing with Symfony 2.0. We have some Ruby guys who would love us to implement a Ruby on Rails solution, and our backend is Python powered — so maybe Django is the way to go. So, I ask you, Slashdotters, what web framework do you find to be the best and why? Why would you avoid others?"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7077-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7077_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:27:37">http://developers.slashdot.org/story/11/08/10/2111203/six-python-web-frameworks-compared</link><title>Six Python Web Frameworks Compared</title><description>snydeq writes "InfoWorld's Rick Grehan provides an in-depth comparison of six Python Web frameworks, including CubicWeb, Django, Pyramid, Web.py, Web2py, and Zope 2. 'No matter what your needs or leanings as a Python developer might be, one of these frameworks promises to be a good fit,' Grehan writes. 'As usual, the choice is highly subjective. You will find zealots for each product, and every zealot is able to present rational reasons why their chosen framework is superior.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7077-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7077_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:28:43">http://books.slashdot.org/story/10/05/26/1524232/django-11-testing-and-debugging</link><title>Django 1.1 Testing and Debugging</title><description>johnmccollum writes "A wealth of tools are available to debug and test Django applications, but knowing when and how to use these resources can intimidate the new user. Django 1.1 Testing and Debugging, by Karen M. Tracey, aims to walk the user through the process of creating a web application from scratch, ensuring that the resulting code is bug-free and ready for production." Keep reading for the rest of John's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7077-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7077_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:32:48">http://books.slashdot.org/story/10/05/12/1343227/matplotlib-for-python-developers</link><title>Matplotlib For Python Developers</title><description>Craig Maloney writes "Ever since there was a collection of numbers, it seems that invariably someone will want a graph of those numbers. There are literally hundreds of different styles of graphs, and almost as many programs and tools to make those graphs. Matplotlib, a library and toolkit for the Python language, provides an easy and effective way to make some impressive graphics with little more than a smattering of Python. Matplotlib for Python Developers is equally impressive at distilling the core set of features of Matplotlib in a way that shows the reader how to get the most out the Matplotlib toolkit." Read below for the rest of Craig's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7077-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7077_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:37:50">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/127206</link><title>Nicaragua Creates Innovative Agricultural Information System With Open Source</title><description>johanneswilm writes "Nicaragua is the second-poorest country of the Americas. It is now also the Latin American country with the most capable web-based information system for agriculture, thanks to open source software. ALBAstryde itself is open source, and it is based on Django and jQuery. It allows the user to play with the data, and its reach is further extended by a net of radio stations which are broadcasting the numbers to remote peasants, who thereby, for the first time ever, get up to date data on prices and general production levels in the country. The implementation for the ministry of agriculture of Nicaragua already contains live data."</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>