<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7082">The raven</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:45:12" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7082-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7082_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:45:15">http://games.slashdot.org/story/13/04/04/1242214/activision-raven-release-2-star-wars-games-under-gpl</link><title>Activision, Raven Release 2 Star Wars Games Under GPL</title><description>hypnosec writes "Activision and Raven Software game studios have open sourced a couple of their games so that people can play as well learn from the code. The gaming companies have released the source code of Star Wars Jedi Knight: Jedi Academy and Jedi Outcast through SourceForge."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7082-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7082_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:46:39">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/165669</link><title>Open Source Robotic Surgeon</title><description>GlobalEcho writes "Researchers have created a second version of the Raven robotic surgeon, with open-source control code. 'UW researchers also created software to work with the Robot Operating System, a popular open-source robotics code, so labs can easily connect the Raven to other devices and share ideas.' Unfortunately for them, according to The Economist, 'there is [a] legal problem. Intuitive Surgical, the company behind the da Vinci [robot], holds patents that could make launching a commercial competitor tricky — at least in the immediate future."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7082-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7082_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:47:47">http://idle.slashdot.org/story/11/08/23/1345222/taken-over-by-aliens-google-has-it-covered</link><title>Taken Over By Aliens? Google Has It Covered</title><description>swandives writes "Imagine what would happen if all the Google engineers turned rogue and held the world's Gmail accounts to ransom. Or if aliens attacked earth and wiped California off the map. Seems the folks over at Google's enterprise division have already considered these scenarios. CIO is running an article, as part of a larger interview with Google Enterprise director of security, Eran Feigenbaum. He's a fascinating guy — in his spare time he practices magic and mentalism, and you may also have heard of him as Eran Raven, a contestant from the NBC television show Phenomenon."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7082-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7082_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:49:25">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/11/05/11/2252234/new-aircraft-is-pilot-optional</link><title>New Aircraft Is Pilot Optional</title><description>Zothecula writes "Although the use of unmanned aerial vehicles such as Global Hawk and Raven for military information gathering has increased sharply in the last decade due to the maturation and miniaturization of enabling technologies, conventional piloted aircraft can still be a better option depending on the mission at hand. Northrop Grumman has unveiled a new intelligence gathering aircraft called the Firebird that falls into the category of an Optionally Piloted Vehicle with its ability to be flown robotically or with a human pilot on board."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7082-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7082_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:51:47">http://idle.slashdot.org/story/11/03/29/1345234/man-accused-of-selling-us-military-drones-on-ebay</link><title>Man Accused of Selling US Military Drones On EBay</title><description>garymortimer writes "47-year-old Henson Chua is in a bit of trouble for trying to sell a RQ-11B 'Raven' Unmanned Aerial Vehicle on eBay. From the article: 'A federal grand jury in Tampa returned an indictment charging Henson Chua, 47, of Manilla, Philippines, with violations of the Arms Export Control Act and smuggling, following an investigation by US Immigration and Customs Enforcement's Homeland Security Investigations. If convicted on all counts, Chua faces a maximum penalty of 20 years in federal prison.'" I'm kicking myself for missing this auction.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7082-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7082_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:53:49">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/09/05/25/223209/robot-warfare-going-open-source</link><title>Robot Warfare Going Open Source</title><description>destinyland writes "Peter Singer, author of the new book Wired for War: The Robotics Revolution and Conflict in the 21st Century, says 'You can build your own version of the Raven drone, which is a widely used military drone, for about $1,000.' Singer argues that 'just like software, warfare is going open source.' He warns that, ultimately, robot warfare may even expand beyond the military using more DIY and off-the-shelf systems. In addition to 43 countries now working on military robots, there are 'non-state actors ranging from Hezbollah to this militia group in Arizona to a bunch of college kids at Swarthmore... One person's hobby — such as the hobbyist who flew a homemade drone from North America to Great Britain — can be another person's terrorist strike option.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7082-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7082_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:57:04">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/118893</link><title>Biden Reveals Location of Secret VP Bunker</title><description>Hugh Pickens writes "Fox News reports that 'Vice President Joe Biden, well-known for his verbal gaffes, may have finally outdone himself, divulging potentially classified information meant to save the life of a sitting vice president.' According to the report, while recently attending the Gridiron Club dinner in Washington, an annual event where powerful politicians and media elite get a chance to cozy up to one another, Biden told his dinnermates about the existence of a secret bunker under the old US Naval Observatory, which is now the home of the vice president. Although earlier reports had placed the Vice-Presidential hide-out in a highly secure complex of buildings inside Raven Rock Mountain near Blue Ridge Summit, Pennsylvania, Fox News reports that the Naval Observatory bunker is believed to be the secure, undisclosed location former Vice President Dick Cheney remained under protection in secret after the 9/11 attacks. According to the report, Biden 'said a young naval officer giving him a tour of the residence showed him the hideaway, which is behind a massive steel door secured by an elaborate lock with a narrow connecting hallway lined with shelves filled with communications equipment.' According to Eleanor Clift, Newsweek magazine's Washington contributing editor 'the officer explained that when Cheney was in lock down, this was where his most trusted aides were stationed, an image that Biden conveyed in a way that suggested we shouldn't be surprised that the policies that emerged were off the wall.' In December 2002, neighbors complained of loud construction work being done at the Naval Observatory, which has been used as a residence by vice presidents since 1974. The upset neighbors were sent a letter by the observatory's superintendent, calling the work 'sensitive in nature' and 'classified' and that it was urgent it be completed on a highly accelerated schedule."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7082-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7082_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:58:13">http://games.slashdot.org/story/09/03/31/0322208/early-look-at-the-new-wolfenstein-game</link><title>Early Look At the New Wolfenstein Game</title><description>Attendees of this year's GDC were given an early look at Wolfenstein, the new shooter in development by id and Raven. We've previously discussed the "Veil" ability that protagonist BJ Blazkowicz uses to hide himself, and much of the coverage relates to how it affects gameplay. "Early on, Blazkowicz stumbles upon an experiment and manages to blow it up, releasing waves of ethereal blue material. The Veil seems to turn gravity on and off as Blazkowicz tries to escape the area, making for some very original gunplay. ... The folks on hand told me that the Veil would be incorporated into game's multiplayer, but wouldn't go into details." A trailer for the game is available at Joystiq, and they had this to say: "Wolfenstein's look and gameplay is dated — and not in a retro chic way. Without the Veil, the game could be mistaken for a last-gen title, so the game's success rests on how compelling this feature will be throughout an entire playthrough."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7082-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7082_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:01:29">http://games.slashdot.org/story/08/09/06/0029241/classic-shooters-heretic-and-hexen-released-under-gpl</link><title>Classic Shooters Heretic and Hexen Released Under GPL</title><description>phanboy_iv writes "Fans of both of the Raven classics, Heretic and Hexen, have been trying for almost a decade to convince Raven Software to release engine source code for the games under the GPL, much like the DOOM engine on which both of them are based. Well, they finally did it! Source code is available at Sourceforge. Both of these games have had the source available for a while, but under a restrictive license that hindered ports and modifications. Now, thanks to dedicated fans, that's no longer a problem."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7082-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7082_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:02:03">http://games.slashdot.org/story/08/08/21/1633236/developer-praises-complexity-of-time-based-puzzles-in-braid</link><title>Developer Praises Complexity of Time-Based Puzzles In "Braid"</title><description>Raven Software game developer Manveer Heir takes a look at the design mechanics of Braid, a recently released puzzle game for Xbox Live Arcade (a review is available at Gamespot). Heir commends Braid's focus on taking an interesting mechanic and exploring it fully through level design, rather than generating complexity with the interaction of many different mechanics. "One of my favorite worlds has time move forward as the player moves to the right, and rewind as the player moves left; Time is being controlled spatially. Another world has the player make a recording of themselves that can interact with certain objects, similar to Cursor*10. ... What is amazing is how complex and devilish some of the puzzles can still be, even though they revolve around the single mechanic for that world. ... Feeling like you have to guess what the designer was thinking is how many old adventure games played out, and it was rarely fun. Feeling like you just made a discovery on your own is what makes this game and games like Portal work so well."</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>