<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7084">Burn after reading review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:05:05" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7084-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7084_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:05:06">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/175485</link><title>Game Review: Torchlight 2</title><description>CowboyNeal writes: "Last week was a big week for gamers, with the release of both Borderlands 2 as well as Torchlight 2. I already shared my thoughts on the former last week, so I got to playing the latter over the weekend. Torchlight 2 is the follow-up to Torchlight, the 2009 point-and-click ARPG created by Runic Games. What's new that the first game didn't have? And, the big question, how does it stack up against Diablo 3? Click the link below to learn my impressions of the game."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7084-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7084_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:05:43">http://news.slashdot.org/story/05/08/31/1229202/lean-software-development</link><title>Lean Software Development</title><description>Jim Holmes writes "Mary and Tom Poppendieck's Lean Software Development: An Agile Toolkit is a great read for anyone interested in agile software development. That includes developers, leads, and managers interested in speeding up development cycles, improving quality, and getting their customers the best value. This book's been out since May, 2003, but it's well worth picking up. The concepts within are absolutely applicable now, and will continue to be for quite a few years." Read on for the rest of Holmes' review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7084-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7084_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:10:13">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/41647</link><title>Linux Toys</title><description>Alex Moskalyuk writes "Remember those 'how-to' and 'home improvement' books that you enjoyed reading as a little kid? In the first half of the last century there was a variety of books, with names like 'Boy Mechanic' or '1,000 Projects for a Boy,' which would give a teenager a variety of projects to work on productively. Building bird houses, creatively reusing helmets from World War I, and later different projects that had to do with radio and transistors - in the pre-television age all that guaranteed some creative time for geeks (whether kids or adults) and allowed them pick up skills, necessary perhaps in real life." Alex reviews below a book that fills a similar niche for the present day, outlining all 13 projects in Linux Toys: 13 Cool Projects for Home, Office and Entertainment. Whether you'd consider all of the projects toys is up to you.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7084-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7084_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:12:16">http://news.slashdot.org/story/02/07/16/1953203/h2k2-wrapup</link><title>H2K2 Wrapup</title><description>Your intrepid reporter took a jaunt down to the H2K2 conference this past weekend, held in the lovely Hotel Pennsylvania. The conference had much more floor space than they had two years ago, and it seemed like more attendance as well. Wireless networks were available, though overcrowded, and if you didn't encrypt your communications, well, you've probably already paid the price. My notes on the conference and the sessions I attended are below, followed by a couple of reader submissions.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7084-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7084_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:13:51">http://news.slashdot.org/story/02/03/28/1359257/the-mousedriver-chronicles</link><title>The MouseDriver Chronicles</title><description>Mark Welch writes: "'The MouseDriver Chronicles' chronicles a modestly successful startup whose mission was to build a product and sell it at a profit -- a concept that seemed almost obscene when the authors launched their new business in mid-1999.) I saw 'The MouseDriver Chronicles' in several bookstores, and passed because it sounded like it would be yet another story of dot-com failure. But finally I decided it looked like a 'fun read' and bought it, and I'm glad I did." Mark has a more complete review, and ChrisD adds his own reaction, below.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7084-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7084_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:15:27">http://news.slashdot.org/story/00/07/02/160253/answers-from-sealand-cto-ryan-lackey-responds</link><title>Answers From Sealand: CTO Ryan Lackey Responds</title><description>A few weeks ago, you asked questions of Ryan Lackey, CTO for HavenCo, a company dedicated to providing secure off-shore data hosting from Sealand, a principality off the coast of England. Ryan has lately survived dental emergencies, the loss of a laptop (it dropped into the North Sea -- how many people can say that?) and other stresses, but he's followed through with some interesting answers. He even has some ideas for how you can make a lot of money, and lists the tools you need to start your own data haven. Kudos to Ryan for taking the time to answer so thoroughly.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>