<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7095">iron in water supply</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:30:19" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7095-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7095_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:30:20">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/179019</link><title>Bennett's Whimsi-Geek Gift Guide For 2012</title><description>Frequent contributor Bennett Haselton writes this week with his favorite novelty science gift items for 2012. Levitation engines, puzzles, optical illusions brought to life, and all of the tips and tricks he's found for getting the products to work correctly. Decorative, whimsical, and not too expensive — except for the items that have earned it by being pretty amazing. Read on for the details, and be sure to mention other good possibilities (Just 14 shopping days left until Christmas) in the comments below.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7095-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7095_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:34:23">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/116499</link><title>Scientists Make Artificial Protein Mimic Blood</title><description>Al writes "Researchers at the University of Pennsylvania have created a protein that can carry and deliver oxygen — a useful step towards developing artificial blood. This would avoid the problems involved with donor blood — contamination, limited storage, and short supply — and lead to easier and faster blood transfusions on the battlefield and in trauma cases. The Penn researchers used three amino acids to make a four-helix columned protein structure put a smaller structure, called a heme, inside it. The heme is a large flat molecule that has an iron atom at its center, which oxygen binds to. The researchers also made the protein structure flexible, so that it can open to receive the oxygen and close again without letting any water in. They did this by linking together the helical columns with loops to restrict their motions, giving the final structure a candelabra shape."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7095-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7095_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:35:12">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/04/02/23/2036241/hardware-hacking-projects-for-geeks</link><title>Hardware Hacking Projects for Geeks</title><description>PHPee (Rob Maeder) writes "Scott Fullam's Hardware Hacking Projects for Geeks is an excellent book outlining all you need to know to get started in the wonderful world of hardware hacking. With step-by-step guides to fifteen useful, amusing and off the wall projects, even a novice hacker can be up and running with some basic hacks in a few hours. The book demonstrates various ways consumer electronics can be modified to do things they were never intended to do, and shows you just how much fun voiding your warranty can be." (We mentioned this book yesterday, too.) Read on for PHPee's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7095-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7095_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:38:10">http://news.slashdot.org/story/00/07/02/160253/answers-from-sealand-cto-ryan-lackey-responds</link><title>Answers From Sealand: CTO Ryan Lackey Responds</title><description>A few weeks ago, you asked questions of Ryan Lackey, CTO for HavenCo, a company dedicated to providing secure off-shore data hosting from Sealand, a principality off the coast of England. Ryan has lately survived dental emergencies, the loss of a laptop (it dropped into the North Sea -- how many people can say that?) and other stresses, but he's followed through with some interesting answers. He even has some ideas for how you can make a lot of money, and lists the tools you need to start your own data haven. Kudos to Ryan for taking the time to answer so thoroughly.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>