<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7102">vlc mac</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:52:14" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7102-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7102_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:52:17">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/12/07/03/1630243/vlc-s-beta-for-android-is-ready-unless-youre-north-american</link><title>VLC 's Beta For Android Is Ready — Unless You're North American</title><description>MrSeb writes "The VideoLAN Project has pushed a beta version of VLC for Android to the Google Play Store. The beta brings most of the functionality of VLC for Linux, Windows, and Mac OS X to Android in a native UI in the Android 4.0 Holo style. However, there are a few hitches. The beta release published to the Google Play Store today is only compatible with ARM systems that use the ARMv7 architecture set and support the NEON instruction set. That means that there are several devices — mostly those released before the Samsung Galaxy S in late 2010, and anything powered by Tegra 2 — that cannot run the current beta. Also, apparently due to a lack of North America-specific Android test devices, VLC for Android is currently not available from the US or Canadian Play Store. Both problems should be rectified soon, though." VLC is one of those impressive programs that just works with nearly any input thrown at it, and one of the first things I put on any computer. I hope the Android version retains pitch-controlled variable-speed playback, perhaps my favorite VLC feature, and something I miss on my tablet.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7102-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7102_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:54:53">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/164871</link><title>VLC 2.0 'Twoflower' Released For Windows &amp; Mac</title><description>Titus Andronicus writes "Years in the making, the major new release of VideoLAN's media player has better support for multicore processors, GPUs, and much, much more. From the announcement: 'Twoflower has a new rendering pipeline for video, with higher quality subtitles, and new video filters to enhance your videos. It supports many new devices and BluRay Discs (experimental). Completely reworked Mac and Web interfaces and improvements in the other interfaces make VLC easier than ever to use. Twoflower fixes several hundreds of bugs, in more than 7000 commits from 160 volunteers.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7102-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7102_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:58:17">http://news.slashdot.org/story/09/12/23/2013219/vlc-team-announces-video-editor-in-the-works</link><title>VLC Team Announces Video Editor In the Works</title><description>eldavojohn writes "Despite news that VLC might not have anyone to work on the Mac release, Lifehacker brings word of a video editor that the VLC team is working on dubbed VideoLAN Media Creator. It hasn't been released yet (git clone git://github.com/VLMC/vlmc.git) but a pre-release is due out soon."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7102-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7102_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:01:46">http://apple.slashdot.org/story/09/12/16/2145251/lack-of-manpower-may-kill-vlc-for-mac</link><title>Lack of Manpower May Kill VLC For Mac</title><description>plasmacutter writes "The Video Lan dev team has recently come forward with a notice that the number of active developers for the project's MacOS X releases has dropped to zero, prompting a halt in the release schedule. There is now a disturbing possibility that support for Mac will be dropped as of 1.1.0. As the most versatile and user-friendly solution for bridging the video compatibility gap between OS X and windows, this will be a terrible loss for the Mac community. There is still hope, however, if the right volunteers come forward."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7102-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7102_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:06:58">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/09/06/18/0951259/benqs-gp1-led-projector-small-package-good-thing</link><title>BenQ's GP1 LED Projector — Small Package, Good Thing</title><description>The first projector I remember seeing in person had three great big glass eyes (for red, green, and blue lamps) and BNC connectors. It probably weighed more than 100 pounds, and had to be carefully calibrated to align the lenses. Now, I've got a projector above my head that weighs less than a Neal Stephenson novel and has a sharper, brighter image than that monster. I've been looking into LED projectors for a few years now; in that time, I've been waiting for them to come down in price and bump up in lumens. So I was very curious about BenQ's GP1 LED projector (also known, somewhat oddly, as "Joybee"), and was happy to get a sample for review. It may seem retrograde to bother with an 800x600, 100 lumen (no missing zero there: one-hundred lumen) projector in 2009 A.D., but for the past four weeks, I've used it as my primary display, and come out happy. It has some drawbacks, but it's an impressive little device for its $499 pricetag, and I hope a harbinger of even better things to come. Read on for my take on what BenQ got right, and what rough spots stick out.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7102-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7102_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:09:25">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/116663</link><title>VLC 0.9.9, The Best Media Player Just Got Better</title><description>Matt Asay points out a recent update to VLC as they narrow in on a 1.0 release. Already a favorite of many, the open source project has made great strides in recent history towards really solidifying the position as best-in-class. This update, 0.9.9, fixes several display bugs and sees some definite performance improvements. "If you've yet to try VLC, do so. Whether you just want to play media files or also want to convert them, VLC can handle just about anything you throw at it. When all other media players fail, whether on Windows, Linux, or the Mac, VLC will almost always deliver. You can download VLC media player 0.9.9 here. It's open source, but that's not why you'll want to keep using it. You'll use it because it's better than its proprietary peers — by a long stretch.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7102-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7102_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:11:16">http://slashdot.org/story/06/12/11/208229/vlc-086-released</link><title>VLC 0.8.6 Released</title><description>h2g2bob writes "VideoLAN yesterday released a new version of VLC media player. A shout out goes to ffmpeg for many of the codec improvements." From the blurb: "Building on feedback from the 29 million downloads of VLC media player 0.8.5, we bring you version 0.8.6 with many bugfixes, as well as a couple of new features we think you will truly enjoy. Most prominent are probably Windows Media Video 9 and Flash Video. Other important changes are improved H.264 decoding, better Windows Unicode support, a Fullscreen controller, and Apple Remote support for Mac OS X."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7102-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7102_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:15:59">http://it.slashdot.org/story/05/11/28/0441234/vlc-media-player-084-is-out</link><title>VLC Media Player 0.8.4 is out</title><description>mctk writes "This new release features many improvements including a new VLC cone, new Mac OS X wizard and extend controls dialogs, tree playlist skins2 support, HTTP interface CGI handling, linux binary codecs loader, UPnP and Bonjour service discovery, shoutcast stream forwarding, new languages... Have a look here for the full list of changes. Binary packages and the source code are available on the VLC download page." Always been one of my favorites on any platform.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7102-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7102_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:20:15">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/57991</link><title>Holmes Wilson Interviewed About Open-Source TV</title><description>flippy writes "Videoblogger Steve Garfield has a new interview with Holmes Wilson of Downhill Battle and Participatory Culture Foundation, talking about the F/OSS internet TV platform that Participatory Culture is developing and their recently released video publishing package, Broadcast Machine. Their RSS / BitTorrent / VLC application ("TiVo for the Internet") is expected to be released for Mac and Windows by the end of this month."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7102-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7102_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:23:43">http://news.slashdot.org/story/04/11/02/0227243/simplest-ogg-streaming-clients-for-non-unix-users</link><title>Simplest Ogg Streaming Clients for non-Unix Users?</title><description>Dr. Smeegee asks: "I recently set up an .ogg stream for beta testing, on a website chronicling my hometown's music scene in the 80's. I stream nothing but independent bands from the Evansville area. I chose IceCast using Ogg Vorbis for obvious reasons. The only problem is, I've been using ogg123 on BSD for so long, I didn't realize that streaming Ogg support is sketchy at best on the Windows and Mac platforms. Can anyone suggest good players? Or am I going to have to downgrade my sound and stream in .mp3?"</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>