<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7112">facebook icons</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:35:59" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7112-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7112_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:36:00">http://mobile.slashdot.org/story/13/05/29/2121230/sheryl-sandberg-facebooks-home-app-needs-some-work</link><title>Sheryl Sandberg: Facebook's Home App Needs Some Work</title><description>Nerval's Lobster writes "Facebook COO Sheryl Sandberg told an audience at AllThingsDigital's D11 conference that the social network's 'Home' app for Android has a viable future despite needing some work. 'I think it will be a long road,' she told the audience. 'We believe that the phone will get reorganized around people—Home is the first iteration of that.' But Home could require a good deal of tweaking, at least if user feedback is any sort of indication. After installing the Home app, the Android user's screen displays a modified version of the Facebook news feed, with an emphasis on images; other features include 'Chat Heads,' a messaging interface that sprinkles the screen with little icons of friends' heads. While that's a great way to get Facebook front-and-center on someone's phone, the software's one-star reviews on the Google Play storefront greatly outnumber the four- and five-star reviews."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7112-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7112_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:39:01">http://news.slashdot.org/story/12/10/23/2038220/the-greatest-battle-of-the-personal-computing-revolution-lies-ahead</link><title>The Greatest Battle of the Personal Computing Revolution Lies Ahead</title><description>As tablets and computer-phones flood the market, the headlines read: "The Personal Computer is Dying." But they are only half true: an artifact of the PC is dying, but the essence of the PC revolution is closer to realization than ever before, while also being closer to loss than ever before.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7112-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7112_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:43:59">http://news.slashdot.org/story/10/08/23/1911247/nmap-developers-release-a-picture-of-the-web</link><title>Nmap Developers Release a Picture of the Web</title><description>iago-vL writes "The Nmap Project recently posted an awesome visualization of the top million site icons (favicons) on the Web, sized by relative popularity of sites. This project used the Nmap Scripting Engine, which is capable of performing discovery, vulnerability detection, and anything else you can imagine with lightning speed. We saw last month how an Nmap developer downloaded 170 million Facebook names, and this month it's a million favicons; I wonder what they'll do next?"</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>