<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7118">part time jobs texas city</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:53:34" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7118-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7118_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:53:36">http://slashdot.org/story/06/08/04/1911221/places-rated-skeptically</link><title>Places Rated, Skeptically</title><description>Readers left more than 500 comments on yesterday's post suggesting that, after accounting for local price differences, the best-paid tech jobs aren't in Silicon Valley or other areas well known for computer jobs, but rather in smaller cities around the country. Quality of life is overall more important than salary, though, and it isn't an easy thing to measure. Several readers pointed to reasons why the most expensive places to live get to be so expensive, and why (for those who can afford to live there in the first place) locations like Silicon Valley are often worth their premiums. Read on for some of the most interesting comments from the discussion in today's Backslash summary.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7118-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7118_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:58:07">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/99/11/11/2329226/the-imagineer-who-came-in-from-the-cold</link><title>The Imagineer Who Came In From The Cold</title><description>Thanks to the many geeks and nerds who answered my SOS the other day about how to use Orlando as a way to write about technology and the future. One of the many standout e-mails was from a genuine Disney Imagineer, with whom I had a clandestine and revealing meeting last night on a deserted EPCOT bench. This was only one of several mystical and powerful encounters with pilgrims flocking to the world's new techno-mecca. Next: Disney's Carousel of Progress and the lost model of his dream city of tomorrow.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7118-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7118_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:59:21">http://news.slashdot.org/story/99/10/08/2123255/notes-toward-a-postcyberpunk-manifesto</link><title>Notes Toward a Postcyberpunk Manifesto</title><description>Lawrence Person writes "With Neil Stephenson and Bruce Sterling hot topics of interest here on Slashdot, I thought my "Notes Toward a Postcyberpunk Manifesto" might help add to /.'s SF debate. This originally appeared last year in an issue of Nova Express, the Hugo-nominated small press SF magazine I edit. However, though it's been translated into Portugese, it's never appeared on the web before. It discusses exactly why original cyberpunk works like Neuromancer were important, and why the work people like Stephenson, Sterling, Egan, Macleod, etc. are doing right now should more properly be thought of as postcyberpunk.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>