<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7131">golf games</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:17:18" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7131-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7131_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:17:21">http://games.slashdot.org/story/13/11/06/029215/why-there-shouldnt-be-a-chess-world-champion</link><title>Why There Shouldn't Be a Chess World Champion</title><description>An anonymous reader writes "An article at Slate makes the case that the time has come to stop crowning World Chess Champions. This week, challenger Magnus Carlsen is trying to take the title from reigning champion Viswanathan Anand. Despite currently holding the title, Anand is very much the underdog, which only serves to illustrate why the current system is broken. The article suggests measuring greatness the same way tennis does. Quoting: 'Here's what Carlsen should do: Beat Anand for the title, and then work with FIDE to institutionalize four big tournaments as chess's Grand Slams, simultaneously eliminating the title of world champion. Corporate funding for even major chess tournaments can come and go with frustrating regularity, meaning FIDE itself has to get involved. Perhaps the grand slam tournaments could be located in three cities permanently—Moscow, Amsterdam, and a Spanish locale such as Linares would be natural picks—with a fourth that would rotate from year to year. This would give chess the same clear and predictable yardstick for greatness that golf and tennis have instead of the extremely crude world champion benchmark.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7131-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7131_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:18:00">http://games.slashdot.org/story/11/07/21/067246/ea-considers-service-based-business-model-for-sports-games</link><title>EA Considers Service-Based Business Model For Sports Games</title><description>Andrew Wilson, head of development for EA Sports, spoke at the Develop 2011 conference about an unusual business plan the company is considering for future games: "[Wilson] raised the subject of Amazon's Whispersync feature, which allows customers to download a digital book for one price and then read it on whichever format they like from PCs to smartphones and Kindle, without having to pay again for each platform. He suggested that eventually EA Sports may well move toward the same model with its own games, even providing all of its titles, from FIFA and Madden to Tiger Woods PGA Tour golf, for one fixed price on multiple platforms – all linked by the same social gaming ecosystem. 'It's about handing over control to the gamer,' he said. 'Ultimately, what we want to get to is this concept where we break down the barriers between the franchises. John Riccitiello, our CEO, says it seems like such a waste – we spend $20-40M making each of these games, but most gamers only ever play one, because the business model is an impediment. So how about we drive toward a model where every gamer can experience everything we make without paying that much more money. You've got to recognize that given the opportunity, the consumer will play and they will bring their friends.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7131-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7131_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:21:48">http://games.slashdot.org/story/10/10/02/1740230/retro-gaming-technologies-released-before-their-time</link><title>Retro Gaming Technologies Released Before Their Time</title><description>Barence writes "Motion-sensing golf game controllers that appeared 20 years before the Nintendo Wii and the 1980s handheld console that operated on solar power are just two of the gems unearthed in this article about retro gaming secrets. Davey Winder has delved into his extensive personal collection of retro hardware to unveil the first handheld console to play '3D games' from 1983, 'the most realistic "gun" game controller ever produced' from way back in 1972, and the device that offered multiplayer computerized Scrabble almost 30 years before the iPad."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7131-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7131_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:24:46">http://games.slashdot.org/story/09/11/07/1622230/visually-impaired-gamer-sues-sony</link><title>Visually Impaired Gamer Sues Sony</title><description>An anonymous reader writes "A visually impaired gamer has sued Sony because game products allegedly violate the Americans With Disabilities Act. 'According to the suit, Sony ignored repeated requests through postal mail and e-mail to come up with reasonable modifications to its games to make them more accessible.' This suit seems to be a combination of National Federation of the Blind v. Target, which complained of inaccessibility to the visually disabled (which settled for $6 million) and Martin v. PGA Tour, Inc., where the US Supreme Court ruled a disabled golfer was entitled to a golf cart where one was not already allowed as a reasonable accommodation. If the plaintiff wins, Sony will have to make 'reasonable accommodations' which are not an 'undue financial burden.' In my humble opinion, providing access for the disabled is not only the right thing to do but it will generate more profit for Sony."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7131-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7131_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:27:44">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/83617</link><title>Nintendo's Sale Dominance Gets Noticed</title><description>Via Kotaku, a Wall Street Journal report on Nintendo's continued dominance of the game charts. The piece rehashes the February NPD numbers and discusses the role the Wii and DS have had in revitalizing a company the WSJ refers to as an 'also-ran'. "To take better advantage of the Wii's growth, EA moved quickly to ramp up game production for the system, acquiring Headgate Studios, a developer in Utah focused entirely on making titles for Nintendo hardware, and shifting resources in other EA development groups to Nintendo projects. The company released four titles for the Wii in March, including a version of its Tiger Woods golf game in which players swing the Wii controller like a club. EA is also working on a line of consumer guides for the Nintendo DS that will be aimed at older players in Japan."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7131-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7131_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:30:26">http://games.slashdot.org/story/07/02/08/2023216/dice-07-underway-in-las-vegas</link><title>DICE '07 Underway in Las Vegas</title><description>The annual AIAS DICE summit is underway in Las Vegas, with games industry movers and shakers congregating to exchange ideas, network, and play a little golf. The event kicked off with a keynote from Sony executive Yair Landau, Doug Lowenstein's final address to the games industry, and a Q&amp;A session with Sony's Phil Harrison. In and amongst the speeches there was a small droplet of news: Sony Online Entertainment's next MMOG will be a spy caper. Code named 'Vista' (because they pushed it back a year, har), the title will put players in 'tuxedos instead of tunics' fighting over secretive information in the modern era.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7131-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7131_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:33:11">http://games.slashdot.org/story/06/02/16/1547242/slashback-mmorpg-trends</link><title>Slashback: MMORPG Trends</title><description>Some additional details on stories we've previously discussed. The Garriott brothers gave a talk at the DICE conference earlier this month, and while Next Generation offered the gist of the Garriot keynote, Gamespy has a detailed look at their predictions. We also talked earlier about World of Warcraft as the new golf. C|Net has a deeper look at the trend of networking in Azeroth. From that article: "With more than 5.5 million people now playing WoW and joining guilds for everything from police officers to soldiers returning from Iraq, it was bound to happen: The rich guys have carved a virtual space to call their own. In fairness, the six-month-old guild isn't just for rich folks. There are plenty of bartenders and regular workaday types in the group as well. But what sets 'We Know' apart is its concentration of movers and shakers in the technology world."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7131-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7131_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:34:17">http://games.slashdot.org/story/06/02/09/1941234/wow-the-next-golf</link><title>WoW the Next "Golf"?</title><description>TheGrapeApe writes "1up has an article about the possibility of World of Warcraft becoming the next "Golf": A place where friends, acquaintances, and perhaps even business partners will meet up to "talk shop" and swap stories. Personally, I can't wait until I have my next job interview in the Deadmines. " I demand extra healing and mana pots from all my employees.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7131-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7131_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:39:40">http://games.slashdot.org/story/06/01/18/176238/first-party-ps3-titles-announced</link><title>First-Party PS3 Titles Announced</title><description>Gamasutra reports on a list of first-party titles that will see launch with the PlayStation 3. From the article: "The specifically listed games are Polyphony Digital's latest Gran Turismo iteration, Genji 2, presumably a sequel to Yoshiki Okamoto's samurai action title for the PlayStation 2, Everybody's Golf 5, the latest in Camelot's popular cartoon golf series, and titles named Monster Carnival, Angel Rings and The Eye Of Judgment. No other information is currently available on the games."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7131-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7131_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:41:33">http://games.slashdot.org/story/06/01/12/1723220/a-look-at-gaming-in-2010</link><title>A Look at Gaming in 2010</title><description>Joel from Sydney writes "Wired News' Lore Sjöberg has written a tongue-in-cheek look at what the world of gaming will look like in 2010. From the article: 'Nintendo and LucasArts are still locked in competition to bring their aging iconic characters to every genre ever invented. The year 2010 saw the release of Darth Maul's Star Wars Tennis, Mario MMORPG, Clone Trooper Golf, Mario's Dating Sim, Jar-Jar's Dating Sim and Mario Storms the Beach at Normandy. Plus, handheld versions of all those.'"</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>