<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7133">museum of natural history</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:46:28" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7133-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7133_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:46:31">http://science.slashdot.org/story/14/02/12/2330234/new-beetle-named-after-charles-darwin-and-david-sedaris</link><title>New Beetle Named After Charles Darwin and David Sedaris</title><description>sciencehabit writes "On Charles Darwin's 205th birthday, one beetle he found in Argentina is being recognized as a new species. An entomologist discovered the insect, with unusually saw-toothed antennae and a label reading 'C. Darwin', in a collection on loan from the Natural History Museum in London, where it had been misplaced for at least decades. The beetle represented a new species, Darwinilus sedarisi, named after Darwin and the writer David Sedaris, whose audiobooks the scientist listened to while preparing specimens."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7133-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7133_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:51:01">http://science.slashdot.org/story/14/02/09/1626226/britains-eastern-coast-yields-oldest-human-footprints-outside-africa</link><title>Britain's Eastern Coast Yields Oldest Human Footprints Outside Africa</title><description>schwit1 writes "They were a British family on a day out — almost a million years ago. Archaeologists announced Friday that they have discovered human footprints in England that are between 800,000 and 1 million years old — the most ancient found outside Africa, and the earliest evidence of human life in northern Europe. A team from the British Museum, London's Natural History Museum and Queen Mary college at the University of London uncovered imprints from up to five individuals in ancient estuary mud at Happisburgh on the country's eastern coast."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7133-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7133_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:55:30">http://science.slashdot.org/story/13/10/28/031219/celebrating-a-century-of-fossil-finds-in-the-la-brea-tar-pits</link><title>Celebrating a Century of Fossil Finds In the La Brea Tar Pits</title><description>An anonymous reader writes "A century ago on Monday, the predecessor to the Natural History Museum of Los Angeles County began a two-year project to uncover the Ice Age creatures that became trapped in the La Brea Tar Pits. 'Digs over the years have unearthed bones of mammoths, mastodons, saber-toothed cats, dire wolves and other unsuspecting Ice Age creatures that became trapped in ponds of sticky asphalt. But it's the smaller discoveries — plants, insects and rodents — in recent years that are shaping scientists' views of life in the region 11,000 to 50,000 years ago.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7133-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7133_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:58:00">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/192925</link><title>Gravity: Can Film Ever Get the Science Right?</title><description>dryriver writes in with a story lamenting the lack of accurate science in movies. "The relationship between science and science fiction has always been tempestuous. Gravity focuses on two astronauts stranded in space after the destruction of their space shuttle. Since Gravity's US release (it comes to the UK in November) many critics have praised the film for its scientific accuracy. But noted astrophysicist Dr Neil deGrasse Tyson, director of the Hayden Planetarium at the American Museum of Natural History in New York, had several issues with the accuracy of Gravity's portrayal of space. Through a series of posts on Twitter, Tyson — who later emphasized that he 'enjoyed the film very much' — highlighted various errors. He noted the Hubble space telescope (orbiting at 350 miles above sea level), the International Space Station (at 250 miles), and a Chinese space station could never be in line of sight of one another. On top of that, most satellites orbit west to east, yet in the film the satellite debris was seen drifting east to west. Tyson also noted how Sandra Bullock's hair did not float freely as it would in zero-gravity. This is arguably not so much an error in physics, but a reflection of the limitations of cinematic technology to accurately portray actors in zero-gravity. That is, of course, without sending them into space for the duration of the film. The Michael Bay film Armageddon is known for its woeful number of inaccuracies, from the space shuttles separating their rocket boosters and fuel tanks in close proximity to each other (risking a collision) and to objects falling on to the asteroid under a gravitational pull seemingly as strong as the Earth's. More than one interested observer tried to work out how big the bomb would have to be to blow up an asteroid in the way demanded in the movie. Answer: Very big indeed. Nasa is reported to have even used Armageddon as part of a test within their training program, asking candidates to identify all the scientific impossibilities within the film."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7133-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7133_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:01:46">http://science.slashdot.org/story/13/03/11/1359207/dr-robert-bakker-answers-your-questions-about-science-and-religion</link><title>Dr. Robert Bakker Answers Your Questions About Science and Religion</title><description>Yesterday we ran the first half of Dr. Robert Bakker's essay in response to your questions. Below you'll find the second part which focuses on the history of science and religion, and the patron saint of paleontology, St. Augustine of Hippo. A big thanks goes out to Dr. Bob for his lengthy reply.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7133-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7133_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:07:22">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/183125</link><title>Dr. Robert Bakker Answers Your Questions</title><description>A while ago you had the chance to ask paleontologist Dr. Robert Bakker a wide variety of questions. Instead of answering them individually, Dr. Bob decided to write a lengthy piece that covers most of your inquiries, and includes personal stories and some of his philosophy. The first part is a narrative about his childhood conversion to fossil studies and how his paleo-CSI approach developed. We'll post the second half, covering his training in the history of theology and how it intersects with his science, tomorrow.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7133-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7133_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:11:39">http://science.slashdot.org/story/13/02/05/1623203/ask-dr-robert-bakker-about-dinosaurs-and-merging-science-and-religion</link><title>Ask Dr. Robert Bakker About Dinosaurs and Merging Science and Religion</title><description>With his trademark hat and beard, Dr. Robert Bakker is one of the most recognized paleontologists working today. Bakker was among the advisers for the movie Jurassic Park, and the character Dr. Robert Burke in the film The Lost World: Jurassic Park is based on him. He was one of the first to put forth the idea that some dinosaurs had feathers and were warm-blooded, and is credited with initiating the ongoing "dinosaur renaissance" in paleontology. Bakker is currently the curator of paleontology for the Houston Museum of Natural Science and the Director of the Morrison Natural History Museum in Colorado. He is also a Christian minister, who contends that there is no real conflict between religion and science, citing the writings and views of Saint Augustine as a guide on melding the two. Dr. Bakker has agreed to take some time from his writing and digging in order to answer your questions. As usual, ask as many questions as you'd like, but please, one question per post.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7133-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7133_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:13:11">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/181021</link><title>Interviews: Ask What You Will of Paleontologist Jack Horner</title><description>John "Jack" R. Horner is the Curator of Paleontology at the Museum of the Rockies, adjunct curator at the National Museum of Natural History, and one of the most famous paleontologists in the world. Known in the scientific community for his research on dinosaur growth and whether or not some species lived in social groups, he is most famous for his work on Jurassic Park and being the inspiration for the character of Alan Grant. Horner caused quite a stir with the publication of his book, How to Build a Dinosaur: Extinction Doesn't Have to Be Forever, in which he proposes creating a "chickensaurus" by genetically "nudging" the DNA of a chicken. Jack has agreed to step away from the genetics lab and put down the bones in order to answer your questions. As usual, you're invited to ask as many questions as you'd like, but please divide them, one question per post.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7133-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7133_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:16:23">http://idle.slashdot.org/story/12/07/11/2233247/bloodsucking-parasite-named-after-bob-marley</link><title>Bloodsucking Parasite Named After Bob Marley</title><description>Hugh Pickens writes "The Christian Science Monitor reports that Gnathia marleyi, a tiny crustacean that feeds off the blood of reef-dwelling Caribbean fish, has been named in honor – for lack of a better term – of the Jamaican musician Bob Marley. Marley, who died in 1981, was an iconic exponent of the Jamaican-born music known as reggae. One of his standards is 'No Woman, No Cry.' Marley joins the 'I have a species named after me' club, which includes Barack Obama, Stephen Colbert, Mick Jagger, and Beyonce. 'I named this species, which is truly a natural wonder, after Marley because of my respect and admiration for Marley's music,' says Paul Sikkel, an assistant professor of marine ecology at Arkansas State University. 'Plus, this species is as uniquely Caribbean as was Marley.' Juvenile gnathid isopods hide within coral rubble or algae so they can launch surprise attacks on fish, and then infest them. As adults, the parasites don't eat. 'We believe that adults subsist for two to three weeks on the last feedings they had as juveniles and then die, hopefully after they have reproduced,' says Sikkel. Specimens of Gnathia marleyi will be housed indefinitely at the American Museum of Natural History in New York City. 'We are currently discussing with AMNH the possibility of creating an exhibit featuring this species that could be viewed by the public.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7133-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7133_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:18:23">http://science.slashdot.org/story/12/03/04/1619248/museum-of-engineered-organisms-opens-in-pittsburgh</link><title>Museum of Engineered Organisms Opens In Pittsburgh</title><description>qeorqe writes "The Center for PostNatural History is a museum and research library about organisms that have been created either by genetic engineering or selective breeding. Included in the collection are Sea Monkeys and GloFish. From the article: 'One of the cool things about natural history museums is that they show you how nature has changed over time, adapting to volatile conditions and extreme challenges. And nothing is more volatile, extreme, or challenging than the human race, so it makes sense that there would be a museum to chronicle just how much we’ve messed with plants, animals, the climate, and in general the world around us. The Center for PostNatural History, opening this week in Pittsburgh, is that museum.'"</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>