<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7137">Cat movies</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:29:02" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7137-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7137_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:29:05">http://entertainment.slashdot.org/story/13/07/22/1216259/the-book-that-is-making-all-movies-the-same</link><title>The Book That Is Making All Movies the Same</title><description>Bruce66423 writes "This Slate story explains how a 2005 book has led to all Hollywood movies following the same structure — to a depressing extent. From the article: '...Summer movies are often described as formulaic. But what few people know is that there is actually a formula—one that lays out, on a page-by-page basis, exactly what should happen when in a screenplay. It’s as if a mad scientist has discovered a secret process for making a perfect, or at least perfectly conventional, summer blockbuster. The formula didn’t come from a mad scientist. Instead it came from a screenplay guidebook, Save the Cat! The Last Book on Screenwriting You’ll Ever Need. In the book, author Blake Snyder, a successful spec screenwriter who became an influential screenplay guru, preaches a variant on the basic three-act structure that has dominated blockbuster filmmaking since the late 1970s.' I've always known we could be manipulated — but this provides a segment by segment, almost minute by minute, guide how to do it."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7137-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7137_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:31:52">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/13/05/15/1525242/google-io-2013-underway-watch-for-updates</link><title>Google I/O 2013 Underway: Watch For Updates</title><description>Google's I/O annual conference is ramping up at San Francisco's Moscone Center. Last year, in the conference keynote, the company took its biggest-yet dive into hardware when it introduced the Nexus 7 tablet, Google Glass, and the ill-fated Nexus Q. The secret is out on Glass, of course: this year, there's a pavilion inside the conference center where I'm sure they'll be showing off applications for it. (Quite a few of the people in the endless lines here are wearing their own, too.) Anticipating the announcements at I/O is practically its own industry, but it's easy to guess that there will be announcements from all the major pots in which Google has its many thousands of (tapping) fingers. Android, search, Chrome, mapping, and all the other ways in which the behemoth of Mountain View is watching what you do. You can watch the keynote talk (talks, really) streamed online from the main conference link above, but this story will be updated with highlights of the announcements, as well with stories that readers contribute. Update: 05/15 16:22 GMT by T : Updates below. Update: 05/15 19:02 GMT by T :Update details: Notes (ongoing) added below on maps, gaming, the Play store, Google+, and more. And, notable, Larry Page is (at this writing) on stage, with an unannounced Q &amp; A session.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7137-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7137_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:34:41">http://news.slashdot.org/story/13/04/23/1615219/the-dark-side-of-amazons-new-pilots</link><title>The Dark Side of Amazon's New Pilots</title><description>I've been really, really excited about digital video distribution lately: first Netflix greenlights jms's return to science fiction TV, and then Amazon announces their new pilots. Perhaps the decade long dearth of any good television is nearing its end! So, with that in mind, I finished up editing Slashdot for the day and sat down to watch some of these new pilots. Only to discover that Amazon has taken away my ability to watch entirely in the name of Digital Restrictions Management.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7137-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7137_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:38:17">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/180397</link><title>Early Pirate Bay Server Immortalized In Museum</title><description>Nerval's Lobster writes "One of the first servers used by notorious torrent tracker The Pirate Bay has ended up at the Computer Museum in Linköping. A picture of the exhibit sent to TorrentFreak shows the server in its original tower casing. The hardware will headline an exhibit on 50 years of file sharing. As the exhibit notes, The Pirate Bay is one of the focal points for the file-sharing phenomenon, used to share both copyrighted works (such as music and movies) and free-for-all material (open-source Linux distributions and the like). The sharing of the former has created a worldwide cat-and-mouse game, with governments doing their best to block file-sharing sites, capture their servers, and prosecute their operators. 'In less than ten years The Pirate Bay has become a contemporary historical phenomenon, due to its distinguished position in the file-sharing debate,' according to the museum exhibit. 'The discussions that have sprung from this simple computer server concerns serious subjects as freedom of speech, global democracy and of course the sole existence of copyright.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7137-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7137_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:41:53">http://entertainment.slashdot.org/story/12/07/20/2020228/movie-review-the-dark-knight-rises</link><title>Movie Review: The Dark Knight Rises</title><description>Unless you've managed to not watch anything in the past three weeks, you're aware that Chris Nolan's final Batman movie is out. With Christian Bale as the low-talking caped crusader, The Dark Knight Rises is two hours and forty-five minutes of of fun. While it lacks a stand-out personal performance like Heath Ledger's Joker in The Dark Knight, it is still a decent ending to this round of Batman movies. There are plenty of familiar faces, and a few new ones as well. Read below for my take on the movie, but be warned: there might be a few spoilers.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7137-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7137_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:43:06">http://books.slashdot.org/story/10/12/06/1328248/beginning-blender</link><title>Beginning Blender</title><description>terrywallwork writes "Lance Flavell and Apress have been busy writing another Blender 2.5 based book. Lance Flavell (known as Lancer in the Blender community) is a very knowledgeable Blender user. So I was very interested to find out about this book when Apress announced its availability. So off I went and ordered the Ebook version of the book in PDF format." Read on for the rest of Terry's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7137-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7137_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:47:27">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/133074</link><title>Russian ASCII Art Animated Cat From 1968</title><description>harrymcc writes "Forty-two years ago, Russian scientists created an impressive sequence of a cat walking about — and it was all the more impressive given that the 'CGI' involved rendering hundreds of images of the cat as ASCII art, then printing out the sequence image by image and photographing it."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7137-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7137_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:51:44">http://science.slashdot.org/story/10/03/07/2037229/algebra-in-wonderland</link><title>Algebra In Wonderland</title><description>theodp writes "As Tim Burton's 'Alice in Wonderland' shatters 3-D and IMAX records en route to a $116.3 million opening, the NY Times offers a rather cerebral op-ed arguing that Alice's search for a beautiful garden can be neatly interpreted as a mishmash of satire directed at the advances taking place in mid-19th century math. Charles Dodgson, who penned 'Alice' under the name Lewis Carroll, was a tutor in mathematics at Christ Church in Oxford who found the radical new math illogical and lacking in intellectual rigor. Op-ed writer Melanie Bayley explains: 'Chapter 6, "Pig and Pepper," parodies the principle of continuity, a bizarre concept from projective geometry, which was introduced in the mid-19th century from France. This principle (now an important aspect of modern topology) involves the idea that one shape can bend and stretch into another, provided it retains the same basic properties — a circle is the same as an ellipse or a parabola (the curve of the Cheshire cat's grin). Taking the notion to its extreme, what works for a circle should also work for a baby. So, when Alice takes the Duchess's baby outside, it turns into a pig. The Cheshire Cat says, "I thought it would."'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7137-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7137_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:52:47">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/115315</link><title>Hulu Again Removed From Boxee and Again Added Back</title><description>An anonymous reader writes "In a mouse and cat game, Hulu the popular online content provider of shows, movies, and more has blocked Boxee yet again from accessing the Hulu content from the Boxee application. Just as Boxee added RSS feeds to include Hulu content, Hulu responded with blocking Boxee users from accessing the content via RSS feeds the very same day. RSS feeds are publicly available and it's really disappointing to hear that a site would block certain applications from accessing their content in such a manner. I would assume that the Boxee development team is currently working on disguising its browser to look like Firefox, Internet Explorer, or some other known browser in an attempt to fool Hulu."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7137-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7137_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:59:08">http://news.slashdot.org/story/07/02/24/2241258/aacs-device-key-found</link><title>AACS Device Key Found</title><description>henrypijames writes "The intense effort by the fair-use community to circumvent AACS (the content protection protocol of HD DVD and Blu-Ray) has produced yet another stunning result: The AACS Device Key of the WinDVD 8 has been found, allowing any movie playable by it to be decrypted. This new discovery by ATARI Vampire of the Doom9 forum is based on the previous research of two other forum members, muslix64 (who found a way to locate the Title Keys of single movies) and arnezami (who extracted the Processing Key of an unspecified software player). AACS certainly seems to be falling apart bit for bit every day now."</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>