<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7141">Cambridge must do</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:56:36" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7141-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7141_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:56:38">http://features.slashdot.org/story/13/02/20/1657209/derek-khanna-answers-your-questions</link><title>Derek Khanna Answers Your Questions</title><description>Last week you had a chance to ask former Republican staffer Derek Khanna about his well publicized firing, copyright law, and the state of the government. Read below to see his answers to your questions.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7141-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7141_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:59:03">http://science.slashdot.org/story/12/02/02/1844205/is-the-earth-gaining-or-losing-mass</link><title>Is the Earth Gaining Or Losing Mass?</title><description>Hugh Pickens writes writes "BBC recently asked physicist and Cambridge University professor Dave Ansell to draw up a balance sheet of the mass that's coming in to the earth, and the mass going out to find out if the earth is gaining or losing mass. By far the biggest contributor to the world's mass is the 40,000 tonnes of dust that is falling from space to Earth every year. 'The Earth is acting like a giant vacuum cleaner powered by gravity in space, pulling in particles of dust,' says Dr. Chris Smith. Another factor increasing the earth's mass is global warming which adds about 160 tonnes a year because as the temperature of the Earth goes up, energy is added to the system, so the mass must go up. On the minus side, at the very center of the Earth, within the inner core, there exists a sphere of uranium five mile in diameter which acts as a natural nuclear reactor so these nuclear reactions cause a loss of mass of about 16 tonnes per year." (Read more, below.)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7141-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7141_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:01:51">http://games.slashdot.org/story/04/04/14/0137208/twisty-little-passages</link><title>Twisty Little Passages</title><description>John Miles writes "It's been almost thirty years since young Laura and Sandy Crowther sat down at a Teletype and took their first steps into the mysterious subterranean world their father, Will, created for them. Now, if Nick Montfort's Twisty Little Passages: An Approach to Interactive Fiction is any indication, Crowther and Woods's pioneering computer game Adventure and its descendants are finally beginning to garner the critical recognition they deserve. At only 286 pages, Twisty Little Passages is a small, accessible book that addresses a deep and complex subject. The author's stated intention is to bring us the first book-length consideration of interactive fiction (IF) as a legitimate literary field, and he has certainly succeeded." Read on for the rest of Miles' review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7141-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7141_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:04:10">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/27207</link><title>Dr. Richard Wallace, part 2</title><description>This is part 2 of the interview with Dr. Richard Wallace. You might want to start with part 1.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7141-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7141_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:05:07">http://news.slashdot.org/story/02/02/28/163234/security-engineering</link><title>Security Engineering</title><description>SilverStr writes: "With all the recent discussion on organizations rethinking their security strategies, I thought I would do a review on one of my favorite books. I have stayed pretty quiet on /. over the years, but security is something I don't think developers anywhere should be taking lightly. Hopefully some of them will get something out of my review and pick this book up." Read on for the rest of his review of Ross Anderson's Security Engineering.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7141-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7141_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:09:36">http://news.slashdot.org/story/01/08/16/2056252/the-fsfs-bradley-kuhn-responds</link><title>The FSF's Bradley Kuhn Responds</title><description>Last week you asked Bradley Kuhn, VP of the Free Software Foundation (FSF) questions about working with RMS, his views on software freedom, and much more. He's answered at length below, on everything from becoming a saint to the "web app loophole," perl, and the next iteration of the GPL.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7141-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7141_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:13:11">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/01/08/07/0050255/computertech-flea-markets</link><title>Computer/Tech Flea Markets?</title><description>Spamlent Green asks: "The recent 'Cashing In On Antique Computers' thread, and the PBS Flea Market documentary made me all misty-eyed for the MIT Swap Fest. I moved from Cambridge to D.C. last year, and haven't been able to find anything like it down here, and I don't mean those bogus 'Comptuer Show and Sale and Monster Truck Rally' events advertised constantly on cheapo UHF stations. So I was curious -- do any DC-MD-No.VA-area Slashdot-ers know of events like this down here -- or anywhere else in the country for that matter? They must be out there ..."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7141-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7141_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:15:08">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/00/04/27/107235/philip-greenspun-answers</link><title>Philip Greenspun Answers</title><description>Here you go: Philip Greenspun talks of life, ArsDigita, fame, Oracle, photography, and that sort of thing in respone to the fascinating questions you submitted earlier this week. Enjoy!</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>