<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7146">why do leaves fall</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:21:58" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7146-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7146_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:22:01">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/191977</link><title>What I Did During My Summer Vacation: Burning Man Edition</title><description>Bennett Haselton writes: "While nothing can really 'prepare' you for your first time at Burning Man, there are a few simple steps that can eliminate a lot of the stress. Unfortunately it can be hard to get information out of the 10-year veterans about how to do things the easy way (some of them probably view the 'easy way' as 'ruining the whole point'). So here's some advice instead from someone who just got back from their first time, and who likes to take the path of least resistance." Keep reading for the rest of Bennett's Burning Man advice.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7146-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7146_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:26:23">http://yro.slashdot.org/story/10/02/10/1517228/power-to-the-pop-ups</link><title>Power To the Pop-Ups</title><description>Slashdot frequent contributor Bennett Haselton writes a piece advocating for Pop-Ups and even more obtrusive advertising. But not for the reasons you might think. He says "Annoying pop-up ads have been a great friend to Internet freedom, by enabling the operation of proxy sites that would be too expensive to operate otherwise. With the rising costs of making new proxy sites to stay ahead of the 'censorware' companies, even more intrusive ads could be an even bigger friend to Internet freedom. Got any ideas for how those more intrusive ads could work?" Clicky clicky below to read his point.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7146-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7146_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:31:22">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/10/01/07/2049224/hotmailers-hawking-hoax-hunan-half-offs</link><title>Hotmailers Hawking Hoax Hunan Half-Offs</title><description>Frequent Slashdot contributor Bennett Haselton writes "An estimated 200,000 Hotmail users currently have their auto-reply set to a message spamming an advertisement for Chinese scam websites, which sell "discounted" electronics. Presumably the spammers compromised a large number of Hotmail accounts to pull this off, but wouldn't it be pretty easy for Hotmail to query for which users have that set as their auto-reply, and turn the auto-reply off for them?" Read below for Bennett's thoughts.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7146-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7146_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:33:27">http://books.slashdot.org/story/09/12/28/1424255/ruby-in-practice</link><title>Ruby In Practice</title><description>littleidea writes "Ruby In Practice is like a sampler platter that picks up where The Ruby Way leaves off. Depending on your tastes each of the different offerings are delicious, but sometimes leave you wishing you had a whole order of just that. Then again, if you eat the whole thing, chances are you won't be hungry." Keep reading for the rest of Andrew's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7146-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7146_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:35:35">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/114779</link><title>How To Be A Geek Goddess</title><description>stoolpigeon writes "The geek world is dominated by those of the male persuasion. For those of us working in a technology related field, or who spend a considerable amount of time pursuing high tech leisure, we usually find women to be in the minority. I've seen considerable discussion over the years on how to change this imbalance but I think it is safe to say that right now that it remains. Many women are interested in using technology, they just don't want to dive in to quite the same depth. Or they may not be interested in the way most men approach it. Columnist and tech-writer Christina Tynan-Wood has attempted to come to their rescue with her book How To Be A Geek Goddess." Read below for the rest of JR's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7146-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7146_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:37:18">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/60302</link><title>JBoss - A Developer's Notebook</title><description>Pankaj Kumar writes "Controversies aside, JBoss has emerged as a credible alternative to commercial J2EE App Servers for developing and deploying Java based server applications. Besides the usual advantages of open source and GPL licensing, what sets it apart is its JMX based microkernel, a light-weight framework to run independently developed Java programs within a single JVM. Together, these make it possible for one to pick and choose components and assemble a custom server anywhere between the two extremes (and beyond!) of a simple Servlet Container and a full-fledged J2EE Server. JBoss - A Developer's Notebook by Norman Richards, a JBoss developer at JBoss, Inc., and Sam Griffith, Jr., a software consultant and trainer, is a no-fluff How-To guide on doing stuff with JBoss in O'Reilly's new Developer Notebook format." Read on for Kumar's review of the book.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7146-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7146_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:39:33">http://entertainment.slashdot.org/story/04/12/08/1625256/the-pocket-and-the-pendant</link><title>The Pocket and the Pendant</title><description>Aeonite (Michael Fiegel) writes "Mark Jeffrey is probably best known to Slashdotters as an online media entrepreneur and one of the co-founders (along with Mike Maerz and Jim Bumgardner) of The Palace, an avatar-based chat system popular in the late 1990s. Jeffrey is not to be confused with Neal Stephenson, though both men have websites featuring clockwork imagery, goatees, and novels which contain references to Sumerian mythology -- Stephenson's Snow Crash and Jeffrey's first novel, The Pocket and the Pendant. From a distance, one might be inclined to believe that similarities to Stephenson's own work are more than cosmetic: Jeffrey thanks Stephenson on the Acknowledgments page of his novel (along with Stephen R. Donaldson and Carl Jung, among others), and one Lulu.com review (mentioned in a press release) describes The Pocket and the Pendant as being 'like Stargate, Harry Potter, Snow Crash and the old Land of the Lost rolled into one.'" Read on for the rest of Fiegel's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7146-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7146_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:44:25">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/25568</link><title>Review: U-571</title><description>Daryl Carpenter writes "After months of grumbling and mild assaults, I finally vent my rage with this penultimate [ed. note: there will be another one?] assault on the cinematic drivel known as "U-571". Did he like it? I don't know. You be the judge.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7146-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7146_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:48:11">http://news.slashdot.org/story/02/03/25/188212/flesh-and-machines-how-robots-will-change-us</link><title>Flesh and Machines: How Robots Will Change Us</title><description>Peter Wayner writes: "A long time ago, I posed for a portrait at a church fair. The priest wandered by, paused for a second, and then caught up to me later. "Do you like the picture?" he asked. When I said it was fine, he told me, "Oh, I think its terrible. It doesn't look like you at all. But that doesn't matter. The artist is supposed to create a picture of what you think you look like." Read on to see what this has to do with robots as Peter reviews Rod Brook's new book.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7146-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7146_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:49:45">http://slashdot.org/story/01/10/29/173252/wil-wheaton-responds-to-your-questions</link><title>Wil Wheaton Responds to your Questions.</title><description>Here we go, answer to Your Questions from Wil Wheaton. Share and Enjoy! A big thanks to Wil for taking the time to answer so many of our questions.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>