<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7147">breast cancer review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:51:28" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7147-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7147_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:51:29">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/108095</link><title>Computer Detection Effective In Spotting Cancer</title><description>Anti-Globalism notes a large study out of the UK indicating that computer-aided detection can be as effective at spotting breast cancer as two experts reading the x-rays. Mammograms in Britain are routinely checked by two radiologists or technicians, which is thought to be better than a single review (in the US only a single radiologist reads each mammogram). In a randomized study of 31,000 women, researchers found that a single expert aided by a computer does as well as two pairs of eyes. CAD spotted nearly the same number of cancers, 198 out of 227, compared to 199 for the two readers. "In places like the United States, 'Where single reading is standard practice, computer-aided detection has the potential to improve cancer-detection rates to the level achieved by double reading,' the researchers said."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7147-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7147_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:53:34">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/25874</link><title>ACLU and ALA Victorious in CIPA Challenge</title><description>Several people have submitted this news blurb about a victory in the CIPA case. If CIPA doesn't ring a bell, my earlier summary should help, or see this article from last month when the suit was heard in court. The ALA's CIPA page has more information, or read the lengthy decision. This is a rather surprising bit of good news; while the government often has great discretion in deciding how funds are spent (read my summary above for how the law worked), the judges in this case accepted the argument that requiring censoring software automatically lead to censoring things that weren't obscene, or child pornography, or "harmful to minors", and that that wasn't acceptable. I've reproduced the first part of the decision below. The government may choose to (and probably will) appeal to the Supreme Court.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>