<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7174">seal team 6</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:40:26" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7174-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7174_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:40:28">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/14/01/06/2344218/australian-team-working-on-engines-without-piston-rings</link><title>Australian Team Working On Engines Without Piston Rings</title><description>JabrTheHut writes "An Australian team is seeking funding for bringing an interesting idea to market: cylinder engines without piston rings. The idea is to use small grooves that create a pressure wave that acts as a seal for the piston, eliminating the piston ring and the associated friction. Engines would then run cooler, could be more energy efficient, and might even burn fuel more efficiently, at least according to the article. Mind you, they haven't even built a working prototype yet. If it works I'd love to fit this into an older car."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7174-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7174_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:42:16">http://yro.slashdot.org/story/13/04/11/0413253/bin-laden-raid-member-to-be-wikileaks-witness</link><title>Bin Laden Raid Member To Be WikiLeaks Witness</title><description>the simurgh writes in with the latest in the court-martial of Bradley Manning. "A military judge cleared the way Wednesday for a member of the team that raided Osama bin Laden's compound to testify at the trial of Pfc. Bradley Manning charged in the WikiLeaks massive classified document leak. Col. Denise Lind ruled for the prosecution during a court-martial pretrial hearing. Prosecutors say the witness, presumably a Navy SEAL, collected digital evidence showing that the al-Qaida leader requested and received from an associate some of the documents Manning has acknowledged leaking. Defense attorneys had argued that proof of receipt wasn't relevant to whether Manning aided the enemy, the most serious charge he faces, punishable by life imprisonment. 'The government must prove beyond a reasonable doubt that the intelligence is given to and received by the enemy,' Lind said. The judge disagreed."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7174-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7174_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:44:03">http://games.slashdot.org/story/12/11/09/0322230/navy-seals-disciplined-for-revealing-secrets-as-consultants-on-video-game</link><title>Navy Seals Disciplined For Revealing Secrets As Consultants On Video Game</title><description>Hugh Pickens writes "CBS reports that seven active duty members of SEAL Team Six, best known for killing Osama bin Laden, have been disciplined for revealing secrets working as paid consultants on a video game, Medal of Honor: Warfighter. The game does not recreate the bin Laden raid, but it does portray realistic missions, such as an attack on a pirates' den in Somalia. Electronic Arts boasts that real commandos, both active duty and retired, help make its games as realistic as possible. EA says Medal of Honor Warfighter was 'written by actual U.S. Tier 1 Operators while deployed overseas,' and that it 'features a dotted line to real world events and provides players a view into globally recognized threats and situations letting them experience the action as it might have unfolded.' It is unclear what secrets members of SEAL Team Six gave away, but while serving as consultants for the game, they used classified material which had been given to them by the Navy and also violated the unwritten code that SEALs are silent warriors who shun the spotlight. 'We do not tolerate deviations from the policies that govern who we are and what we do as Sailors in the United States Navy,' says Deputy Commander of Naval Special Warfare, Rear Admiral Garry Bonelli. 'The non-judicial punishment decisions made today send a clear message throughout our Force that we are and will be held to a high standard of accountability.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7174-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7174_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:45:54">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/156630</link><title>When Schools Are the Police</title><description>First time accepted submitter Is Any Nickname Left writes "The Washington Post has an article on school systems with their own police forces. It focuses on Texas, which has the highest number of 'School Police Departments,' of which there are so many they have their own trade association. Highlights: 1) Houston fourth-grader stood on a stool so he could see the judge. He pleaded guilty. To a scuffle on a school bus. 2) 275,000 juvenile tickets in fiscal 2009, to students as young as 5. 3) Austin middle school student ticketed after she sprayed herself with perfume when classmates said she smelled. 4) a 17-year-old was in court after he and his girlfriend poured milk on each other. 'She was mad at me because I broke up with her,' he said. I waiting for the Alamo Heights Special Airborne Brigade and SEAL TEAM CROCKETT."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7174-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7174_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:47:50">http://news.slashdot.org/story/11/05/14/195241/disney-seeks-trademark-on-seal-team-6</link><title>Disney Seeks Trademark On 'Seal Team 6'</title><description>The Grim Reefer2 writes "MediaBistro has learned that the Walt Disney Company has applied for a trademark on the phrase 'Seal Team 6,' the name of the special forces unit that killed the world's most wanted man. Disney now owns the exclusive rights to put Seal Team 6 on 'clothing, footwear, headwear, toys, games and entertainment and education services.' Disney made the move only two days after bin Laden's death was announced." According to a report in the Orlando Sentinel, "this is not the first time a company has trademarked SEAL Team 6. Previous owner NovaLogic, Inc., abandoned two associated trademarks in 2006. Those trademarks focused on computer and video gaming."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7174-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7174_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:50:51">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/10/09/02/0017208/li-ion-batteries-get-green-seal-of-approval</link><title>Li-Ion Batteries Get Green Seal of Approval</title><description>thecarchik writes "It is not an easy task to compare the environmental effects of battery powered cars to those caused by conventionally fueled automobiles. The degree to which manufacture, usage and disposal of the batteries used to store the necessary electrical energy are detrimental to the environment is not exactly known. Now, for the first time, a team of Empa scientists have made a detailed life cycle assessment (LCA) or ecobalance of lithium-ion (Li-ion) batteries, in particular the chemically improved (i.e. more environmentally friendly) version of the ones most frequently used in electric vehicles. Researchers decided to find out for sure. They calculated the ecological footprints of electric cars fitted with Li-ion batteries, taking into account all possible relevant factors, from those associated with the production of individual parts all the way through to the scrapping of the vehicle and the disposal of the remains, including the operation of the vehicle during its lifetime."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7174-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7174_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:54:14">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/127710</link><title>Seals Face Assault Charges After Terrorist Capture</title><description>Three Navy SEALs are facing assault charges after the capture of one of the most wanted terrorists in Iraq, Ahmed Hashim Abed. Abed is believed to have organized the murder and mutilation of four Blackwater USA security guards in Fallujah. The accused terrorist, who had a bloody lip, claims that he was punched in the face and not giving a foot massage, or allowed to listen to his iPod as one might expect when a SEAL team captures you. The SEALs have requested a trial by court-martial.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7174-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7174_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:58:54">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/60154</link><title>Gen Con Indy 2005 In A Nutshell</title><description>Every year, the pilgrimage to Gen Con brings tabletop roleplayers, wargamers, boardgame enthusiasts, and LARPers together for four days of unbridled nerdery. Besides participating in games, some of which have been around for decades, there are always new releases and previews to tantalize the gaming public. Gen Con is the tabletop industry's version of E3, where the year ahead is laid out by the big names. Read on for a taste of what your Friendly Local Gaming Store will have to offer in the near future.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7174-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7174_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:02:44">http://slashdot.org/story/02/10/14/2023216/latest-salvos-in-the-ongoing-battle-of-webcasting</link><title>Latest Salvos in the Ongoing Battle Of Webcasting</title><description>detroitindustrial writes "The Register reports on a backroom deal that screws small webcasters. The Voice of Webcasters, working with the RIAA, negotiated a deal that Congress is trying to make into a law. These rates give big discounts to the largest webcasters, while leaving around 96% of the smaller webcasters to suffer and die under the CARP rate. This is being done through the bill H.R. 5469, the Small Webcaster Amendment Act of 2002. It was originally a one paragraph bill to delay the CARP rates for 6 months, and was widely supported in its original form by the webcasting community. After the RIAA rewrote it, it turned into 30-page monstrosity that had no relation to the original bill. It has already passed in the House. Ann Gabriel, who was on the International Webcasting Associaion legislative committee, recently resigned in disgust over this sell out." It appears that the Register article misrepresents a few of the issues. Rusty Hodge, of SomaFM, has more on the actual effects of HR 5469...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7174-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7174_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:05:36">http://yro.slashdot.org/story/01/11/30/1739226/felten-vs-riaa-hearing</link><title>Felten vs. RIAA Hearing</title><description>On Wednesday I attended a hearing in Felten vs. RIAA, the lawsuit filed by Professor Felten, other Princeton researchers, and USENIX against the RIAA, SDMI, Verance, and the Department of Justice. As you already know, the judge dismissed the case. But taking a look at the hearing might provide some insight into how the judicial system works.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>