<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7176"> weather in nyc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:41:02" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7176-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7176_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:41:04">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/14/04/19/1444216/the-design-flaw-that-almost-wiped-out-an-nyc-skyscraper</link><title>The Design Flaw That Almost Wiped Out an NYC Skyscraper</title><description>Hugh Pickens DOT Com (2995471) writes "Joel Werner writes in Slate that when Citicorp Center was built in 1977 it was, at 59 stories, the seventh-tallest building in the world but no one figured out until after it was built that although the chief structural engineer, William LeMessurier, had properly accounted for perpendicular winds, the building was particularly vulnerable to quartering winds — in part due to cost-saving changes made to the original plan by the contractor. "According to LeMessurier, in 1978 an undergraduate architecture student contacted him with a bold claim about LeMessurier's building: that Citicorp Center could blow over in the wind," writes Werner. "LeMessurier realized that a major storm could cause a blackout and render the tuned mass damper inoperable. Without the tuned mass damper, LeMessurier calculated that a storm powerful enough to take out the building hit New York every 16 years." In other words, for every year Citicorp Center was standing, there was about a 1-in-16 chance that it would collapse." (Read on for more.)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7176-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7176_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:42:38">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/13/06/18/1832251/with-an-eye-toward-disaster-nyc-debuts-solar-charging-stations</link><title>With an Eye Toward Disaster, NYC Debuts Solar Charging Stations</title><description>Nerval's Lobster writes "When hurricane Sandy pummeled New York City last fall, it left a sizable percentage of the metropolis without electricity. Residents had trouble keeping their phones and tablets charged, and often walked across whole neighborhoods to reach zones with power. Come the next disaster, at least a few citizens could communicate a little easier thanks to 25 solar-powered charging stations going up around the city. The stations—known as 'Street Charge' — are the result of a partnership between AT&amp;T, Brooklyn design studio Pensa, and portable solar-power maker Goal Zero (with approval by the city's Parks Department). The first unit will deploy in Brooklyn's Fort Green Park on June 18, followed in short order by others in Union Square, Central Park, the Rockaways, and other locations. Each station incorporates lithium-ion batteries in addition to solar panels; charging a phone to full capacity could take as long as two hours, but the time necessary for a partial charge is much shorter. But a couple of charging stations also won't help very much if half the city is without power: In order to help mitigate the effects of the next hurricane, New York City major Michael Bloomberg has put forward a $20 billion plan for seawalls, levees, and dozens of other improvements. 'Sandy exposed weaknesses in the city's telecommunications infrastructure — including the location of critical facilities in areas that are susceptible to flooding,' reads one section of the plan's accompanying report. The city will harden the system 'by increasing the accountability of telecommunications providers to invest in resiliency and by using new regulatory authority to enable rapid recovery after extreme weather events.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7176-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7176_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:45:09">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/12/11/07/1847207/how-coresite-survived-sandy</link><title>How CoreSite Survived Sandy</title><description>Nerval's Lobster writes "When Hurricane Sandy hit the East Coast, the combination of high winds, rain, and storm surges wreaked havoc on homes and businesses alike. With a data center on the Avenue of the Americas, CoreSite Realty escaped the worst the storm had to offer. But was it coincidence or careful planning? Slashdot sat down for an interview with Billie Haggard, CoreSite's senior vice president of data centers. He's responsible for the design, construction, maintenance, facilities staffing and uptime, reliability and energy efficiency of CoreSite's data centers. He described what it took to weather the worst weather to hit New York City in decades."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7176-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7176_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:46:43">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/12/09/02/019252/high-tech-companies-becoming-fools-for-the-city</link><title>High Tech Companies Becoming Fools For the City</title><description>theodp writes "Drawn by amenities and talent, the WSJ reports that tech firms are saying goodbye to office parks and opting for cities. Pinterest, Zynga, Yelp, Square, Twitter, and Salesforce.com are some of the more notable tech companies who are taking up residence in San Francisco. New York City's Silicon Alley is now home to more than 500 new start-up companies like Kickstarter and Tumblr, not to mention the gigantic Google satellite in the old Port Authority Building. London, Seattle, and even downtown Las Vegas are also seeing infusions of techies. So, why are tech companies eschewing Silicon Valley and going all Fool for the City? 'Silicon Valley proper is soul-crushing suburban sprawl,' Paul Graham presciently explained in 2006. 'It has fabulous weather, which makes it significantly better than the soul-crushing sprawl of most other American cities. But a competitor that managed to avoid sprawl would have real leverage.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7176-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7176_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:48:50">http://ask.slashdot.org/story/03/04/30/0524229/using-commoditized-computers-setups-for-stock-trading</link><title>Using Commoditized Computers Setups for Stock Trading?</title><description>An anonymous reader asks: "Thanks to Walmart, TigerDirect, and Gnu/Linux, I can get computers at about $200 now. Thanks to Matrox, I have several multi-head video cards. Thanks to a hacker's convention last year, I have a truckload of monitors that haven't been put to use yet. I've been out of the financial markets since 1996. I'm itching to get back in now, especially since conditions will be very favorable shortly. Since I've lost my shirt in the markets already (most investors/traders loose their shirts at least once before striking it rich, and my beating was especially instructive), I'm now ready for better returns. Gnu/Linux is well known to support multiple monitor setups. I've seen 4 monitor setups per box in some financial firms, and I recently read a story on the National Weather Service using 3 monitor setups on another OSDN channel. I've also used a Quotrek trading monitor in the past, for monitoring stocks and other financials in real-time. This was before I was a penguinista. Now that I know a bit about Linux systems, I'd like to know the following: What Gnu/Linux applications can I use to monitor and/or process stocks, options, bonds, financial news, and other related information via low cost Gnu/Linux computing solutions, broadband, and multi-head video cards? Free software only, please"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7176-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7176_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:52:32">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/12228</link><title>Plugging Holes In The GPL</title><description>For years, the GNU Public License -- the copyleft which Linux has flourished under -- has lived a life that is close to charmed. Talk has surfaced of a possible upcoming court challenge to the GPL, but author Peter Wayner looks here slightly further into the future, speculating on what changes might preserve the GPL against other marketplace challenges as well. Richard M. Stallman has doubtless been wrestling with the issues presented here since before he released the GPL at all; I hope that Wayner's thoughts will raise discussion that will strengthen the GPL as it evolves.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>