<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7207">earthquake</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:49:23" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7207-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7207_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:49:26">http://yro.slashdot.org/story/14/04/05/2144208/under-revised-quake-estimates-dozens-of-nuclear-reactors-face-problems</link><title>Under Revised Quake Estimates, Dozens of Nuclear Reactors Face Problems</title><description>mdsolar (1045926) writes "Owners of at least two dozen nuclear reactors across the United States, including the operator of Indian Point 2, in Buchanan, N.Y., have told the Nuclear Regulatory Commission that they cannot show that their reactors would withstand the most severe earthquake that revised estimates say they might face, according to industry experts. As a result, the reactors' owners will be required to undertake extensive analyses of their structures and components. Those are generally sturdier than assumed in licensing documents, but owners of some plants may be forced to make physical changes, and are likely to spend about $5 million each just for the analysis."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7207-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7207_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:52:36">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/200199</link><title>8.2 Earthquake Off the Coast of Chile, Tsunami Triggered</title><description>An 8.2-magnitude earthquake has struck roughly 60km off the cost of Chile. Its depth was approximately 20.1km. A tsunami has been generated, and evacuations have been ordered along the coast near the strike. Tsunami warnings were also issued for Peru and Ecuador. According to the Associated Press, "Coastal residents of northern Chile evacuated calmly as waves measuring almost 2 meters (6 1/2 feet) struck ahead of a tsunami that was expected to come ashore later. ... Chile's emergency service reported some roads blocked by landslides caused by the quake, but said no injuries had been reported so far."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7207-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7207_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:53:53">http://science.slashdot.org/story/14/04/01/1930208/how-a-seismic-cloak-could-slow-down-an-earthquake</link><title>How a 'Seismic Cloak' Could Slow Down an Earthquake</title><description>Daniel_Stuckey writes "The United States is currently gripped in a bout of earthquake mania, following a series of significant tremors in the West. And any time Yellowstone, LA, or San Francisco shakes, people start to wonder if it's a sign of The Big One to come. Yet even after decades of research, earthquake prediction remains notoriously hard, and not every building in quake-prone areas has an earthquake-resistant design. What if, instead of quaking in our boots, we could stop quakes in their tracks? Theoretically, it's not a crazy idea. Earthquakes propagate in waves, and if noise-canceling headphones have taught us anything, it's that waves can be absorbed, reflected, or canceled out. Today, a paper published in Physical Review Letters suggests how that might be done. It's the result of French research into the use of metamaterials—broadly, materials with properties not found in nature—to modify seismic waves, like a seismic cloaking device."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7207-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7207_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:58:15">http://news.slashdot.org/story/14/03/29/1234206/51-earthquake-hits-california</link><title>5.1 Earthquake Hits California</title><description>An anonymous reader writes "A 5.1 earthquake hit Southern California at 9:09PM local time on Friday. It was preceded by a 3.6 earthquake, then followed by 3.4 and 3.6 quakes, as well as 100+ smaller aftershocks. The United States Geological Survey has a map showing the epicenter. There have been no reported deaths, though roughly 50 people have been displaced from their homes. 'The shake caused a rock slide in Carbon Canyon, causing a car to overturn, according to the Brea Police Department. Fullerton police received reports of water main breaks and windows shattering, but primarily had residents calling about burglar alarms being set off by the quake.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7207-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7207_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:02:32">http://science.slashdot.org/story/14/03/26/1423247/physicists-produce-antineutrino-map-of-the-world</link><title>Physicists Produce Antineutrino Map of the World</title><description>KentuckyFC (1144503) writes "The origin of the heat generated inside the Earth is one of the great mysteries of geophysics. Researchers know that almost all this heat is generated by the decay of radioactive elements such as potassium-40, thorium-232 and uranium-238. But what they don't know is how these elements are distributed inside the planet and how much heat each contributes. In the next few years, they hope to get some answers thanks to the emerging science of antineutrino geophysics. Since radioactive decay produces antineutrinos, an experiment that measures these particles coming out of the Earth should provide a detailed picture of the distribution of the elements within it. 

But there's a problem. Nuclear reactors also produce copious numbers of antineutrinos and these can swamp the signal from inside the Earth. What's needed is a map showing the distribution of reactor antineutrinos so that geophysicists can choose the best places to put their experiments. Just such a map is exactly what a team of nuclear physicists has now produced. The map shows that planned experiments in Hawaii and Curacao, off the coast of Venezuela, are in excellent locations and that Japan has recently become a much better site thanks to the shut down of the country's nuclear industry following the 2011 Tohoku earthquake. But a European experiment currently being planned in south-east France doesn't come off so well."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7207-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7207_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:05:32">http://slashdot.org/story/14/03/11/1636250/japan-marks-3rd-anniversary-of-tsunami-disaster</link><title>Japan Marks 3rd Anniversary of Tsunami Disaster</title><description>AmiMoJo writes "Today Japan marks the third anniversary of the 11th of March 2011 disaster when the country was hit by a magnitude 9 earthquake huge tsunami and severe nuclear accident. More than 18,500 people were killed or went missing. Nearly 3,000 others died while evacuated from their homes, and over a quarter of a million people were still living in temporary housing as of February. Work to build new housing on higher ground is lagging behind schedule. 

Three reactors melted down at the Fukushima Daiichi nuclear power plant following the quake and tsunami, but the exact cause of the accident is still unknown. How massive amounts of radioactive materials from the reactors were dispersed is also unclear. Today was also the day when hundreds of former residents announced that they were suing TEPCO, the plant operator, and the government for additional compensation." Although the nuclear accident was dwarfed by the other devastation, the effects of the meltdown will be felt for much longer. The Bulletin of Atomic Scientists published an article today on the reactors that didn't meltdown, and the NRC chair has some comments on the progress at Fukishima.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7207-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7207_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:09:28">http://slashdot.org/story/14/03/09/181244/3-years-later-a-fukushima-workers-eyewitness-story</link><title>3 Years Later: A Fukushima Worker's Eyewitness Story</title><description>Lasrick writes "Tuesday, March 11 is the 3rd anniversary of the Fukushima disaster. In this article, a worker at the Fukushima Daiichi Nuclear Power Station gives his eyewitness account of what happened there in the immediate wake of a massive earthquake and tsunami that caused three of the station's reactor cores to melt." The witness, says the story, "was promised anonymity as a condition of providing his account."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7207-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7207_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:11:21">http://news.slashdot.org/story/14/02/21/180251/safety-measures-fail-to-stop-fukushima-plant-leaks</link><title>Safety Measures Fail To Stop Fukushima Plant Leaks</title><description>AmiMoJo writes "The operator of the Fukushima Daiichi plant has been developing countermeasures to deal with repeated leaks from tanks of contaminated water. But despite the measures, 100 tons of radioactive water leaked on Wednesday and Thursday. 'The leaked water was among the most severely contaminated that Tepco has reported in the aftermath of the March 2011 disaster at the Fukushima Daiichi plant, when damage caused by an earthquake and a tsunami led to meltdowns in three of the plant’s reactors. Each liter of the water contained, on average, 230 million becquerels of particles giving off beta radiation, the company said. About half of the particles were likely to be strontium 90, which is readily taken up by the human body in the same way that calcium is, and can cause bone cancer and leukemia.' The estimated volume of the leaked radioactive materials caused Japan's nuclear regulator to rank the leak a level-3 serious accident. The international scale of nuclear and radiological events ranges from zero to 7."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7207-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7207_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:13:55">http://science.slashdot.org/story/13/12/24/183229/scientists-predict-earthquakes-location-and-strength</link><title>Scientists Predict Earthquake's Location and Strength</title><description>A new study has been published in Nature Geoscience (abstract) detailing how scientists correctly anticipated the location and strength of an earthquake earlier this year. On September 5th, a 7.6 earthquake rocked Costa Rica's Nicoya Peninsula. That region had seen earthquakes of (roughly) magnitude 7 in 1853, 1900, and 1950, so "geoscientists had forecast that a magnitude 7.7 to 7.8 quake should occur around the year 2000, plus or minus 20 years." "The Nicoya Peninsula is prone to earthquakes because it's an area of subduction, where the Cocos Plate is pushing underneath the Caribbean Plate, moving at a rate of about 8.5 centimeters per year. When regions such as this suddenly slip, they produce a megathrust earthquake. Most of the world's largest earthquakes — including the magnitude 9.0 Tohoku-Oki quake in Japan in 2011 and the magnitude 9.15 Sumatra-Andaman earthquake in 2004, both of which produced devastating tsunamis — fall into this category. .. The close study of this region allowed scientists to calculate how much strain was building in the fault and in May 2012 they published a study in which they identified two locked spots capable of producing an earthquake similar to the one in 1950. In September of that year, the landward patch ruptured and produced the earthquake. The offshore one is still locked and capable of producing a substantial but smaller earthquake, an aftershock with a magnitude as high as 6.9, the researchers say."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7207-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7207_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:16:24">http://science.slashdot.org/story/13/12/07/1928210/killer-qualities-of-japanese-fault-revealed</link><title>Killer Qualities of Japanese Fault Revealed</title><description>Lasrick sends this report from Nature News: "The devastating 2011 earthquake and tsunami in Japan shocked researchers who did not expect that the seismic fault involved could release so much energy. Now the world's deepest-drilling oceanographic ship has been able to pin down the odd geology that made this disaster so horrific. The fault turns out to be unusually thin and weak, the researchers report in Science this week1–3. The results will help to pin down whether other offshore faults around the world are capable of triggering the same scale of disaster. ... The coring revealed a very thin clay layer, about 5 meters thick, separating the two sliding tectonic plates (abstract). 'That’s just weird,' says Emily Brodsky of the University of California, Santa Cruz (UCSC), who is an author on all three Science papers this week. 'Usually it’s tens of meters or more.' Lab tests confirmed that this wet clay layer is extremely slippery, and gets even more so under stress (abstract). As sliding creates friction and heat, water in the clay gets pressurized and pushes up against the impermeable rock around it. That 'jacks open the fault” says Brodsky, allowing it to slip even more. The temperature sensors found that more than a year after the quake, the fault was still up to 0.31 C warmer than its surroundings (abstract). From this they could extrapolate how much heat was generated from friction during the sliding event. Their calculations confirmed the very low friction of the 5-meter-thick clay layer."</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>