<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7211">punctuation guide</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:23:18" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7211-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7211_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:23:20">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/166239</link><title>Book Review: Microsoft Manual of Style</title><description>benrothke writes "The Chicago Manual of Style (CMS), now in its 16th edition, is the de facto style guide for American writers. It deals with aspects of editorial practice, grammar, usage, document preparation and more. It's just one of many style guides for writers. The Microsoft Manual of Style, just released in its 4th edition, attempts to do for the technical writers what the CMS has done for journalists and other writers." Read below for the rest of Ben's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7211-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7211_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:24:26">http://news.slashdot.org/story/09/06/15/1331252/drupal-6-ultimate-community-site-guide</link><title>Drupal 6: Ultimate Community Site Guide</title><description>Michael J. Ross writes "Among the more popular and better-regarded content management systems (CMSs), Drupal is distinguished partly by its building-block approach, in which a website's functionality is built up in pieces, each of which is a module (either core or contributed). The opposite approach — using far fewer but more encompassing modules — is generally preferred by non-developers who do not relish integrating a sizable collection of modules or trying to modify the underlying code. Nonetheless, anyone who wishes to build a Drupal-based social website, can learn how to do so in a new e-book titled Drupal 6: Ultimate Community Site Guide." Read below for the rest of Michael's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7211-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7211_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:27:31">http://news.slashdot.org/story/05/08/12/1650234/podcasting</link><title>Podcasting</title><description>SFEley (Stephen Eley) writes "Todd Cochrane's Podcasting: The Do-It-Yourself Guide has been heavily pushed in the podcasting community as the first of a wave of podcasting books to be released in the next several months. All of these books will surely cover the same themes, more or less: what podcasts are, how to listen to them, and how to produce your own. The popularity of podcasting is exploding right now, with coverage in every press outlet and Apple hyping it as The Next Big Thing. It's easy to see that there will be a huge demand for these books, even if they don't do much more than state the obvious. So what about this one? Other than being the first, does it offer any compelling virtues for the would-be podcaster or listener?" Read on for Eley's answer to that question.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7211-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7211_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:31:25">http://science.slashdot.org/story/04/03/17/2041238/everything-and-more</link><title>Everything and More</title><description>Chris Cowell-Shah writes "If David Foster Wallace can't explain infinity to us, nobody can. At least, that's what I told myself while anxiously waiting for his Everything and More: A Compact History of Infinity. The book promised to be an intellectual history of the mathematical concept of infinity, with heavy doses of history, math, and philosophy. And while it proves heavy going at times, I'm pleased to say that it delivers admirably on this promise." Read on for Cowell-Shah's lengthy review of Everything and More.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>