<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7216">salmonella</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:06:20" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7216-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7216_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:06:22">http://news.slashdot.org/story/14/03/30/2053246/million-jars-of-peanut-butter-dumped-in-new-mexico-landfill</link><title>Million Jars of Peanut Butter Dumped In New Mexico Landfill</title><description>Hugh Pickens DOT Com (2995471) writes "The Guardian reports that a million jars of peanut butter are going to be dumped in a New Mexico landfill and bulldozed over after retailer Costco refused to take shipment of the peanut butter and declined requests to let it be donated to food banks or repackaged or sold to brokers who provide food to institutions like prisons. The peanut butter comes from a bankrupt peanut-processing plant that was at the heart of a salmonella outbreak in 2012 and although 'all parties agreed there's nothing wrong with the peanut butter from a health and safety issue,' court records show that on a 19 March conference call Costco said 'it would not agree to any disposition ... other than destruction.' 

The product was tested extensively and determined to be safe. Costco initially agreed to allowing the peanut butter to be sold, but rejected it as 'not merchantable' because of leaking peanut oil. So instead of selling or donating the peanut butter, with a value estimated at $2.6m, the estate is paying about $60,000 to transport 950,000 jars – or about 25 tons – to the Curry County landfill in Clovis, where public works director Clint Bunch says it 'will go in with our regular waste and covered with dirt'. Despite the peanut butter being safe, Curry County landfill employee Tim Stacy says that no one will be able to consume the peanut butter once it's dumped because it will be immediately rolled over with a bulldozer, destroying the supply. Stacy added more trash will then be dumped on top of the pile. Sonya Warwick, spokeswoman for New Mexico's largest food bank, declined to comment directly on the situation, but she noted that rescued food accounted for 74% of what Roadrunner Food Bank distributed across New Mexico last year. 'Access to rescued food allows us to provide a more well-rounded and balanced meal to New Mexicans experiencing hunger.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7216-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7216_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:08:43">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/14/02/28/1637257/water-filtration-with-a-tree-branch</link><title>Water Filtration With a Tree Branch</title><description>Taco Cowboy writes "Dirty water is a major cause of mortality in the developing world. 'The most common water-borne pathogens are bacteria (e.g. Escherichia coli, Salmonella typhi, Vibrio cholerae), viruses (e.g. adenoviruses, enteroviruses, hepatitis, rotavirus), and protozoa (e.g. giardia). These pathogens cause child mortality and also contribute to malnutrition and stunted growth of children.' People have been working on engineering cheaper and cheaper filtration systems for years, but now a group of researchers has found a promising and simple solution: a tree branch. 'Approximately 3 cm^3 of sapwood can filter water at the rate of several liters per day, sufficient to meet the clean drinking water needs of one person.' 'Before experimenting with contaminated water, the group used water mixed with red ink particles ranging from 70 to 500 nanometers in size. After all the liquid passed through, the researchers sliced the sapwood in half lengthwise, and observed that much of the red dye was contained within the very top layers of the wood, while the filtrate, or filtered water, was clear. This experiment showed that sapwood is naturally able to filter out particles bigger than about 70 nanometers.' The team tested E. coli-contaminated water, and the branch was able to filter out 99 percent of the bacterial cells."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7216-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7216_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:13:05">http://news.slashdot.org/story/12/12/03/0214220/scientists-develop-sixty-day-bread</link><title>Scientists Develop Sixty Day Bread</title><description>Hugh Pickens writes writes "BBC reports that scientists have developed a technique that can make bread stay mold-free for 60 days that could also be used with a wide range of foods including fresh turkey and many fruits and vegetables. At its laboratory on the campus of Texas Tech University in Lubbock, Don Stull of Microzap showed off the long, metallic microwave device that resembles an industrial production line. Originally designed to kill bacteria such as MRSA and salmonella, the researchers discovered it could kill the mold spores in bread in around 10 seconds. 'We treated a slice of bread in the device, we then checked the mold that was in that bread over time against a control,' says Stull. 'And at 60 days it had the same mold content as it had when it came out of the oven.' Food waste is a massive problem in most developed countries. In the US, figures released this year suggest that the average American family throws away 40% of the food they purchase — which adds up to $165 Billion annually. There is some concern that consumers might not take to bread that lasts for so long and Stull acknowledges it might be difficult to convince some people of the benefits. 'We'll have to get some consumer acceptance of that. Most people do it by feel and if you still have that quality feel they probably will accept it.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7216-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7216_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:17:49">http://idle.slashdot.org/story/12/10/12/0157244/seafood-raised-on-animal-feces-approved-for-consumers</link><title>Seafood Raised on Animal Feces Approved for Consumers</title><description>If you are a seafood lover and wish that you could eat more fish raised on pig feces, your dreams are coming true. Due to fierce competition in the Chinese tilapia industry, farmers are increasingly switching to feces instead of commercial feed. From the article: "At Chen Qiang’s tilapia farm in Yangjiang city in China’s Guangdong province, which borders Hong Kong, Chen feeds fish partly with feces from hundreds of pigs and geese. That practice is dangerous for American consumers, says Michael Doyle, director of the University of Georgia’s Center for Food Safety. 'The manure the Chinese use to feed fish is frequently contaminated with microbes like salmonella,' says Doyle, who has studied foodborne diseases in China."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7216-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7216_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:18:34">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/157880</link><title>Seagulls Spreading Resistant Bacteria On Beaches</title><description>bs0d3 writes "Dr. Patrice Nordmann has disclosed the results of a small study that looked for resistant bacteria in seagull poop landing on Miami Beach in Florida. During April 2010, they collected 52 stool samples and found within them 83 isolates of gut bacteria such as E. coli. Wired's Maryn McKenna writes, 'Seven of the E. coli carried genes that direct production of CTX-M enzymes, a troublesome resistance factor that protects bacteria from the very broad category of drugs called extended-spectrum beta-lactams and that has recently spread worldwide. In addition, 14 of the E. coli were also carrying the gene for the CMY-2 enzyme, which confers the same ESBL resistance on Salmonella. Nine of the isolates were multi-drug resistant.' This has led some scientists to the conclusion that this is one avenue these bacterias are taking in human infections worldwide. The resistance factors identified in the seagull feces match ones that cause highly resistant infections in humans, and correlate with data collected on beaches in Portugal, Sweden, and France."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7216-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7216_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:22:46">http://science.slashdot.org/story/09/10/31/0510212/disease-may-prevent-manned-journey-to-mars</link><title>Disease May Prevent Manned Journey To Mars</title><description>Pickens writes "Science Daily News reports that human missions to Mars and all other long-term space flights might be compromised by disease, first because space travel appears to weaken astronauts' immune systems; and second, because it increases the virulence and growth of microbes. 'When people think of space travel, often the vast distances are what come to mind first,' says Jean-Pol Frippiat from Nancy-University in France, 'but even after we figure out a way to cover these distances in a reasonable amount of time, we still need to figure out how astronauts are going to overcome disease and sickness.' Frippiat says studies show that immune systems of both people and animals in space flight conditions are significantly weaker than their grounded counterparts and that common pathogens such as Salmonella, E. coli and Staphylococcus reproduce more rapidly in space flight conditions, leading to increased risk of contamination, colonization and serious infection."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7216-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7216_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:24:24">http://science.slashdot.org/story/09/10/03/1325255/huge-iss-science-report-released</link><title>Huge ISS Science Report Released</title><description>Earthquake Retrofit writes "NASA has released an extensive report (PDF) on science results from over 100 experiments performed at the International Space Station. From the summary: 'One of the most compelling results reported is the confirmation that the ability of common germs to cause disease increases during spaceflight, but that changing the growth environment of the bacteria can control this virulence. The Effect of Spaceflight on Microbial Gene Expression and Virulence experiment identified increased virulence of space-flown Salmonella typhimurium, a leading cause of food poisoning. New research on subsequent station missions will target development of a vaccine for this widespread malady." I can't tell if this is good news, bad, or both. Also from a quick look at the report, I see that soybeans grow bigger in space with no harmful effect."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7216-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7216_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:28:04">http://science.slashdot.org/story/07/09/25/1140253/germs-taken-into-space-may-come-back-deadlier</link><title>Germs Taken Into Space May Come Back Deadlier</title><description>westlake writes "Sounds like the plot for a B-movie, doesn't it? Germs go into space and come back stronger and deadlier than ever. Except, it really happened. In a medical experiment, salmonella carried about the space shuttle in the fall of 2006 proved far more lethal to lab mice than their earth-bound source. 90% dead vs. 60% dead in twenty-six days, with half the mice dying at 1/3 the oral dose. Apparently 167 genes in the space-evolved strain had changed. The likely cause: In microgravity the force of fluids passing over the cells is low, similar to conditions in the gastrointestinal tract, and the cells adapted quickly to the new environment."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7216-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7216_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:31:46">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/65004</link><title>Anatomy of a Virus</title><description>Roland Piquepaille writes "No, I'm not talking about a computer virus here, but about a real one, the Epsilon 15, which attacks the bacterium Salmonella. By writing a few lines of computer code, biologists from Purdue University have found a way to control a high-resolution microscope. This allowed them to look inside a virus. While previous teams were able to visualize the highly symmetric outer shell of other viruses, these researchers were able to see the whole structure of Epsilon 15, including its tail, its genome and even its core. This better knowledge of viruses which attack bacteria could lead to great advances in medicine, especially when antibiotics become inefficient because of bacteria resisting them."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7216-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7216_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:34:33">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/40982</link><title>Bacteria More Virulent in Microgravity</title><description>Tortured Potato writes "Did you know that salmonella become more virulent in simulated microgravity? No one's sure why, either. Professor Cheryl Nickerson of Tulane University is hoping to find out why when an experiment with brewer's yeast gets sent up on a Russian Progress rocket to the Space Station next year."</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>