<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7218">edward kennedy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:36:38" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7218-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7218_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:36:41">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/10/04/28/2213223/government-approves-first-us-offshore-wind-farm</link><title>Government Approves First US Offshore Wind Farm</title><description>RobotRunAmok writes "In a groundbreaking decision that some say will usher in a new era of clean energy, US Interior Secretary Ken Salazar said today he was approving the nation's first offshore wind farm, the controversial Cape Wind project off of Cape Cod. The project has undergone years of environmental review and political maneuvering, including opposition from the late Senator Edward M. Kennedy, whose home overlooks Nantucket Sound, and from Wampanoag Indian tribes who complained that the 130 turbines, which would stand more than 400 feet above the ocean surface, would disturb spiritual sun greetings and possibly ancestral artifacts and burial grounds on the seabed. But George Bachrach, president of the Environmental League of Massachusetts, hailed the decision, saying it was 'a critical step toward ending our reliance on foreign oil and achieving energy independence.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7218-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7218_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:37:38">http://news.slashdot.org/story/08/04/26/0053213/senate-proposal-to-clarify-state-secrets-doctrine</link><title>Senate Proposal To Clarify 'State Secrets' Doctrine</title><description>I Don't Believe in Imaginary Property writes "Sen. Edward Kennedy (D-MA) and other lawmakers are pushing legislation to limit the power of the state secrets doctrine in blocking lawsuits. The doctrine has been used as a 'get out of jail free' card in cases like the EFF's warrantless wiretapping lawsuit. This new legislation would make it harder for the administration to invoke the doctrine, and provide new allowances, such as using attorneys with security clearances to enable the lawsuits to go forward even when the issue is appropriately raised." Update: 04/28 16:58 GMT by KD : The New Yorker is running a detailed piece, State Secrets, by Patrick Radden Keefe, about how the use of the state secrets doctrine is playing out in one particular case.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7218-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7218_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:40:16">http://games.slashdot.org/story/04/11/22/007222/new-video-game-recreates-kennedy-assassination</link><title>New Video Game Recreates Kennedy Assassination</title><description>theodp writes "Lee Harvey Oswald-wannabes will be able to simulate the assassination of President John F. Kennedy when Traffic Games releases the $9.99 JFK Reloaded on Monday to coincide with the 41st anniversary of Kennedy's murder in Dallas. 'It is despicable,' said a spokesman for Massachusetts Sen. Edward Kennedy, the late president's brother."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7218-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7218_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:41:14">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/50695</link><title>Bush, Kerry, and Nader Respond to Youth Voter Questions</title><description>Slashdot readers both contributed and helped moderate questions for the New Voters Project Presidential Youth Debate. You can read the answers below, but if you'd like to see an expanded introduction, thumbnails of the candidates, and different formatting, go to the Youth Debate page. And that's not all: We're supposed to get candidates' rebuttals on or about October 17, so don't touch that dial!</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7218-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7218_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:43:34">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/48961</link><title>Senator Blacklisted by No-Fly List</title><description>sig writes "Senator Edward Kennedy (D-MA) was turned down for a flight from Washington, D. C. to Boston because his name turned up on the TSA No-Fly list. He eventually got on a flight, but was again denied on his way back to D.C. It took 3 weeks of calls to Tom Ridge and the Department of Homeland Security for the ordeal to get straightened out. But what are ordinary citizens supposed to do if the Secretary of Homeland Security won't take their calls?" There's also a New York Times story.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7218-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7218_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:44:52">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/25312</link><title>Macs Ostracized on Capitol Hill</title><description>jonerik writes "Wired News has an article today on the last Apple holdout on Capitol Hill, Ngozi Pole. Pole, the office and systems administrator at Sen. Edward Kennedy's (D-MA) Boston and Washington D.C. offices, argues that the Senate Office of the Sergeant at Arms (SAA), which makes technology recommendations to senators, wants to make its job as easy as possible by pushing Windows-based applications as much as they can. According to the article, 'The SAA allocates $250,000 per six-year term to each senator. The department had hoped Pole would use the budget to replace aging Macs in Kennedy's offices. Instead, Pole will spend the remainder of his budget through 2003 filling Senator Kennedy's Washington office with new flat-panel iMacs.' Unsurprisingly, the SAA declined to comment."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7218-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7218_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:49:13">http://slashdot.org/story/98/07/31/1438228/foreign-tech-labor-for-us-bill-in-trouble</link><title>Foreign Tech Labor for US Bill in Trouble</title><description>JobSeeker writes "Yesterday, key House and Senate Republicans reached a final agreement on the bill to hire as many as 190,000 foreign professionals over the next six years. It is scheduled to be voted on in the House this afternoon, even though the White House administration threatens to veto it on the groups that US worker protections have been watered down. Sen. Edward Kennedy (D-Mass) plans to block debate on this bill in the Senate. This weekend the Senate will recess until the end of August but by then re-election campaigns will be in full swing. "</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>