<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7219">honda insight</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:51:12" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7219-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7219_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:51:13">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/09/08/18/1534231/worlds-only-diesel-electric-honda-insight</link><title>World's Only Diesel-Electric Honda Insight</title><description>Jake Staub writes "Just replaced the gasoline engine in a Honda Insight with a Diesel engine. On a 3,000 mile cross-country shakedown journey the car averaged 92mpg over 1,800 miles. Around a very hilly town in Northwest Washington, the car is averaging 78mpg. These mileage averages are without the electric side of the vehicle fully functional. With a bit more tinkering on the electric side and through a slight gearing change through tire size, it is anticipated that the car will likely average 100mpg. The build for the car has been documented on the web site and is as close to open source as my time allows. The car was built by two guys in a garage in Southern Maryland. If we can do it I don't see any reason why major auto manufacturers can't do it since we used their parts."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7219-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7219_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:53:03">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/08/10/02/210250/plug-in-hybrids-may-not-go-mainstream-toyota-says</link><title>Plug-in Hybrids May Not Go Mainstream, Toyota Says</title><description>mattnyc99 writes "Honda's challenger to the Prius — the Insight hybrid that we discussed so lividly a month ago — got its official unveiling today at the Paris auto show, with insiders confirming it would be cheaper than the world's most popular 'green' car while still hitting the same fuel-efficiency range. But the hybrid-electric showdown comes in the midst of a sudden rethink by Toyota about plug-in hybrids. Apparently all the recent hype — over the production version of the Chevy Volt, plus Chrysler's new electric trio and even the cool new Pininfarina EV also unveiled today — has execs from the world's number one automaker, and alt-fuel experts, questioning how many people will really buy electric cars, whether people will really charge them at night to keep the grid clear, whether batteries will make them too expensive and more. "</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7219-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7219_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:55:15">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/08/09/05/0141244/redesigned-bulkier-honda-insight-to-challenge-prius</link><title>Redesigned, Bulkier Honda Insight to Challenge Prius</title><description>In what probably amounts to good news for consumers eyeing a hybrid for their next vehicle purchase, Honda is resurrecting the "Insight" name, this time in the form of a five-seat, Prius-like hatchback. The automaker's announcement included the tantalizing statement that the cost would be "significantly below [that of] hybrids available today," but provided no further details on pricing. Although Honda may have some trouble unseating Toyota's dominance of this particular hybrid market, hopefully the Insight's reintroduction will help to make hybrid cars even more affordable to consumers. This is also welcome news to folks like myself who, after the initial flurry of excitement when the now-retired original Insight was introduced in '99, were left scratching their heads at Honda's hybrid strategy as Toyota picked up their dropped ball and ran with it.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7219-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7219_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:56:30">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/40605</link><title>Softwar : An Intimate Portrait of Larry Ellison</title><description>prostoalex writes "In the high-tech industry few people achieve such glamour and general recognition as Larry Ellison, the chief executive officer of Oracle Corp. Ellison is known for provocative interviews, for being called the industry's 'other billionaire,' for being brutal to the competitors while staying within ethical limits, and for genuine opposition to a Redmond-based software company called Microsoft." Read on for the rest of Alex's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7219-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7219_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:59:53">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/02/12/02/0326234/239-mpg-car</link><title>239 MPG Car</title><description>Kozmik writes "VW/Audi has a history of being a leader in creating super fuel efficient vehicles. They currently sell the most fuel efficient car in the world, 3L Lupo and the Audi A2, and the most fuel efficient station wagon (Jetta TDI Wagon). Now VW is experimenting with something along the lines of the Honda Insight ( a 2 person vehicle ). The 1L VW concept car can achieve .89L/100kms or 239MPG. With Biodiesel and Ultra low sulfur diesel becoming available, hopefully more of these vehicles will come to North America. These fuels are already available in Europe and combined with the new catalyst technology they use, these new engines produce very low emissions." It's nice to talk about alternative fuels, but I have yet to see a gas station selling one of them.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7219-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7219_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:03:18">http://ask.slashdot.org/story/02/07/08/2314215/alternative-fuel-vehicle-recommendations</link><title>Alternative-Fuel Vehicle Recommendations?</title><description>Ellen Spertus asks: "My husband and I lease a pure electric GM EV-1, which we love, and need to replace our second car, a conventional Honda Accord, which recently died. We'd get a second EV-1, but GM has stopped making them. I haven't been able to find any available all-eletric car with the range (&gt;=50 miles roundtrip) and speed (&gt;=65 mph) that I need. Does the Slashdot community have any experience, wisdom, or advice on choosing an alternative fuel car?"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7219-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7219_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:05:24">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/00/07/17/1429234/ars-reviews-honda-insight</link><title>Ars Reviews Honda Insight</title><description>GeekLife.com writes "Ars Technica has posted another of their indepth reviews, this time of the Honda Insight (that gas-electric hybrid). Not just a normal Honda Insight, though, this one's been tricked up with LCD screens replacing the side mirrors, and a *portable windmill* that can recharge the battery. Not the prettiest of devices, but with gas prices continuing up, it's definitely starting to look a bit more attractive."</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>