<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7241">flight simulators</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:28:29" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7241-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7241_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:28:31">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/181547</link><title>Royal Canadian Air Force Sees More Sims In the Future of Fighter Pilot Training</title><description>dakohli writes "Currently, Canadian Fighter Pilots spend about 20% of their 'stick' time in Simulators. RCAF General Blondin states that this will rise to 50/50 in the future. The article goes on to state that the U.S. Army is moving in this direction, although the U.S. Air Force is a little more skeptical. Aircraft are expensive to fly, and if the fidelity of a simulator is good enough then perhaps real pilots will spend even less time actually in the air. Slashdotters, do you think that this will actually make recruiting pilots more difficult, or is it a sign of the things to come beyond Military Aviation?"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7241-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7241_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:30:06">http://games.slashdot.org/story/11/08/27/1745235/open-source-simulator-flightgear-releases-v24</link><title>Open Source Simulator FlightGear Releases v2.4</title><description>mikejuk writes "The latest version of FlightGear, 2.4, has just been released — and it has some significant improvements. Now it simulates weather so that you can ride the up draft from a range of hills and seek out thermals — but watch out for the simulated fog! For the future the implementation of an HLA interface means that you can build clusters of interacting simulators and perhaps even work with commercial flight simulators." The FlightGear website has gotten a long-deserved upgrade, too.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7241-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7241_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:30:49">http://science.slashdot.org/story/10/01/03/199219/ideas-for-exploiting-nasas-srtm-data</link><title>Ideas For Exploiting NASA's SRTM Data</title><description>MaxTardiveau writes with an excerpt from an article where the pictures are worth clicking through for: "Ten years ago, in February 2000, NASA mapped the entire world in eleven days. It's true: the mission was called the Shuttle Radar Topography Mission (SRTM), and over the course of eleven days, it used a big radar attached to the space shuttle to get elevation data from the vast majority of solid Earth; practically all land between 60 degrees North and 56 degrees South was included, with a resolution of 30 meters (90 feet). Over 9 terabytes of data were captured. It then took two years to process that data and make it usable (and it is still being refined to this day). This data is freely available to anyone, and the number of possible applications is almost infinite. It's been used in GIS, cartography, environmental planning, weather modeling (weather patterns are enormously influenced by the topography), flight simulators, Google Earth, and the list goes on. In this short article, I would like to give you a quick tour of the kinds of things this data can reveal. My hope is to get you thinking about what else could be done with this incredible resource."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7241-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7241_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:34:24">http://books.slashdot.org/story/09/11/23/149240/writing-for-video-game-genres</link><title>Writing For Video Game Genres</title><description>Aeonite writes "The third book in a pseudo-trilogy, Writing for Video Game Genres: From FPS to RPG, offers advice from 21 experts in the field of video game writing, pulled from the ranks of the IGDA's Game Writers Special Interest Group and wrangled together by editor Wendy Despain. It follows in the footsteps of Professional Techniques for Video Game Writing and Game Writing: Narrative Skills for Videogames, and in keeping with the trend, offers the most specific, targeted advice for how to write for an assortment of game genres." Read below for the rest of Michael's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7241-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7241_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:38:33">http://games.slashdot.org/story/07/09/01/2038210/google-earth-flight-simulator</link><title>Google Earth Flight Simulator</title><description>insidedesign writes "Blogger Marco has recently discovered that the newest version of Google Earth includes a flight simulator. Though simple in comparison to full-blown simulators, Google Earth's is fun and addictive. To get started, press Ctrl+Alt+A for the initial dialog (on OS X, Command+Option+A). Then choose your plane (F16 or SR22) and initial airport. Joysticks are supported; it has even been reported that force feedback works. The game's controls are sensitive so it takes some getting used to. Here are all the available controls. For a quick overview, check out this YouTube video."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7241-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7241_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:39:50">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/85123</link><title>What Can 4-yr-olds Understand About Science?</title><description>dr.karl.b asks: "My 3 and a half year old son is in Kindergarten. Here in Germany that includes 3 to 6 year olds. He is supposed to explain what his parents' occupations are. I am a scientist, and despite all the advice I have received saying he can't understand what I do, I am determined to try. I study self-motion perception, from basic-science vestibular processing to the role of real-motion cues in flight simulation. We have several cool labs in my institute, like robot-arm motion simulators and full-immersion virtual reality set-ups. We can easily compete with amusement parks for wow-factor, but I have 2 questions: How can I explain my work to my son? How can I invite his class (3-6 yr olds) to our institute to have them learn AND have fun, rather than ONLY have fun?"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7241-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7241_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:40:44">http://games.slashdot.org/story/06/12/18/177206/co-pilots-may-sim-instead-of-fly-to-train</link><title>Co-Pilots May Sim Instead of Fly To Train</title><description>CyberLord Seven writes "The Washington Post has up an article on a proposed new standard that would allow co-pilots, and co-pilots only, to gain most of their flight experience through flight simulators rather than through actual flight on smaller planes." From the article: "The move is designed to allow foreign airlines, especially those in Asia and the Middle East that face shortages of pilots, to more quickly train and hire flight crews. The United States isn't expected to adopt the new rules anytime soon, but international pilots trained under the new standards will be allowed to fly into and out of the country. The change is generating some controversy. Safety experts and pilot groups question whether simulators -- which have long been hailed as an important training tool -- are good enough to replace critical early flight experience." It should be pointed out this isn't just Microsoft Flight Simulator they are playing. These are motion-controlled capsules that simulate the realities of an aircraft's movement.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7241-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7241_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:42:33">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/05/02/17/231205/sim-icarus-boeing-777-handmade-flight-deck</link><title>Sim Icarus Boeing 777 Handmade Flight Deck</title><description>ShadowsMV writes "Three technology students finishing up their degrees at the DuPage Campus of DeVry University spent a term designing and building one of the most nifty flight simulators yet. Named the Sim Icarus Flight Deck, it accurately recreates the primary flight accessory controls of the Boeing 777, and interfaces directly with Microsoft Flight Simulator 2004. They have tons of pictures and lists of everything you need! Previous flight decks featured on slashdot include An awesome homebuilt and wideview with 13 Monitors And 9 PCs."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7241-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7241_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:44:56">http://science.slashdot.org/story/04/12/02/1624223/student-satellite-ready-for-space</link><title>Student Satellite Ready for Space</title><description>An anonymous contributor writes "Nearly one hundred students from all over Europe have been working hard on SSETI Express Satellite (Student Space Education and Technology Initiative). Last week a handful of students gathered at the Netherlands to put the finishing touches to the flight model. The final exams in the space simulators will follow in January - the last hurdle before launch in May 2005. The satellite has been largely designed and built via the Internet. The students keep each other informed about the latest developments using a special news server and weekly chat sessions."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7241-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7241_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:46:29">http://games.slashdot.org/story/04/03/21/2358226/video-game-publishers-outsource-development</link><title>Video-Game Publishers Outsource Development</title><description>randomErr writes "According to a San Jose Mercury News article reprinted at the Miami Herald: 'Mark Vange is in the vanguard of globalizing the video-game industry. He employs 30 game developers in St. Petersburg, Russia, who have worked on everything from flight simulators to dragon-fighting games. 'We can get the work done for half the cost that it takes in the U.S.,' said Vange, president of Ketsujin Studios. Similar outsourcing of video-game production is being done in places like China, India, Vietnam and parts of Eastern Europe. California game developers, who are the creative force behind a $10 billion industry in the U.S. market, view the trend with a combination of fear and anticipation'."</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>