<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7261">elvish language</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:17:22" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7261-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7261_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:17:24">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/12/04/13/1646215/oracle-and-google-spar-over-whether-programming-languages-can-be-copyrighted</link><title>Oracle and Google Spar Over Whether Programming Languages Can Be Copyrighted</title><description>pcritter writes "With the Oracle v. Google trial date set for next Monday, the Judge has asked Google and Oracle to take a position on whether a programming language is copyrightable. This presumably relates to whether Google violated copyright by using a variant of the Java language and its APIs in the Android framework. Oracle, who thinks it can be, has used J.R.R. Tolkein's Elvish language as an examples (PDF) of a language that can be copyrighted. Google disagrees (PDF)."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7261-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7261_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:20:44">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/98578</link><title>The Children of Hurin</title><description>stoolpigeon writes "Throughout much of his life, J.R.R. Tolkien worked on a series of stories set in his well known middle earth. A few he considered his "Great Tales" and he would return to them often, writing them multiple times and in multiple forms. One story that he worked on often over many years was the tale of Hurin and his children Turin and Nienor. Following his death, Tolkien's youngest son Christopher has worked to collect, edit and publish much of what his father wrote but never published. The tale of Hurin's children has been told in part already in some of those works. But it is in this book that for the first time the complete tale is told from start to finish of The Children of Hurin." Read below for the rest of JR's review.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>