<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7307">causes of the cold war</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:51:03" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7307-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7307_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:51:04">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/174957</link><title>50 Years of Research and Still No Microwave Weapons</title><description>DevotedSkeptic writes in with a story about the lack of usable microwave technology to come from 50 years of military research. "For some Pentagon officials, the demonstration in October 2007 must have seemed like a dream come true — an opportunity to blast reporters with a beam of energy that causes searing pain. The event in Quantico, Virginia, was to be a rare public showing for the US Air Force's Active Denial System: a prototype non-lethal crowd-control weapon that emits a beam of microwaves at 95 gigahertz. Radiation at that frequency penetrates less than half a millimetre into the skin, so the beam was supposed to deliver an intense burning sensation to anyone in its path, forcing them to move away, but without, in theory, causing permanent damage. However, the day of the test was cold and rainy. The water droplets in the air did what moisture always does: they absorbed the microwaves. And when some of the reporters volunteered to expose themselves to the attenuated beam, they found that on such a raw day, the warmth was very pleasant. The story is much the same in other areas of HPM weapons development, which began as an East–West technology race nearly 50 years ago. In the United States, where spending on electromagnetic weapons is down from cold-war levels, but remains at some US$47 million per year, progress is elusive. 'There's lots of smoke and mirrors,' says Peter Zimmerman, an emeritus nuclear physicist at King's College London and former chief scientist of the US Arms Control and Disarmament Agency in Washington DC. Although future research may yield scientific progress, he adds, 'I cannot see they will build a useful, deployable weapon.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7307-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7307_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:54:45">http://science.slashdot.org/story/12/05/09/1454257/jars-of-irradiated-russian-animals-find-a-new-purpose</link><title>Jars of Irradiated Russian Animals Find a New Purpose</title><description>scibri writes with bits and pieces from the article: "From the early 1950s to the end of the cold war, nearly 250,000 animals were systematically irradiated in the Russian town of Ozersk. Fearful of a nuclear attack by the United States, the Soviet Union wanted to understand how radiation damages tissues and causes diseases such as cancer. Now, these archives have become important to a new generation of radiobiologists, who want to explore the effects of the extremely low doses of radiation — below 100 millisieverts — that people receive during medical procedures such as computed-tomography diagnostic scans, and by living close to the damaged Fukushima nuclear reactors in Japan."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7307-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7307_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:56:12">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/00/12/15/1619213/rethinking-virtual-community-part-three</link><title>Rethinking Virtual Community: Part Three</title><description>Virtual communities that only offer information, data and text-based messaging are sometimes fragmented, brittle and cold. They don't allow the kind of sequential communications and storytelling vital to any community, work or personal. Those that emphasize human contact are too limited. The Virtual Community of tomorrow may have to incorporate both. (This is the third in a series.)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7307-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7307_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:59:03">http://yro.slashdot.org/story/00/03/03/1043233/database-nation</link><title>Database Nation</title><description>We've got a double-headed review of Simson Garfinkel's new book Database Nation: The Death of Privacy at the End of the 21st Century. It's a thought-provoking vision of the future which frankly scares the heck out of me.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7307-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7307_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:00:04">http://news.slashdot.org/story/99/10/07/1316214/a-history-of-modern-computing</link><title>A History of Modern Computing</title><description>cmalek has sent us a review of Paul E. Cerruzi's A History Of Moderning Computing, which delves into the past of the machines we use today. To read more about your computer's ancestors, click below.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>