<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7402">little johnny</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:31:07" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7402-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7402_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:31:09">http://interviews.slashdot.org/story/14/04/07/1726243/interviews-jonathan-coulton-answers-your-questions</link><title>Interviews: Jonathan Coulton Answers Your Questions</title><description>We recently had the chance to talk with internet rock star and former code monkey Jonathan Coulton. We asked him a number of your questions and a few of our own about music, technology, and copyright issues. Read below to see what he had to say.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7402-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7402_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:32:43">http://games.slashdot.org/story/09/12/11/095201/nyts-games-to-avoid-an-ironic-perfect-gamer-wish-list</link><title>NYT's "Games To Avoid" an Ironic, Perfect Gamer Wish List</title><description>MojoKid writes "From October to December, the advertising departments of a thousand companies exhort children to beg, cajole, and guilt-trip their parents for all manner of inappropriate digital entertainment. As supposedly informed gatekeepers, we sadly earthbound Santas are reduced to scouring the back pages of gaming review sites and magazines, trying to evaluate whether the tot at home is ready for Big Bird's Egg Hunt or Bayonetta. Luckily, The New York Times is here to help. In a recent article provokingly titled 'Ten Games to Cross off Your Child's Gift List,' the NYT names its list of big bads — the video games so foul, so gruesome, so perverse that we'd recommend you buy them immediately — for yourself. Alternatively, if you need gift ideas for the surly, pale teenager in your home whose body contains more plastic then your average d20, this is the newspaper clipping to stuff in your pocket. In other words, if you need a list like this to understand what games to not stuff little Johnny's stocking with this holiday season, you've got larger issues you should concern yourself with. We'd suggest picking up an auto-shotty and taking a few rounds against the horde — it's a wonderful stress relief and you're probably going to need it."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7402-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7402_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:34:32">http://games.slashdot.org/story/09/12/10/1922250/ftc-says-virtual-worlds-bad-for-minors</link><title>FTC Says Virtual Worlds Bad For Minors</title><description>eldavojohn writes "A new report from the FTC is claiming minors have access to explicit content via online virtual worlds such as those found in online games. The report makes five recommendations to keep little Johnny away from the harms of Barrens chat: Use more effective age-screening mechanisms to prevent children from registering in adult virtual worlds; Use or enhance age-segregation techniques to make sure that people interact only with others in their age group; Re-examine language filters to ensure that they detect and eliminate messages that violate rules of behavior in virtual worlds; Provide more guidance to community enforcers in virtual worlds so they are better able to review and rate virtual world content, report potential underage users, and report any users who appear to be violating rules of behavior; and Employ a staff of specially trained moderators who are equipped to take swift action against rule violations."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7402-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7402_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:36:00">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/07/12/23/1359259/head-tracking-w-the-wiimote</link><title>Head Tracking w/ the Wiimote</title><description>mrneutron2003 writes "This guy just doesn't know when to stop. Johnny Chung Lee graces us with yet another one of his inventive Wiimote projects. This time it involves using the Wiimote and a pair of inexpensive LED safety goggles (with the standard LED's replaced with InfraRed ones) to allow positional head tracking , achieving an effect similar to what is experienced with three dimensional displays and CAVE systems. The video dramatically illustrates the effect. Game developers take note. This simple little variation on infrared tracking could allow for some seriously immersive gameplay in the future." This guy deserves a medal.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7402-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7402_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:36:49">http://news.slashdot.org/story/07/12/19/170238/jerry-bruckheimer-teams-with-mtv-for-games</link><title>Jerry Bruckheimer Teams With MTV For Games</title><description>Well-known action film and television producer Jerry Bruckheimer has teamed up with MTV Games to make games. Stephen Totilo and the MTV Multiplayer blog had a chance to speak candidly with the director himself, as well as the MTV executive behind the deal, Jeff Yapp. "Bruckheimer: I think the same kind of stuff we bring to television and films, we always want to look at things a little differently from other people. Pirate films were dead for a long time and we put Johnny Depp in it and created an unforgettable character. We did the same thing with fighter pilots in "Top Gun" and dancers in "Flashdance." So we're just trying to see things a little differently."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7402-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7402_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:37:30">http://slashdot.org/story/06/09/29/1340200/star-fox-command-review</link><title>Star Fox Command Review</title><description>Beginning with the original 1993 SNES title, Nintendo has toyed with the space combat series Star Fox in a number of ways. Star Fox Adventures added a doodad-hunting adventure format, while last year's Star Fox Assault included ground-based battles that managed to actually detract from the game's appeal. Now on the DS, the Star Fox series has experienced yet another format shift: Star Fox Command. Command offers some simple strategy elements, an innovative control scheme, and the tried and true dogfighting gameplay the series is known for. It also dwells on one of the series' weaknesses, plot, to the detriment of the game. Despite that and a few other issues, Star Fox Command will provide some quality space combat for anyone looking to kill some time, and a few aliens. Read on for my impressions of Nintendo's latest core series release.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7402-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7402_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:40:03">http://slashdot.org/story/06/07/07/1812240/the-uss-net-wide-for-terrorist-names</link><title>The U.S.'s Net Wide For 'Terrorist' Names</title><description>Yesterday's report of name-based blocking of money transfers as a result of U.S. Treasury policies intended to reduce the flow of money to Middle Eastern terrorists drew more than 800 comments. Western Union money transfers were at the heart of the linked Associated Press article, but as some of these comments point out, that's not the only case of interference in electronic financial transactions based on the names of the participants, akin to the use of the much-derided no-fly list. Read on for the Backslash summary of the conversation.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7402-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7402_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:42:02">http://news.slashdot.org/story/05/07/27/1542234/stealing-the-network-how-to-own-an-identity</link><title>Stealing the Network: How to Own an Identity</title><description>Scott Pinzon writes "Writing sonnets, screenplays, or an epic poem in your third language is a breeze compared to the toughest of art forms, didactic fiction. That might explain why the various chapters of Stealing the Network: How to Own an Identity range from appalling to exciting. Whether you see the glass of STN: Identity as half empty or half full depends on whether this is your cup of poison -- but on a technical level, it rocks." Read on for the rest of Pinzon's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7402-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7402_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:45:51">http://news.slashdot.org/story/05/04/08/1849245/planet-simpson</link><title>Planet Simpson</title><description>Aeonite (Michael Fiegel) writes "The title of Planet Simpson: How a Cartoon Masterpiece Defined a Generation says it all. In its exploration of the first 15 seasons from The Simpsons, the book does much more than relate funny moments, reprint favorite quotes and point out trivia that you might have missed in your first (or fifteenth) watching of any particular episode. To be certain, those things are there, but they're really secondary to the overall 'mission' of the book, which is to relate the rise of the cartoon to the political, social and cultural realities of the 1990s and early 2000s." Read on for the rest of Fiegel's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7402-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7402_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:47:35">http://entertainment.slashdot.org/story/04/12/08/1625256/the-pocket-and-the-pendant</link><title>The Pocket and the Pendant</title><description>Aeonite (Michael Fiegel) writes "Mark Jeffrey is probably best known to Slashdotters as an online media entrepreneur and one of the co-founders (along with Mike Maerz and Jim Bumgardner) of The Palace, an avatar-based chat system popular in the late 1990s. Jeffrey is not to be confused with Neal Stephenson, though both men have websites featuring clockwork imagery, goatees, and novels which contain references to Sumerian mythology -- Stephenson's Snow Crash and Jeffrey's first novel, The Pocket and the Pendant. From a distance, one might be inclined to believe that similarities to Stephenson's own work are more than cosmetic: Jeffrey thanks Stephenson on the Acknowledgments page of his novel (along with Stephen R. Donaldson and Carl Jung, among others), and one Lulu.com review (mentioned in a press release) describes The Pocket and the Pendant as being 'like Stargate, Harry Potter, Snow Crash and the old Land of the Lost rolled into one.'" Read on for the rest of Fiegel's review.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>