<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7405">light therapy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:52:04" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7405-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7405_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:52:06">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/165891</link><title>MIT Fiber Points To Woven Glasses-Free 3D Displays</title><description>MrSeb writes "Electrical engineers and material scientists at MIT have created a fiber-borne laser that could be woven to form a flexible display that could project different 3D images in any number of directions, to any number of viewers. MIT's fiber is similar to standard telecoms fiber, but it has a tiny droplet of fluid embedded in the core. When laser light hits the fluid, it scatters, effectively creating a 360-degree laser beam. The core is then surrounded by layers of liquid crystal, which can be controlled like 'pixels,' allowing the laser light to escape from specific points anywhere along the length of the fiber. This means that you could have a display that shows one picture on the 'front' and another on the 'back' — or different, glasses-free 3D images for everyone sitting in front and behind. In the short term, the laser fiber is more likely to have a significant application in photodynamic therapy, an area of medicine where drugs are activated using light. Photodynamic therapy is one of the only ways to treat cancer in a relatively non-invasive and non-toxic manner. MIT's laser could be threaded into almost any part of the body, where the ability to produce pixels of laser light at any point along its length would make it a highly accurate device."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7405-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7405_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:54:02">http://science.slashdot.org/story/11/08/11/1942204/human-brain-is-sensitive-to-light-in-ears</link><title>Human Brain Is Sensitive To Light In Ears</title><description>vuo writes "Finnish researchers have shown that the human brain contains photoreceptors that react to intracranial illumination. Light is provided through the ear canal with bright-light headsets by Valkee. These devices, much like earphones or should we say 'earlumes,' are registered medical devices. Retinal illumination or bright-light therapy has been previously assumed to be the only way light indirectly affects brains. Light therapy helps with mood swings, seasonal affective disorder, jetlag and other circadian rhythm disruptions."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7405-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7405_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:56:48">http://science.slashdot.org/story/11/07/08/1645218/the-birth-of-optogenetics</link><title>The Birth of Optogenetics</title><description>Dr. Tom writes "Scientists at MIT and other labs have created transgenic neurons that fire when exposed to light. The technique targets specific cell types in live primates. They are already talking about the possibilities for therapy and behavior modification by optically stimulating specific brain circuits."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7405-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7405_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:58:12">http://science.slashdot.org/story/10/03/16/016246/golden-nanocages-to-put-the-heat-on-cancer-cells</link><title>Golden Nanocages To Put the Heat On Cancer Cells</title><description>ElectricSteve writes "Researchers have been searching for a highly targeted medical treatment that attacks cancer cells but leaves healthy tissue alone. The approach taken by scientists at Washington University in St. Louis is to use 'gold nanocages' that, when injected, selectively accumulate in tumors. When the tumors are later bathed in laser light, the surrounding tissue is barely warmed, but the nanocages convert light to heat, killing the malignant cells. ... Although the tumors took up enough gold nanocages to give them a black cast, only 6 percent of the injected particles accumulated at the tumor site. They would like that number to be closer to 40 percent so that fewer particles would have to be injected. They plan to attach tailor-made ligands to the nanocages that recognize and lock onto receptors on the surface of the tumor cells. ... The scientists at WUSTL have just received a five-year, $2.1M grant from the National Cancer Institute to continue their work with photothermal therapy." Note that Gizmag features a stupid Subscribe nag that covers your screen after about a minute; sounds like a job for NoScript. Last year we discussed somewhat similar research using titanium dioxide nanoparticles to target a particular kind of brain cancer.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7405-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7405_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:00:46">http://science.slashdot.org/story/09/09/16/2236206/gene-therapy-cures-color-blind-monkeys</link><title>Gene Therapy Cures Color-Blind Monkeys</title><description>SpuriousLogic writes "After receiving injections of genes that produce color-detecting proteins, two color-blind monkeys have seen red and green for the first time. Except in its extreme forms, color blindness isn't a debilitating condition, but it's a convenient stand-in for other types of blindness that might be treated with gene therapy. The monkey success raises the possibility of reversing those diseases, in a manner that most scientists considered impossible. 'We said it was possible to give an adult monkey with a model of human red-green color blindness the retina of a person with normal color vision. Every single person I talked to said, absolutely not,' said study co-author Jay Neitz, a University of Washington ophthalmologist. 'And almost every unsolved vision defect out there has this component in one way or another, where the ability to translate light into a gene signal is involved.' The full-spectrum supplementation of the squirrel monkeys' sight, described Wednesday in Nature, comes just less than a year after researchers used gene therapy to restore light perception in people afflicted by Leber Congenital Amaurosis, a rare and untreatable form of blindness."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7405-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7405_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:01:37">http://science.slashdot.org/story/09/08/15/2015220/gene-therapy-causes-blind-woman-to-grow-new-fovea</link><title>Gene Therapy Causes Blind Woman To Grow New Fovea</title><description>Al writes "A woman with a rare, inherited form of blindness is now able to read, thanks to a gene therapy that caused a new fovea — the part of the retina that is most densely populated with photoreceptors — to grow in her eye. The patient suffers from Leber congenital amaurosis, meaning an abnormal protein makes her photoreceptors have a severely impaired sensitivity to light. She received the experimental treatment twelve months ago when physicians injected a gene encoding a functional copy of the protein into a small part of one eye — about eight-to-nine millimeters in diameter. Along with two other patients receiving the same treatment, her eyesight improved after just a few weeks. Now the physicians report that this patient seems to have developed a new fovea, exactly where she received the injection. Because the woman has been effectively blind since birth, the results suggest that the brain is able to adapt to new visual stimuli remarkably quickly."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7405-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7405_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:03:30">http://science.slashdot.org/story/09/06/21/1433249/mayo-clinic-reports-dramatic-outcomes-in-prostate-cancer-treatment</link><title>Mayo Clinic Reports Dramatic Outcomes In Prostate Cancer Treatment</title><description>Zorglub writes "Two prostate cancer patients who had been told their condition was inoperable are now cancer-free as the result of an experimental therapy, the Mayo Clinic in Rochester announced Friday. 'Cancer has a propensity for turning off T cells. Dr. Allison hypothesized that if you block the off-switch, T cells will stay turned on and create a prolonged immune response. Dr. Kwon, then at NIH, demonstrated that CTLA-4 blockage could be used to treat aggressive forms of prostate cancer in mice. There was one limitation to that concept — the worry that by simply leaving all the T cells on there may not be enough response aimed at the tumor. Dr. Kwon called Dr. Allison and designed the trial together. The idea: use androgen ablation or hormone therapy to ignite an immune approach — a pilot light — and then, after a short interval of hormone therapy, introduce an anti-CTLA-4 antibody that acts like gasoline to this pilot light and overwhelms the cancer cells.' After the treatment, the patients' tumors shrunk to such a degree that they could be successfully removed."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7405-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7405_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:05:08">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/119151</link><title>Paro the Therapeutic Robot Baby Seal</title><description>Mike writes "Paro is a therapeutic baby seal robot that is exploring new dimensions in animal therapy. Created to act as a companion for hospital patients and the elderly, the adorable baby harp seal bot aims to increase relaxation and decrease stress. Paro can sense and respond to its immediate environment through five integrated sensors that detect touch, light, sound, temperature, and posture, and it is even capable of learning and responding to a name."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7405-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7405_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:06:17">http://slashdot.org/story/06/10/31/2256209/fastest-waves-ever-photographed</link><title>Fastest Waves Ever Photographed</title><description>starfoot writes, "Pictures of the fastest waves ever photographed, traveling at 99.997% of the speed of light, were presented today at the APS Division of Plasma Physics meeting in Philadelphia. The waves were formed in the wake of an intense laser pulse passing through a plasma of electrons and ionized atoms. The waves create enormous electric fields (over 100 billion electron volts/meter), which can be used to rapidly accelerate charged particles to high energies in the span of a few meters. The pictures will help scientists better understand wakefield interactions — an important factor in their quest to replace machines that accelerate particles over the course of miles with compact, tabletop versions. High energy particle accelerators are vital for cutting edge physics and many types of medical therapy, and miniaturizing them would be a boon for both basic physics research and medicine."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7405-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7405_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:08:40">http://slashdot.org/story/06/06/29/1617259/is-setihome-where-your-cycles-belong</link><title>Is SETI@home Where Your Cycles Belong?</title><description>Yesterday's post about a Wall Street Journal article critiquing the current allocation of distributed number-crunching projects drew a huge range of comments, some favoring the proposition that seemingly quixotic distributed-computing endeavors (specifically, the alien-hunting SETI@home project) were diverting resources better spent on closer-to-home, pragmatic research, such as cancer or climate prediction, or perhaps best never converted to electricity in the first place. Read on for the Backslash summary of the conversation.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>