<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7406">does my child have adhd</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:11:17" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7406-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7406_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:11:19">http://science.slashdot.org/story/04/01/14/2147242/neural-feedback-training-as-therapy-for-adhd</link><title>Neural Feedback Training as Therapy for ADHD?</title><description>jamesh asks: "I asked Slashdot (anonymously) a while back about my daughter, who has been diagnosed with ADHD. The Ritalin has made a lot of difference but things are still not quite right, and she has developed various vocal tics (grunting, odd little noises, words and so forth... think Tourette's Syndrome, only not nearly as bad), which is one of the side effects of stimulant medication. She's now a lot less of an outcast and appears able to better interact with other kids, but we're still looking at alternate treatments. It may be the trendy new thing, but we've now started down the road of neural feedback therapy. Does anyone out there have any experience in this treatment? First hand 'I've tried it once and it changed/ruined my life' anecdotes would be great, but if you have a child, friend or acquaintance who has been through this treatment, it would be really useful to hear about their experiences." We also discussed ADHD treatments in another related Ask Slashdot but I don't see any mention of such a therapy in that discussion. Has anyone heard of studies or reports on patients of Neural Feedback Therapy?</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7406-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7406_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:12:21">http://ask.slashdot.org/story/02/12/08/2314237/dealing-with-adhd-and-other-problems-in-young-children</link><title>Dealing with ADHD and Other Problems in Young Children?</title><description>A Worried Parent asks: "My 6yo daughter has been diagnosed with ADHD and is currently taking a certain stimulant whose name starts with R. I don't like it, but for the moment her happiness has improved, as opposed to when she's not medicated where she appears unhappy and frustrated with her inability to find her way in the world. She's sat through an IQ test, and the result was 147, which means she's better at doing IQ tests than 99.9% of 6 year olds. I wasn't that surprised but her teachers were, she's very clever but has difficulty following instructions - which is kind of a requirement in a classroom environment. If she's in a group of kids being given instructions she'll be looking at something else, playing with the grass, singing quietly to herself, etc. She'll suddenly become aware of all the kids wandering off to follow said instructions and then panic because she wasn't paying attention. In a group of people her attention just sort of switches off. I don't think this is something she can change. Any thoughts on how to help? Don't bother quoting the books on this one, i'm after first hand experiences. (i've read enough books :p)"</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>