<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7417">dota 2 heroes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:27:33" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7417-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7417_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:27:34">http://games.slashdot.org/story/12/07/11/174235/cowboyneal-on-dota-2-modern-games-and-software-development</link><title>CowboyNeal On Dota 2, Modern Games, and Software Development</title><description>CowboyNeal writes "Unless you don't care about PC gaming at all, by now you're aware of Valve's entry into the MOBA/ARTS genre, Dota 2. Despite still being in a closed beta, it's currently the number one game on Valve's Steam gaming service, and judging from Valve's earlier declaration regarding Steam on Linux, it's only a matter of time, even if that time be a year or more, before we see Dota 2 come to Linux as well as Mac. Valve has big plans for Dota 2, no less big than what happened with Team Fortress 2, even if it took them a few years to get to where Team Fortress 2 is today. What makes the current state of Dota 2 noteworthy, however, is that it has managed to displace Team Fortress 2 as Steam's most popular game, while still being tested in a closed beta." Read on for the rest of CowboyNeal's thoughts on games, and what it's like being a Slashdot poll option.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7417-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7417_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:29:42">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/142804</link><title>Blizzard Unveils Custom StarCraft 2 Game Types, Encourages Map Design</title><description>StarCraft 2 launched in July, and since most of the developers' efforts since then have gone into tweaking balance issues, fixing bugs and further developing Battle.net integration, the second part of the trilogy is still quite a ways off. So, in lieu of announcements about Heart of the Swarm, the devs are using Blizzcon to showcase the map-editing tools and encourage the community to get more involved with custom maps and game types. Using the map editor, they created internally four custom games for StarCraft 2, which they’ll soon be releasing over Battle.net for free alongside three fan creations that won a recent contest. Read on for more details.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7417-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7417_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:31:12">http://games.slashdot.org/story/10/03/31/067217/heroes-of-newerth-open-beta-about-to-start</link><title>Heroes of Newerth Open Beta About To Start</title><description>You may recall last summer when we discussed Heroes of Newerth, a title from S2 Games that's based on the popular Defense of the Ancients mod from Warcraft III. We passed out some closed beta keys, and there seemed to be a ton of interest, in part due to the fact that they have a Linux client. Well, if any of you missed it or want to see how the game has progressed since then, now is your chance — the open beta begins tonight (March 31). There's a countdown on the sign-up page that shows when you can register.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7417-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7417_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:31:54">http://games.slashdot.org/story/09/10/06/0548202/lead-dev-on-dota-allstars-joins-valve</link><title>Lead Dev On DotA: Allstars Joins Valve</title><description>Brian Y. Chen writes "Defense of the Ancients: Allstars, a Warcraft 3 mod, is now played by millions and translated into 10 different languages. The extreme interest in the game has inspired developers unrelated to the mod itself to begin creating commercial games with similar gameplay: Heroes of Newerth, League of Legends and Demigod. Now it seems that Icefrog, the famously anonymous lead developer of DotA, will be taking the helm of a new team at Valve."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7417-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7417_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:33:37">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/121533</link><title>New RTS Based on DotA Offers Native Linux Client</title><description>S2 Games, longtime fans of the "Defense of the Ancients" (DotA) mod for Warcraft 3, have decided to create an entire game based around it (which IceFrog had no objection to). Without offending their still-active NDA, I can say that Heroes of Newerth is shaping up to be a very polished RTS, with the ability to play both via S2's own online service and local games, something that even Blizzard seems to be missing these days. Unlike most publishers, S2 has also decided to simultaneously release Windows, Mac, and Linux clients, making this one of the best looking games that I have ever seen on my Linux box. Additionally, S2 would like to invite another 400 players to the HoN beta, so if you are an RTS fan (and especially if you are a DotA fan) just send an email to scuttlemonkey at slashdot dot org with the subject line of "HoN Beta Key Request" and I'll reply to the first 400 requests as best I can. Update 20:37 GMT by SM: In case you don't notice in your haste to create a beta account, let me remind you that this game is still under strict NDA, so please no specifics in the discussion below. Update 00:01 GMT by SM: Well, given the 800+ emails that flooded my inbox in the first half hour or so we're all out of beta keys, but keep an eye out for a release date. Update 01:00 GMT by SM: Apparently your friends over at S2 games were quite impressed with the level of interest and are furnishing another 2,000 beta keys for me to continue working through the requests in my inbox (I'm at around 1,500 requests total as of this update, and only about 350 keys sent out). Please be patient as I slowly try to catch up. Also a point of clarification, while IceFrog doesn't mind S2 diving in to this space with a game based on DotA (competition is good in the long run after all), he wanted to make sure loyal fans of DotA knew that he plans to continue developing and improving DotA for WC3. Update 7/10/2009 13:06 GMT by SM: to all those still waiting on a beta invite, please be patient. I use gmail as the central repository for my email for ease-of-use, and while I was only expecting to have to hand out 400 keys, apparently gmail has an email cap of 500 per day. Last night my account got locked for excessive use, so I am waiting on the wrist-slap to expire so I can continue my key-spam. It looks like all who have requested a key so far will get one.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>