<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7433">747-8</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:52:07" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7433-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7433_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:52:09">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/13/10/06/2239208/why-the-faa-may-finally-relax-in-flight-device-rules</link><title>Why the FAA May Finally Relax In-Flight Device Rules</title><description>Nick Bilton at the New York Times has been writing skeptically for years about the FAA's ban on even the most benign electronic devices during takeoff and landing on commercial passenger flights. He writes in the NYT's Bits column about the gradual transformation that may (real soon now) result in slightly more sensible rules; a committee established to review some of those in-flight rules has recommended the FAA ease up, at least on devices with no plausible negative effect on navigation. From the article: "The New York Times employed EMT Labs, an independent testing facility in Mountain View, Calif., to see if a Kindle actually gave off enough electromagnetic emissions to affect a plane. The findings: An Amazon Kindle emitted less than 30 microvolts per meter when in use. That is only 0.00003 of a volt. A Boeing 747 must withstand 200 volts per square meter. That is millions of Kindles packed into each square meter of the plane. Still, the F.A.A. said “No.” ... But then something started to change: society." Of course, the rules that committees recommend aren't always the ones that prevail on the ground or in the sky.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7433-02"><link>http://science.slashdot.org/story/12/09/16/2222201/shuttle-endeavour-embarking-to-los-angeles-museum</link><title>Shuttle Endeavour Embarking to Los Angeles Museum</title><description>Endeavour will be the second of NASA's space shuttles to leave the Kennedy Space Center. The ship will piggyback on top of a specially modified 747 and head to a Los Angeles museum this week. From the article: "Endeavour's lifespan was relatively short by shuttle standards - 25 missions over 20 years, totaling 299 days in space. But those flights ran the gamut of orbital odysseys, including the sheer moxie of its May 1992 debut when three astronauts made an impromptu and unprecedented spacewalk to rescue a stranded Intelsat communications satellite."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7433-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7433_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:54:55">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/172063</link><title>Up Close With the Enterprise Shuttle At the Intrepid Museum</title><description>An anonymous reader writes "As you probably remember, the Space Shuttle Enterprise was flown on the back of a 747 to New York City where it was then delivered to the USS Intrepid. As sad as it was to see a space shuttle retired (and NASA take a major step down in the space flight abilities) this was one of the most amazingly geektastic events in recent memory. Now the shuttle is on top of the aircraft carrier's flight deck, living in its very own pavilion. As of tomorrow it will go on display as part of the Intrepid Sea, Air &amp; Space Museum, but today we got a sneak peek at the shuttle."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7433-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7433_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:57:03">http://developers.slashdot.org/story/12/06/12/1228245/russian-programmers-dominate-at-google-code-jam</link><title>Russian Programmers Dominate At Google Code Jam</title><description>New submitter Migala77 writes "Now that the third round for Google Code Jam is finished and only 25 contestants are left, we can look at which nationalities performed well and which didn't. Code Jam contestant foxlit has the stats, and some interesting things can be seen. Although there were over 3000 contestants from India in the qualification round (17% of the total) , only 3 of those managed to reach the third round (0.7% of the round 3 contestants) . This in contrast to Russia with 77 out of 747, and Belarus with 13 out of 114 reaching the third round. The U.S. performed somewhat below average too, with only 25 out of 2166 contestants making it to the third round."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7433-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7433_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:00:13">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/168313</link><title>Congress Wants To Resurrect Laser-Wielding 747</title><description>Harperdog writes "Noah Schactman has a great piece on the Airborne Laser, the ray gun-equipped 747 that became a symbol of wasteful Pentagon weaponeering. Despite sixteen years and billions of dollars in development, the jet could never reliably blast a missile in trials. Now the House Armed Services Committee's Strategic Forces wants the Airborne Laser to be used to defend us against the threat of North Korea's failed missiles."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7433-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7433_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:01:40">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/167727</link><title>The Space Shuttle Discovery's Last Mile (Video)</title><description>Timothy Lord was in the closest civilian parking lot to where the Space Shuttle Discovery touched down from her last flight \-- as a passenger on top of a 747, but it was still a space shuttle flying... a flight that was the sad epitaph for an American era. Timothy's shots of the landing approach are much like all the others you've seen. What's interesting is the variety of people he talked with. One came all the way from Tokyo. And there was the young man who got a Master's in Aeronautical Engineering to work on the space program, which sadly shut down, and who is now looking for a job with SpaceX or one of the other private space-bound companies. We hope there are lots of opportunities in the near future for him, and for thousands if not millions of others who want to go into space or, ground-bound, help our efforts to go where only science fiction writers' imaginations have gone before.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7433-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7433_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:04:06">http://science.slashdot.org/story/12/04/10/1237254/nasa-shuttle-discovery-set-to-buzz-washington-dc</link><title>NASA Shuttle Discovery Set To Buzz Washington, DC</title><description>coondoggie writes "Barring bad weather, NASA said the space shuttle Discovery mounted atop the space agency's 747 Shuttle Carrier Aircraft will make a series of low passes — 1,500 ft. — around parts of Washington DC on April 17 between 10-11 am eastern daylight time." Discovery will be on its way to the Smithsonian from Florida; this is a rare chance in the post-shuttle era for people to still see a shuttle in flight; I'm planning a marathon drive to reach the parking lot at the Steven F. Udvar-Hazy Center for what NASA's calling Shuttle Fly-In Day, in hopes of catching a glimpse.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7433-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7433_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:06:19">http://news.slashdot.org/story/10/10/20/1510235/boeing-747-recycled-into-a-private-residence</link><title>Boeing 747 Recycled Into a Private Residence</title><description>Ponca City writes "Nicholas Jackson writes in the Atlantic about a woman who requested only curvilinear/feminine shapes for her new home and has purchased an entire Boeing 747-200. They transported it by helicopter to her 55-acre property in the remote hills of Malibu and after deconstructing it, had all 4,500,000 pieces put back together to form a main house and six ancillary structures including a meditation pavilion, an animal barn, and an art studio building. 'The scale of a 747 aircraft is enormous — over 230 feet long, 195 feet wide and 63 feet tall with over 17,000 cubic feet of cargo area alone and represents a tremendous amount of material for a very economical price of less than $50,000,' writes Architect David Hertz. 'In researching airplane wings and superimposing different airplane wing types on the site to scale, the wing of a 747, at over 2,500 sq. ft., became an ideal configuration to maximize the views and provide a self supporting roof with minimal additional structural support needed.' Called the 'Wing House,' as a structure and engineering achievement, the aircraft encloses an enormous amount of space using the least amount of materials in a very resourceful and efficient manner, and the recycling of the 4.5 million parts of this 'big aluminum can' is seen as an extreme example of sustainable reuse and appropriation. Interestingly enough, the architects had to register the roof of the house with the FAA so pilots flying overhead would not mistake it as a downed aircraft."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7433-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7433_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:07:35">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/10/10/16/1956204/why-the-web-mustnt-become-the-new-tv</link><title>Why the Web Mustn't Become the New TV</title><description>An anonymous reader writes "This article argues that Rupert Murdoch's bid to own complete control of BSkyB is only part of an ongoing process to make the internet a totally 'linear' experience. The increase in the use of paginated content and the proliferation of video over transcribed interviews are, the author argues, part of a tidal shift from a browsable internet experience to a linear one that will move the user's experience of media from genuine choice to a series of locked-down 'information rides,' in order to re-secure advertising exposure. The author also writes, 'Current worries among publishing houses that magazines and newspapers will succumb to the digital written word on the internet are perhaps analogous to Victorian fears about mechanical horses taking over from real horses in the drawing of carriages. The point is being missed, the wrong fear being indulged.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7433-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7433_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:09:25">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/10/10/09/0023211/faa-reports-heat-in-cargo-holds-can-ignite-laptop-batteries</link><title>FAA Reports Heat In Cargo Holds Can Ignite Laptop Batteries</title><description>SpuriousLogic writes "US aviation officials are warning air carriers that new research shows lithium batteries are sensitive to heat and can ignite in-flight if transported in cargo compartments that get too hot. The Federal Aviation Administration also acknowledged publicly for the first time Friday that a United Parcel Service 747-400 plane that crashed in Dubai last month killing both pilots was carrying a large quantity of lithium batteries. Since the early 1990s, there have been dozens of incidents of batteries igniting in flight. But it has not been known what triggered many of the fires. FAA now says recent research has identified heat as the trigger and is offering air carriers advice on how to reduce the risk of fire."</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>