<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7438">facebook privacy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:14:54" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7438-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7438_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:14:57">http://yro.slashdot.org/story/14/04/17/2241218/new-facebook-phone-app-lets-you-stalk-your-friends</link><title>New Facebook Phone App Lets You Stalk Your Friends</title><description>Hugh Pickens DOT Com (2995471) writes "Iain Thomson reports that Facebook is adding a new application called 'Nearby Friends' that alerts smartphone users when their friends are nearby. 'If you turn on Nearby Friends, you'll occasionally be notified when friends are nearby, so you can get in touch with them and meet up,' says Facebook in a statement. 'For example, when you're headed to the movies, Nearby Friends will let you know if friends are nearby so you can see the movie together or meet up afterward.' The feature, which is opt-in, allows users to select which friends get a warning that you are in the area, and prepare a subset of people who might like to know when you're near, if they have the Nearby Friends activated as well. According to Josh Constine what makes 'Nearby Friends' different than competitors and could give it an advantage is that it's centered around broadcasting proximity, not location. 'If someone's close, you'll know, and can ping them about their precise location and meeting up. Broadcasting location is creepy so we're less likely to share it, and can cause awkward drop-ins where someone tries to come see you when you didn't want them to.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7438-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7438_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:16:43">http://yro.slashdot.org/story/14/04/15/2155210/52-million-photos-in-fbis-face-recognition-database-by-next-year</link><title>52 Million Photos In FBI's Face Recognition Database By Next Year</title><description>Advocatus Diaboli writes "The EFF has been investigating the FBI's Next-Generation Identification (NGI) scheme, an enormous database of biometric information. It's based on the agency's fingerprint database, which already has 100 million records. But according to the documents EFF dug up, the NGI database will include 52 million images of people's faces by 2015. At least 4.3 million images will have been taken outside any sort of criminal context. 'Currently, if you apply for any type of job that requires fingerprinting or a background check, your prints are sent to and stored by the FBI in its civil print database. However, the FBI has never before collected a photograph along with those prints. This is changing with NGI. Now an employer could require you to provide a 'mug shot' photo along with your fingerprints. If that's the case, then the FBI will store both your face print and your fingerprints along with your biographic data.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7438-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7438_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:18:35">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/14/04/14/198212/google-buys-drone-maker-titan-aerospace</link><title>Google Buys Drone Maker Titan Aerospace</title><description>garymortimer (1882326) writes "Google has acquired drone maker Titan Aerospace. Titan is a New Mexico-based company that makes high-flying solar powered drones. There's no word on the price Google paid, but Facebook had been in talks to acquire the company earlier this year for a reported $60 million. Presumably, Google paid more than that to keep it away from Facebook. 'Google had just recently demonstrated how its Loon prototype balloons could traverse the globe in a remarkably short period of time, but the use of drones could conceivably make a network of Internet-providing automotons even better at globe-trotting, with a higher degree of control and ability to react to changing conditions. Some kind of hybrid system might also be in the pipeline that marries both technologies.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7438-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7438_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:20:59">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/200363</link><title>Why No One Trusts Facebook To Power the Future</title><description>redletterdave (2493036) writes "Facebook owns virtually all the aspects of the social experience—photos (Instagram), status updates (Facebook), location services (Places)—but now, Facebook is transitioning from a simple social network to a full-fledged technology company that rivals Google, moonshot for moonshot. Yet, it's Facebook's corporate control of traffic that leads many to distrust the company. In a sense, people are stuck. When the time comes for someone to abandon Facebook, whether over privacy concerns or frustration with the company, Facebook intentionally makes it hard to leave. Even if you delete your account, your ghost remains—even when you die, Facebook can still make money off you. And that's not behavior fit for a company that's poised to take over the future."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7438-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7438_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:23:16">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/14/03/28/1917236/michael-abrash-joins-oculus-calls-facebook-final-piece-of-the-puzzle</link><title>Michael Abrash Joins Oculus, Calls Facebook 'Final Piece of the Puzzle'</title><description>trawg writes: "Programming legend Michael Abrash has announced that he has joined the Oculus team to work on the Rift VR headset as Chief Scientist, and will be once again working with John Carmack to bring VR to life. His post covers a lot of ground, including the history of his quest for VR, and ends with his explanation of why he thinks the Facebook acquisition is ultimately a good thing — they have the engineering, resources and long-term commitment 'to solve the hard problems of VR.'" Abrash has long maintained a blog about VR tech — it's worth reading if the subject matter interests you.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7438-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7438_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:25:35">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/199965</link><title>Minnesota Teen Wins Settlement After School Takes Facebook Password</title><description>schwit1 (797399) writes "A Minnesota school district has agreed to pay $70,000 to settle a lawsuit that claimed school officials violated a student's constitutional rights by viewing her Facebook and email accounts without permission. The lawsuit, filed in 2012 by the American Civil Liberties Union of Minnesota, alleged that Riley Stratton, now 15, was given detention after posting disparaging comments about a teacher's aide on her Facebook page, even though she was at home and not using school computers. After a parent complained about the Facebook chat, the school called her in and demanded her password. With a sheriff deputy looking on, she complied, and they browsed her Facebook page in front of her, according to the report. 'It was believed the parent had given permission to look at her cellphone,' Minnewaska Superintendent Greg Schmidt said Tuesday. But Schmidt said the district did not have a signed consent from the parent. That is now a policy requirement, he said.'" Asks schwit1, "How is this not a violation of the CFAA?" It sounds like the school was violating Facebook's Terms of Service, too.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7438-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7438_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:27:09">http://news.slashdot.org/story/14/03/19/225204/officials-nsas-prism-targets-email-addresses-not-keywords</link><title>Officials: NSA's PRISM Targets Email Addresses, Not Keywords</title><description>wiredmikey writes "The US government's PRISM Internet spying program exposed by Edward Snowden targets suspect email addresses and phone numbers but does not search for keywords like terrorism, officials said Wednesday. Top lawyers of the country's intelligence apparatus including the NSA and FBI participated Wednesday in a public hearing on the controversial US data-mining operations that intercept emails and other Internet communications including on social media networks like Facebook, Google or Skype. 'We figure out what we want and we get that specifically, that's why it's targeted collection rather than bulk collection,' Robert Litt, general counsel at the Office of the Director of National Intelligence, told the hearing. Under authority of the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act, the NSA asks Internet service providers to hand over messages sent from or received by certain accounts such as terrorist@google.com, the Justice Department's Brad Wiegmann said, using a hypothetical example."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7438-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7438_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:28:13">http://yro.slashdot.org/story/14/03/10/1553211/pinterest-reveals-its-first-transparency-report</link><title>Pinterest Reveals Its First Transparency Report</title><description>SmartAboutThings writes "There's been a lot of brouhaha surrounding privacy these days, and despite the fact that Pinterest isn't among the most targeted websites when it comes to government data requests, the company, which is said to have near 80 million users, has decided to make public its first ever transparency report. Given the nature of the service and the fact that it is much smaller than Facebook, it was only natural not to expect too many data requests. According to Pinterest's report, from July to December 2013, the company has received only 7 warrants, 5 subpoenas, 1 civil subpoena, and 0 other requests about 13 user accounts. Compare that to Microsoft which has received more than 35,000 requests during the second half of last year while Facebook received somewhere around 15,000."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7438-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7438_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:30:47">http://yro.slashdot.org/story/14/02/27/2316200/tor-is-building-an-anonymous-instant-messenger</link><title>Tor Is Building an Anonymous Instant Messenger</title><description>An anonymous reader writes in with news about a new anonymous instant messenger client on the way from Tor. "Forget the $16 billion romance between Facebook and WhatsApp. There's a new messaging tool worth watching. Tor, the team behind the world's leading online anonymity service, is developing a new anonymous instant messenger client, according to documents produced at the Tor 2014 Winter Developers Meeting in Reykjavik, Iceland."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7438-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7438_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:31:38">http://yro.slashdot.org/story/14/02/25/177235/facebook-shuts-down-facebook-email-system</link><title>Facebook Shuts Down @Facebook Email System</title><description>First time accepted submitter beaker_72 writes "The BBC are reporting that Facebook will end their email system which provided users an @Facebook.com email address in March. The official line from Facebook is that not many people have been using the service. Is that really the case or have they found it too challenging to monetize that part of their service? Did users stay away from this 'service' because they've become more savvy and recognized it for what it was — another way to harvest their data? Or is it the case that the market is currently saturated with free webmail services and there wasn't room for another one?"</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>