<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7439">make crown</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:32:20" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7439-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7439_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:32:23">http://linux.slashdot.org/story/14/02/27/2227238/experimental-port-of-debian-to-openrisc</link><title>Experimental Port of Debian To OpenRISC</title><description>Via Phoronix comes news that Debian has been ported to the OpenRISC architecture by Christian Svensson. Quoting his mailing list post: "Some people know that I've been working on porting Glibc and doing some toolchain work. My evil master plan was to make a Debian port, and today I'm a happy hacker indeed! ... If anyone want to try this on real hardware (would be very cool to see how this runs IRL), ping me on IRC [#openrisc on freenode] and I'll set you up with instructions how to use debootstrap - just point to a repo with the debs and you're all set, the wonders of binary distributions." For those who don't know, OpenRISC is the completely open source RISC processor intended as the crown jewel of the Opencores project. A working port of glibc and a GNU/Linux distribution is a huge step toward making use of OpenRISC practical. There's a screencast of the system in action, and source on Github (at posting time, it was a month out of date from the looks of it). Christian Svensson's Github account also has repos for the rest of the toolchain.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7439-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7439_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:33:47">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/196751</link><title>Book Review: The Digital Crown</title><description>benrothke writes "With Adobe Flash, it's possible to quickly get a pretty web site up and running; something that many firms do. But if there is no content behind the flashy web page, it's unlikely anyone will return. In The Digital Crown: Winning at Content on the Web, author Ahava Leibtag does a fantastic job on showing how to ensure that your web site has what it takes to get visitors to return, namely great content." Read below for the rest of Ben's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7439-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7439_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:36:30">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/183125</link><title>Dr. Robert Bakker Answers Your Questions</title><description>A while ago you had the chance to ask paleontologist Dr. Robert Bakker a wide variety of questions. Instead of answering them individually, Dr. Bob decided to write a lengthy piece that covers most of your inquiries, and includes personal stories and some of his philosophy. The first part is a narrative about his childhood conversion to fossil studies and how his paleo-CSI approach developed. We'll post the second half, covering his training in the history of theology and how it intersects with his science, tomorrow.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7439-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7439_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:37:54">http://science.slashdot.org/story/12/11/14/2014213/nate-silver-turns-his-eye-to-the-american-league</link><title>Nate Silver Turns His Eye To the American League</title><description>Lasrick writes "Nate Silver is at it again. This time, instead of the presidential election, he's focusing on the baseball's Most Valuable Player race for the American league. It's a race that embodies the split among baseball fans between those who think of it from a mathematical perspective (the Moneyball generation) and those who prefer the traditional, feel-of-the-game perspective. Here's a quote: 'On Thursday, the American League will announce the recipient of its Most Valuable Player award. The winner is likely to be Miguel Cabrera, the Detroit Tigers star who won the league’s triple crown by leading in batting average (.330), home runs (44) and runs batted in (139). It might seem as if these statistics make Cabrera, the first triple crown winner in either league since 1967, a shoo-in for the M.V.P. But most statistically minded fans would prefer that it go to another player, Mike Trout of the Los Angeles Angels.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7439-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7439_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:40:27">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/12/09/11/1450205/a-look-inside-oak-ridge-labs-supercomputing-facility</link><title>A Look Inside Oak Ridge Lab's Supercomputing Facility</title><description>1sockchuck writes "Three of the world's most powerful supercomputers live in adjacent aisles within a single data center at Oak Ridge National Laboratory in Tennessee. Inside this facility, technicians are busy installing new GPUs into the Jaguar supercomputer, the final step in its transformation into a more powerful system that will be known as Titan. The Oak Ridge team expects the GPU-accelerated machine to reach 20 petaflops, which should make it the fastest supercomputer in the Top 500. Data Center Knowledge has a story and photos looking at this unique facility, which also houses the Kraken machine from the University of Tennessee and NOAA's Gaea supercomputer."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7439-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7439_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:43:17">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/12/06/13/1756205/amd-and-arm-team-up</link><title>AMD and ARM Team Up</title><description>Vigile writes "Today AMD is making an announcement that is the first step in a drastic transition for the company by integrating an ARM Cortex A5 processor on the same die with upcoming Fusion APUs. Starting in late 2013, all AMD APUs (processors that are combinations of x86 cores and Radeon SIMD arrays) will also integrate an ARM Cortex A5 processor to handle security for online transactions, banking, identity protection and DRM integration. The A5 is the smallest Cortex processor available, and that would make sense to use it in a full APU so it will not take up more than 10-15 square mm of die space. This marks the first time AMD has licensed ARM technology and while many people were speculating a pure ARM+Radeon hybrid, this move today is being described as the 'first step' for AMD down a new road of dexterity as an IP-focused technology company with their GPU technology as 'the crown jewel.' So while today's announcement might focus on using ARM processors for security purposes, the future likely holds much more these two partners."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7439-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7439_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:43:48">http://yro.slashdot.org/story/12/01/11/225212/ibm-tops-most-patents-list-for-19th-straight-year</link><title>IBM Tops "Most Patents List" For 19th Straight Year</title><description>bednarz writes "IBM retained its patent crown for 2011, topping the list of patent winners for the 19th year in a row. The only other U.S. company to make the top 10, Microsoft, fell from third place to sixth place, according to IFI Claims Patent Services' list of the top 50 U.S. patent assignees. HP and Intel fell out of the top 10 and landed 14th and 16th, respectively. Apple moved up to No. 39 after breaking into the top 50 for the first time last year. Asian firms account for 25 of the top 50, and U.S. firms hold 17 slots."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7439-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7439_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:44:33">http://books.slashdot.org/story/11/06/02/1511219/book-review----javascript-the-definitive-guide-6th-edition</link><title>Book Review -- JavaScript: the Definitive Guide, 6th Edition</title><description>Michael J. Ross writes "Released during the early days of the Web, in 1995, JavaScript has come a long way: Initially a client-side scripting language typically (mis)used for decorative effects, it is now an essential part of countless major websites. Its increasing capabilities and popularity are due to several factors, including the development of libraries that resolve earlier stumbling blocks that held the language back (such as inconsistencies among the implementations in different vendors' browsers). JavaScript: The Definitive Guide, authored by David Flanagan, was first published just one year later, in 1996, with several significant updates made since then." Read below for the rest of Michael's review</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7439-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7439_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:46:24">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/136728</link><title>Cemetery Seeks To Change Image With Concerts and Exhibits</title><description>The management of Wheat Ridge, Colorado's Olinger Crown Hill Cemetery wants to change its image by hosting special events including art exhibits and concerts. The 103-year-old burial ground hopes that the events will change perceptions of their cemetery as "something more than a spot for solemn rituals." From the article: "The push to make the cemetery feel more like an ordinary part of the community began a few years ago and is gaining momentum. Crown Hill now urges people to tour the grounds and examine works by the Mexican artist and architect Dionicio Rodriguez — his only pieces in the state are scattered throughout the grounds."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7439-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7439_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:47:40">http://developers.slashdot.org/story/09/04/09/1819241/what-if-oracle-bought-sun-microsystems</link><title>What If Oracle Bought Sun Microsystems?</title><description>snydeq writes "Fatal Exception's Neil McAllister believes Oracle is next in line to make a play for Sun now that IBM has withdrawn its offer. Dismissing server market arguments in favor of Cisco or Dell as suitors, McAllister suggests that MySQL, ZFS, DTrace, and Java make Sun an even better asset to Oracle than to IBM. MySQL as a complement to Oracle's existing database business would make sense, given Oracle's 2005 purchase of Innobase, and with 'the long history of Oracle databases on Solaris servers, it might actually see owning Solaris as an asset,' McAllister writes. But the 'crown jewel' of the deal would be Java. 'It's almost impossible to overestimate the importance of Java to Oracle. Java has become the backbone of Oracle's middleware strategy,' McAllister contends."</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>