<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7447">running shoes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:08:54" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7447-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7447_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:08:57">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/196211</link><title>Brain Function "Boosted For Days After Reading a Novel"</title><description>cold fjord writes "The Independent reports, 'Being pulled into the world of a gripping novel can trigger actual, measurable changes in the brain that linger for at least five days after reading ... The new research, carried out at Emory University ... found that reading a good book may cause heightened connectivity in the brain and neurological changes that persist in a similar way to muscle memory. The changes were registered in the left temporal cortex, an area of the brain associated with receptivity for language, as well as the primary sensory motor region of the brain. Neurons of this region have been associated with tricking the mind into thinking it is doing something it is not, a phenomenon known as grounded cognition — for example, just thinking about running, can activate the neurons associated with the physical act of running. "The neural changes that we found associated with physical sensation and movement systems suggest that reading a novel can transport you into the body of the protagonist," said neuroscientist Professor Gregory Berns, lead author of the study. "We already knew that good stories can put you in someone else's shoes in a figurative sense. Now we're seeing that something may also be happening biologically."'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7447-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7447_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:10:45">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/13/12/03/1951213/epson-tries-to-one-up-google-glass-with-moverio-goggles-video</link><title>Epson Tries to One-up Google Glass with Moverio-Goggles (Video)</title><description>In the world of head-worn displays, Google Glass seems to lately get most of the praise as well as most of the dirty looks, though it's far from alone. At this year's DroidCon in London, I talked with Epson Europe product manager Marc-Antoine Godfroid about a very different kind of head-worn display: the Moverio BT-100. Epson's display is running a Google operating system, but it isn't competing with Glass, at least not directly. The hardware in this case is a relatively high-definition stereo display meant for immersion (whether that means information overlays or watching recorded video) hooked to an external control unit running Android, rather than the sparer, information-dashboard, all-in-one approach of Glass. One other big difference: Epson's stereo, full-color headset is cheaper than Glass, and available now. Hit the link below to see what it looks like.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7447-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7447_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:13:44">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/12/07/09/1915232/student-creates-worlds-fastest-shoe-with-a-printer</link><title>Student Creates World's Fastest Shoe With a Printer</title><description>An anonymous reader writes "Engineer and designer Luc Fusaro from the Royal College of Art in London has developed a prototype running shoe that can be uniquely sculpted to any athlete's foot. It's as light as a feather too, weighing in at 96 grams. The prototype is aptly named, Designed to Win, and is 3D printed out of nylon polyamide powder, which is a very strong and lightweight material. The manufacturing process uses selective laser sintering (SLS), which fuses powdered materials with a CO2 laser to create an object. This process means 3D scans can be taken of the runner's foot so as to ensure the shoe matches the shape perfectly. Fusaro can also change the stiffness of the soles according to the athlete's physical abilities. The shoe can improve performance by 3.5%, meaning a 10 second 100-meter sprinter could see his time drop by 0.35 seconds, which is a huge time saving relatively speaking. Imagine if Usain Bolt put a pair of these running shoes on."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7447-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7447_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:16:36">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/12/01/18/0736214/ces-recap-gadgets-and-blisters</link><title>CES Recap: Gadgets and Blisters</title><description>I was in Las Vegas last week to see the 2012 Consumer Electronics Show. (Officially, it's the International Consumer Electronics Show, but no one calls it "ICES.") I've been to CES just a few times before, but usually as the finish line of a marathon drive from Seattle, rather than a plane flight from Tennessee as it was this time around. I've also never arrived with an armload of video equipment, which brings its own hassles. (Did you notice our videos?) Following are a few thoughts about the experience.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7447-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7447_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:18:43">http://idle.slashdot.org/story/11/05/22/227247/creator-of-chinas-great-firewall-pelted-with-shoes</link><title>Creator of China's Great Firewall Pelted With Shoes</title><description>Hugh Pickens writes "The Guardian reports that Chinese police are seeking a man who said he threw eggs and shoes at the architect of China's 'great firewall', the world's most sophisticated and extensive online censorship system as his claims were cheered by many internet users, in a reflection of growing anger among them about increasingly stringent controls. The office of Fang Binxing, known as the father of the great firewall, denied the attack had happened, but Associated Press said police were sent to the university to investigate a shoe-throwing incident targeting Fang, citing an officer at the Luojiashan public security bureau. The Twitter user who claimed to have pelted him, who posts under the pseudonym @hanunyi, wrote: 'The egg missed the target. The first shoe hit the target. The second shoe was blocked by a man and a woman.' Earlier this year Fang closed a microblog within days of opening it after thousands of Chinese internet users left comments, almost all of them deriding him as 'a running dog for the government' and 'the enemy of netizens'. Meanwhile admirers of the shoe attacker showered the anonymous young man with promises of everything from Nike trainers to replace his lost footwear, to iPads, sex and jobs."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7447-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7447_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:21:50">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/10/12/20/1924216/microchips-now-in-tombstones-toilets-fish-lures</link><title>Microchips Now In Tombstones, Toilets, &amp; Fish Lures</title><description>Hugh Pickens writes "Steve Johnson writes in the Mercury News that microchips are going into a staggering array of once decidedly low-tech items — from gravestone markers and running shoes to fish lures and writing pens. In the future, 'where won't we find chips?' asks analyst Jordan Selburn. 'The answer is pretty close to nowhere.' For example, one company sells a coin-size, stainless steel-encased microchip for gravestone markers that tells the dead person's story in text, photos, video or audio histories, which visitors can access by pointing their Internet-enabled cell phones at it. The company says it has sold thousands of 'Memory Medallions.' There's AquaOne Technologies, who sell a toilet containing chips that automatically shut off the water when it springs a leak or starts to overflow, but Japanese company Toto goes one better with an intelligent toilet that gathers health-related data from the user's urine. Pro-Troll puts a chip in its fish lures that 'duplicates the electrical nerve discharge of a wounded bait fish,' prompting other fish to bite it."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7447-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7447_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:24:24">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/09/06/18/0951259/benqs-gp1-led-projector-small-package-good-thing</link><title>BenQ's GP1 LED Projector — Small Package, Good Thing</title><description>The first projector I remember seeing in person had three great big glass eyes (for red, green, and blue lamps) and BNC connectors. It probably weighed more than 100 pounds, and had to be carefully calibrated to align the lenses. Now, I've got a projector above my head that weighs less than a Neal Stephenson novel and has a sharper, brighter image than that monster. I've been looking into LED projectors for a few years now; in that time, I've been waiting for them to come down in price and bump up in lumens. So I was very curious about BenQ's GP1 LED projector (also known, somewhat oddly, as "Joybee"), and was happy to get a sample for review. It may seem retrograde to bother with an 800x600, 100 lumen (no missing zero there: one-hundred lumen) projector in 2009 A.D., but for the past four weeks, I've used it as my primary display, and come out happy. It has some drawbacks, but it's an impressive little device for its $499 pricetag, and I hope a harbinger of even better things to come. Read on for my take on what BenQ got right, and what rough spots stick out.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7447-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7447_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:25:09">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/117527</link><title>Do We Need Running Shoes To Run?</title><description>prostoalex writes to tell us The Daily Mail has an interesting look at current research in the field of running and injuries related to running. Most of the evidence pointed at a lack of any need for running shoes. Some of the more interesting points: the more expensive the running shoes, the greater the probability of getting an injury; some of the planet's best and most intense runners run barefoot; Stanford running team, having access to the top-notch modern shoes sent in for free by manufacturers, after a few rounds of trial and error still chose to train with no shoes at all."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7447-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7447_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:27:03">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/115589</link><title>Traveling With Tom Bihn's Checkpoint Flyer</title><description>Some people care about bags; obsession is a better word. (See the Bags subforum of the Every Day Carry Forums for evidence.) How are the straps attached? Is that 1050 denier, or 1600? Makers like Crumpler, Ortlieb and Maxpedition inspire impressive brand-loyalty, but probably no bag maker has customers more enthusiastic than Tom Bihn's. (There really is a Tom Bihn, too -- he's been designing travel bags since he was a kid; now he has a factory with "all the cool toys" to experiment with designs and materials.) When I started looking for a protective case for my MacBook Pro, I discovered that a few of my coworkers were part of the Bihn Army, and after some Tupperware-style evangelism I was convinced to buy a few items from the Bihn line-up: a backpack (used); then a messenger bag (new); then a mid-sized briefcase, used, which is now my portable filing cabinet. (Take this bias for what you will; I stuck with my previous messenger bag for more than a decade.) For a just-completed trip to Israel, which I couldn't quite make in true one-bag travel fashion, I brought along one of the newest Bihn Bags — the Checkpoint Flyer — and found it to be worth its (considerable) price. Read on for my review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7447-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7447_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:28:36">http://games.slashdot.org/story/08/12/08/120213/review-wrath-of-the-lich-king</link><title>Review: Wrath of the Lich King</title><description>Since shortly after its release in late 2004, World of Warcraft has held the position of the most popular MMO, quickly outstripping predecessors such as Everquest and Ultima Online, and continuing to hold the lead despite competition from contemporaries and newer offerings, like Warhammer Online. When World of Warcraft's first expansion, The Burning Crusade, was released, it built on an already rich world by using feedback from players and two extra years of design experience to work on condensing the game to focus more on the best parts. Now, with the release of Wrath of the Lich King, Blizzard seems to have gotten themselves ahead of the curve; in addition to the many changes intended to remove the "grind" aspect that is so prevalent in this genre, they've gone on to effectively put themselves in the player's shoes and ask, "What would make this more fun? Wouldn't it be cool if..?" Read on for the rest of my thoughts.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>