<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7456">gps reviews</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:39:04" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7456-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7456_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:39:06">http://books.slashdot.org/story/13/06/03/1410243/book-review-creating-mobile-apps-with-jquery-mobile</link><title>Book Review: Creating Mobile Apps With JQuery Mobile</title><description>sagecreek writes "You can judge this book, at least in part, by the lengthy tagline on its cover: 'Learn to make practical, unique, real-world sites that span a variety of industries and technologies with the world's most popular mobile development library.' jQuery might not be your favorite framework on the long, long list of JavaScript possibilities. But Shane Gliser unabashedly describes himself as a jQuery 'fanboy...if it's officially jQuery, I love it.' Gliser is an experienced mobile developer and blogger who operates Roughly Brilliant Digital Studios. He also has some background in mobile UX (user experience), and both qualities show in this smoothly written, well-illustrated, 234-page how-to book that focuses on jQuery Mobile, a 'touch-optimized' web framework for smartphones and tablets." Read below for the rest of sagecreek's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7456-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7456_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:42:21">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/13/05/15/1525242/google-io-2013-underway-watch-for-updates</link><title>Google I/O 2013 Underway: Watch For Updates</title><description>Google's I/O annual conference is ramping up at San Francisco's Moscone Center. Last year, in the conference keynote, the company took its biggest-yet dive into hardware when it introduced the Nexus 7 tablet, Google Glass, and the ill-fated Nexus Q. The secret is out on Glass, of course: this year, there's a pavilion inside the conference center where I'm sure they'll be showing off applications for it. (Quite a few of the people in the endless lines here are wearing their own, too.) Anticipating the announcements at I/O is practically its own industry, but it's easy to guess that there will be announcements from all the major pots in which Google has its many thousands of (tapping) fingers. Android, search, Chrome, mapping, and all the other ways in which the behemoth of Mountain View is watching what you do. You can watch the keynote talk (talks, really) streamed online from the main conference link above, but this story will be updated with highlights of the announcements, as well with stories that readers contribute. Update: 05/15 16:22 GMT by T : Updates below. Update: 05/15 19:02 GMT by T :Update details: Notes (ongoing) added below on maps, gaming, the Play store, Google+, and more. And, notable, Larry Page is (at this writing) on stage, with an unannounced Q &amp; A session.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7456-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7456_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:44:55">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/168719</link><title>Book Review: Fitness For Geeks</title><description>jsuda writes "You would think that geeks would be as interested in fitness as dogs are of TV. After all, geeks already put in hours of finger dancing on keyboards, assembling hefty code fragments, and juggling PHP programming functions. Although intended, in part, as a guide to real physical fitness the book, Fitness for Geeks, entices geeks with what they are really interested in–the science of fitness, nutrition, and exercise. In 11 chapters over 311 pages (including notes and an index) author, Bruce W Perry, describes in great detail the science of fitness and all of its components–food selections, timings, and fastings; exercising of all types; sleep, rest, and meditation; the benefits of hormesis (shocking the body with stresses); and the benefits of natural sunlight." Read on for the rest of jsuda's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7456-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7456_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:48:04">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/166519</link><title>NHTSA Suggestion Would Cripple In-Car GPS Displays</title><description>bricko writes "The recently issued National Highway Transportation Safety Agency guidelines for automakers to minimize distraction for in-vehicle electronics included a proposal to freeze maps on navigation systems. No more scrolling maps...just static pictures. 'Every current installed navigation system uses the car as a fixed point, and shows the map moving around it. NHTSA wants that changed so as to keep the map fixed. Even showing the position of the car moving on the map could be considered a dynamic image. The recommendation seems to suggest that the position of the car could only be updated every couple of seconds. Likewise, the map could be refreshed once the car has left the currently displayed area. This recommendation would essentially make navigation unusable. The system could still give an auditory warning for the next turn, but without being able to glance down at the map and see how close the next street is would likely lead to a lot of missed turns and resultant frustration.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7456-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7456_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:50:17">http://mobile.slashdot.org/story/10/12/27/1351252/hello-android-third-edition</link><title>Hello, Android Third Edition</title><description>eldavojohn writes "The third edition of Hello, Android brings the book up to date on Android versions from 1.5 to 2.2 (FroYo). The book is predominantly tied to the Eclipse editing environment with several pages devoted to screen shots of the IDE. As the title suggests, this book aims to give the user the equivalent of a "Hello, world!" application in Android and succeeds in doing that but doesn't take the reader much further. From creating a sudoku application with increasing support to dabbling in OpenGL ES, the book's prime audience are people who know a little Java (with no aversion to Eclipse) and XML but absolutely no Android. You can find the source for all the examples." Keep reading for the rest of eldavojohn's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7456-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7456_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:51:43">http://science.slashdot.org/story/10/08/02/1258208/beautiful-data</link><title>Beautiful Data</title><description>eldavojohn writes "Beautiful Data: The Stories Behind Elegant Data Solutions is an addition to six or so other books in the 'Beautiful' series that O'Reilly has put out. It is not a comprehensive guide on data but instead a glimpse into success stories about twenty different projects that succeeded in displaying data — oftentimes in areas where others have failed. While this provides, for the most part, disjointed stories, it is a very readable book compared to most technical books. Beautiful Data proves to be quite the cover-to-cover page turner for anyone involved in building interfaces for data or the statistician at a loss for the best way to intuitively and effectively relay knowledge when given voluminous amounts of raw data. That said, it took me almost two months to make it through this book, as each chapter revealed a data repository or tool I had no idea existed. I felt like a child with an attention deficit disorder trying my hand at nearly everything. While the book isn't designed to relay complete theory on data (like Tufte), it is a great series of short success stories revolving around the entire real world practice of consuming, aggregating, realizing and making beautiful data." Keep reading for the rest of eldavojohn's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7456-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7456_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:54:24">http://mobile.slashdot.org/story/09/12/13/1648205/are-sat-nav-systems-becoming-information-overload</link><title>Are Sat-Nav Systems Becoming Information Overload?</title><description>curtS writes "The Economist's tech editor reviews the ever-more-detailed assistance of mobile GPS devices, and wonders if the attention-sucking visual complexity isn't more trouble than it's worth. He contrasts the simplicity of London's Underground map (not directionally accurate but visually easy to understand) and his own habit of dimming the display and using the audio commands for guidance."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7456-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7456_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:56:50">http://news.slashdot.org/story/09/05/27/1327255/beginning-python-visualization</link><title>Beginning Python Visualization</title><description>aceydacey writes "Sometimes a picture is worth a thousand words. Beginning Python Visualization: Creating Visual Transformation Scripts, published in February 2009 by Apress, shows how Python and its related tools can be used to easily and effectively turn raw data into visual representations that communicate effectively. The author is Shai Vaingast, a professional engineer and engineering manager who needed to train scientists and engineers to do this kind of programming work. He was looking for a tutorial and reference work, and unable to find a suitable text, wound up writing his first book. He writes in the easy and clear style of someone comfortable and engaged with the subject matter." Keep reading for the rest of aceydacey's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7456-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7456_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:57:24">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/07/04/18/1921217/us-soldiers-hate-new-high-tech-gear</link><title>U.S. Soldiers Hate New High-Tech Gear</title><description>mattnyc99 writes "Land Warrior, the Army's wireless equipment package featuring helmet cams, GPS, laser range-finders and a host of other state-of-the-art electronics, is finally ready for deployment on a global battlefield network in Iraq after 15 years of R&amp;D at the Pentagon. But in a report for Popular Mechanics, Noah Shachtman not only tries on the new digital armor—he talks to troops who don't like it at all. As if that wasn't disheartening enough for the future of tech at war, the real Land Warrior system doesn't even match up to its copycat gear in Ghost Recon 2."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7456-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7456_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:58:16">http://slashdot.org/story/06/06/29/1221208/a-car-navigation-system-that-takes-pictures</link><title>A Car Navigation System That Takes Pictures</title><description>Brandon Miniman writes "Navman has brought to market the first in-car navigation system with a built in camera, the iCN 750. The camera lets you take pictures of places you've been. Geographical coordinates are then assigned to each picture, so that you can bring up a gallery, and choose your destination by clicking on a picture." Add to this an always-on, all-sides video camera to document that it was the minivan that strayed into your lane, and it'll be even better.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>