<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7457">the music man lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:58:48" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7457-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7457_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:58:50">http://features.slashdot.org/story/14/03/02/2041246/the-fat-man-george-sanger-answers-your-questions-about-music-and-games</link><title>"The Fat Man" George Sanger Answers Your Questions About Music and Games</title><description>A while ago you had a chance to ask composer George Sanger about making music and sound effects for games, television, and film. Below you'll find "The Fat Man's" answers to those questions.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7457-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7457_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:01:17">http://news.slashdot.org/story/07/04/23/1223248/u2-bringing-spider-man-to-broadway</link><title>U2 Bringing Spider-man to Broadway</title><description>Music Juice writes "A Broadway musical based on the web-slinging superhero is in the works, Marvel Studios said Friday. It will be directed by Tony winner Julie Taymor with new music and lyrics by U2 frontman Bono and guitarist The Edge. The musical will be the first time a Marvel Comics character has been the subject of a show on Broadway, the company said. No opening date was announced, but Marvel said a reading would take place this summer. "</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7457-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7457_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:04:02">http://news.slashdot.org/story/05/03/22/1418238/mc-chris-answers-your-questions</link><title>mc chris Answers Your Questions</title><description>mc chris, the "beloved" rapper behinds such classics as Fett's Vette and The Tussin in addition to voicing Hesh on Cartoon Networks Sealab 2021 has responded to reader questions. The riveting results are just one click away. You know you want it. And his tour has dates in NC, SC, FL, GA and more. You know you want those too.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7457-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7457_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:04:53">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/54904</link><title>The 'Dear Friends' Final Fantasy Concert First Hand</title><description>Last Saturday night I had the pleasure of enjoying the "Dear Friends" concert of Final Fantasy music in Rosemont, Illinois. Composer Nobuo Uematsu is well known among game players for the intricate melodies that create the backdrop for most of the Final Fantasy titles. Even the older titles, 8-bit compositions though they were, made for evocative soundscapes. When taken into the hands of a skilled orchestra Uematsu's works are incredibly stirring pieces of music. Read on for my impressions from the start of the first U.S. concert series composed entirely of video game music. Update: 02/25 21:08 GMT by Z : Coincidentally, GamesIndustry.biz has an interview with Nobuo Uematsu available for perusal today.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7457-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7457_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:07:28">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/51897</link><title>Trekkies Director Roger Nygard Answers</title><description>Last week we called for questions for Roger Nygard, the director of Trekkies, and its recently released sequel. He replies today with answers to many of your questions in a riveting interview set to stun. Or some other appropriate trek joke. Read on for the glorious answers (which might include some offensive language in the form of lyrics from a Star Trek themed band)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7457-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7457_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:08:17">http://slashdot.org/story/01/10/29/173252/wil-wheaton-responds-to-your-questions</link><title>Wil Wheaton Responds to your Questions.</title><description>Here we go, answer to Your Questions from Wil Wheaton. Share and Enjoy! A big thanks to Wil for taking the time to answer so many of our questions.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7457-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7457_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:10:16">http://news.slashdot.org/story/00/12/21/150204/answers-from-they-might-be-giants</link><title>Answers From 'They Might Be Giants'</title><description>We put up the 'Ask TMBG' post the Friday before last (Dec. 8) . Here's their response, just in time for the major Judeo/Christian winter holidays. Enjoy!</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7457-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7457_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:12:29">http://slashdot.org/story/99/02/26/107210/reviewvirtual-faith</link><title>Review:Virtual Faith</title><description>Jon Katz, known to everyone here, has sent us a review of Tom Beaudoin's book Virtual Faith, a book that explores the issue of the Internet, the Web, and Faith. Interestings stuff for the philosphical amongst us.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7457-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7457_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:13:04">http://slashdot.org/story/99/01/31/107204/lyrics-site-may-go-commercial</link><title>Lyrics Site May Go Commercial</title><description>Secret Asian Man writes "In this New York Times article, entitled Lyrics Site in Copyright Dispute May Go Commercial" it appears that the International Lyrics Server might go commercial in order to reopen, and share the profits with the music industry. Rather strange story. Even mentions Linux, as an aside. " The NYT Article requires a free login. Hope this all works out, else I'll never get the words right to any of the songs I sing loudly and offkey. Now what about OLGA?</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>