<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7463">hollywood actress</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-20 14:36:54" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7463-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7463_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-20 14:36:56">http://search.slashdot.org/story/11/10/18/2136254/microsoft-patenting-celebrity-shaped-binging</link><title>Microsoft Patenting Celebrity-Shaped Bing'ing</title><description>theodp writes "GeekWire reports that Microsoft is seeking a patent on the concept of applying the persona of a celebrity to Internet searches, allowing people to see search results shaped by the personalities and preferences of Hollywood celebrities like Miley Cyrus, Taylor Swift, Megan Fox, and Jessica Lange. A search for an evening dress using the persona of Jessica Lange, explains Microsoft, would return dresses that reflect the actress's 'style and/or fashion preferences,' including 'color, fit, designer, cut, etc.' Your move, Google."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7463-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7463_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-20 14:38:22">http://science.slashdot.org/story/07/08/03/1622231/winnie-wrote-a-math-book</link><title>Winnie Wrote a Math Book</title><description>SoyChemist writes "Hollywood is not known for providing a wealth of positive female role models. Danica McKellar, the actress that played Winnie Cooper on The Wonder Years and Elsie Snuffin on The West Wing, has written a math book for teenage girls. 'Math Doesn't Suck' is done in the style of a teen magazine. It even includes a horoscope, cute doodles of shoes and jewelry, and testimonials from attractive young career women that use math at work. It focuses on fractions and pre-algebra and uses mnemonics like calling a reciprocal a 'refliprocal', because you just take the fraction and flip it upside down. Wired interviewed McKellar about the new book and her crusade to eliminate the achievement gap between boys and girls in math courses. McKellar graduated Summa Cum Laude from UCLA. While studying there, she co-authored a proof and presented it at a conference. After she and Mayim Bialik — star of Blossom and a PhD in neuroscience — appeared in a 20/20 episode about intellectual actresses, several literary agents came knocking on her door."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7463-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7463_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-20 14:39:40">http://slashdot.org/story/07/07/25/1725238/mst3k-is-back-sort-of</link><title>MST3K is Back, Sort Of</title><description>Polar Star writes "Retrocrush reports that Mike Nelson, Kevin Murphy, and Bill Corbett are back making fun of crappy movies again in a new incarnation called The Film Crew. In the first of many new DVDs to be released, they take on a 1969 abomination called Hollywood After Dark which features a still-not-very-young Rue McClanahan as a down-on-her-luck actress who becomes a stripper. Needless to say, it's one of the scariest movies you'll ever see. There's plenty of funny jokes throughout, and they definitely prove themselves worthy of carrying on the MST3K tradition." Update 1925 GMT by SM: Corrected a few oversights and pointed to The Film Crew's actual website.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7463-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7463_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-20 14:40:36">http://slashdot.org/story/05/06/27/0926218/wil-wheaton-strikes-back</link><title>Wil Wheaton Strikes Back</title><description>You may recall that sometime last November we put up a request for questions to be passed on to author, voice actor, comedian, and card shark Wil Wheaton. Seven months and many adventures later, Wil has responded in depth to the excellent queries Slashdot users put to him. If you're curious about what's kept him, what it's like to be a Teen Titan, or how to use the LCARS User Interface, read on for his responses.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7463-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7463_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-20 14:41:41">http://news.slashdot.org/story/05/06/22/1959237/from-alien-to-the-matrix</link><title>From Alien to The Matrix</title><description>Spencerian writes "Roz Kaveney's From Alien to the Matrix is definitely a love-to-hate book for me, and probably for most fanboys who've forgotten more than the author knows about the meanings, philosophy, and humor found in many popular SF films of the last 35 years. If you love to argue and curse when you read something that's so way off base in interpretation or appears to lack any research in even the basic meanings that most Americans found in a SF film, then this is your book. But if you hate arguing with your non-fannish significant other on why you really liked a particular movie, save your money by not buying this book. Oh, and dump your boy/girlfriend, too." Read on for the rest of Spencerian's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7463-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7463_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-20 14:43:13">http://news.slashdot.org/story/01/01/25/1922200/shadow-of-the-vampire</link><title>Shadow Of The Vampire</title><description>If you need to escape Hype Sunday, or even if you don't, go see Shadow Of The Vampire.The odd and the slightly twisted will go nuts over this film by E. Elias Merhige. William Dafoe is astounding as the vampire Count Orlock, and John Malkovich is his wonderful icky and obsessive self as the director whose only moral value is getting his film made at any cost. Spoilage warning: plot is discussed, no endings. A brief and useful Nosferatu primer is included, free of charge.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7463-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7463_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-20 14:44:40">http://news.slashdot.org/story/99/08/08/1742241/lo-tech-cinema</link><title>Lo-Tech Cinema</title><description>By Hollywood standards, the "The Blair Witch Project" is shockingly Lo-Tech, employing none of the expensive techno-tricks that increasingly overwhelm movie after movie. But the BWP, thumping expensive hi-tech competitors like "The Haunting" and "Deep Blue Sea," uses technology brilliantly, if minimally, in its making and marketing. Here's to a new Lo-Tech genre in cinema.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7463-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7463_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-20 14:45:50">http://news.slashdot.org/story/98/12/12/1632242/impeachment-and-the-internet</link><title>Impeachment and the Internet</title><description>On the Net and the Web this year, we saw one kind of revolution after another: the Web helped elected a governor, saw the spread of new kinds of messaging communities like ICQ and Hotline, the rapid spread of politicized movements like OS and Free Software, the storming of the digital world by retailers and big cornporations, and oh yes, we were shocked by the sudden and highly pornographic appearance here of the Kenneth Starr report one day. But it's easy to be online for days and not quite grasp what's going on out there, which is a full-blown constitutional crisis. The differences between the old and new information cultures have never been more clearly defined than by Linda, Monica, Ken, Bill, Sam, Cokie and the members of the House Judiciary Committee.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>