<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7472">python re tutorial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:40:58" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7472-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7472_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:41:01">http://interviews.slashdot.org/story/11/09/14/1554243/eben-upton-answers-your-questions</link><title>Eben Upton Answers Your Questions</title><description>Last week you asked the Director of the Raspberry Pi Foundation, Eben Upton, about developing an ultra-low-cost computer and running a charitable organization. Below you'll find his answers. Thanks go out to a busy Eben for responding so quickly.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7472-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7472_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:42:16">http://developers.slashdot.org/story/11/08/19/1215257/book-review-the-python-standard-library-by-example</link><title>Book Review: The Python Standard Library By Example</title><description>thatpythonguy writes "Addison-Wesley publishers has released The Python Standard Library By Example, another Python book that strategically fits in between programming cookbooks and library reference manuals. It brings the Python standard library that much closer to Python programmers and helps make them more proficient in their trade." Read below for Ahmed's first Slashdot review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7472-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7472_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:43:13">http://books.slashdot.org/story/11/04/27/1218207/book-review-amazon-simpledb-developer-guide</link><title>Book Review: Amazon SimpleDB Developer Guide</title><description>KuanH writes "Amazon SimpleDB Developer Guide is billed as a complete guide to using Amazon's SimpleDB database API. It's most detailed for PHP. It's helpful for Python. But the Java code and explanations aren't up to the standard of the others. It includes a primer on using Amazon S3 with SimpleDB: files stored on S3, file metadata stored in SimpleDB — again, less good for Java. It also covers tuning to reduce usage costs, caching using memcached, and ways to batch-update and make serial or parallel requests to SimpleDB. However, it's missing some information that beginners might need, and it's perhaps not quite advanced enough for the more experienced. Downloadable example code is available only for PHP." Keep reading for the rest of Kuan's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7472-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7472_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:44:53">http://books.slashdot.org/story/10/05/26/1524232/django-11-testing-and-debugging</link><title>Django 1.1 Testing and Debugging</title><description>johnmccollum writes "A wealth of tools are available to debug and test Django applications, but knowing when and how to use these resources can intimidate the new user. Django 1.1 Testing and Debugging, by Karen M. Tracey, aims to walk the user through the process of creating a web application from scratch, ensuring that the resulting code is bug-free and ready for production." Keep reading for the rest of John's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7472-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7472_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:46:33">http://books.slashdot.org/story/10/05/10/1340245/hacking-vim-72</link><title>Hacking Vim 7.2</title><description>briancarper writes "Vim is an open-source text editor with a power and flexibility matched only by the steepness of its learning curve. As the author of this book states, 'Vim Can Do Everything' but configuring it to do so is sometimes daunting. Hacking Vim 7.2 aims to help the average Vimmer get the most out of customizing Vim, for fun and productivity." Read on for the rest of briancarper's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7472-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7472_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:48:09">http://news.slashdot.org/story/09/03/18/1327241/beginning-gimp-from-novice-to-professional-2nd-ed</link><title>Beginning GIMP: From Novice to Professional 2nd Ed</title><description>r3lody writes "An extremely large amount of the information we get on a daily basis comes from what we see. Imagery is therefore very important to those who want to communicate with us. When computers had advanced enough to be able to process images in a digital fashion, the market opened up for programs that could manipulate them in many ways. While many professionals would opt for the paid programs, there is a free alternative: GIMP (Gnu Image Manipulation Program). The only stumbling block is learning how to use it properly. That is where Beginning GIMP: From Novice to Professional, Second Edition by Akkana Peck comes in." Read below for the rest of Ray's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7472-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7472_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:49:13">http://news.slashdot.org/story/08/07/23/1339226/practical-django-projects</link><title>Practical Django Projects</title><description>Chromodromic writes "Apress's newest Django offering, Practical Django Projects by James Bennett, weighs in lightly at 224 pages of actual tutorial content, but trust me, they're dense pages. Filled with pragmatic examples which directly address the kinds of development issues you will encounter when first starting out with Django, this book makes an important addition to the aspiring Django developer's reference shelf. In particular, the book's emphasis on demonstrating best practices while building complete projects does an excellent job of accelerating an understanding of Django's most powerful features — in a realistic, pragmatic setting — and which a developer will be able to leverage in very short order." Read below for the rest of Greg's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7472-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7472_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:50:19">http://news.slashdot.org/story/07/04/23/1429230/beginning-ruby</link><title>Beginning Ruby</title><description>TimHunter writes "Peter Cooper's Beginning Ruby: From Novice to Professional has two audiences, novices with no programming experience who want to learn Ruby as their first programming language, and veterans who want to add Ruby to their programming toolkit. Cooper's response to this challenge is a solid entry in the limited arena of Ruby tutorials. Even though the early chapters are marred by the occasional reference to an advanced topic, readers will appreciate the plentiful examples and thoughtful description of the Ruby language." Read below for the rest of Tim's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7472-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7472_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:51:18">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/81675</link><title>EVE Online Answers Your Questions</title><description>Last week at GDC I had the privilege of sitting down to speak with a representative from CCP, the folks who maintain EVE Online. The week before, we'd asked for questions to pass on. I had the chance to put them directly to Magnus Bergsson, CMO at CCP. He very directly tackles the recent scandal involving a CCP developer, the reason why EVE's hardcore gameplay is so appealing, the balance between casual and hardcore players, and some information on the future of the game. Read on for his answers to your questions in a transcript of the interview, as well as audio live from the GDC Expo floor.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7472-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7472_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:52:41">http://slashdot.org/story/07/01/08/1536255/sql-hacks</link><title>SQL Hacks</title><description>Scott Walters writes "Many of the recipes in SQL Hacks will improve the SQL you write day to day, and many will give you the confidence to attempt much more involved tasks with SQL. Other recipes will rarely if ever be needed, but make for a entertaining and education reading in a similar way that "worse case survival scenario" books do — SQL is pitted against the most difficult analysis tasks just as survival scenario books pit humans against pavement and lions. SQL Hacks fits well in the Hacks series, which raises the bar on advanced books by offering large, eclectic sets of tricks for problems that an unambitious person (a non-hacker) wouldn't ever push technology hard enough to run into. Put another way, the questions answered in a good Hacks book are ones that would get a "good question" comment rather than a an "RTFM!" response. It does a good job continuing where O'Reilly's SQL Cookbook left off, which is always difficult with two books written at slightly different times by different authors. Still, it's harder to review a Hacks book than a Learning book as, with hacks, the sky is the limit, and the reader will always find herself wishing for more. To this end, I hope O'Reilly continues to publish newer editions of their various Hacks books, drawing in more and more content in each edition, and identifying recipes that might better serve in the Cookbook counterpart." Read the rest of Scott's review.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>