<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7475">software consultant work at home</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:55:49" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7475-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7475_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:55:52">http://yro.slashdot.org/story/12/06/14/160233/vermont-senate-hopeful-jeremy-hansen-responds-on-mostly-direct-democracy</link><title>Vermont Senate Hopeful Jeremy Hansen Responds On (Mostly) Direct Democracy</title><description>Last week, you asked questions of Vermont Senate candidate Jeremy Hansen, running on an unusual platform: Hansen pledges to take advantage of modern communications if elected, and (with exceptions he outlines in his answers) vote based on the opinion of his district's voters on a per-issue basis. Read below Hansen's answers about such a system could work; he addresses concerns about security, practicality, morality, and more. "Before I start with the answers," he writes in introduction, "I want to clear a few things up. I am running as an independent for a Vermont Senate seat, not the U.S. Senate, so questions about classified and similar material do not (for the most part) apply. Also, for everyone's reference, there are 44,000 registered voters in Vermont's Washington County Senate district. Many of the concerns about managing input from very large populations are not as applicable here." Read on for more.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7475-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7475_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:58:15">http://slashdot.org/story/06/03/21/2329216/answers-from-our-man-in-jordan</link><title>Answers from 'Our Man in Jordan'</title><description>At the beginning of this month we sent your questions to Isam Bayazidi of Amman, Jordan. He's a Slashdot reader, founder of the Jordan Planet blogging community, and (I know this from personal experience) knows the best places to buy discount-priced computer components in his home town. Enjoy!</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7475-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7475_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:01:39">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/59794</link><title>Infosec Career Hacking</title><description>nazarijo writes "Plenty of people are curious as to how to become an information security professional. It's a profession that has a bit of an establishment atmosphere to it where entry to various levels is granted in secret. And it's often hard to understand where to start. Infosec Career Hacking attempts to demystify this process and show you not only generic strategies for employment, but ones specific to the information security field." Read on for the rest of Nazario's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7475-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7475_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:03:58">http://news.slashdot.org/story/05/06/15/2047253/essential-mac-os-x-server-administration</link><title>Essential Mac OS X Server Administration</title><description>norburym writes " Essential Mac OS X Server Administration, written by Michael Bartosh and Ryan Faas, has been eagerly anticipated by the OS X Panther Server community. The wait is finally over and the authors have satisfied their audience with a meticulously written and detailed volume on OS X Server administration. This is not a book for the beginner: if you're an IT professional with an OS X Server deployment and want to gain a thorough understanding and appreciation of integrating Panther Server into your particular environment then this book will fully meet your expectations. Bartosh and Fass present a complete exploration of OS X Server software and services and client considerations between the covers of a volume essential to any systems administrator responsible for a cross-platform network." Read on for Norbury-Glaser's detailed review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7475-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7475_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:06:44">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/48751</link><title>Wi-Foo: The Secrets of Wireless Hacking</title><description>prostoalex writes "Wireless LANs seem to be enjoying the tremendous amount of interest lately, if you judge by the number of book covers and articles written on the topic. It's no wonder that this year the sales of WLAN equipment will grow 20% and generate $2.1 billion \- everyone seems to be installing a wireless network in their office, their apartment complex or their own backyard. With extending the network into the radio world one is always extending the opportunities for unwelcome visitors to become part of the network. This book is a hands-on guide on hacking wireless networks followed by the recipes and principles to protect WLANs." Read on for the rest of prostoalex's review of Wi-Foo .</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7475-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7475_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:09:13">http://news.slashdot.org/story/04/02/17/1654255/indian-techies-answer-about-onshore-insourcing</link><title>Indian Techies Answer About 'Onshore Insourcing'</title><description>This is an unusual Slashdot Interview, since instead of using email I asked all the questions in person last week either at LinuxAsia2004 or in casual meetings with local LUG members and other techies I met during the conference. Some of your questions were answered quite well by other Slashdot readers in the original post. (Slashdot has many readers both in and from India.) I also inserted a number of personal observations, which I usually don't do in these interviews, because it seemed to be the best way to answer some of the questions. And some questions were nearly unanswerable, as you'll see when you read the rest of this article.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7475-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7475_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:12:09">http://interviews.slashdot.org/story/03/08/01/1615232/lobbyist-morgan-reed-answers-your-questions</link><title>Lobbyist Morgan Reed Answers Your Questions</title><description>A long, long time ago, you asked lobbyist Morgan Reed questions about lobbying, undue industry influence on United States laws as they apply to the tech sector, the future of internet taxation, and more. Reed, in the meantime, has switched jobs: he's now working for the Association for Competitive Technology (as he candidly and lightheartedly acknowledges, "the enemy" to many Slashdot readers, since they lobby for large software corporations, notably Microsoft), and is finally free to answer your questions. Read on for about as inside a viewpoint as you can find on how you can affect your elected representatives, from someone whose job is to do just that. Update: 08/01 19:24 GMT by M : That's Morgan Reed, not Reed Morgan. We suck.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7475-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7475_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:13:42">http://features.slashdot.org/story/00/03/30/1339259/the-rise-of-the-chickclickers</link><title>The Rise Of The Chickclickers</title><description>Young women between the ages of 13 and 30 are pouring online. They're at the heart of the rapidly growing movement of women onto the Net. Political correctness aside, men and women are not alike, at least not online. They may have equal skills, but they choose to do very different things. Along with open source, younger women may trigger another political, media and social transformation in cyberspace.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7475-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7475_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:16:32">http://features.slashdot.org/story/99/05/04/1437206/ebay-launches-the-era-of-virtual-property</link><title>eBay launches the era of Virtual Property</title><description>On eBay, people are shelling out thousands of dollars for gaming characters, symbols, armor, magical potions of trinkets. The media has missed the real story as usual: it isn't online violence, it's digital property. eBay may be even more significant than Mp3's. As the middle-class plunges into gaming, the Net is facing real world problems like housing costs and congestion. The result is another landmark in Net evolution: the owning of virtual property, something that may change the nature of Net economics and knock the gaming world for a loop.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>