<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7477">china bird flu</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:39:03" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7477-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7477_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:39:04">http://science.slashdot.org/story/13/05/26/1751201/tests-show-that-deadly-new-flu-could-spread-among-people</link><title>Tests Show That Deadly New Flu Could Spread Among People</title><description>An anonymous reader writes in with another news story about how the bird flu may wipe us out. "A new bird flu that has killed 36 people in China can spread from ferret to ferret through the air. A laboratory test showing airborne transmission of the H7N9 avian influenza virus between the animals has raised fears that the virus is poised to become a human pandemic. The H7N9 avian influenza virus emerged suddenly at the end of February and has infected 131 people. A few patients may have caught the virus from other infected people, but no evidence has emerged that H7N9 can readily transmit from human to human."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7477-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7477_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:40:02">http://science.slashdot.org/story/13/04/24/1639203/modelling-reveals-likely-spread-of-new-h7n9-avian-flu</link><title>Modelling Reveals Likely Spread of New H7N9 Avian Flu</title><description>ananyo writes "With Taiwan announcing the first case of H7N9 avian flu outside mainland China, researchers have revealed how the virus may spread in China — and beyond. The projections use risk maps developed for human infection by another, well-established avian flu — H5N1. Indeed, when human cases of H7N9 are overlaid on a risk map, they appear to fall within the highest risk areas for H5N1. The map suggests that high-risk areas for H7N9 might include Shandong province (where the first case was reported 23 April) and a belt extending around the Bohai sea to Liaoning province in the north. Though there has been no evidence of sustained human-to-human spread of H7N9 so far, researchers have analyzed airline passenger data for China. Eastern China — the epicenter of the current the H7N9 outbreak — is one of the world's busiest hubs for airline traffic. From the Nature story: 'A quarter of the global population outside of China lives within two hours of an airport with a direct flight from the outbreak regions, and 70% if a single connecting flight is included.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7477-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7477_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:41:44">http://slashdot.org/story/06/10/31/1741233/timely-book-on-bird-flu</link><title>Timely Book On Bird Flu</title><description>Lifelongactivist writes, "A new free book about bird flu has been published by Michael Greger, M.D., the US Humane Society's director of public health and animal agriculture. Bird Flu: a Virus of Our Own Hatching (the site contains the entire book text) tells why modern industrialized agricultural methods, including factory farming, antibiotics misuse, and the use of animal refuse as a food source (!) for chickens and other livestock, have led to a staggering increase in the number of 'zoonotic' diseases that can leap from animals to people, and make a bird flu pandemic likely. The book discusses in practical terms what you can do to prevent infection and what to do if you do catch the disease. The book is especially timely given yesterday's news that a new, vaccine-resistant variant of H5N1 has been detected in China." 
Update: 10/31 19:44 GMT by KD : Corrected to read "vaccine-resistant."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7477-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7477_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:42:57">http://slashdot.org/story/06/04/01/1712242/china-buys-google</link><title>China Buys Google</title><description>Fry-kun writes "The Register reports that a controlling amount of Google's Class B stock was purchased today a corporate entity owned by the Chinese Ministry of Information." From the article: "Amongst the assets acquired by the Chinese government is NASA's Ames Research Center. Google announced a partnership with Ames last year, and, as it turns out, the move laid the groundwork for the takeover by the PRC. The Chinese will gain control of the world's largest wind tunnels - devices that when opened up could be used to push the smell of Mu Shu Pork across much of Silicon Valley, or conversely be used to spread avian bird flu, or mind-altering substances."</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>