<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7483">facebook paying?</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:54:25" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7483-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7483_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:54:27">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/198873</link><title>Girl's Facebook Post Costs Her Dad $80,000</title><description>Hugh Pickens DOT Com writes "BBC reports that when Dana Snay learned her father had been awarded an $80,000 cash settlement in an age-discrimination lawsuit against his former employer, she couldn't resist bragging about it on Facebook. 'Mama and Papa Snay won the case against Gulliver,' the teen posted to her 1,200 Facebook friends. 'Gulliver is now officially paying for my vacation to Europe this summer. SUCK IT.' Trouble was her father had signed a confidentiality agreement so the school refused to pay a dime and a Florida appeals court has found in the school's favor. 'Snay violated the agreement by doing exactly what he had promised not to do,' wrote Judge Linda Ann Wells. 'His daughter then did precisely what the confidentiality agreement was designed to prevent.' Snay's father said in depositions that he and his wife knew they had to say something to their daughter because she suffered 'psychological scars' from issues during her enrollment at the school and was aware that they were in mediation with Gulliver attorneys. Attorneys say it's unlikely confiding in Dana Snay would have jeopardized the settlement — it was the facebook post that did them in. 'Remember when all you had to worry about was your daughter posting naked selfies of herself on Facebook?' writes Elie Mystal at Above the Law. 'Now, things are worse.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7483-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7483_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:56:50">http://yro.slashdot.org/story/14/02/10/2318244/3-reasons-to-hate-mass-surveillance-3-ways-to-fight-it</link><title>3 Reasons To Hate Mass Surveillance; 3 Ways To Fight It</title><description>This site's "Your Rights Online" section, sadly, has never suffered for material. The revelations we've seen over the last year-and-change, though, of widespread spying on U.S. citizens, government spying in the E.U. on international conferences, the UK's use of malware against citizens, and the use of modern technology to oppress government protesters in the middle east and elsewhere shows how persistent it is. It's been a banner year on that front, and the banner says "You are being spied on, online and off." A broad coalition of organizations is calling today "The Day We Fight Back" against the growing culture of heads-they-win, tails-you-lose surveillance, but all involved know this is not a one-day struggle. (Read more, below.)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7483-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7483_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:57:48">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/14/01/07/1754253/should-facebook-likes-count-as-commercial-endorsements</link><title>Should Facebook 'Likes' Count As Commercial Endorsements?</title><description>Slashdot contributor Bennett Haselton writes: "Facebook settled out of court over displaying ads that told you which of your friends had 'liked' a product or service, and another lawsuit is currently pending over the use of minors' pictures specifically in similar ads. (Not to be confused with another recently filed lawsuit alleging that Facebook converts private messages into public 'likes'.) Google+ tried to limit its liability by only showing the faces of users over 18 when showing which friends 'like' a page. I'm all for more privacy for social networking users, and if it's true that Facebook has been silently marking users as publicly 'liking' a page because they mentioned the page in a private message, the plaintiff's lawyers ought to clean them out for that one. But in cases where you willingly and knowingly 'liked' a page, Facebook and Google+ ought to be able to tell that to your friends in advertisements, without being sued for it." Read on for the rest of Bennett's thoughts.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7483-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7483_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:59:25">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/13/09/16/0029203/california-school-district-hires-firm-to-monitor-students-social-media</link><title>California School District Hires Firm To Monitor Students' Social Media</title><description>An anonymous reader writes "A suburban Los Angeles school district is taking a novel approach to tackling the problem of cyber-bullying. It's paying a company to snoop on students' social media pages. 'The district in Glendale, California, is paying $40,500 to a firm to monitor and report on 14,000 middle and high school students' posts on Twitter, Facebook and other social media for one year. Though critics liken the monitoring to government stalking, school officials and their contractor say the purpose is student safety. As classes began this fall, the district awarded the contract after it earlier paid the firm, Geo Listening, $5,000 last spring to conduct a pilot project monitoring 9,000 students at three high schools and a middle school. Among the results was a successful intervention with a student "who was speaking of ending his life" on his social media, said Chris Frydrych, CEO of the firm.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7483-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7483_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:01:07">http://news.slashdot.org/story/13/08/26/1741251/how-deadbeat-facebook-friends-and-using-all-caps-can-lower-your-credit-score</link><title>How Deadbeat Facebook Friends and Using ALL-CAPS Can Lower Your Credit Score</title><description>McGruber writes "CNN has the news that some financial lending companies claim that Facebook social connections can be a good indicator of a person's creditworthiness. One company determines if you are friends with someone who was late paying back a loan; if so, that is bad news for you. It is even worse news if the delinquent friend is someone you frequently interact with. Another company gathers information from the manner in which a customer fills out the online loan application. The chances of getting a loan improve if you spend time reading information about the loan on their website. Conversely, if you fill out the application typing in all-caps (or with no caps), you are knocked down a couple pegs in that company's eyes. A third lender requires that small business borrowers grant them access to the borrowers' PayPal, eBay and other online payment accounts (what could possibly go wrong with that?), thereby disclosing real-time sales and delivery information."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7483-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7483_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:03:19">http://news.slashdot.org/story/13/07/21/1139242/twitter-co-founder-biz-stone-to-facebook-start-a-premium-subscription-service</link><title>Twitter Co-Founder Biz Stone To Facebook: Start a Premium Subscription Service</title><description>An anonymous reader writes "Twitter co-founder Biz Stone today decided to offer some business advice for Facebook: launch a premium subscription service. For $10 a month, Stone figures the company could get rid of ads on its site for those willing to pay to go 'premium.' He says in part: ' Anywhoo, now that I’m using it and thinking about it, I’ve got an idea for Facebook. They could offer Facebook Premium. For $10 a month, people who really love Facebook (and can afford it), could see no ads. Maybe some special features too. If 10% percent of Facebook signed up, that’s $1B a month in revenue. Not too shabby. It’s a different type of company, but by way of validation, have a look at Pandora’s 1Q14 financial results. Of all Pandora’s revenue generators, the highest growth year-over-year by far (114% growth rate) is in subscriptions—people paying a monthly fee for an ad-free experience....."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7483-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7483_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:05:38">http://ask.slashdot.org/story/13/06/21/203237/ask-slashdot-what-should-a-non-profit-look-for-in-a-web-host</link><title>Ask Slashdot: What Should a Non-Profit Look For In a Web Host?</title><description>An anonymous reader writes "We are a large (multi-national) non-profit and currently deal with 503s on a near daily basis. We've worked on this for over a year and the host hasn't been able to figure out how to fix it. We're paying for a managed host and need to evaluate other options. My boss has tasked me with evaluating a new one. I'm the most geeky of the group, so I know the terms, but don't have a sense of what's actually needed to suit our needs. We sometimes have upwards of 1,000 people browsing the site at the same time, so my sense is that we shouldn't need massive amounts of power or bandwidth... but, somehow that's not working on our current host. Can anyone help me get a sense of what types of hosting will best suit the needs of a 'large' non-profit? We're not Facebook, but we're not a mom-and-pop shop. Any help or tips would be fantastic, particularly if you've also selected a new hosting provider in the past year or so. I don't necessarily need actual names (though those would be nice, too) but at least some tips on what makes a huge difference when suddenly a whole bunch of people around the world read an email and want to help out."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7483-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7483_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:06:51">http://tech.slashdot.org/story/13/05/27/0053228/yahoo-joins-growing-list-of-bidders-for-hulu</link><title>Yahoo Joins Growing List of Bidders For Hulu</title><description>An anonymous reader writes "It's reported that Yahoo has formally put in a bid to buy Hulu only a week after adding Tumblr to the family. From the article: 'Yahoo just spent $1.1 billion of its cash hoard to acquire Tumblr, a blogging site with 300 million mostly young-ish visitors and 24 billion minutes of usage per month. Yahoo CEO Marissa Mayer's team can slap a lot of tasteful, personalized native ads into the Tumblr content streams to monetize the fast growing site. It's the same way that Facebook and Twitter hope to get into the tens of billions in revenue league, but it's a long and winding road. Now Yahoo is taking a run at Hulu, with its 4 million subscribers paying $7.99 per month, original programming , and more than 70,000 full TV episodes. Hulu could immediately put Yahoo's video efforts and revenue in a different league.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7483-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7483_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:07:34">http://yro.slashdot.org/story/13/05/16/169236/irish-judge-orders-the-internet-to-delete-video</link><title>Irish Judge Orders 'The Internet' To Delete Video</title><description>New submitter edanto writes "A young Irish man wrongly accused of jumping from a taxi without paying the fare has secured a judgement from an Irish court ordering the video removed from the entire Internet. Experts from Google, Youtube, Facebook, and others must tell the court in two weeks if this is technically possible. The thing is, the video is accurate, it is only a comment that wrongly identified Eoin McKeogh as the fare-jumper in the video that is inaccurate. It's not clear if the judge has made any orders about the comment."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7483-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7483_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:08:07">http://news.slashdot.org/story/13/02/03/223236/the-top-paying-tech-companies-for-interns</link><title>The Top Paying Tech Companies For Interns</title><description>theodp writes "For those students for whom it's all about the Benjamins, BusinessInsider's Alyson Shontell has compiled a nice list of 20 Tech Companies That Pay Interns Boatloads Of Money. 'If you intern for a high-profile tech company,' notes Shontell, 'you can make more money than the average US citizen. Facebook, for example, pays its average intern $6,056 per month. That ends up being a base salary of about $72,000 per year.' Sure beats making a 'measly' $5,808 per month at LinkedIn, where you might find yourself having to participate in embarrassing sing-a-longs and Flash Mobs!"</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>