<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7492">oldest jokes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:20:56" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7492-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7492_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:20:57">http://idle.slashdot.org/story/08/07/31/1518205/the-worlds-oldest-joke</link><title>The World's Oldest Joke</title><description>The world's oldest recorded joke has been traced back to 1900 BC and it appears that toilet humor was popular with the ancients just like it is today. The Sumerian saying goes like this, "Something which has never occurred since time immemorial; a young woman did not fart in her husband's lap." The people who brought you written language and the wheel also brought you the fart joke. Dr Paul McDonald, senior lecturer at the University of Wolverhampton said, "Jokes have varied over the years, with some taking the question and answer format while others are witty proverbs or riddles. What they all share however, is a willingness to deal with taboos and a degree of rebellion. Modern puns, Essex girl jokes and toilet humor can all be traced back to the very earliest jokes identified in this research."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7492-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7492_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:23:24">http://ask.slashdot.org/story/06/01/17/1810239/safe-options-for-surfing-while-on-the-road</link><title>Safe Options for Surfing While on the Road?</title><description>Sooner Boomer asks: "My oldest brother is an over-the-road truck driver. He subscribes to several wireless services at truck stops (Flying J, Pilot, etc.). I've tried to help him and educate him as much as possible, but he still has two problems; connectivity (poor signal strength) and security. His truck has a fiberglass shell, so that is not the problem. He has to run IE because this is the only browser supported for the log-in process. We've talked about wireless routers with reflectors on the antennas to boost signal strength, and to help with security. I'm still looking for better security though. Are there "live" linux browsers that can be run once a connection is made in windows? It's really gotten annoying because he has to reformat/reinstall about every two-three months. Ideas? Good trucker jokes?"</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>