<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7499">gold price</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:11:47" name="Slashdot" id="FW14-e111"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e111-7499-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7499_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:11:49">http://hardware.slashdot.org/story/13/12/14/0110203/surge-in-litecoin-mining-leads-to-graphics-card-shortage</link><title>Surge In Litecoin Mining Leads To Graphics Card Shortage</title><description>New submitter Kenseilon writes "Extremetech reports that the recent price hike of Litecoins has triggered yet another arms race for the *coinminers out there, leading to a shortage of AMD graphics cards. While Bitcoin mining is quickly becoming unfeasible for GPU rigs with general purpose graphics cards, there are several alternative currencies with opportunities. The primary candidate is now Litecoin, which has the aim of 'being silver if Bitcoin is gold' Swedish Tech site Sweclockers also reports [in Swedish] that GPU manufacturer Club3D have told them that miners are becoming a new important group of potential customers. However, concerns are being raised that this is a temporary boom that may hurt AMD in the long run, since gamers, their core consumer group, may not be able to acquire the cards and instead opt for Nvidia."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7499-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7499_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:13:37">http://mobile.slashdot.org/story/13/09/10/1757234/apple-unveils-iphone-5c-iphone-5s</link><title>Apple Unveils iPhone 5C, iPhone 5S</title><description>Nerval's Lobster writes "Apple unveiled the iPhone 5C and iPhone 5S today, which will replace the company's current iPhone 5. Apple CEO Tim Cook and other executives took to a stage in California to introduce both devices. The cheaper iPhone 5C features a plastic casing available in a variety of colors (green, blue, reddish-pink, yellow, white); Apple seems to have done its best to make the device look high quality, with the backing and sides molded of a single piece of plastic; on the hardware side of things, the iPhone 5C comes with a 4-inch Retina display, A6 processor, and 8-megapixel camera. The other new Apple design, the iPhone 5S, is the company's next-generation 'hero' device. While the iPhone 5 was a radical new design, the 5S is an iterative upgrade; on the outside, it looks pretty much the same as its predecessor (the new iPhone features a new color, gold, in addition to the 'traditional' black or white aluminum body). The iPhone 5S has an A7 chip built on 64-bit architecture (capable of running 32-bit and 64-bit apps), which is pretty speedy, to put it mildly. There's also the M7 'motion co-processor' which boosts the actions of the accelerometer, compass, and gyroscope—in theory, opening the door to more refined motion-related apps, such as ones devoted to exercise." The iPhone 5S also has a sensor built into the home button that will allow you to unlock the device with your fingerprint. Both new phone will be available for purchase on Friday, Sept. 20th. Apple announced that iOS 7 will be rolling out on Wednesday, Sept. 18th.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7499-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7499_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:14:51">http://science.slashdot.org/story/13/04/26/1925206/2014-planetary-resources-to-launch-their-first-satellites</link><title>2014: Planetary Resources To Launch Their First Satellites</title><description>symbolset writes "Planetary Resources wants to mine asteroids for their sweet, sweet minerals and make a business of it. The sparky little company has been writ up here on Slashdot numerous times. With the backing of such billionaires as Eric Schmidt, Larry Page, James Cameron, and many others, and such luminaries as major NASA project managers, engineers and scientists, you have to think they might have a good shot at it. Recently they picked up a huge engineering, procurement and construction partner: Bechtel. Their operations are already cash-flow positive by selling tech invented to pursue their goals, so they're a legitimate business running lean and intending to make good. Yesterday they announced the plan to launch their first space missions — the Arkyd Series 100 LEO Space Telescopes — as soon as next year. Beginning in 2014 their satellites will be scanning the skies from Low Earth Orbit for lucrative rocks that happen to be heading our way, and incidentally doing for-pay work to keep the lights on. For a reasonable fee they'll sell you the right to retask one of these telescopes to take a picture of anything you want that it can see, for a fair price. The plan is to follow up with harvester craft to go get these asteroids, mulch them, and sell their bits for profit. Some talk has been made of selling what are uncommon terrestrial minerals like gold and platinum, refined on orbit and deorbited at great expense as a business plan, but frankly that's absurd. 'Extraterrestrial Asteroid Bits' ought to go for a higher price on the collector market than gold or platinum ever would, and the temporal preeminence should draw a premium price. 'This 69 mg specimen (769 of 10,000) was one of the first commercially harvested bits of asteroid returned to Earth. Lucite embedded for permanent display, with case. Certificate of authenticity included.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7499-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7499_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:16:40">http://games.slashdot.org/story/13/04/26/1318214/paul-thurrot-predicts-november-debut-500-tag-for-xbox-720</link><title>Paul Thurrot Predicts November Debut, $500 Tag For Xbox 720</title><description>New submitter inkribbon writes that Microsoft blogger Paul Thurrott has now predicted that Microsoft's Xbox 720 console will actually hit the market this November. Thurrott offers a mix of what he considers cold, known facts and "clearly identified conjecture" about the upcoming device. Important to users is this confidently offered claim about the price: "Microsoft will initially offer two pricing models for the console: a standalone version for $499 and a $299 version that requires a two-year Xbox LIVE Gold commitment at an expected price of $10 per month."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7499-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7499_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:19:23">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/178383</link><title>Prediction Market Site InTrade Bans US Customers</title><description>MyFirstNameIsPaul writes "In an announcement dated Monday, Nov 26, 2012, Dublin-based InTrade stated 'that due to legal and regulatory pressures, InTrade can no longer allow U.S. residents to participate in our real-money prediction markets.' The Washington Post reports that the Commodity Futures Trading Commission filed a complaint in federal court against InTrade for 'illegally facilitating bets on future economic data, the price of gold and even acts of war,' demonstrating just how far the long arm of U.S. law can reach."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7499-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7499_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:21:04">http://beta.slashdot.org/story/175759</link><title>Super Bacteria Create Gold</title><description>SchrodingerZ writes "With the price of gold skyrocketing in today's market, Michigan State University researchers have discovered a bacterium that can withstand high toxicity levels that are necessary to create natural gold. '"Microbial alchemy is what we're doing — transforming gold from something that has no value into a solid, precious metal that's valuable," said Kazem Kashefi, assistant professor of microbiology and molecular genetics.' The bacteria is Cupriavidus metallidurans, which is conditioned to be tolerant to heavy, toxic metals and to be 25 times stronger than most bacteria. When put into gold-chloride (a natural forming toxic liquid), the bacteria reproduces and converts the liquid into a gold nugget. The complete process takes about a week to perform. This experiment is currently on tour as an art exhibit called 'The Great Work of the Metal Lover.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7499-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7499_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:23:28">http://games.slashdot.org/story/12/08/20/1515258/review-new-super-mario-bros-2-illustrates-nintendos-greatest-problem</link><title>Review: New Super Mario Bros. 2 Illustrates Nintendo's Greatest Problem</title><description>Jon Brodkin writes "There’s a new Super Mario Bros. game out for the 3DS handheld console. It’s called New Super Mario Bros. 2 and features Mario, Princess Peach, Bowser, and the same fun gameplay you’ve come to expect from Nintendo’s most iconic game series. But this latest adventure stands out by not standing out at all." Read below for the rest of Jon's review.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7499-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7499_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:24:10">http://news.slashdot.org/story/11/12/30/2048237/hp-wanted-12b-for-webos-and-palm</link><title>HP Wanted $1.2B For WebOS and Palm</title><description>PolygamousRanchKid passes along this quote: "As baffling as it may seem, HP was trying to rid itself of Palm without taking a loss on its purchase, a source with knowledge of the negotiations told [VentureBeat]. The company seemingly ignored that Palm's value had fallen significantly since HP purchased the smartphone pioneer in April 2010, thanks to the spectacular failure of the HP Touchpad tablet. And the fact that HP didn't make any progress with its new webOS phones, the Pre 3 and Veer, didn't help either. ... The $1.2 billion asking price shines some light on a story we heard from another source: At one point, HP's team tried to pitch the sale to Facebook but was practically laughed out of the room. And yes, Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg was present at the meeting, although he apparently didn't say much (I'm sure whatever he was thinking at the time would have been gold)."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7499-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7499_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:25:55">http://science.slashdot.org/story/11/10/04/2257211/climate-change-driving-war</link><title>Climate Change Driving War?</title><description>New submitter Stirling Newberry writes "You may have heard of The Great Moderation (PDF), which argues that business cycles have become less volatile over time, and the Green Revolution, a set of initiatives that led to increased global food production. These, it has been argued, have led to a marked decrease in war across the world. But not so fast, says a study in Science. It may well be that periods of war, past and present, can be linked to changes in climate: 'The most direct way in which extreme climate shifts influence human society is through agriculture, Zhang says; a falling supply of crops will drive up the price of gold and cause inflation. Similarly, epidemics can be exacerbated by famine. And when people are miserable, they are likely to become angry with their governments and each other, resulting in war. But golden ages rise out of these dark periods, the team argues. For instance, a 100-year cold period beginning in 1560 caused shortened crop growing seasons. The researchers found a causal linkage with a decline in average human height by nearly an inch during this period, and the century was rife with disease and conflict. But the world began to warm in 1650; when Charles II was crowned king of England in 1660, the coronation sparked the Enlightenment era in Europe.'"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e111-7499-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e111/7499_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:26:59">http://interviews.slashdot.org/story/11/06/22/1737237/amir-taaki-answers-your-questions-about-bitcoin</link><title>Amir Taaki Answers Your Questions About Bitcoin</title><description>Last week, you asked questions (many rather pointed!) of Amir Taaki, co-founder of Bitcoin Consultancy, which develops Bitcoin related services, exchanges and Bitcoin itself. (They also own Britcoin.co.uk.) Says Taaki: "When creating video games I spent much time imagining tools to make artists lives easier, and how we could keep funding developers to write free software. One contribution of mine to the community was a site where developers could get funded for developing features and I'd love nothing more than to pay people to write free software." With regard to Bitcoin, similarly, "We need fulltime developers thinking about the problems and solutions needed to keep this system running. We aim to get all the creative thinkers from the community and provide a mechanism for enabling their work." Below find his answers to the questions readers raised.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>