<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7009">linkedin engineering</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:09:56" name="SourceForge" id="FW14-e158"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e158-7009-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e158/7009_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:09:57">http://sourceforge.net/projects/hibernate/?source=directory-featured</link><title>Hibernate</title><description>Relational Persistence for Idiomatic Java</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e158-7009-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e158/7009_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:13:59">http://sourceforge.net/projects/secufe-cmp-test/?source=directory</link><title>Software Engineering CU Test</title><description>No description</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e158-7009-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e158/7009_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:14:57">http://sourceforge.net/projects/tceav/?source=directory</link><title>Teamcenter Engineering Admin View</title><description>Teamcenter Engineering Admin View is a utility that allows detailed analysis of configuration files for Teamcenter Engineering (TcE) from Siemens PLM Software. It will allow you to view and analyze exported Ruletrees and Workflow Procedure files. Source Code is now stored in GitHub. https://github.com/nader-eloshaiker/Teamcenter-AdminView</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e158-7009-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e158/7009_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:17:09">http://sourceforge.net/projects/socialauth/?source=directory</link><title>SocialAuth</title><description>Java Library for authentication with social sites like Facebook</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e158-7009-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e158/7009_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:18:26">http://sourceforge.net/projects/socialauth-android/?source=directory</link><title>SocialAuth-Android</title><description>SocialAuth Android is an Android version of popular SocialAuth Java library. Now you do not need to integrate multiple SDKs if you want to integrate your application with multiple social networks. You just need to add few lines of code after integrating the SocialAuth Android library in your app. The API enables user authentication and sharing updates through different various social networks and hides all the intricacies of generating signatures &amp; token, doing security handshakes and provide an easy mechanism to build cool social apps. With this library, you can: Quickly build share functionality for posting updates on facebook, twitter, linkedin and more Easily create a Share button or a social bar containing various social networks Access profile of logged in user for easy user registration Import friend contacts of logged in user (Email, Profile URL and Name) Do much more using our flexible API like extend it for more network</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e158-7009-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e158/7009_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:22:39">http://sourceforge.net/projects/librecad/?source=directory</link><title>LibreCAD</title><description>LibreCAD Open Source 2D-CAD</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e158-7009-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e158/7009_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:24:30">http://sourceforge.net/projects/geoserver/?source=directory</link><title>GeoServer</title><description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. Designed for interoperability, it publishes data from any major spatial data source using open standards: WMS, WFS, WCS, WPS and REST</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e158-7009-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e158/7009_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:28:42">http://sourceforge.net/projects/scidavis/?source=directory</link><title>SciDAVis</title><description>SciDAVis is a user-friendly data analysis and visualization program primarily aimed at high-quality plotting of scientific data. It strives to combine an intuitive, easy-to-use graphical user interface with powerful features such as Python scriptability.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e158-7009-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e158/7009_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:29:36">http://sourceforge.net/projects/gretl/?source=directory</link><title>gretl</title><description>GNU Regression, Econometrics and Time-series Library</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e158-7009-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e158/7009_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:31:26">http://sourceforge.net/projects/bowtie-bio/?source=directory</link><title>Bowtie</title><description>Bowtie, an ultrafast, memory-efficient short read aligner for short DNA sequences (reads) from next-gen sequencers. Please cite: Langmead B, et al. Ultrafast and memory-efficient alignment of short DNA sequences to the human genome. Genome Biol 10:R25.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>