<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7135">Ahmed Dogan assassination</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:00:35" name="SourceForge" id="FW14-e158"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e158-7135-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e158/7135_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:00:38">http://sourceforge.net/projects/ahmedateeqzia/?source=directory</link><title>Ahmed Ateeq Zia</title><description>Usama Ahmed</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e158-7135-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e158/7135_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:01:43">http://sourceforge.net/projects/asuos/?source=directory</link><title>ASU OS 12.05</title><description>Applied Science University Operating System based on Linux</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e158-7135-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e158/7135_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:03:09">http://sourceforge.net/projects/flexbar/?source=directory</link><title>Flexbar</title><description>flexible barcode and adapter removal for sequencing platforms</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e158-7135-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e158/7135_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:04:07">http://sourceforge.net/projects/chessgameai/?source=directory</link><title>Chess Game AI Phantoms</title><description>Phantoms Chess Where Pawns Can become Queens Chess Game is zero-sum two-player. Team Members: Phantoms Team * Leader Gehad Sayed Kaseb Gehad.Kaseb@gmail.com * Co-leader Rawia Ahmed * Research team Hagar Samir Safaa Mohamed * Design and Implementation team Ahmed Helal Aya Eid Aya Tarek Eman Saleh Fatma El zhraa Ibrahim Hanan Mohamed John Samir Mina Victor Nahla Ibrahim Samira Magdy Samr Ayman * Integration Team Marwa Ayman Nahla Essam * Interface and Communication team Abderahmn Samy Sherif Ibrahim * Testing team Gehad Ahmed Hassan Mohamed * Documentation team Nasma Abdallah Nourhan Tarek Egypt, Cairo University, Faculty of Engineering, Computer Department</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e158-7135-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e158/7135_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:05:48">http://sourceforge.net/projects/forallah/?source=directory</link><title>auto_michlet</title><description>In the name of Allah the most merciful and gracious. Peace and prayers upon prophet Mohamed and all prophets. This project automates the call to michlet (www.cyberiad.net/michlet.htm) to compute the total resistance of a triamaran with certain main/side hulls arrangement. This can help in developing optimization codes. Simply enter the desired stagger,separation in the .sci file and run this .sci file. It will embed your inputs in michlet in.mlt file, call michlet automation script and read the total resistance. Don't forget to adjust path_michlet,path_file according to where you will extract our project. This work is a product of our research group feesabeeliAllah mainly developed by Mohamed Abdelsalam (auto-it script) and Ahmed El-bastawesy (triamaran in template preparation). Michlet is a third party freeware available at: Please direct any questions to: mohamed.rov@gmail.com ahmedelbastawesy99@gmail.com</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>