<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7010">manchester united FC football</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-17 22:21:55" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7010-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7010_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 22:21:59">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57597432/you-only-sing-when-you-re-winning-football-factions-and-rock-rivalries-in-manchester-and</link><title>‘You only sing when you're winning’: football factions and rock rivalries in Manchester and Liverpool</title><description>* ‘You only sing when you're winning’: football factions and rock rivalries in Manchester and Liverpool

Simon Warner

...the cities of liverpool and manchester, urban centres with quite different...competition between the teams liverpool fc and manchester united, a rivalry expressed on occasions...

Journal: Soccer &amp; Society , vol. 12, no. 1, pp. 58-73, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7010-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7010_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 22:23:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/36032738/making-the-seemingly-impossible-appear-possible-effects-of-conjunction-fallacies-in-evaluations-of</link><title>Making the seemingly impossible appear possible: Effects of conjunction fallacies in evaluations of bets on football games</title><description>* Making the seemingly impossible appear possible: Effects of conjunction fallacies in evaluations of bets on football games (Citations: 1)

Håkan Nilsson, Patric Andersson

...predictions concerning the outcomes of football games. the conjunction rule states...g., stoke city will beat manchester united) was combined with one or two predictions that had high likelihood of success (e.g., liverpool fc will beat wigan), it was...

Journal: Journal of Economic Psychology - J ECON PSYCH , vol. 31, no. 2, pp. 172-180, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7010-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7010_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 22:23:58">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57341073/internationalisation-and-sport-branding-strategy-a-french-perception-of-the-big-four-brands</link><title>Internationalisation and sport branding strategy: a French perception of the Big Four brands</title><description>* Internationalisation and sport branding strategy: a French perception of the Big Four brands

Nicolas Chanavat, Guillaume Bodet

...satellite fans' perceptions of professional-football brands, as this constitutes a...big four brands of arsenal football club (fc), chelsea fc, liverpool fc and manchester united are conducted. findings – the paper...

Journal: Qualitative Market Research: An International Journal , vol. 12, no. 4, pp. 460-481, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7010-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7010_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 22:25:48">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42697143/our-club-our-rules-fan-communities-at-fc-united-of-manchester</link><title>‘Our club, our rules’: fan communities at FC United of Manchester</title><description>* ‘Our club, our rules’: fan communities at FC United of Manchester (Citations: 3)

Adam Brown

...essay concerns the formation of fc united of manchester, a fan owned non league football club in england, that was formed during the glazer take over of manchester united. it considers some of the...

Journal: Soccer &amp; Society , vol. 9, no. 3, pp. 346-358, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7010-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7010_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 22:27:11">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10336658/cultural-participation-the-making-of-distinction-a-nd-the-case-of-fans-of-fc-united-of-manchester</link><title>Cultural Participation, the Making of Distinction a nd the Case of Fans of FC United of Manchester</title><description>* Cultural Participation, the Making of Distinction a nd the Case of Fans of FC United of Manchester

George Poulton

...operation of distinction am ongst fc united of manchester fans. it begins with a...practices and state regulation within football aimed at breaking the strong relat ionship between football and the working class, have led to the watching of football being a cultural activity evenly...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7010-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7010_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 22:29:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42676149/coming-to-america-historical-ontologies-and-united-states-soccer</link><title>Coming to America: Historical Ontologies and United States Soccer</title><description>* Coming to America: Historical Ontologies and United States Soccer

Gary Armstrong, James Rosbrook-Thompson

...gaining a foothold in the united states sporting market and therein becoming a credible adversary to the holy trinity of gridiron football, baseball, and basketball. this article...soccer's development in the united states and that led to...

Journal: Identities-global Studies in Culture and Power - IDENTITIES-GLOB STUD CULT POW , vol. 17, no. 4, pp. 348-371, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7010-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7010_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-17 22:30:46">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/12250006/the-sociology-of-english-football-in-the-1990s-fandom-business-and-future-research1</link><title>The Sociology of English Football in the 1990s: Fandom, Business and Future Research1</title><description>* The Sociology of English Football in the 1990s: Fandom, Business and Future Research1

Rex Nash

...redirect academic analysis of english football within the context of its...fandom, and supporter responses to football's transformation. future research areas...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>