<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7014">Asian culture</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:24:55" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7014-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7014_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:24:58">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/41538812/immigrant-acts-on-asian-american-cultural-politics</link><title>Immigrant Acts: On Asian American Cultural Politics</title><description>* Immigrant Acts: On Asian American Cultural Politics (Citations: 138)

David Palumbo-Liu, Lisa Lowe

Journal: Journal of Asian Studies - J ASIAN STUD , vol. 57, no. 3, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7014-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7014_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:26:17">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11317325/asian-american-cultural-identity-and-attitudes-toward-mental-health-services</link><title>Asian-American cultural identity and attitudes toward mental health services</title><description>* Asian-American cultural identity and attitudes toward mental health services (Citations: 87)

Donald R. Atkinson, Ruth H. Gim

Journal: Journal of Counseling Psychology - J COUNS PSYCHOL , vol. 36, no. 2, pp. 209-212, 1989</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7014-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7014_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:27:39">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/38518656/asian-cultural-values-and-the-counseling-process-current-knowledge-and-directions-for-future</link><title>Asian Cultural Values and the Counseling Process: Current Knowledge and Directions for Future Research</title><description>* Asian Cultural Values and the Counseling Process: Current Knowledge and Directions for Future Research (Citations: 51)

B. S. K. Kim, D. R. Atkinson, D. Umemoto

Journal: Counseling Psychologist - COUNS PSYCHOL , vol. 29, no. 4, pp. 570-603, 2001</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7014-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7014_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:29:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/30421420/risk-of-tuberculosis-in-immigrant-asians-culturally-acquired-immunodeficiency</link><title>Risk of tuberculosis in immigrant Asians: culturally acquired immunodeficiency?</title><description>* Risk of tuberculosis in immigrant Asians: culturally acquired immunodeficiency? (Citations: 21)

P. J. Finch, F. J. Millard, J. D. Maxwell

...study of the 620 asian immigrants with tuberculosis notified in...there was a peak among asians from east africa, and in...

Journal: Thorax , vol. 46, no. 1, pp. 1-5, 1991</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7014-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7014_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:30:15">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39016805/the-stigma-of-mental-illness-in-asian-cultures</link><title>The stigma of mental illness in Asian cultures</title><description>* The stigma of mental illness in Asian cultures (Citations: 39)

Chee Hong Ng

Journal: Australian and New Zealand Journal of Psychiatry - AUST N Z J PSYCHIAT , vol. 31, no. 3, pp. 382-390, 1997</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7014-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7014_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:31:42">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/44897349/public-relations-in-three-asian-cultures-an-analysis</link><title>Public Relations in Three Asian Cultures: An Analysis</title><description>* Public Relations in Three Asian Cultures: An Analysis (Citations: 38)

K. Sriramesh, Yungwook Kim, Mioko Takasaki

Journal: Journal of Public Relations Research - J PUBLIC RELAT RES , vol. 11, no. 4, pp. 271-292, 1999</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7014-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7014_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:33:18">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/47356486/being-asian-americanidentity-cultural-constructs-and-stereotype-perception</link><title>Being Asian AmericanIdentity, Cultural Constructs, and Stereotype Perception</title><description>* Being Asian AmericanIdentity, Cultural Constructs, and Stereotype Perception (Citations: 39)

Daphna Oyserman, Izumi Sakamoto

...about stereotypes was explored among asian americans. the authors proposed four components of asian american identity: feelings of interdependence...racism. a sample of 162 asian american university students perceived stereotypes about asian americans as focusing primarily on...

Journal: The Journal of Applied Behavioral Science , vol. 33, no. 4, pp. 435-453, 1997</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7014-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7014_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:34:55">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5618311/cultural-influences-on-the-relation-between-pleasant-emotions-and-unpleasant-emotions-asian</link><title>Cultural influences on the relation between pleasant emotions and unpleasant emotions: Asian dialectic philosophies or individualism-collectivism?</title><description>* Cultural influences on the relation between pleasant emotions and unpleasant emotions: Asian dialectic philosophies or individualism-collectivism? (Citations: 48)

Ulrich Schimmack, Shigehiro Oishi, Ed Diener

...of unpleasant emotions (fue) in asian, non-asian collectivistic, and western cultures. as predicted, fpe-fue correlations were less negative in asian cultures than in other cultures. we also observed a tendency for the culture effect to be moderated by...

Journal: Cognition &amp; Emotion - COGNITION EMOTION , vol. 16, no. 6, pp. 705-719, 2002</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7014-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7014_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:36:09">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40596894/medicine-in-a-multi-cultural-society-the-effect-of-cultural-background-on-beliefs-about-medications</link><title>Medicine in a multi-cultural society: the effect of cultural background on beliefs about medications</title><description>* Medicine in a multi-cultural society: the effect of cultural background on beliefs about medications (Citations: 36)

Robert Horne, Lı́da Graupner, Susie Frost, John Weinman, Siobhan Melanie Wright, Matthew Hankins

...identified themselves as having an asian or european cultural background. there was a significant association between cultural background and beliefs about the...themselves to have a european cultural background had significantly more experience with prescribed medication than those who selected an asian cultural background. the relationship between cultural background and beliefs about medicines...

Journal: Social Science &amp; Medicine - SOC SCI MED , vol. 59, no. 6, pp. 1307-1313, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7014-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7014_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 16:37:29">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11761449/are-the-learning-styles-of-asian-international-students-culturally-or-contextually-based</link><title>Are the Learning Styles of Asian International Students Culturally or Contextually Based?</title><description>* Are the Learning Styles of Asian International Students Culturally or Contextually Based? (Citations: 33)

Joseph Kee-Kuok Wong

...three main difficulties highlighted by asian international students are: different learning styles, cultural barriers and language problems. this...of appropriate teaching strategies with asian international students. learning styles, culture, asian international undergraduates, learning difficulties, higher...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>