<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7019">Alek Wek</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:05:32" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7019-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7019_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:05:35">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/3567105/personality-similarity-in-twins-reared-apart-and-together</link><title>Personality Similarity in Twins Reared Apart and Together</title><description>* Personality Similarity in Twins Reared Apart and Together (Citations: 520)

Alike Tellegen, David T. Lykken, Thomas J. Bouchard, Kimerly J. Wilcox, Nancy L. Segal, Stephen Rich

We administered the Multidimensional Personality Questionnaire (MPQ) to 217 monozygotic and 114 dizygotic reared-together adult twin pairs and 44 monozygotic and 27 dizygotic reared-apart adult twin pairs. A four-parameter biometric model (incorporating genetic, additive versus nonadditive, shared family-environment, and unshared environment components) and five reduced models were fitted through maximum-likelihood techniques to data obtained with ...

Journal: Journal of Personality and Social Psychology - PSP , vol. 54, no. 6, pp. 1031-1039, 1988</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7019-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7019_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:06:50">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/2738928/are-business-cycles-all-alike</link><title>Are Business Cycles All Alike</title><description>* Are Business Cycles All Alike (Citations: 112)

M. W. Watson

Published in 1986.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7019-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7019_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:08:10">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/35255342/sequence-of-a-staphylococcal-plasmid-gene-vga-encoding-a-putative-atp-binding-protein-involved-in</link><title>Sequence of a staphylococcal plasmid gene, vga, encoding a putative ATP-binding protein involved in resistance to virginiamycin Alike antibiotics</title><description>* Sequence of a staphylococcal plasmid gene, vga, encoding a putative ATP-binding protein involved in resistance to virginiamycin Alike antibiotics (Citations: 72)

J Allignet

Journal: Gene , vol. 117, no. 1, pp. 45-51, 1992</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7019-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7019_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:09:34">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/35429645/alike-cells-in-the-rat-stomach-contain-ghrelin-and-do-not-operate-under-gastrin-control</link><title>Alike cells in the rat stomach contain ghrelin and do not operate under gastrin control</title><description>* Alike cells in the rat stomach contain ghrelin and do not operate under gastrin control (Citations: 129)

C Dornonville de la Cour, M Björkqvist, A. K Sandvik, I Bakke, C.-M Zhao, D Chen, R Håkanson

Ghrelin is a 28 a.a. gastric peptide, recently identified as a natural ligand of the growth hormone secretagogue receptor (orphan receptor distinct from the receptor for growth hormone releasing hormone). In the present study, radioimmunoassay demonstrated ghrelin-like material in the rat oxyntic mucosa with moderate amounts also in antrum and duodenum. Small amounts were found in the distal ...

Journal: Regulatory Peptides - REGUL PEPTIDES , vol. 99, no. 2, pp. 141-150, 2001</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7019-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7019_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:11:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/38545263/are-all-associations-alike-member-diversity-associational-type-and-the-creation-of-social-capital</link><title>Are All Associations Alike?Member Diversity, Associational Type, and the Creation of Social Capital</title><description>* Are All Associations Alike?Member Diversity, Associational Type, and the Creation of Social Capital (Citations: 110)

DIETLIND STOLLE, THOMAS R. ROCHON

Associational memberships have become the indicator of choice for examining the formation and destruction of social capital. Memberships in associations are believed to create generalized interpersonal trust, which can be used as a lubricant that makes possible a variety of forms of social interaction and cooperation. Clearly, not all types of associations will be equally effective in their relative capacity ...

Journal: American Behavioral Scientist - AMER BEHAV SCI , vol. 42, no. 1, pp. 47-65, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7019-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7019_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:12:12">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6651072/must-like-cases-be-treated-alike</link><title>Must Like Cases Be Treated Alike?</title><description>* Must Like Cases Be Treated Alike? (Citations: 65)

David A. Strauss

...must like cases be treated alike?...

Journal: SSRN Electronic Journal , 2002</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7019-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7019_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:13:41">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/15024012/autocrine-induction-of-collagenase-by-serum-amyloid-alike-and-beta-2-microglobulin-like-proteins</link><title>Autocrine induction of collagenase by serum amyloid Alike and beta 2-microglobulin-like proteins</title><description>* Autocrine induction of collagenase by serum amyloid Alike and beta 2-microglobulin-like proteins (Citations: 59)

C. Brinckerhoff, T. Mitchell, M. Karmilowicz, B Kluve-Beckerman, M. Benson

Journal: Science , vol. 243, no. 4891, pp. 655-657, 1989</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7019-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7019_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:15:03">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/3956867/the-role-of-the-5-untranslated-region-of-an-mrna-in-translation-regulation-during-development</link><title>The role of the 5 ′ untranslated region of an mRNA in translation regulation during development</title><description>* The role of the 5 ′ untranslated region of an mRNA in translation regulation during development (Citations: 139)

Alike W van der Velden, Adri A. M Thomas

Cap-dependent ribosomal scanning occurs on the majority of cellular 5′ UTRs. This process is severely hampered on long 5′ UTRs, containing AUGs and secondary structure. These characteristics are often found in mRNAs encoding regulatory proteins like proto-oncogenes, growth factors, their receptors, and homeodomain proteins. A number of these mRNAs use an alternative mechanism of translation initiation, involving an ...

Journal: International Journal of Biochemistry &amp; Cell Biology - INT J BIOCHEM CELL BIOL , vol. 31, no. 1, pp. 87-106, 1999</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7019-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7019_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:16:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/38252175/neuropsychological-intellectual-and-behavioral-findings-in-patients-with-centrotemporal-spikes</link><title>Neuropsychological, intellectual, and behavioral findings in patients with centrotemporal spikes with and without seizures</title><description>* Neuropsychological, intellectual, and behavioral findings in patients with centrotemporal spikes with and without seizures (Citations: 80)

Josef Weglage, Alike Demsky, Michael Pietsch, Gerd Kurlemann

Journal: Developmental Medicine and Child Neurology - DEVELOP MED CHILD NEUROL , vol. 39, no. 10, pp. 646-651, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7019-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7019_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 17:18:17">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/31928211/are-all-subcortical-dementias-alike-verbal-learning-and-memory-in-parkinson-s-and-huntington-s</link><title>Are all subcortical dementias Alike?: Verbal learning and memory in Parkinson's and huntington's disease patients</title><description>* Are all subcortical dementias Alike?: Verbal learning and memory in Parkinson's and huntington's disease patients (Citations: 76)

Paul J. Massman, Dean C. Delis, Nelson Butters, Bonnie E. Levin, David P. Salmon

The utility of the concept of «subcortical dementia» was investigated by comparing the verbal learning and memory abilities of Parkinson's disease (PD) patients with those of Huntington's disease (HD) patients. Many similarities between the PD and HD groups emerged, including impaired immediate memory spans, inconsistency of recall across learning trials, deficient use of a semantic clustering learning strategy, ...

Journal: Journal of Clinical and Experimental Neuropsychology - J CLIN EXP NEUROPSYCHOL , vol. 12, no. 5, pp. 729-744, 1990</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>