<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7027">prefered or preferred</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:17:46" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7027-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7027_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:17:49">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/30993587/physical-activity-preferences-preferred-sources-of-assistance-and-perceived-barriers-to-increased</link><title>Physical Activity Preferences, Preferred Sources of Assistance, and Perceived Barriers to Increased Activity among Physically Inactive Australians</title><description>* Physical Activity Preferences, Preferred Sources of Assistance, and Perceived Barriers to Increased Activity among Physically Inactive Australians (Citations: 124)

Michael L. Booth, Adrian Bauman, Neville Owen, Christopher J. Gore

...and included questions on the preferred sources of assistance or support to become physically active, preferred activities, and barriers to regular...60 to 78 years, injury or poor health were the most frequently cited barriers to activity. the most-preferred source of advice or assistance changed with age: more...

Journal: Preventive Medicine - PREV MED , vol. 26, no. 1, pp. 131-137, 1997</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7027-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7027_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:19:13">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/895993/human-performance-using-computer-input-devices-in-the-preferred-and-non-preferred-hands</link><title>Human performance using computer input devices in the preferred and non-preferred hands</title><description>* Human performance using computer input devices in the preferred and non-preferred hands (Citations: 64)

Paul Kabbash, I. Scott MacKenzie, William Buxton

...and dragging tasks using the preferred and non-preferred hands. tasks were tested using...experiment shows that the non-preferred hand is more than a poor approximation of the preferred hand. the hands are complementary...

Conference: Computer Human Interaction - CHI , pp. 474-481, 1993</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7027-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7027_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:20:17">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/3588715/positive-genetic-correlation-between-female-preference-and-preferred-male-ornament-in-sticklebacks</link><title>Positive genetic correlation between female preference and preferred male ornament in sticklebacks</title><description>* Positive genetic correlation between female preference and preferred male ornament in sticklebacks (Citations: 116)

Theo C. M. Bakker

Journal: Nature , vol. 363, no. 6426, pp. 255-257, 1993</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7027-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7027_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:21:13">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10988316/taste-preferences-color-preferences-and-flower-choice-in-hummingbirds</link><title>TASTE PREFERENCES, COLOR PREFERENCES, AND FLOWER CHOICE IN HUMMINGBIRDS</title><description>* TASTE PREFERENCES, COLOR PREFERENCES, AND FLOWER CHOICE IN HUMMINGBIRDS (Citations: 74)

F. GARY STILES

...role of taste and color preferences in food choice by hummingbirds...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7027-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7027_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:22:19">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/2005598/estimation-of-logit-choice-models-using-mixed-stated-preferences-and-revealed-preferences</link><title>Estimation of logit choice models using mixed stated preferences and revealed preferences information</title><description>* Estimation of logit choice models using mixed stated preferences and revealed preferences information (Citations: 47)

M. A. Bradley, A. Daly

Published in 1991.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7027-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7027_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:23:30">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/3598390/preference-simulation-and-preference-programming-robustness-issues-in-priority-derivation</link><title>Preference simulation and preference programming: robustness issues in priority derivation</title><description>* Preference simulation and preference programming: robustness issues in priority derivation (Citations: 58)

Ami Arbel, Luis G. Vargas

Journal: European Journal of Operational Research - EJOR , vol. 69, no. 2, pp. 200-209, 1993</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7027-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7027_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:24:28">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/35580824/conditioned-preferences-young-children-prefer-flavors-associated-with-high-dietary-fat</link><title>Conditioned preferences: Young children prefer flavors associated with high dietary fat</title><description>* Conditioned preferences: Young children prefer flavors associated with high dietary fat (Citations: 75)

S JOHNSON, L MCPHEE, L BIRCH

Journal: Physiology &amp; Behavior - PHYSIOL BEHAV , vol. 50, no. 6, pp. 1245-1251, 1991</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7027-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7027_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:25:19">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/37430501/the-control-of-movement-in-the-preferred-and-non-preferred-hands</link><title>The control of movement in the preferred and non-preferred hands</title><description>* The control of movement in the preferred and non-preferred hands (Citations: 57)

J. Annett, Marian Annett, P. T. W. Hudson, Ann Turner

...difference in skill between the preferred and non-preferred hands was investigated using a...relative slowness of the non-preferred hand in the positioning phase...

Journal: Quarterly Journal of Experimental Psychology - QUART J EXP PSYCHOL , vol. 31, no. 4, pp. 641-652, 1979</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7027-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7027_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:26:13">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/38467266/econometric-issues-in-estimating-consumer-preferences-from-stated-preference-data-a-case-study-of</link><title>Econometric Issues In Estimating Consumer Preferences From Stated Preference Data: A Case Study Of The Value Of Automobile Travel Time</title><description>* Econometric Issues In Estimating Consumer Preferences From Stated Preference Data: A Case Study Of The Value Of Automobile Travel Time (Citations: 41)

John Calfee, Clifford Winston, Randolph Stempski

...the econometric analysis of stated preference data in the context of...be used in estimating stated preferences based on respondents' ratings. © 2001...

Journal: Review of Economics and Statistics - REV ECON STATIST , vol. 83, no. 4, pp. 699-707, 2001</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7027-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7027_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:27:02">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/24799905/coping-with-chronic-illness-strategy-preferences-changes-in-preferences-and-associated-emotional</link><title>Coping with chronic illness: Strategy preferences, changes in preferences and associated emotional reactions</title><description>* Coping with chronic illness: Strategy preferences, changes in preferences and associated emotional reactions (Citations: 16)

L VINEY, M WESTBROOK

Journal: Journal of Chronic Diseases , vol. 37, no. 6, pp. 489-502, 1984</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>