<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7029">best buy store closings</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:39:41" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7029-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7029_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:39:44">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/59230485/businesses-as-cultural-icons-their-application-towards-understanding-urban-morphology</link><title>Businesses as Cultural Icons: Their Application towards Understanding Urban Morphology</title><description>* Businesses as Cultural Icons: Their Application towards Understanding Urban Morphology

Stephanie Lawrence

...boxes"; others are unique one-store shops. the varied data set includes grocery stores, drug stores, prepared food vendors, confectioneries, coffee houses, electronic stores, and an adult entertainment store. business rankings are premised upon...

Published in 2008.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7029-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7029_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:40:50">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/649/adaptive-disk-spindown-via-optimal-rent-to-buy-in-probabilistic-environments1</link><title>Adaptive Disk Spindown via Optimal Rent-to-Buy in Probabilistic Environments1</title><description>* Adaptive Disk Spindown via Optimal Rent-to-Buy in Probabilistic Environments1 (Citations: 57)

P. Krishnan, P. M. Long, J. S. Vitter

...in the single rent-to-buy decision problem, without a priori...need to decide when to buy the resource, given that we can rent the resource for $1 per unit time or buy it once and for all...

Published in 1995.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7029-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7029_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:42:02">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/859926/adaptive-disk-spindown-via-optimal-rent-to-buy-in-probabilistic-environments</link><title>Adaptive Disk Spindown via Optimal Rent-to-Buy in Probabilistic Environments</title><description>* Adaptive Disk Spindown via Optimal Rent-to-Buy in Probabilistic Environments (Citations: 56)

P. Krishnan, Philip M. Long, Jeffrey Scott Vitter

...in the single rent-to-buy decision problem, without a priori...need to decide when to buy the resource, given that we can rent the resource for $1 per unit time or buy it once and for all...

Journal: Algorithmica , vol. 23, no. 1, pp. 31-56, 1999</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7029-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7029_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:43:09">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6063265/supervising-an-unsupervised-neural-network</link><title>Supervising an Unsupervised Neural Network</title><description>* Supervising an Unsupervised Neural Network

The Duy Bui, Duy Khuong Nguyen, Tien Dat Ngo

...that has the ability of storing information as well as storing the association between a pair...

Conference: Asian Conference on Intelligent Information and Database Systems - ACIIDS , pp. 307-312, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7029-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7029_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:44:17">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/47755738/tackling-dynamic-problems-with-multiobjective-evolutionary-algorithms</link><title>Tackling Dynamic Problems with Multiobjective Evolutionary Algorithms</title><description>* Tackling Dynamic Problems with Multiobjective Evolutionary Algorithms (Citations: 2)

Lam T. Bui, Minh-Ha Nguyen, Jürgen Branke, Hussein A. Abbass

...empirical comparison shows that the best alternatives are competitive with other...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7029-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7029_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:45:34">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50951749/real-time-communication-for-multicore-systems-with-multi-domain-ring-buses</link><title>Real-Time Communication for Multicore Systems with Multi-domain Ring Buses</title><description>* Real-Time Communication for Multicore Systems with Multi-domain Ring Buses

Bach D. Bui, Rodolfo Pellizzoni, Deepti K. Chivukula, Marco Caccamo

We address the problem of scheduling real-time data transactions on a multicore processor bus. In particular, to in-crease system predictability and tighten WCET estimation, we propose to employ a software-controllable Multi-Domain Ring Bus (MDRB) architecture. The problem of scheduling periodic real-time transactions on MDRB is challenging because the bus allows multiple non-overlapping transactions to ...

Conference: Real-Time Computing Systems and Applications - RTCSA , pp. 23-32, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7029-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7029_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:46:42">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/52490313/thermoelectric-devices-solid-state-refrigerators-and-electrical-generators-in-the-classroom</link><title>Thermoelectric Devices: Solid-State Refrigerators and Electrical Generators in the Classroom</title><description>* Thermoelectric Devices: Solid-State Refrigerators and Electrical Generators in the Classroom

Edmund J. Winder, Arthur B. Ellis, George C. Lisensky

...are available at many department stores. if several model sizes are available, buy the least expensive: all contain...buildup (fig. 4a). in a closed circuit, as shown in figure...

Journal: Journal of Chemical Education - J CHEM EDUC , vol. 73, 1996</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7029-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7029_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:47:52">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/37807802/a-qualitative-study-of-micromarketing-merchandising-in-the-us-apparel-retail-industry</link><title>A qualitative study of micromarketing merchandising in the US apparel retail industry</title><description>* A qualitative study of micromarketing merchandising in the US apparel retail industry

Jaya Halepete, Jan Hathcote, Cara Peters

...while micromarketing merchandising for their store. based on the area the store is located in, the importance of each variable can be adjusted to best suit specific stores. originality/value – understanding the importance...

Journal: Journal of Fashion Marketing and Management , vol. 9, no. 1, pp. 71-82, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7029-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7029_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:48:55">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/1242840/acm-sigcomm-computer-communication-review</link><title>ACM SIGCOMM computer communication review</title><description>* ACM SIGCOMM computer communication review

Andrew T. Campbell, Mischa Schwartz

...the local area, only supports best effort services, and uses shared...more than $100 billion to buy 3g radio spectrum licenses and...

Journal: Computer Communication Review - CCR , vol. 31, no. 5, pp. 20-24, 2001</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7029-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7029_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 18:49:43">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/299385/tailoring-the-interaction-with-users-in-electronic-shops</link><title>Tailoring the Interaction With Users in Electronic Shops</title><description>* Tailoring the Interaction With Users in Electronic Shops (Citations: 51)

Liliana Ardissono, Anna Goy

...the construction of adaptive web stores which customize the interactions with users, suggesting the items best fi tting their needs, and adapting the description of the store catalog to their preferences and...

Published in 1999.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>