<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7034">sony vaio laptop</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:25:37" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7034-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7034_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:25:40">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4452041/dynamic-power-management-of-laptop-hard-disk-poster-paper</link><title>Dynamic power management of laptop hard disk (poster paper)</title><description>* Dynamic power management of laptop hard disk (poster paper)

Tajana Šimunić, Luca Benini, Peter Glynn, Giovanni De Micheli

...states. the measurement results on sony vaio laptop show that our policy has...different policies implemented on the sony vaio laptop is shown in table 1...

Conference: Design, Automation, and Test in Europe - DATE , 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7034-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7034_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:26:38">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/41448/dynamic-power-management-for-portable-systems</link><title>Dynamic power management for portable systems</title><description>* Dynamic power management for portable systems (Citations: 165)

Tajana Simunic, Luca Benini, Peter W. Glynn, Giovanni De Micheli

...smartbadge portable device [18], the sony vaio laptop hard disk and wlan card...with other dpm algorithms for laptop hard disk and wlan card...

Conference: Mobile Computing and Networking - MOBICOM , pp. 11-19, 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7034-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7034_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:27:39">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/25056/dynamic-power-management-of-laptop-hard-disk</link><title>Dynamic Power Management of Laptop Hard Disk</title><description>* Dynamic Power Management of Laptop Hard Disk (Citations: 17)

Tajana Simunic, Luca Benini, Peter W. Glynn, Giovanni De Micheli

...optimal power management policies for laptop hard disk are obtained with...states. the measurement results on sony vaio laptop show that our policy has...

Conference: Design, Automation, and Test in Europe - DATE , 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7034-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7034_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:28:39">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4984591/learning-and-consolidation-of-novel-spoken-words</link><title>Learning and Consolidation of Novel Spoken Words</title><description>* Learning and Consolidation of Novel Spoken Words (Citations: 21)

Matthew H. Davis, Anna Maria Di Betta, Mark J. E. Macdonald, M. Gareth Gaskell

Two experiments explored the neural mechanisms under- lying the learning and consolidation of novel spoken words. In Experiment 1, participants learned two sets of novel words on successive days. A subsequent recognition test revealed high levels of familiarity for both sets. However, a lexical decision task showed that only novel words learned on the previous day engaged in lexical competition ...

Journal: Journal of Cognitive Neuroscience , vol. 21, no. 4, pp. 803-820, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7034-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7034_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:29:41">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/2437623/device-aware-cache-replacement-algorithm-for-heterogeneous-mobile-storage-devices</link><title>Device-Aware Cache Replacement Algorithm for Heterogeneous Mobile Storage Devices</title><description>* Device-Aware Cache Replacement Algorithm for Heterogeneous Mobile Storage Devices (Citations: 2)

Young-jin Kim, Jihong Kim

Hard disks, most prevalent mass-storage devices, have high power consumption and high response time for random I/O requests. Recent remarkable technology improvement of flash memory has made it a rising secondary storage device but flash memory still has high cost per bit. Usage of heterogeneous storage devices such as a pair of a hard disk and a flash ...

Conference: International Conference on Embedded Software and Systems - ICESS , pp. 13-24, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7034-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7034_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:31:03">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50671687/an-analysis-of-energy-efficient-communication-in-ad-hoc-wireless-local-area-network</link><title>An Analysis of Energy Efficient Communication in Ad-Hoc Wireless Local Area Network</title><description>* An Analysis of Energy Efficient Communication in Ad-Hoc Wireless Local Area Network (Citations: 1)

Sandip Vijay, S. C. Sharma, Vishal Gupta

Despite a power saving function IEEE 802.11 network interfaces still consume a vast amount of the overall energy budget of a self-sustained end system. Hence, further efforts are necessary to reduce the energy demand of an IEEE 802.11 network interface. In this paper several aspects of energy consumption and efficient utilization of limited energy resources of IEEE ...

Conference: International Conference on Emerging Trends in Engineering &amp; Technology - ICETET , 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7034-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7034_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:32:13">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/59807141/learning-and-consolidation-of-novel-spoken-words</link><title>Learning and Consolidation of Novel Spoken Words</title><description>* Learning and Consolidation of Novel Spoken Words

Matthew H. Davis, Anna Maria Di Betta, Mark J. E. Macdonald, M. Gareth Gaskell

Two experiments explored the neural mechanisms underlying the learning and consolidation of novel spoken words. In Experiment 1, participants learned two sets of novel words on successive days. A subsequent recognition test revealed high levels of familiarity for both sets. However, a lexical decision task showed that only novel words learned on the previous day engaged in lexical competition with ...

Published in 2008.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7034-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7034_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:33:20">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5647389/korean-fricatives-production-perception-and-laryngeal-typology</link><title>Korean fricatives: Production, perception, and laryngeal typology</title><description>* Korean fricatives: Production, perception, and laryngeal typology

Charles B. Chang

Four experiments were conducted to investigate the contrast between the two voiceless sibilant fricatives of Korean. The results of Experiment 1 show that before /a/, the two fricatives differ in total segment duration, aspiration duration, F1 onset, intensity buildup, and voice quality. The results of Experiment 2 indicate that while segmental duration is not a significant cue in perception, aspiration ...

Published in 2007.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>