<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7037">how to write journalistic review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 13:53:48" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7037-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7037_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 13:53:51">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57681864/mentoring-academic-journal-reviewers-brokering-reviewing-knowledge</link><title>Mentoring academic journal reviewers: brokering reviewing knowledge</title><description>* Mentoring academic journal reviewers: brokering reviewing knowledge

John Adamson

...data from correspondence between experienced reviewer/mentors and new reviewer/mentees at an online journal. with the overlying objective of improving internal review quality, the mentoring programme has...yielding benefits in sensitising new reviewers how to give constructive feedback to authors, argued in this study as ‘brokering’ knowledge of reviewing practice. additionally, reviewer/mentors report that they too...

Journal: Innovations in Education and Teaching International - INNOV EDUC TEACH INT , vol. 49, no. 2, pp. 223-232, 2012</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7037-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7037_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 13:54:14">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10590204/how-to-write-a-research-journal-article-in-engineering-and-science1</link><title>How to write a research journal article in engineering and science1</title><description>* How to write a research journal article in engineering and science1

Scott A. Socolofsky

...what should be included and how the information should be conveyed. fortunately, scientific and engineering journal articles follow an accepted format...is also provided with respect to style, getting started, and the revision/review process....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7037-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7037_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 13:54:28">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/12331135/weblogs-and-journalism-a-typology-to-explore-the-blurring-boundaries</link><title>Weblogs and Journalism A Typology to Explore the Blurring Boundaries</title><description>* Weblogs and Journalism A Typology to Explore the Blurring Boundaries (Citations: 14)

DAVID DOMINGO, ARI HEINONEN

...weblogs do not even pretend to be journal\- istic or related to current events in the sense...expect a paradigm shift in journalism in the internet era. in order to contrib- ute to the debate on the influences of weblogs on journalism and make it more system...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7037-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7037_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 13:54:44">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10250443/editorial-how-to-write-effective-reviews-for-the-journal-of-pediatric-psychology</link><title>Editorial: How to Write Effective Reviews for the Journal of Pediatric Psychology</title><description>* Editorial: How to Write Effective Reviews for the Journal of Pediatric Psychology (Citations: 3)

Dennis Drotar

...the quality of editorial reviews is critical to the success of any scholarly journal, and the journal of pediatric psychology (jpp) is no exception. reviewers generously volunteer their time and...the context of multiple responsibilities, reviewers are asked to assume the difficult task of reviewing manuscripts that are often complex...

Journal: Journal of Pediatric Psychology - J PEDIAT PSYCHOL , vol. 34, no. 2, pp. 113-117, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7037-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7037_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 13:55:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/38561830/how-to-write-for-scientific-and-technical-journals</link><title>How to Write for Scientific and Technical Journals</title><description>* How to Write for Scientific and Technical Journals (Citations: 2)

Herman Estrin

...the four reasons for writing for publication are to advance professionally, to gain prestige, to obtain financial payment, and to receive psychological compensation. editors reject...subject. before sending a manuscript to a journal, one must consider the journal's editorial and review policy and its style sheet...

Journal: Journal of Business Communication - J Bus Comm , vol. 18, no. 3, pp. 55-58, 1981</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7037-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7037_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 13:55:17">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57844152/how-to-write-a-research-report-for-journal-publication</link><title>How to Write a Research Report for Journal Publication</title><description>* How to Write a Research Report for Journal Publication

Leonard J. West

...of the important differences between writing a thesis or dissertation to satisfy requirements for a graduate degree and writing a research report for publication in a professional journal. as well, from this author's vantage point as a reviewer of manuscripts submitted for publication...

Journal: The Journal of Education for Business , vol. 67, no. 3, pp. 132-136, 1992</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7037-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7037_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 13:55:33">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10009771/this-is-not-an-article-just-some-thoughts-on-how-to-write-one</link><title>This is Not an Article Just Some Thoughts on How to Write One</title><description>* This is Not an Article Just Some Thoughts on How to Write One

Carsten Sørensen

...a hard battle in order to finish our latest, newest, and definitely, best paper to date, we do not think...will understand why i chose to call it "this is not an article — just some food for thought on how to write one" ....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7037-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7037_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 13:56:29">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/44771636/a-powerful-lesson-in-how-not-to-write-about-the-middle-east</link><title>A Powerful Lesson in How Not to Write About the Middle East</title><description>* A Powerful Lesson in How Not to Write About the Middle East

Mark LeVine

Journal: Contemporary Sociology-a Journal of Reviews \- CONTEMP SOCIOL , vol. 35, no. 5, pp. 456-458, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7037-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7037_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 13:57:16">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/61420767/how-to-write-a-review-paper</link><title>How to write a review paper</title><description>* How to write a review paper

Nader Ale Ebrahim

...make a summary table of reviewed papers. avoid plagiarism. write a journal article based on literature review....

Published in 2013.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7037-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7037_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 13:58:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/37857423/the-dos-and-don-ts-of-writing-a-journal-article</link><title>The “dos and don'ts” of writing a journal article</title><description>* The “dos and don'ts” of writing a journal article

Tauno Kekäle, Petra de Weerd-Nederhof, Sara Cervai, Massimo Borelli

...purpose of this piece is to give some guidelines on typical problems that lead to rejection, and how to avoid these. design/methodology/approach...can find good suggestions about how to write a paper for the journal of workplace learning....

Journal: Journal of Workplace Learning , vol. 21, no. 1, pp. 71-80, 2009</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>