<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7040">vom fass gent</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:48:57" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7040-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7040_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:48:59">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6345398/habitat-preferences-of-istiophorid-billfishes-in-the-western-north-atlantic-applicability-of</link><title>HABITAT PREFERENCES OF ISTIOPHORID BILLFISHES IN THE WESTERN NORTH ATLANTIC: APPLICABILITY OF ARCHIVAL TAG DATA TO HABITAT BASED STOCK ASSESSMENT METHODOLOGIES</title><description>* HABITAT PREFERENCES OF ISTIOPHORID BILLFISHES IN THE WESTERN NORTH ATLANTIC: APPLICABILITY OF ARCHIVAL TAG DATA TO HABITAT BASED STOCK ASSESSMENT METHODOLOGIES (Citations: 8)

John E. Graves, David W. Kerstetter, Brian E. Luckhurst, Eric D. Prince

...those spent in descent or ascent. the depth of dives was...

Published in 2003.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7040-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7040_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:49:59">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/38705982/differential-heating-and-cooling-rates-in-bigeye-tuna-thunnus-obesus-lowe-a-model-of-non-steady</link><title>Differential heating and cooling rates in bigeye tuna (Thunnus obesus Lowe): a model of non-steady state heat exchange</title><description>* Differential heating and cooling rates in bigeye tuna (Thunnus obesus Lowe): a model of non-steady state heat exchange (Citations: 5)

Hans Malte, Christina Larsen, Michael Musyl, Richard Brill

...pressure data) occurred midway during ascents and averaged 2·fl·s...

Journal: Journal of Experimental Biology - J EXP BIOL , vol. 210, no. 15, pp. 2618-2626, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7040-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7040_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 19:50:51">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48951957/cryoclastic-origin-of-particles-on-the-surface-of-enceladus</link><title>Cryoclastic origin of particles on the surface of Enceladus</title><description>* Cryoclastic origin of particles on the surface of Enceladus

W. Degruyter, M. Manga

The deposits on Enceladus are cryoclastic in originLink deposit to eruption temperaturePrediction of particle size with height

Journal: Geophysical Research Letters - GEOPHYS RES LETT , vol. 38, no. 16, 2011</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>