<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7044">song of ice and fire</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:14:04" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7044-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7044_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:14:12">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11111030/a-study-of-contemporary-high-fantasy-in-george-r-r-martin-s-a-song-of-ice-and-fire-and-steven</link><title>A Study of Contemporary High Fantasy in George R. R. Martin's A Song of Ice and Fire and Steven Erikson's Malazan Book of the Fallen</title><description>* A Study of Contemporary High Fantasy in George R. R. Martin's A Song of Ice and Fire and Steven Erikson's Malazan Book of the Fallen

Magnus Vike</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7044-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7044_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:15:17">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/7016031/intrinsic-membrane-properties-underlying-spontaneous-tonic-firing-in-neostriatal-cholinergic</link><title>Intrinsic Membrane Properties Underlying Spontaneous Tonic Firing in Neostriatal Cholinergic Interneurons</title><description>* Intrinsic Membrane Properties Underlying Spontaneous Tonic Firing in Neostriatal Cholinergic Interneurons (Citations: 74)

Ben D. Bennett, Joseph C. Callaway, Charles J. Wilson

...entry shaped the falling phase of the action potential waveform and activated calcium-dependent potassium channels. blockade of big- conductance channels caused spike broadening. application of apamin, which blocks small-conductance channels, abolished the slow spike afterhyperpolarization (ahp) and caused a tran- sition to burst firing. in the absence of synaptic input, a range of tonic firing patterns are observed, suggesting that...

Published in 2000.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7044-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7044_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:16:28">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/41910330/physical-influences-of-landscape-on-a-large-extent-ecological-disturbance-the-northeastern-north</link><title>Physical influences of landscape on a large-extent ecological disturbance: the northeastern North American ice storm of 1998</title><description>* Physical influences of landscape on a large-extent ecological disturbance: the northeastern North American ice storm of 1998 (Citations: 25)

Andrew A. Millward, Clifford E. Kraft

...affected the eastern adirondack forests of northern new york. ice damage produced widespread breakage of limbs and trunks in susceptible trees. although ice storms are common within northeastern...exceeded damage caused by typical ice storms in the recent past. while plot and stand-scale ecological impacts of ice storms have received attention insofar...

Journal: Landscape Ecology - LANDSCAPE ECOL , vol. 19, no. 1, pp. 99-111, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7044-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7044_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:17:39">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/3151586/gfdl-s-cm2-global-coupled-climate-models-part-ii-the-baseline-ocean-simulation</link><title>GFDL's CM2 Global Coupled Climate Models. Part II: The Baseline Ocean Simulation</title><description>* GFDL's CM2 Global Coupled Climate Models. Part II: The Baseline Ocean Simulation (Citations: 78)

ANAND GNANADESIKAN, KEITH W. DIXON, STEPHEN M. GRIFFIES, V. BALAJI, MARCELO BARREIRO, J. ANTHONY BEESLEY, WILLIAM F. COOKE, THOMAS L. DELWORTH, RUDIGER GERDES, MATTHEW J. HARRISON, ISAAC M. HELD, WILLIAM J. HURLINhttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=3151586&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=song of ice and fire

...rizes the new physical features of the models and examines the simulations that they produce. of the two new coupled climate...hydrographic fields such as temperature and salinity, more realistic ventilation of the deep ocean, and currents that are closer to...

Published in 2005.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7044-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7044_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:19:03">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/26441537/effect-of-electronic-flame-off-parameters-on-copper-bonding-wire-free-air-ball-deformability-heat</link><title>Effect of electronic flame off parameters on copper bonding wire: Free-air ball deformability, heat affected zone length, heat affected zone breaking force</title><description>* Effect of electronic flame off parameters on copper bonding wire: Free-air ball deformability, heat affected zone length, heat affected zone breaking force (Citations: 4)

C. J. Hang, W. H. Song, I. Lum, M. Mayer, Y. Zhou, C. Q. Wang, J. T. Moon, J. Persic

...to decrease the loop height and thereby the package thickness.online measurements of deformability and haz breaking force at temperatures close to the bonding temperature of 220°c are new tools used in this study to evaluate the effects of electronic flame off (efo) current and firing time on the cu fab deformability and the haz length and tensile strength. fabs with 50μm...

Journal: Microelectronic Engineering - MICROELECTRON ENG , vol. 86, no. 10, pp. 2094-2103, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7044-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7044_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:20:09">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57563658/corporeal-and-sonic-diagrams-for-cinematic-ethics-in-rolf-de-heer-s-dance-me-to-my-song</link><title>Corporeal and sonic diagrams for cinematic ethics in Rolf De Heer's Dance Me to My Song</title><description>* Corporeal and sonic diagrams for cinematic ethics in Rolf De Heer's Dance Me to My Song

Anna Hickey-Moody

...by heather (as the character of julia) and is clearly about ‘her world’. the ethic of engagement exemplified by this film...engages with the disabled body and soundscapes associated with the disabled body through an ‘ethics of listening’, new sonic and filmic bodies can be – and are – created....

Journal: Discourse: Studies in The Cultural Politics of Education , vol. 31, no. 4, pp. 499-511, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7044-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7044_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:21:29">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/51044369/the-simulation-towards-a-robust-wireless-sensor-network-for-the-environment-control</link><title>The simulation towards a robust wireless sensor network for the environment control</title><description>* The simulation towards a robust wireless sensor network for the environment control

Jun Steed Huang, Xiaoxiao Liu, Qingqing Yang, Xuehua Song

...sensor network in the river of ontario, we gained a series experience of the implementation, such as sensor nodes' energy control, dormancy/ awaken, node positioning and network overlaying. we have transmitted the live data to the center of monitor laboratory successfully. the purpose of this application is to monitor the weather, and control the water damage; as...

Conference: International Conference on Consumer Electronics, Communications and Networks - CECNet , 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7044-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7044_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:22:39">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5971751/an-investigation-into-the-ionic-chemical-composition-and-mixing-state-of-biomass-burning-particles</link><title>An Investigation into the Ionic Chemical Composition and Mixing State of Biomass Burning Particles Recorded During TRACE-P P3B Flight#10</title><description>* An Investigation into the Ionic Chemical Composition and Mixing State of Biomass Burning Particles Recorded During TRACE-P P3B Flight#10 (Citations: 10)

C. H. Song, Y. Ma, D. Orsini, Y. P. Kim, R. J. Weber

...1 molar ratios between k+ and no3− and between nh4+ and (so42−+ inferred organics) suggest the presence of fine-mode kno3, (nh4)2so4, and nh4(organics) aerosols. under the...than k2so4 in a mixture of no3−, so42−, k+, nh4+, and organic anions, the measurements suggest that aerosols could be composed of biomass burning particles (kno3) mixed...

Journal: Journal of Atmospheric Chemistry - J ATMOS CHEM , vol. 51, no. 1, pp. 43-64, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7044-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7044_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:23:51">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11412958/optimized-autonomous-space-in-situ-sensor-web-for-volcano-monitoring</link><title>Optimized Autonomous Space In-situ Sensor-Web for Volcano Monitoring</title><description>* Optimized Autonomous Space In-situ Sensor-Web for Volcano Monitoring (Citations: 12)

Wen-Zhan Song, Behrooz Shirazi, Renjie Huang, Mingsen Xu, Nina Peterson, Rick LaHusen, John Pallister, Dan Dzurisin, S. Moran, M. Lisowski, Aaron Kiely, Joshua Doubledayhttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=11412958&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=song of ice and fire

...way communication capability between ground and space assets, use both space and ground data for optimal allocation of limited power and bandwidth resources on the ground...2) advancing sensor-web power and communication resource management technology; and 3) enabling scalability for seamless infusion of future space and in-situ assets into the...

Journal: IEEE Journal of Selected Topics in Applied Earth Observations and Remote Sensing - IEEE J SEL TOP APPL EARTH OBS , vol. 3, no. 4, pp. 1-10, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7044-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7044_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:24:59">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/14396536/design-and-deployment-of-sensor-network-for-real-time-high-fidelity-volcano-monitoring</link><title>Design and Deployment of Sensor Network for Real-Time High-Fidelity Volcano Monitoring</title><description>* Design and Deployment of Sensor Network for Real-Time High-Fidelity Volcano Monitoring (Citations: 2)

Wen-Zhan Song, Renjie Huang, Mingsen Xu, Behrooz A. Shirazi, Richard LaHusen

...a gateway. the main contribution of this paper is the design of a robust sensor network optimized for rapid deployment during periods of volcanic unrest and provide real-time long-term...lab environment, the outdoor campus, and the volcano crater. despite the heavy rain, snow, and ice as well as gusts exceeding...

Journal: IEEE Transactions on Parallel and Distributed Systems - TPDS , vol. 21, no. 11, pp. 1658-1674, 2010</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>