<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7045">Natural Parks America</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:26:05" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7045-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7045_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:26:09">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5584913/invasion-of-artificial-ponds-in-do-ana-natural-park-southwest-spain-by-an-exotic-estuarine-copepod</link><title>Invasion of artificial ponds in Doñana Natural Park, southwest Spain, by an exotic estuarine copepod</title><description>* Invasion of artificial ponds in Doñana Natural Park, southwest Spain, by an exotic estuarine copepod (Citations: 10)

Dagmar Frisch, Héctor Rodríguez-Pérez, Andy J. Green

...brackish ponds situated in donana natural park and the guadalquivir delta between...in the area of donana natural park has important implications for the...

Journal: Aquatic Conservation-marine and Freshwater Ecosystems - AQUAT CONSERV , vol. 16, no. 5, pp. 483-492, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7045-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7045_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:27:03">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5829918/chytrid-fungus-infection-related-to-unusual-mortalities-of-salamandra-salamandra-and-bufo-bufo-in</link><title>Chytrid fungus infection related to unusual mortalities of Salamandra salamandra and Bufo bufo in the Peñalara Natural Park, Spain</title><description>* Chytrid fungus infection related to unusual mortalities of Salamandra salamandra and Bufo bufo in the Peñalara Natural Park, Spain (Citations: 21)

Jaime Bosch, Iñigo Martínez-Solano

...in central spain, the penalara natural park, the disease almost extirpated the...

Journal: Oryx , vol. 40, no. 01, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7045-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7045_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:28:02">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/55003239/automatically-separating-anthropogenic-from-natural-sounds-in-parks</link><title>Automatically separating anthropogenic from natural sounds in parks</title><description>* Automatically separating anthropogenic from natural sounds in parks

Jack Gillette, Paul Schomer

Journal: Journal of The Acoustical Society of America \- J ACOUST SOC AMER , vol. 129, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7045-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7045_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:29:11">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/14665488/national-parks-in-america</link><title>National Parks in America</title><description>* National Parks in America

Unknown

Journal: Nature , vol. 129, no. 3269, pp. 933-933, 1932</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7045-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7045_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:30:05">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5458505/fire-management-in-parks-and-protected-areas-introduction-and-summary</link><title>Fire Management in Parks and Protected Areas: Introduction and Summary</title><description>* Fire Management in Parks and Protected Areas: Introduction and Summary

Bruce M. Kilgore

...in vegetation,wildlife,and other natural features are part of the way natural ecosystems function.the original,somewhat simplis- tic,and static concept of "park preservation"has since been expanded into a broader concept of perpetuating natural park resources and natural park processes over time.only in this way can the national park service (nps) and other agencies...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7045-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7045_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:31:07">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/45424617/pyrolysis-gas-chromatography-mass-spectrometry-of-soil-organic-matter-extracted-from-a-brazilian</link><title>Pyrolysis-gas chromatography/mass spectrometry of soil organic matter extracted from a Brazilian mangrove and Spanish salt marshes</title><description>* Pyrolysis-gas chromatography/mass spectrometry of soil organic matter extracted from a Brazilian mangrove and Spanish salt marshes (Citations: 2)

Fernando Perobelli Ferreira, P. Buurman, F. Macias, X. L. Otero, R. Boluda

...marshes (betanzos ria and corrubedo natural parks, galicia, and the albufera natural park, valencia) was investigated by pyrolysis...

Journal: Soil Science Society of America Journal - SSSAJ , vol. 73, no. 3, pp. 841-851, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7045-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7045_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:32:15">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42587348/reginald-h-thomson-and-planning-for-strathcona-park-1912-15</link><title>Reginald H. Thomson and planning for Strathcona Park, 1912–15</title><description>* Reginald H. Thomson and planning for Strathcona Park, 1912–15

William H Wilson

...of british columbia's strathcona park in 1912, some patterns of rural nature park planning in north america were already established. strathcona was...repeated and exemplified there. all park superintendents had to plan for tourist access to and within parks, for scenic preservation and for...

Journal: Planning Perspectives , vol. 17, no. 4, pp. 373-387, 2002</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7045-08"><link>http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48276149/conservation-strategy-of-a-nature-reserve-in-mediterranean-ecosystems-the-effects-of-protection</link><title>Conservation strategy of a nature reserve in Mediterranean ecosystems: the effects of protection from grazing on biodiversity</title><description>* Conservation strategy of a nature reserve in Mediterranean ecosystems: the effects of protection from grazing on biodiversity (Citations: 24)

José R. Verdú, Manuel B. Crespo, Eduardo Galante

...protection of natural areas has caused the elimination...and endemicity, the font roja natural park in alicante province (se iberian...

Journal: Biodiversity and Conservation - BIODIVERS CONSERV , vol. 9, no. 12, pp. 1707-1721, 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7045-09"><link>http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/7013126/influence-of-plant-community-structure-on-natural-enemies-of-pine-needle-scale-homoptera</link><title>Influence of Plant Community Structure on Natural Enemies of Pine Needle Scale (Homoptera: Diaspididae) in Urban Landscapes</title><description>* Influence of Plant Community Structure on Natural Enemies of Pine Needle Scale (Homoptera: Diaspididae) in Urban Landscapes (Citations: 8)

John F. Tooker, Lawrence M. Hanks

...landscapes, and scarce in more natural, park-like habitats. rates of parasitism...more diverse and abundant in natural habitats and appear to be...

Journal: Environmental Entomology - ENVIRON ENTOMOL , vol. 29, no. 6, pp. 1305-1311, 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7045-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7045_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 20:36:25">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Error.html</link><title>Lead poisoning in waterfowl from the Ebro Delta, Spain: Calculation of lead exposure thresholds for mallards</title><description>* Lead poisoning in waterfowl from the Ebro Delta, Spain: Calculation of lead exposure thresholds for mallards (Citations: 27)

R. Guitart, J. To-Figueras, R. Mateo, A. Bertolero, S. Cerradelo, A. Martínez-Vilalta

...92 at the ebro delta natural park. sediment examination showed a lead...

Journal: Archives of Environmental Contamination and Toxicology - ARCH ENVIRON CONTAM TOXICOL , vol. 27, no. 3, pp. 289-293, 1994</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>