<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7048">pictures auvergne</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:00:06" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7048-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7048_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:00:09">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6777027/hd-174884-a-strongly-eccentric-short-period-early-type-binary-system-discovered-by-corot</link><title>HD 174884: a strongly eccentric, short-period early-type binary system discovered by CoRoT</title><description>* HD 174884: a strongly eccentric, short-period early-type binary system discovered by CoRoT (Citations: 1)

C. Maceroni, J. Montalb치n, E. Michel, P. Harmanec, A. Prsa, M. Briquet, E. Niemczura, T. Morel, D. Ladjal, M. Auvergne, A. Baglin, F. Baudinhttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=6777027&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=pictures auvergne

...the results provide a consistent picture of the system composed of...

Journal: Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics - ASTRON ASTROPHYS , vol. 508, no. 3, pp. 1375-1389, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7048-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7048_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:01:17">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/53348329/the-dynamics-of-a-variable-star-phase-space-reconstruction-and-dimension-computation</link><title>The dynamics of a variable star - Phase-space reconstruction and dimension computation</title><description>* The dynamics of a variable star - Phase-space reconstruction and dimension computation

M. Auvergne, A. Baglin

...this reconstruction allows one to picture the attractor and/or to...

Journal: Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics - ASTRON ASTROPHYS , vol. 168, pp. 118-124, 1986</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7048-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7048_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:02:25">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/53241176/satellites-data-and-field-activity-volcanology</link><title>Satellites data and field activity: Volcanology</title><description>* Satellites data and field activity: Volcanology

Laurence Durand

...can be visited (http://www.auvergne-volcan.com/accueil/accueil.asp...at different places and take pictures of specific formations. when pupils collect samples or take pictures, they use gps to locate...

Published in 2010.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7048-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7048_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:03:38">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/35743968/molecular-basis-of-voltage-dependence-of-connexin-channels-an-integrative-appraisal</link><title>Molecular basis of voltage dependence of connexin channels: An integrative appraisal</title><description>* Molecular basis of voltage dependence of connexin channels: An integrative appraisal (Citations: 17)

Daniel Gonz치lez, Juan M. G칩mez-Hern치ndez, Luis C. Barrio

...up to date and precise picture of the molecular and structural...are brought about. the emerging picture indicates that cx channels can...

Journal: Progress in Biophysics &amp; Molecular Biology - PROG BIOPHYS MOL BIOL , vol. 94, no. 1, pp. 66-106, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7048-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7048_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:04:34">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5900813/premature-dissolution-of-the-microsporocyte-callose-wall-causes-male-sterility-in-transgenic-tobacco</link><title>Premature Dissolution of the Microsporocyte Callose Wall Causes Male Sterility in Transgenic Tobacco</title><description>* Premature Dissolution of the Microsporocyte Callose Wall Causes Male Sterility in Transgenic Tobacco (Citations: 123)

Dawn Worrall, Diane L. Hird, Wyatt Paul, John Draper

Male sterility in a petunia cytoplasmic male sterile line has been attributed to the early appearance of active callase, a P-1,3-glucanase, in the anther locule. This leads to premature dissolution of the callose walls surrounding the microsporogenous cells. We have mimicked this aspect of the petunia line in transgenic tobacco by engineering the secretion of a modified ...

Journal: Plant Cell , vol. 4, no. 7, pp. 759-771, 1992</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7048-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7048_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:05:42">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/41152067/negative-emotional-state-shortens-the-duration-of-the-chewing-sequence</link><title>Negative emotional state shortens the duration of the chewing sequence</title><description>* Negative emotional state shortens the duration of the chewing sequence

V. Deiss, L. Rossignol, P. Bourdiol

...we employed an association of pictures and sounds taken from the international affective picture system (iaps) and the international...

Journal: Food Quality and Preference - FOOD QUAL PREFERENCE , vol. 20, no. 1, pp. 57-61, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7048-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7048_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:07:12">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/29461055/long-term-changes-in-intracranial-dural-arteriovenous-fistulae-leading-to-worsening-in-the-type-of</link><title>Long-term changes in intracranial dural arteriovenous fistulae leading to worsening in the type of venous drainage</title><description>* Long-term changes in intracranial dural arteriovenous fistulae leading to worsening in the type of venous drainage (Citations: 23)

C. Cognard, E. Houdart, A. Casasco, J. Gabrillargues, J. Chiras, J. J. Merland

...any charge in the clinical pictures indicates a repeat angiogram. stenosis...

Journal: Neuroradiology , vol. 39, no. 1, pp. 59-66, 1997</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7048-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7048_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:08:18">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40181419/toxicity-assessment-of-the-herbicides-sulcotrione-and-mesotrione-toward-two-reference-environmental</link><title>Toxicity Assessment of the Herbicides Sulcotrione and Mesotrione Toward Two Reference Environmental Microorganisms: Tetrahymena pyriformis and Vibrio fischeri</title><description>* Toxicity Assessment of the Herbicides Sulcotrione and Mesotrione Toward Two Reference Environmental Microorganisms: Tetrahymena pyriformis and Vibrio fischeri (Citations: 7)

J. L. Bonnet, F. Bonnemoy, M. Dusser, J. Bohatier

...to obtain a more accurate picture of the environmental impact of...

Journal: Archives of Environmental Contamination and Toxicology - ARCH ENVIRON CONTAM TOXICOL , vol. 55, no. 4, pp. 576-583, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7048-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7048_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:09:30">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39182245/lemierre-s-syndrome-and-genetic-polymorphisms-a-case-report</link><title>Lemierre's syndrome and genetic polymorphisms: a case report</title><description>* Lemierre's syndrome and genetic polymorphisms: a case report (Citations: 5)

Jean-Michel Constantin, Jean-Paul Mira, Renaud Guerin, Sophie Cayot-Constantin, Olivier Lesens, Florence Gourdon, Jean-Pierre Romaszko, Philippe Linval, Henri Laurichesse, Jean-Etienne Bazin

...syndrome presents a classic clinical picture, the pathophysiology of which remains...

Journal: BMC Infectious Diseases - BMC INFECT DIS , vol. 6, no. 1, pp. 115-4, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7048-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7048_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:10:40">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/18850157/emission-quenching-induced-by-intervalence-charge-transfer-in-pr3+-or-tb3+-doped-ynbo4-and-canb2o6</link><title>Emission quenching induced by intervalence charge transfer in Pr3+- or Tb3+-doped YNbO4 and CaNb2O6</title><description>* Emission quenching induced by intervalence charge transfer in Pr3+- or Tb3+-doped YNbO4 and CaNb2O6 (Citations: 2)

P. Boutinaud, E. Cavalli, M. Bettinelli

...on this basis a detailed picture of the excited-state dynamics...

Journal: Journal of Physics-condensed Matter - J PHYS-CONDENS MATTER , vol. 19, no. 38, 2007</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>