<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7051">dinosaur names</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:13:36" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7051-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7051_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:13:39">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5279555/feathered-dinosaurs-flying-dinosaurs-crown-dinosaurs-and-the-name-aves</link><title>Feathered dinosaurs, flying dinosaurs, crown dinosaurs, and the name "Aves</title><description>* Feathered dinosaurs, flying dinosaurs, crown dinosaurs, and the name "Aves (Citations: 20)

Jacques Gauthier, Kevin de Queiroz

...the taxon name "aves" is currently used for...everyone wants to talk about—namely, those com- posed of bird-line archosaurs, the feathered dinosaurs, the flying dinosaurs, and the crown di- nosaurs...

Published in 2001.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7051-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7051_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:14:43">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/15076516/database-dinosaur-name-game</link><title>DATABASE: Dinosaur Name Game</title><description>* DATABASE: Dinosaur Name Game

Unknown

Journal: Science , vol. 310, no. 5748, pp. 597e-597e, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7051-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7051_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:15:50">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/30653681/the-fort-mcmurray-demonstration-project-in-social-marketing-theory-design-and-evaluation</link><title>The Fort McMurray Demonstration Project in Social Marketing: theory, design, and evaluation</title><description>* The Fort McMurray Demonstration Project in Social Marketing: theory, design, and evaluation (Citations: 2)

Tee L Guidotti, Lynda Ford, Malynda Wheeler

...identity to the project, a dinosaur named “safetysaurus.” the project integrated...

Journal: American Journal of Preventive Medicine - AMER J PREV MED , vol. 18, no. 2, pp. 163-169, 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7051-04"><link>http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/56589030/top-dinosaur-hunters-are-worst-at-naming</link><title>Top dinosaur hunters are worst at naming</title><description>* Top dinosaur hunters are worst at naming

Zoë Corbyn

Journal: Nature , 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7051-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7051_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:17:57">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57747564/naming-dinosaur-species-the-performance-of-prolific-authors</link><title>Naming dinosaur species: the performance of prolific authors</title><description>* Naming dinosaur species: the performance of prolific authors

MICHAEL J. BENTON

...of the 321 authors who named all 1400 species of dinosaurs since 1824 shows that prolific...author was othniel marsh, who named 98 species of dinosaurs (including 80 non-avian dinosaurs and 18 mesozoic birds), but only 35 (36%) of his names are currently regarded as valid...

Journal: Journal of Vertebrate Paleontology - J VERTEBRATE PALEONTOL , vol. 30, no. 5, pp. 1478-1485, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7051-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7051_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:19:03">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/49709841/the-bristol-dinosaur-project</link><title>The Bristol Dinosaur Project</title><description>* The Bristol Dinosaur Project

Michael J. Benton, Remmert Schouten, Edward J. A. Drewitt, Pedro Viegas

...by substantial funding. the bristol dinosaur project focuses on the fourth dinosaur ever named in the world, thecodontosaurus, discovered in bristol in 1834, and named in 1836. the dinosaur is not in itself spectacular...

Journal: Proceedings of The Geologists Association - PROC GEOL ASSOC</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7051-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7051_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:20:13">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5480745/crouching-theropod-and-navahopus-sauropodomorph-tracks-from-the-early-jurassic-navajo-sandstone-of</link><title>Crouching Theropod and Navahopus Sauropodomorph Tracks from the Early Jurassic Navajo Sandstone of USA</title><description>* Crouching Theropod and Navahopus Sauropodomorph Tracks from the Early Jurassic Navajo Sandstone of USA (Citations: 2)

Jesper Milàn, David B. Loope, Richard G. Bromley

...and trackways of small theropod dinosaurs are particularly abundant within one 10−m−thick interval. this paper describes a crouching trace from a theropod dinosaur that shows impressions of all...to be from a sauropodomorph dinosaur. it is named navahopus coyoteensis isp. nov. on...

Journal: Acta Palaeontologica Polonica - ACTA PALAEONTOL POL , vol. 53, no. 2, pp. 197-205, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7051-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7051_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:21:22">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11285115/they-call-it-like-they-see-it-spontaneous-naming-and-attention-to-shape</link><title>They call it like they see it: spontaneous naming and attention to shape</title><description>* They call it like they see it: spontaneous naming and attention to shape (Citations: 17)

Larissa K. Samuelson, Linda B. Smith

...found that children's spontaneous names were cued by the perceptual feature of shape. experiment 2 examines the relation between spontaneous productions, name general- izations in a structured...the perceptual properties of the named object that activated the child's lexical category of dinosaur. although it is unlikely that...

Journal: Developmental Science - DEV SCI , vol. 8, no. 2, pp. 182-198, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7051-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7051_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:22:26">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57578346/a-new-early-dinosaur-saurischia-sauropodomorpha-from-the-late-triassic-of-argentina-a</link><title>A new early dinosaur (Saurischia: Sauropodomorpha) from the Late Triassic of Argentina: a reassessment of dinosaur origin and phylogeny</title><description>* A new early dinosaur (Saurischia: Sauropodomorpha) from the Late Triassic of Argentina: a reassessment of dinosaur origin and phylogeny (Citations: 4)

Martin D. Ezcurra

...thought that the oldest known dinosaur assemblages were not diverse, and...saturnalia than to any other dinosaur. thus, the saturnalia + chromogisaurus clade is named here as the new subfamily...

Journal: Journal of Systematic Palaeontology - J SYST PALAEONTOL , vol. 8, no. 3, pp. 371-425, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7051-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7051_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:23:22">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/41461572/a-new-species-of-the-primitive-dinosaur-thecodontosaurus-saurischia-sauropodomorpha-and-its</link><title>A new species of the primitive dinosaur Thecodontosaurus (Saurischia: Sauropodomorpha) and its implications for the systematics of early dinosaurs</title><description>* A new species of the primitive dinosaur Thecodontosaurus (Saurischia: Sauropodomorpha) and its implications for the systematics of early dinosaurs (Citations: 49)

Adam M. Yates

...south wales are redescribed and named as a new species, thecodontosaurus...has important implications for early dinosaur phylogenetics. thecodontosaurus provides evidence that...

Journal: Journal of Systematic Palaeontology - J SYST PALAEONTOL , vol. 1, no. 1, pp. 1-42, 2003</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>