<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7056">ROADM</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:47:07" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7056-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7056_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:47:10">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/1258008/some-theoretical-aspects-of-road-traffic-research</link><title>Some theoretical aspects of road traffic research</title><description>* Some theoretical aspects of road traffic research (Citations: 957)

J. G. Wardrop</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7056-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7056_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:48:05">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/3255291/integrins-and-signal-transduction-pathways-the-road-taken</link><title>Integrins and signal transduction pathways: the road taken</title><description>* Integrins and signal transduction pathways: the road taken (Citations: 1230)

E. A Clark, J. S Brugge

Journal: Science , vol. 268, no. 5208, pp. 233-239, 1995</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7056-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7056_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:49:04">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/1330101/smart-cars-on-smart-roads-problems-of-control</link><title>Smart cars on smart roads: problems of control</title><description>* Smart cars on smart roads: problems of control (Citations: 503)

Pravin Varaiya

Key features of one automated intelligent vehicle/highway system (IVHS) are outlined, it is shown how core driver decisions are improved, a basic IVHS control system architecture is proposed, and a design of some control subsystems is offered. Some experimental work is summarized. A system that promises a threefold increase in capacity is outlined, and a four-layer hierarchical control ...

Journal: IEEE Transactions on Automatic Control - IEEE TRANS AUTOMAT CONTR , vol. 38, no. 2, pp. 195-207, 1993</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7056-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7056_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:50:09">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4134702/the-amyloid-hypothesis-of-alzheimer-s-disease-progress-and-problems-on-the-road-to-therapeutics</link><title>The Amyloid Hypothesis of Alzheimer's Disease: Progress and Problems on the Road to Therapeutics</title><description>* The Amyloid Hypothesis of Alzheimer's Disease: Progress and Problems on the Road to Therapeutics (Citations: 1925)

John Hardy, Dennis J. Selkoe

It has been more than 10 years since it was first proposed that the neurodegeneration in Alzheimer's disease (AD) may be caused by deposition of amyloid beta-peptide (Abeta) in plaques in brain tissue. According to the amyloid hypothesis, accumulation of Abeta in the brain is the primary influence driving AD pathogenesis. The rest of the disease process, including ...

Journal: Science , vol. 297, no. 5580, pp. 353-356, 2002</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7056-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7056_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:51:20">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/156629/model-based-object-tracking-in-monocular-image-sequences-of-road-traffic-scenes</link><title>Model-based object tracking in monocular image sequences of road traffic scenes</title><description>* Model-based object tracking in monocular image sequences of road traffic scenes (Citations: 381)

D. Roller, Kostas Daniilidis, Hans-hellmut Nagel

...in monocular image sequences from road traf- fic scenes recorded by...results on various real world road traffic scenes are presented and...

Journal: International Journal of Computer Vision - IJCV , vol. 10, no. 3, pp. 257-281, 1993</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7056-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7056_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:52:31">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/1271544/the-road-to-serfdom</link><title>The Road to Serfdom</title><description>* The Road to Serfdom (Citations: 755)

F. A. Hayek

Journal: SSRN Electronic Journal , 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7056-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7056_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:53:36">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/2377016/on-kinematic-waves-ii-a-theory-of-traffic-flow-on-long-crowded-roads</link><title>On Kinematic Waves. II. A Theory of Traffic Flow on Long Crowded Roads</title><description>* On Kinematic Waves. II. A Theory of Traffic Flow on Long Crowded Roads (Citations: 658)

M. J. Lighthill, G. B. Whitham

Journal: Proceedings of The Royal Society A: Mathematical, Physical and Engineering Sciences , vol. 229, no. 1178, pp. 317-345, 1955</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7056-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7056_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:54:53">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/3694298/roads-and-their-major-ecological-effects</link><title>ROADS AND THEIR MAJOR ECOLOGICAL EFFECTS</title><description>* ROADS AND THEIR MAJOR ECOLOGICAL EFFECTS (Citations: 632)

Richard T. T. Forman, Lauren E. Alexander

...ef- fects mainly occur near roads. road networks interrupt horizontal ecological flows...inhibit important interior species. thus, road density and network structure are informative landscape ecology assays. australia has huge road-reserve networks of native vegetation...

Journal: Annual Review of Ecology and Systematics - ANNU REV ECOL SYST , vol. 29, no. 1, pp. 207-231, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7056-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7056_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:56:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/132489/clock-rate-versus-ipc-the-end-of-the-road-for-conventional-microarchitectures</link><title>Clock rate versus IPC: the end of the road for conventional microarchitectures</title><description>* Clock rate versus IPC: the end of the road for conventional microarchitectures (Citations: 435)

Vikas Agarwal, M. S. Hrishikesh, Stephen W. Keckler, Doug Burger

The doubling of microprocessor performanceevery three years has been the result of two factors: more transistors per chip and superlinear scaling of the processor clock with technology generation. Our results show that, due to both diminishing improvements in clock rates and poor wire scal- ing as semiconductordevices shrink, the achievable performance growth of conventional microarchitectures will slow substantially. In this ...

Conference: International Symposium on Computer Architecture - ISCA , pp. 248-259, 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7056-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7056_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:57:13">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/400560/an-active-testing-model-for-tracking-roads-in-satellite-images</link><title>An Active Testing Model for Tracking Roads in Satellite Images</title><description>* An Active Testing Model for Tracking Roads in Satellite Images (Citations: 282)

Donald Geman, Bruno Jedynak

...a new approach for tracking roads from satellite images, and therebyillustrate...amp;quot; (matchedfilters for short road segments) one at a time...

Journal: IEEE Transactions on Pattern Analysis and Machine Intelligence - PAMI , vol. 18, no. 1, pp. 1-14, 1996</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>