<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7057">web of science</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:58:19" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7057-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7057_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:58:22">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4395407/impact-of-data-sources-on-citation-counts-and-rankings-of-lis-faculty-web-of-science-versus-scopus</link><title>Impact of data sources on citation counts and rankings of LIS faculty: Web of science versus scopus and google scholar</title><description>* Impact of data sources on citation counts and rankings of LIS faculty: Web of science versus scopus and google scholar (Citations: 103)

Lokman I. Meho, Kiduk Yang

Journal: Journal of The American Society for Information Science and Technology - JASIS , vol. 58, no. 13, pp. 2105-2125, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7057-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7057_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 21:59:26">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10496198/as-we-may-search-comparison-of-major-features-of-the-web-of-science-scopus-and-google-scholar</link><title>As we may search - Comparison of major features of the Web of Science, Scopus, and Google Scholar citation-based and citation-enhanced databases</title><description>* As we may search - Comparison of major features of the Web of Science, Scopus, and Google Scholar citation-based and citation-enhanced databases (Citations: 58)

Peter Jacso</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7057-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7057_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:00:48">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4436476/a-framework-for-web-science</link><title>A Framework for Web Science</title><description>* A Framework for Web Science (Citations: 48)

Tim Berners-lee, Wendy Hall, James A. Hendler, Kieron O'hara, Nigel Shadbolt, Daniel J. Weitzner

...text sets out a series of approaches to the analysis and synthesis of the world wide web, and other web-like information structures. a comprehensive...set out an agenda for web science, the science of decentralised information systems. web science is required both as a way to understand the web, and as a way to...

Journal: Foundations and Trends in Web Science \- FTWEB , vol. 1, no. 1, pp. 1-130, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7057-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7057_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:01:58">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/44645344/the-seamless-web-technology-science-etcetera-etcetera</link><title>The Seamless Web: Technology, Science, Etcetera, Etcetera</title><description>* The Seamless Web: Technology, Science, Etcetera, Etcetera (Citations: 50)

T. P. Hughes

Journal: Social Studies of Science \- SOC STUD SCI , vol. 16, no. 2, pp. 281-292, 1986</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7057-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7057_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:02:59">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4361663/web-science-an-interdisciplinary-approach-to-understanding-the-web</link><title>Web science: an interdisciplinary approach to understanding the web</title><description>* Web science: an interdisciplinary approach to understanding the web (Citations: 52)

James A. Hendler, Nigel Shadbolt, Wendy Hall, Tim Berners-lee, Daniel J. Weitzner

...the web must be studied as an...

Journal: Communications of The ACM - CACM , vol. 51, no. 7, pp. 60-69, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7057-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7057_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:04:16">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42315624/information-searching-strategies-in-web-based-science-learning-the-role-of-internet-self-efficacy</link><title>Information searching strategies in web-based science learning: the role of internet self-efficacy</title><description>* Information searching strategies in web-based science learning: the role of internet self-efficacy (Citations: 51)

Meng-Jung Tsai, Chin-Chung Tsai

...students' information searching strategies in web-based science learning activities and further examine the influence of students' internet self-efficacy on...proposed a framework for analysing web-based searching strategies. this study also reflected the importance of explicitly helping students acquire better metacognitive web searching strategies....

Journal: Innovations in Education and Teaching International - INNOV EDUC TEACH INT , vol. 40, no. 1, pp. 43-50, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7057-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7057_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:05:28">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5516612/comparison-of-pubmed-scopus-web-of-science-and-google-scholar-strengths-and-weaknesses</link><title>Comparison of PubMed, Scopus, Web of Science, and Google Scholar: strengths and weaknesses</title><description>* Comparison of PubMed, Scopus, Web of Science, and Google Scholar: strengths and weaknesses (Citations: 40)

Matthew E. Falagas, Eleni I. Pitsouni, George A. Malietzis, Georgios Pappas

...coverage and prac- tical utility of pubmed, scopus, web of science, and google scholar. the official web pages of the data- bases were used...published after 1995) compared with web of science. google scholar, as for the web in general, can help in the retrieval of even the most obscure information...

Journal: Faseb Journal - FASEB J , vol. 22, no. 2, pp. 338-342, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7057-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7057_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:06:39">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6094279/comparing-alternatives-to-the-web-of-science-for-coverage-of-the-social-sciences-literature</link><title>Comparing alternatives to the Web of Science for coverage of the social sciences' literature</title><description>* Comparing alternatives to the Web of Science for coverage of the social sciences' literature (Citations: 40)

Michael Norris, Charles Oppenheim

...the web of science is no longer the only database which offers citation indexing of the social sciences. scopus, csa illumina and google...was ranked first. when issues of functionality, the quality of record processing and depth of coverage are taken into account, scopus and web of science have a significant advantage over...

Journal: Journal of Informetrics , vol. 1, no. 2, pp. 161-169, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7057-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7057_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:07:43">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4487190/internal-and-external-collaboration-scripts-in-web-based-science-learning-at-schools</link><title>Internal and External Collaboration Scripts in Web based Science Learning at Schools</title><description>* Internal and External Collaboration Scripts in Web based Science Learning at Schools (Citations: 37)

Ingo Kollar, Frank Fischer, James D. Slotta

...secondary schools participated. two versions of an external collaboration script (high vs. low structured) supporting argumentation were embedded within a web-based collaborative inquiry curriculum. students...script supported all learners, regardless of their internal scripts, concerning the acquisition of domain-general knowledge. learners' internal scripts influenced the acquisition of domain-specific knowledge. results from...

Published in 2005.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7057-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7057_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:08:54">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/12915613/three-options-for-citation-tracking-google-scholar-scopus-and-web-of-science</link><title>Three options for citation tracking: Google Scholar, Scopus and Web of Science</title><description>* Three options for citation tracking: Google Scholar, Scopus and Web of Science (Citations: 26)

Nisa Bakkalbasi, Kathleen Bauer, Janis Glover, Lei Wang

...were also gathered from each of the three sources. results: for oncology 1993 web of science returned the highest average number of citations, 45.3. scopus returned the highest average number of citations (8.9) for oncology 2003. web of science returned the highest number of citations for condensed matter physics...

Journal: Biomedical Digital Libraries - Biomed Digit Libr , vol. 3, no. 1, 2006</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>