<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7063">Spanish unemployment</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:47:39" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7063-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7063_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:47:42">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/35206994/the-causes-of-spanish-unemployment-a-structural-var-approach</link><title>The causes of Spanish unemployment: A structural VAR approach</title><description>* The causes of Spanish unemployment: A structural VAR approach (Citations: 66)

Juan José Dolado, Juan F. Jimeno

...review the main causes of spanish unemployment and weight them by estimating...we associate different causes of unemployment with shocks of different nature...

Journal: European Economic Review - EUR ECON REV , vol. 41, no. 7, pp. 1281-1307, 1997</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7063-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7063_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:48:38">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5236256/the-regional-distribution-of-spanish-unemployment-a-spatial-analysis</link><title>The regional distribution of Spanish unemployment: A spatial analysis</title><description>* The regional distribution of Spanish unemployment: A spatial analysis (Citations: 21)

Enrique López-Bazo, Tomás del Barrio, Manuel Artis

...analysing the regional distribution of unemployment. as we are interested in...of the provincial distribution of unemployment rates in spain. results point to increasing spatial dependence in the distribution of regional unemployment rates, and a change in...

Journal: Papers in Regional Science - PAP REG SCI , vol. 81, no. 3, pp. 365-389, 2002</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7063-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7063_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:49:46">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6130608/spanish-unemployment-the-end-of-the-wild-ride</link><title>Spanish Unemployment: The End of the Wild Ride?</title><description>* Spanish Unemployment: The End of the Wild Ride? (Citations: 15)

Samuel Bentolila, Juan F. Jimeno

...the last quarter century, the spanish unemployment rate has gone from 3...

Published in 2003.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7063-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7063_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:50:52">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/34395775/on-the-persistence-of-spanish-unemployment-rates</link><title>On the persistence of Spanish unemployment rates</title><description>* On the persistence of Spanish unemployment rates (Citations: 7)

Diego Romero-Ávila, Carlos Usabiaga

...the hysteresis hypothesis for the unemployment rate of the spanish regions over the period 1976...the hysteresis hypothesis in regional spanish unemployment. the results are robust across...

Journal: Empirical Economics - EMPIR ECON , vol. 35, no. 1, pp. 77-99, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7063-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7063_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:52:04">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5701019/spanish-unemployment-persistence-and-the-ladder-effect</link><title>Spanish Unemployment Persistence and the Ladder Effect</title><description>* Spanish Unemployment Persistence and the Ladder Effect (Citations: 6)

Fabrice Collard, Raquel Fonseca, Rafael Munoz

...this paper aims to examine unemployment persistence in spain by the...is then calibrated on the spanish economy. our results replicate the...

Published in 2002.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7063-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7063_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:53:10">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/13025103/can-a-carbon-permit-system-reduce-spanish-unemployment</link><title>Can a carbon permit system reduce Spanish unemployment?</title><description>* Can a carbon permit system reduce Spanish unemployment? (Citations: 7)

Taran Fæhn, Antonio G. Gómez-Plana, Snorre Kverndokk

...impact of carbon policy on unemployment in spain and whether recycling...carbon permits does not aggravate spanish unemployment. in fact, if supplied with revenue recycling schemes, unemployment rates may actually fall. contrary...

Journal: Energy Economics - ENERG ECON , vol. 31, no. 4, pp. 595-604, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7063-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7063_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:54:24">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6080413/the-ecological-fallacy-in-a-time-series-context-evidence-from-spanish-regional-unemployment-rates</link><title>The ecological fallacy in a time series context: evidence from Spanish regional unemployment rates</title><description>* The ecological fallacy in a time series context: evidence from Spanish regional unemployment rates (Citations: 2)

Juan Carlos Duque, Manuel Artís, Raúl Ramos

...a time series context. using spanish regional unemployment data, this paper shows that...

Journal: Journal of Geographical Systems , vol. 8, no. 4, pp. 391-410, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7063-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7063_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:55:36">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/13915273/can-the-matching-model-account-for-spanish-unemployment</link><title>Can the matching model account for Spanish unemployment?</title><description>* Can the matching model account for Spanish unemployment? (Citations: 3)

Raquel Fonseca, Rafael Muñoz

...explaining the dynamics of the spanish labour market, focussing in particular on the high persistence of unemployment and the dynamics around the...calibrated and simulated for the spanish economy. two sources of disturbances...

Published in 2003.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7063-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7063_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:56:42">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5268182/the-rise-and-fall-of-spanish-unemployment-a-chain-reaction-theory-perspective</link><title>The Rise and Fall of Spanish Unemployment: A Chain Reaction Theory Perspective</title><description>* The Rise and Fall of Spanish Unemployment: A Chain Reaction Theory Perspective (Citations: 2)

Marika Karanassou, Hector Sala

...the evolution of spanish unemployment has been quite idiosyncratic. the full employment levels of the early seventies were followed by unemployment rates that were the highest...investigate the determinants of this unemployment trajectory using the analytical framework of the chain reaction theory (crt). we show that unemployment may not gravitate towards its...

Published in 2008.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7063-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7063_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 22:57:53">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/58214716/reducing-spanish-unemployment-under-the-emu</link><title>Reducing Spanish unemployment under the EMU</title><description>* Reducing Spanish unemployment under the EMU

Olivier Blanchard, Juan F. Jimeno

...what will it take? the spanish economy has grown at close to 3% per year, and the unemployment rate has fallen by 4...will have to decrease its unemployment rate, with one of its two hand to decrease its unemployment rate, with one of its...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>