<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7067">used kindle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:12:41" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7067-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7067_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:12:45">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/36459192/dissociation-of-seizure-traits-in-inbred-strains-of-mice-using-the-flurothyl-kindling-model-of</link><title>Dissociation of seizure traits in inbred strains of mice using the flurothyl kindling model of epileptogenesis</title><description>* Dissociation of seizure traits in inbred strains of mice using the flurothyl kindling model of epileptogenesis (Citations: 4)

Dominick Papandrea, Tara M. Anderson, Bruce J. Herron, Russell J. Ferland

...characteristics observed in the flurothyl kindling model are under genetic control...we examined in the flurothyl kindling model were dissociable between c57bl...

Journal: Experimental Neurology - EXP NEUROL , vol. 215, no. 1, pp. 60-68, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7067-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7067_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:13:56">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48189244/development-of-new-anticonvulsants-using-the-kindling-model</link><title>Development of New Anticonvulsants Using the Kindling Model</title><description>* Development of New Anticonvulsants Using the Kindling Model (Citations: 1)

W. McIntyre Burnham, Deborah Lonsdale, Afshin Shahzamani, Claudia Perez-Cruz, Heather E. Edwards

...years, our laboratory has been using the kindling model in a search for...intractable epilepsy; (2) the limbic kindling model and how it should be used in pharmacological studies related to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7067-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7067_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:14:56">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/38050881/evaluation-of-development-specific-targets-for-antiepileptogenic-therapy-using-rapid-kindling</link><title>Evaluation of development-specific targets for antiepileptogenic therapy using rapid kindling: Antiepileptogenic Therapy during Development</title><description>* Evaluation of development-specific targets for antiepileptogenic therapy using rapid kindling: Antiepileptogenic Therapy during Development

Raman Sankar, Stéphane Auvin, Young Se Kwon, Eduardo Pineda, Don Shin, Andréy Mazarati

Journal: Epilepsia , vol. 51, pp. 39-42, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7067-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7067_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:15:56">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/47733524/limbic-epileptogenesis-a-model-study-using-kindling-from-the-amygloid-cortical-nucleus</link><title>Limbic Epileptogenesis: A Model Study Using Kindling from the Amygloid Cortical Nucleus</title><description>* Limbic Epileptogenesis: A Model Study Using Kindling from the Amygloid Cortical Nucleus

A. F. Bikbaev, A. V. Karpova, S. A. Chepurnov, N. E. Chepurnova, L. B. Kalimullina

...of limbic epileptogenesis was studied using a model of electrical kindling from different rostrocaudal segments of...of temporal epilepsy are analyzed using various animal models [9, 10]. electrical kindling (low-level stimulation that causes...

Journal: Doklady Biological Sciences , vol. 383, no. 1, pp. 99-102, 2002</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7067-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7067_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:17:04">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/35208225/an-efficient-method-for-time-course-studies-of-antiepileptic-drugs-using-the-kindled-rat-seizure</link><title>An efficient method for time course studies of antiepileptic drugs using the kindled rat seizure model</title><description>* An efficient method for time course studies of antiepileptic drugs using the kindled rat seizure model

M HEIT, W SCHWARK

Journal: Journal of Pharmacological Methods , vol. 18, no. 4, pp. 319-325, 1987</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7067-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7067_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:18:14">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/59178522/the-brief-wondrous-life-of-the-syracuse-kindle</link><title>The Brief Wondrous Life of the Syracuse Kindle</title><description>* The Brief Wondrous Life of the Syracuse Kindle

Melinda Dermody, Suzanne Preate, Nancy Turner, Scott Warren

...a new technology, i.e., kindle dx, for delivery of ebooks, gauging user reactions to e-book readers, and using kindle statistics and user feedback to...a statement regarding our discontinued use of kindles in december 2009. we will describe what we learned that is both kindle-specific and e-book reader...

Published in 2010.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7067-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7067_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:19:24">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/35110107/transfer-of-epileptogenesis-between-perirhinal-cortex-and-amygdala-induced-by-electrical-kindling</link><title>Transfer of epileptogenesis between perirhinal cortex and amygdala induced by electrical kindling</title><description>* Transfer of epileptogenesis between perirhinal cortex and amygdala induced by electrical kindling (Citations: 8)

Jo-Anne M Buchanan, David K Bilkey

...expect a transfer between prc kindling and amygdaloid kindling. using kindling transfer, the present study was...the early stages of amygdaloid kindling than either controls or those partially kindled. this suggests that primary prc kindling may facilitate amygdaloid access to...

Journal: Brain Research - BRAIN RES , vol. 771, no. 1, pp. 71-79, 1997</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7067-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7067_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:20:33">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/35110106/transfer-between-atropine-induced-spiking-in-the-perirhinal-cortex-and-electrical-kindling-of-the</link><title>Transfer between atropine-induced spiking in the perirhinal cortex and electrical kindling of the amygdala</title><description>* Transfer between atropine-induced spiking in the perirhinal cortex and electrical kindling of the amygdala (Citations: 2)

Jo-Anne M Buchanan, David K Bilkey

...during non-seizure inducing infusions. using kindling transfer, the present study sought...were elicited during initial amygdaloid kindling. these findings suggest that ais (and/or atropine-induced behavioural seizures) and amygdala-kindled seizures share, at some level...

Journal: Brain Research - BRAIN RES , vol. 771, no. 1, pp. 63-70, 1997</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7067-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7067_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:21:44">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/34424941/regionspecific-changes-in-prodynorphin-mrna-and-ir-dynorphin-a-levels-after-kindled-seizures</link><title>Regionspecific changes in prodynorphin mRNA and ir-dynorphin A levels after kindled seizures</title><description>* Regionspecific changes in prodynorphin mRNA and ir-dynorphin A levels after kindled seizures (Citations: 9)

P. Romualdi, G. Bregola, A. Donatini, A. Capobianco, M. Simonato

...seizures.experiments have been run using kindling,one of the most valuable...increase (threefold)1 h after kindled seizures,and return to baseline...

Journal: Journal of Molecular Neuroscience - J MOL NEUROSCI , vol. 13, no. 1, pp. 69-75, 1999</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7067-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7067_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:22:56">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/34637169/adjunctive-brainstem-behaviors-in-the-rat</link><title>Adjunctive brainstem behaviors in the rat</title><description>* Adjunctive brainstem behaviors in the rat

Orlando J. Andy, Xiao-Bing Qian, Mathew Lundien, Cora Dearman, Jack Andy, Robin W. Rockhold, Michael Andrews

...sixty-one adult rats were used. kindling was induced by mechanical and...which lesions and drugs were used separately and in different combinations. cocaine was used to accentuate, and dextrorphan to attenuate the kindling process. behaviors were visually analyzed...

Journal: Integrative Physiological and Behavioral Science - INTEGRAT PHYSIOL BEHAV SCI , vol. 31, no. 4, pp. 315-330, 1996</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>