<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7070">compact flash memory card</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:47:20" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7070-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7070_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:47:24">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/2187001/lgedbms-a-small-dbms-for-embedded-system-with-flash-memory</link><title>LGeDBMS: A Small DBMS for Embedded System with Flash Memory</title><description>* LGeDBMS: A Small DBMS for Embedded System with Flash Memory (Citations: 18)

Gye-jeong Kim, Seung-cheon Baek, Hyun-sook Lee, Han-deok Lee, Moon Jeung Joe

...to the widespread adaptation of flash memory as main data storages, respectively. as a result, managing the data on flash memory has been gaining in sig...read/write/erase behaviors of flash memory are radically different than that...

Conference: Very Large Data Bases - VLDB , pp. 1255-1258, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7070-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7070_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:48:27">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/1523286/a-compact-on-chip-ecc-for-low-cost-flash-memories</link><title>A compact on-chip ECC for low cost flash memories</title><description>* A compact on-chip ECC for low cost flash memories (Citations: 21)

Toru Tanzawa, Tomoharu Tanaka, Ken Takeuchi, Riichiro Shirota, Seiichi Aritome, Hiroshi Watanabe, Gertjan Hemink, Kazuhiro Shimizu, Shinji Sato, Yuji Takeuchi, Kazunori Ohuchi

...a compact on-chip error correcting circuit (ecc) for low cost flash memories has been developed. the total...an experimental 64m-bit nand flash memory. the cumulative sector error rate...

Journal: IEEE Journal of Solid-state Circuits - IEEE J SOLID-STATE CIRCUITS , vol. 32, no. 5, pp. 662-669, 1997</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7070-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7070_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:49:28">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/18494245/che-and-chisel-characterization-procedure-for-compact-flash-cell-model</link><title>CHE and CHISEL characterization procedure for compact Flash cell model</title><description>* CHE and CHISEL characterization procedure for compact Flash cell model

A. Regnier, B. Saillet, J. M. Portal, R. Bouchakour

...electron) characterization procedure for a compact flash memory cell model. as a core element of the flash memory model, a philips mos model...to extract the full model card including the che and chisel...

Journal: Journal of Non-crystalline Solids - J NON-CRYST SOLIDS , vol. 353, no. 5, pp. 625-629, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7070-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7070_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:50:42">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/54804108/portable-tremor-monitor-system-for-real-time-full-wave-monitoring-and-analysis</link><title>Portable tremor monitor system for real-time full-wave monitoring and analysis</title><description>* Portable tremor monitor system for real-time full-wave monitoring and analysis

Meng-Hsiang Yang, Yung-Hoh Sheu, Yuan-Hsing Shih, M. S. Young

...wave form in an expansible compact flash memory card. with a rechargeable battery and...during daily activity on the compact flash memory card within the device. after collection...

Journal: Review of Scientific Instruments - REV SCI INSTR , vol. 74, pp. 1303-1309, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7070-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7070_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:51:52">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50374961/memory-device-packaging-from-leadframe-packages-to-wafer-level-packages</link><title>Memory device packaging - from leadframe packages to wafer level packages</title><description>* Memory device packaging - from leadframe packages to wafer level packages (Citations: 2)

Wei Koh

...appetite for digital storage. hence, memory cards in the form of usb drive (u-drive), compact flash (cf), secured digital (sd), memory stick, and multimedia card (mmc) are now proliferating in...fbga). (2) review of the flash memory card packages - non-volatile memory flash and sram packages are generally...

Conference: Conference on) High Density Packaging and Microsystem Integration, International Symposium on - HDP , 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7070-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7070_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:53:06">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/1621284/a-programmable-dsp-solution-to-a-solid-state-audio-player</link><title>A programmable DSP solution to a solid state audio player</title><description>* A programmable DSP solution to a solid state audio player

Jeff Hayes, Stephen Handley, Jason Kridner, Mark Nadeski

...audio media stored on a flash memory card. this card can hold up to an...quality approaching that of a compact disc (cd). the flash memory cards provide much better audio quality...

Journal: IEEE Transactions on Consumer Electronics - IEEE TRANS CONSUM ELECTRON , vol. 45, no. 3, pp. 975-979, 1999</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7070-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7070_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:54:18">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4030991/ubiquitous-mobile-access-to-real-time-patient-monitoring-data</link><title>Ubiquitous mobile access to real-time patient monitoring data</title><description>* Ubiquitous mobile access to real-time patient monitoring data (Citations: 19)

S. P. Nelwan, T. B. van Dam, P. Klootwijk, S. H. Meij

...can also be stored on compact flash memory cards for data collection purposes. additional...

Published in 2002.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7070-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7070_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:55:26">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10568515/characterization-of-a-high-resolution-acquisition-system-for-marine-geophysical-applications</link><title>Characterization of a High Resolution Acquisition System for Marine Geophysical Applications</title><description>* Characterization of a High Resolution Acquisition System for Marine Geophysical Applications (Citations: 3)

S. Shariat Panahi, F. Alegria, A. Manuel

...recording. a datalogger based on compact flash memory cards and 24 bits analog-to...

Conference: IEEE Instrumentation and Measurement Technology Conference - I2MTC , pp. 1317-1320, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7070-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7070_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:56:34">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/27076408/a-low-power-datalogger-based-on-compactflash-memory-for-ocean-bottom-seismometers</link><title>A Low-Power Datalogger Based on CompactFlash Memory for Ocean Bottom Seismometers</title><description>* A Low-Power Datalogger Based on CompactFlash Memory for Ocean Bottom Seismometers (Citations: 1)

Shahram Shariat-Panahi, Sergi Ventosa, Javier Cadena, Antoni Manuel-Lazaro, Antoni Bermúdez, Valentí Sallarés, Jaume Piera

...minimized to increase autonomy, and compact flash memory cards have been used as the...

Journal: IEEE Transactions on Instrumentation and Measurement - IEEE TRANS INSTRUM MEAS , vol. 57, no. 10, pp. 2297-2303, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7070-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7070_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-18 23:57:48">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/51656573/unmanned-aerial-vehicle-uav-operated-megapixel-spectral-camera</link><title>Unmanned aerial vehicle (UAV) operated megapixel spectral camera</title><description>* Unmanned aerial vehicle (UAV) operated megapixel spectral camera

Jussi Mäkynen, Christer Holmlund, Heikki Saari, Kai Ojala, Tapani Antila

...half-maximum (fwhm). an internal memory buffer allows 16 mpix of...data is stored in a compact flash memory card which provides the mass storage...

Published in 2011.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>