<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7078">count in korean</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:39:46" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7078-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7078_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:39:49">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/28578773/association-of-serum-glutamyltransferase-with-c-reactive-protein-levels-and-white-blood-cell</link><title>Association of serum γ-glutamyltransferase with C-reactive protein levels and white blood cell count in Korean adults</title><description>* Association of serum γ-glutamyltransferase with C-reactive protein levels and white blood cell count in Korean adults

Yong-Jae Lee, Jong-Koo Kim, Jung-Hyun Lee, Hye-Ree Lee, Dae-Ryong Kang, Jae-Yong Shim

Journal: Clinical Chemistry and Laboratory Medicine - CLIN CHEM LAB MED , vol. 46, no. 10, pp. 1410-1415, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7078-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7078_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:41:00">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/18200807/application-of-an-improved-in-vivo-counting-program-to-korean-nuclear-power-plants</link><title>Application of an improved in vivo counting program to Korean nuclear power plants</title><description>* Application of an improved in vivo counting program to Korean nuclear power plants

Tae Young Kong, Hee Geun Kim

...contamination, but can also result in the excessively conservative estimation of radioactive contamination. in this paper, previous experiments to improve in vivo counting at npps are introduced briefly and the practical application of techniques presented in those experiments to korean npps is demonstrated in detail....

Journal: Applied Radiation and Isotopes - APPL RADIAT ISOTOPES , vol. 67, no. 7, pp. 1311-1314, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7078-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7078_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:42:07">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/37385183/the-effect-of-the-korean-number-system-on-young-children-s-counting-a-natural-experiment-in</link><title>The Effect of the Korean Number System On Young Children's Counting: A Natural Experiment in Numerical Bilingualism</title><description>* The Effect of the Korean Number System On Young Children's Counting: A Natural Experiment in Numerical Bilingualism (Citations: 10)

Myung Ja Song, Herbert P. Ginsburg

in korea, two number systems are in simultaneous ux. one is somewhat...system facilitates the acquisition of counting. korean children initially suffer from their numerical ‘bhgualism’: they find it difficult to learn two counting systems at the same time...

Journal: International Journal of Psychology - INT J PSYCHOL , vol. 23, no. 1-6, pp. 319-332, 1988</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7078-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7078_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:43:09">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57801311/korean-chinese-parents-language-attitudes-and-additive-bilingual-education-in-china</link><title>Korean-Chinese parents' language attitudes and additive bilingual education in China</title><description>* Korean-Chinese parents' language attitudes and additive bilingual education in China

Fang Gao, Jae Park

...indigenous cultures. this is apparent in its bilingual education programme for ethnic minorities, among which korean diaspora communities are to be counted. korean-chinese people in china have been exposed to...parents are exposed to the koreans in the peninsula, the clearer they realise the importance of putonghua and korean, not only affectively, but also referentially in function of a cross-national...

Journal: Journal of Multilingual and Multicultural Development - J MULTILING MULTICULT DEVELOP , vol. ahead-of-p, no. ahead-of-p, pp. 1-14, 2012</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7078-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7078_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:44:16">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/13034164/effects-of-stress-final-segments-and-vowel-quality-on-syllable-counts-a-case-study-of-koreans</link><title>Effects of stress, final segments, and vowel quality on syllable counts: a case study of Koreans' syllable counts of bisyllabic English words</title><description>* Effects of stress, final segments, and vowel quality on syllable counts: a case study of Koreans' syllable counts of bisyllabic English words

Byung-jin Lim

...the current study examines in detail effects of stress, final segments, and vowel-quality on syllable counts of bisyllabic english words by koreans. proportionally more words are judged...stress on the second syllable. in addition, word-final stops often induce a vowel insertion at the end of words resulting in increase of syllable counts while sonorous final segments such...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7078-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7078_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:45:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10275216/numeral-classifiers-and-counting-speed-differences-between-korean-and-english</link><title>Numeral Classifiers and Counting Speed Differences between Korean and English</title><description>* Numeral Classifiers and Counting Speed Differences between Korean and English

Suann Robinson

...classification affect processing speeds of counting. much research suggests that particular...language by testing differences between korean and english speakers' reaction times in object counting in matching and non-matching numeral...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7078-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7078_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:46:59">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/33859482/hair-counts-from-scalp-biopsy-specimens-in-asians</link><title>Hair counts from scalp biopsy specimens in Asians</title><description>* Hair counts from scalp biopsy specimens in Asians (Citations: 15)

Hyun-Jeong Lee, Seog-Jun Ha, Joo-Han Lee, Jin-Wou Kim, Hyung-Ok Kim, David A. Whiting

...significantly lower (p &lt; .05) in koreans than in whites and blacks. in koreans, female subjects had a significantly...hair density is significantly lower in koreans than in whites or blacks. slight sexual difference exists in follicular counts in koreans. our data could be used...

Journal: Journal of The American Academy of Dermatology - J AMER ACAD DERMATOL , vol. 46, no. 2, pp. 218-221, 2002</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7078-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7078_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:48:08">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39773178/plurality-and-other-semantic-aspects-of-common-nouns-in-korean</link><title>Plurality and other semantic aspects of common nouns in Korean</title><description>* Plurality and other semantic aspects of common nouns in Korean (Citations: 11)

Beom-Mo Kang

...i show that the semantic count/mass distinction of common nouns is as important in korean as in english, despite the fact that...much like those of english count nouns except that the denotation of a syntactically singular count noun in korean may include a semantically plural...

Journal: Journal of East Asian Linguistics - J EAST ASIAN LINGUIST , vol. 3, no. 1, pp. 1-24, 1994</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7078-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7078_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:49:06">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/37112552/replication-of-the-association-between-a-chromosome-9p21-polymorphism-and-coronary-artery-disease</link><title>Replication of the association between a chromosome 9p21 polymorphism and coronary artery disease in Japanese and Korean populations</title><description>* Replication of the association between a chromosome 9p21 polymorphism and coronary artery disease in Japanese and Korean populations (Citations: 44)

Kunihiko Hinohara, Toshiaki Nakajima, Megumi Takahashi, Shigeru Hohda, Taishi Sasaoka, Ken-ichi Nakahara, Kouji Chida, Motoji Sawabe, Takuro Arimura, Akinori Sato, Bok-Soo Lee, Ji-min Banhttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=37112552&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=count in korean

...associations of rs1333049 with cad in japanese (604 patients and 1,151 controls) and koreans (679 patients and 706 controls). we found a significant association in both japanese [odds ratio (or...49, p = 0.00027, allele count model] and koreans (or = 1.19, 95% ci; 1.02–1.38, p = 0.025, allele count model). these observations demonstrated that...

Journal: Journal of Human Genetics - J HUM GENET , vol. 53, no. 4, pp. 357-359, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7078-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7078_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:50:18">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/31111762/relation-between-insulin-resistance-and-hematological-parameters-in-elderly-koreans-southwest-seoul</link><title>Relation between insulin resistance and hematological parameters in elderly Koreans—Southwest Seoul (SWS) Study</title><description>* Relation between insulin resistance and hematological parameters in elderly Koreans—Southwest Seoul (SWS) Study (Citations: 13)

K. M Choi, J Lee, Y. H Kim, K. B Kim, D. L Kim, S. G Kim, D. H Shin, N. H Kim, I. B Park, D. S Choi, S. H Baik

in this study, we investigated the relation between insulin resistance and hematological parameters in elderly koreans. this study included 1314 non...as hemoglobin concentrations and wbc counts in elderly koreans. this suggests that increased erythropoiesis...

Journal: Diabetes Research and Clinical Practice - DIABETES RES CLIN PRACT , vol. 60, no. 3, pp. 205-212, 2003</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>