<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7079">a-team theme music</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:51:17" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7079-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7079_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:51:19">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10398149/are-we-experienced-listeners-a-review-of-the-musical-capacities-that-do-not-depend-on-formal</link><title>Are we “experienced listeners”? A review of the musical capacities that do not depend on formal musical training</title><description>* Are we “experienced listeners”? A review of the musical capacities that do not depend on formal musical training (Citations: 44)

E. Bigand, B. Poulin-Charronnat

...the capacity for processing western music. this includes perceiving the relationships between a theme and its variations, perceiving musical tensions and relaxations, generating musical expectancies, integrating local structures in...of data highlights that some musical capacities are acquired through exposure to music without the help of explicit training. these capacities reach such a degree of sophistication that they...

Journal: Cognition , vol. 100, no. 1, pp. 100-130, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7079-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7079_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:52:36">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57804994/a-music-therapy-educator-and-undergraduate-students-perceptions-of-their-music-project-s-relevance</link><title>A music therapy educator and undergraduate students’ perceptions of their music project's relevance for Sichuan earthquake survivors</title><description>* A music therapy educator and undergraduate students’ perceptions of their music project's relevance for Sichuan earthquake survivors

Tian Gao, Clare OCallaghan, Lucanne Magill, Sisi Lin, Junhan Zhang, Jingwen Zhang, Jiaao Yu, Xiaomeng Shi

...killed approximately 70,000 people, a music therapy educator led three teams, totalling 41 music therapy students, who provided music performances and activities to survivors...the educator's and five music therapy student volunteers’ perceptions of their music project's relevance during a stabilization-through-music phase in june–july 2008...

Journal: Nordic Journal of Music Therapy - NORD J MUSIC THER , vol. ahead-of-p, no. ahead-of-p, pp. 1-24, 2012</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7079-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7079_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:53:35">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/13151010/variations2-retrieving-and-using-music-in-an-academic-setting-university-music-students-teachers</link><title>VARIATIONS2: RETRIEVING AND USING MUSIC IN AN ACADEMIC SETTING University music students, teachers, and researchers discover and retrieve musical works and navigate within them, then create annotations and share them with other users</title><description>* VARIATIONS2: RETRIEVING AND USING MUSIC IN AN ACADEMIC SETTING University music students, teachers, and researchers discover and retrieve musical works and navigate within them, then create annotations and share them with other users

Jon W. Dunn, Donald Byrd, Mark Notess, Jenn Riley, Ryan Scherle

Published in 2006.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7079-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7079_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:54:48">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/44830943/firecrackers-and-duds-cooperating-music-teachers-perspectives-on-their-relationships-with</link><title>“Firecrackers” and “Duds”Cooperating Music Teachers' Perspectives on Their Relationships With Student Teachers</title><description>* “Firecrackers” and “Duds”Cooperating Music Teachers' Perspectives on Their Relationships With Student Teachers

Tami J. Draves

...coded and analyzed for emerging themes. power emerges as a strong theme. when discussing relationships with student...defined by the researcher on a continuum from student—teacher relationship to team-teaching relationship to a collaborative partnership. generally, the cooperating music teachers find the more collaborative...

Journal: Journal of Music Teacher Education , vol. 18, no. 1, pp. 6-15, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7079-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7079_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:55:55">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11093062/ducational-format-the-use-of-a-conceptual-tool-as-a-means-of-reflection-upon-two-edu-cational</link><title>ducational Format: the Use of a conceptual Tool as a Means of Reflection upon two edu cational Settings using Music Technology in Italy</title><description>* ducational Format: the Use of a conceptual Tool as a Means of Reflection upon two edu cational Settings using Music Technology in Italy

Nick Breeze, Filippo Fanò

...uk. this european union funded team was part of the kaleidoscope network of excellence (http://www.noe-kaleidosco- pe.org). an underpinning belief of the team was that the traditional concept...of recent technological developments, and a new approach is needed to apply to the organisation of learning activities; the team called this new approach "format...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7079-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7079_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:57:02">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/1967082/toward-the-scientific-evaluation-of-music-information-retrieval-systems</link><title>Toward the scientific evaluation of music information retrieval systems</title><description>* Toward the scientific evaluation of music information retrieval systems (Citations: 25)

J. Stephen Downie

...the findings-to-date of a project to assist in the efforts being made to establish a trec-like evaluation paradigm within the music information retrieval (mir) research community...adoption, and subsequent validation, of a "reasonable person" approach to "relevance" assessment; and, the development of a secure, yet accessible, research environment...

Conference: International Symposium/Conference on Music Information Retrieval - ISMIR , 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7079-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7079_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:58:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/3958878/the-scientific-evaluation-of-music-information-retrieval-systems-foundations-and-future</link><title>The Scientific Evaluation of Music Information Retrieval Systems: Foundations and Future</title><description>* The Scientific Evaluation of Music Information Retrieval Systems: Foundations and Future (Citations: 19)

J. Stephen Downie

Journal: Computer Music Journal - COMPUT MUSIC J , vol. 28, no. 2, pp. 12-23, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7079-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7079_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 00:59:18">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48231808/music-indexing-and-retrieval-for-multimedia-digital-libraries</link><title>Music Indexing and Retrieval for Multimedia Digital Libraries</title><description>* Music Indexing and Retrieval for Multimedia Digital Libraries

Nicola Orio

...problem of the retrieval of music documents from multimedia digital libraries. some of the peculiarities of the music language are described, showing similarities...and retrieval of textual and music documents. after reviewing the main approaches to music retrieval, a novel methodology is presented, which...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7079-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7079_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:00:23">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/14408742/variations2-retrieving-and-using-music-in-an-academic-setting</link><title>Variations2: retrieving and using music in an academic setting</title><description>* Variations2: retrieving and using music in an academic setting (Citations: 12)

Jon W. Dunn, Donald Byrd, Mark Notess, Jenn Riley, Ryan Scherle

...university music students, teachers, and researchers discover and retrieve musical works and navigate within them...

Journal: Communications of The ACM - CACM , vol. 49, no. 8, pp. 53-58, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7079-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7079_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:01:34">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6097078/theoretical-and-methodological-issues-related-to-long-term-creative-cognition-the-case-of-musical</link><title>Theoretical and methodological issues related to long term creative cognition: the case of musical composition</title><description>* Theoretical and methodological issues related to long term creative cognition: the case of musical composition (Citations: 1)

Nicolas Donin, Jacques Theureau

...the theme of large temporal span of cognition is emerging as a key issue in cognitive anthropology...it through the analysis of a musical composition process, that of voi...

Journal: Cognition, Technology &amp; Work , vol. 9, no. 4, pp. 233-251, 2007</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>