<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7083">I'm on the road again</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:27:00" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7083-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7083_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:27:03">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/36870186/on-the-road-again-predicting-the-job-transfer-decision</link><title>On the road again: Predicting the job transfer decision</title><description>* On the road again: Predicting the job transfer decision (Citations: 55)

Jeanne M. Brett, Anne H. Reilly

Journal: Journal of Applied Psychology - J APPL PSYCHOL , vol. 73, no. 4, pp. 614-620, 1988</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7083-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7083_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:28:12">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/36870187/on-the-road-again-predicting-the-job-transfer-decision</link><title>On the Road Again: Predicting the Job Transfer Decision</title><description>* On the Road Again: Predicting the Job Transfer Decision (Citations: 9)

Jeanne M. Brett, Anne H. Reilly

...behavior in a model of the individual job transfer decision. results showed that willingness to relocate strongly predicted the decision to accept or reject...

Journal: Journal of Applied Psychology - J APPL PSYCHOL , vol. 73, no. 4, pp. 614-620, 1988</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7083-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7083_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:29:23">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/41376991/on-the-road-again-competitive-effects-and-condition-dependent-dispersal-in-male-baboons</link><title>On the road again: competitive effects and condition-dependent dispersal in male baboons</title><description>* On the road again: competitive effects and condition-dependent dispersal in male baboons (Citations: 4)

P. M. R. Clarke, S. P. Henzi, L. Barrett, D. Rendall

Journal: Animal Behaviour - ANIM BEHAV , vol. 76, no. 1, pp. 55-63, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7083-04"><link>http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/38564453/on-the-road-again-dual-career-commuter-relationships</link><title>On the Road Again: Dual-Career Commuter Relationships</title><description>* On the Road Again: Dual-Career Commuter Relationships (Citations: 1)

J. C. Rotter, D. E. Barnett, M. L. Fawcett

Journal: The Family Journal , vol. 6, no. 1, pp. 46-48, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7083-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7083_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:32:04">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40593801/health-care-reform-in-the-united-states-on-the-road-to-nowhere-again</link><title>Health care reform in the United States: On the road to nowhere (again)?</title><description>* Health care reform in the United States: On the road to nowhere (again)? (Citations: 1)

Morris L. Barer, Theodore R. Marmor, Ellen M. Morrison

Journal: Social Science &amp; Medicine - SOC SCI MED , vol. 41, no. 4, pp. 453-460, 1995</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7083-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7083_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:33:17">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50382932/automatic-extraction-of-road-maps-determining-the-sealed-surface</link><title>Automatic extraction of road maps: Determining the sealed surface</title><description>* Automatic extraction of road maps: Determining the sealed surface (Citations: 1)

Kalyan Takru, Timo Rolf Bretschneider, Graham Leedham

...an incomplete skeletal representation of the road map, i.e. the basic road network, is available. for example...slightly over a tenth of the actual road network. in the second step the network is converted to the road map, i.e. the representation of areas that are...

Conference: Geoscience and Remote Sensing IEEE International Symposium - IGARSS , 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7083-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7083_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:34:31">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/26973505/flexibility-of-transport-choice-in-a-real-option-setting-an-experimental-case-study</link><title>Flexibility of Transport Choice in a Real-Option Setting: An Experimental Case Study</title><description>* Flexibility of Transport Choice in a Real-Option Setting: An Experimental Case Study (Citations: 1)

Laurent Denant-Boèmont, Sabrina Hammiche

...able to switch to using the road again until they reach the end of the line. on the contrary, highway choice is flexible in that the road hauler can change road at any time. building upon the irreversibility of one of the two choices, the authors build a model in...

Journal: Journal of Intelligent Transportation Systems - J INTELL TRANSPORT SYST , vol. 14, no. 3, pp. 140-153, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7083-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7083_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:35:37">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/14066337/south-county-redistricting-committee-completes-work-mountain-road-panel-to-meet-again-october-27</link><title>SOUTH COUNTY REDISTRICTING COMMITTEE COMPLETES WORK; MOUNTAIN ROAD PANEL TO MEET AGAIN OCTOBER 27</title><description>* SOUTH COUNTY REDISTRICTING COMMITTEE COMPLETES WORK; MOUNTAIN ROAD PANEL TO MEET AGAIN OCTOBER 27

Bob Mosier

...at school boundary lines for the area south of the south river has completed its work, while the panel studying the issue along the mountain road corridor in pasadena will meet again on monday, october 27, 2008. the mountain road corridor committee's meeting will be held at 7:00 p.m. at marley middle school, located...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7083-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7083_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:36:52">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/25147416/effect-of-traffic-pollution-on-respiratory-and-allergic-disease-in-adults-cross-sectional-and</link><title>Effect of traffic pollution on respiratory and allergic disease in adults: cross-sectional and longitudinal analyses</title><description>* Effect of traffic pollution on respiratory and allergic disease in adults: cross-sectional and longitudinal analyses

Mar Pujades-Rodríguez, Tricia McKeever, Sarah Lewis, Duncan Whyatt, John Britton, Andrea Venn

...background: epidemiological research into the role of traffic pollution on chronic respiratory and allergic disease has focused primarily on children. studies in adults, in...exposure to traffic: distance between the home and nearest main road and modelled outdoor nitrogen dioxide (no2) concentration at the home location. using multiple regression...

Journal: BMC Pulmonary Medicine - BMC Pulm Med , vol. 9, no. 1, pp. 42-11, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7083-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7083_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:38:00">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42176636/pollution-maps-of-grass-contamination-by-platinum-group-elements-and-polycyclic-aromatic</link><title>Pollution maps of grass contamination by platinum group elements and polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons from road traffic</title><description>* Pollution maps of grass contamination by platinum group elements and polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons from road traffic

Abdourahamane Tankari Dan-Badjo, Guido Rychen, Cecile Ducoulombier

...by placing ryegrass pots 0 m, 10 m, 25 m and 50 m from the road. this method thus allowed the measurement of pge and pah...respectively, from 0 to 50 m away from the road. the pollution maps show that the maximum depositions occur precisely along the road plan. the highest pollution levels of grasses...

Journal: Agronomy for Sustainable Development - AGRON SUSTAIN DEV , vol. 28, no. 4, pp. 457-464, 2008</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>