<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7084">Burn after reading review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:38:58" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7084-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7084_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:39:02">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5132109/metacognitive-monitoring-during-and-after-reading</link><title>Metacognitive Monitoring During and After Reading</title><description>* Metacognitive Monitoring During and After Reading (Citations: 3)

Keith W. Thiede, Thomas D. Griffin, Jennifer Wiley, Joshua S. Redford</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7084-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7084_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:40:12">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39834254/a-randomized-experiment-of-a-mixed-methods-literacy-intervention-for-struggling-readers-in-grades</link><title>A randomized experiment of a mixed-methods literacy intervention for struggling readers in grades 4–6: effects on word reading efficiency, reading comprehension and vocabulary, and oral reading fluency</title><description>* A randomized experiment of a mixed-methods literacy intervention for struggling readers in grades 4–6: effects on word reading efficiency, reading comprehension and vocabulary, and oral reading fluency

James S. Kim, Jennifer F. Samson, Robert Fitzgerald, Ardice Hartry

...examine the causal effects of read 180, a mixed-methods literacy intervention, on measures of word reading efficiency, reading comprehension and vocabulary, and oral reading fluency and (2) to examine...norm-referenced measures of word reading efficiency, reading comprehension, and vocabulary. although read 180 had a positive impact on oral reading fluency and attendance, these effects...

Journal: Reading and Writing - READ WRIT , vol. 23, no. 9, pp. 1109-1129, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7084-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7084_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:41:22">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48183291/a-global-perspective-on-teen-pregnancy</link><title>A Global Perspective on Teen Pregnancy</title><description>* A Global Perspective on Teen Pregnancy

Andrew L. Cherry, Lisa Byers, Mary Dillon

after reading this chapter and answering the...determinants of teenage pregnancy and review the gaps in knowledge and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7084-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7084_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:42:32">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/59327881/preparticipation-cardiovascular-screening-application-of-an-extended-italian-model-in-scotland</link><title>Preparticipation cardiovascular screening: application of an extended Italian model in Scotland</title><description>* Preparticipation cardiovascular screening: application of an extended Italian model in Scotland

W S Hillis, K Stewart, M Burns, A Kidd, J MacLean, P D Macintyre

...blood pressure &gt;140/90 after two readings.ecgsatrial arrhythmias and heart block...of pathology and require further review. echocardiography confirms changes consistent with...

Journal: British Journal of Sports Medicine - BRIT J SPORT MED , vol. 45, no. 2, pp. e2-e2, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7084-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7084_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:43:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39834214/the-role-of-reading-self-concept-and-home-literacy-practices-in-fourth-grade-reading-comprehension</link><title>The role of reading self-concept and home literacy practices in fourth grade reading comprehension</title><description>* The role of reading self-concept and home literacy practices in fourth grade reading comprehension (Citations: 4)

Tami Katzir, Nonie K. Lesaux, Young-Suk Kim

...an urban school district. children’s reading comprehension, word reading, and verbal ability were assessed using standardized measures. reading self-concept was assessed with...analyses demonstrated that all three reading self-concept subscales were positively related to reading comprehension after controlling for verbal ability and word reading skills, and aspects of hle...

Journal: Reading and Writing - READ WRIT , vol. 22, no. 3, pp. 261-276, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7084-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7084_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:44:54">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10820936/language-impairment-at-school-entry-and-later-reading-disability-connections-at-lexical-versus</link><title>Language Impairment at School Entry and Later Reading Disability: Connections at Lexical Versus Supralexical Levels of Reading</title><description>* Language Impairment at School Entry and Later Reading Disability: Connections at Lexical Versus Supralexical Levels of Reading (Citations: 17)

David L. Share, Mark Leikin

...lexical and supralexical processes in reading in order to gain a more fine-grained picture of the relationships between early language impairment and later reading disabilities. we hypothesized that early...unrelated to lexical aspects of reading. these data highlight the multicomponential nature of reading and suggest that different measures of reading cannot simply be regarded as...

Journal: Scientific Studies of Reading \- SCI STUD READ , vol. 8, no. 1, pp. 87-110, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7084-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7084_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:46:08">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39834292/children-s-oral-narrative-and-reading-skills-in-the-first-3-years-of-reading-instruction</link><title>Children’s oral narrative and reading skills in the first 3 years of reading instruction</title><description>* Children’s oral narrative and reading skills in the first 3 years of reading instruction (Citations: 1)

Elaine Reese, Sebastian Suggate, Jennifer Long, Elizabeth Schaughency

...link between oral narrative and reading skills in the first 3 years of reading instruction. study 1 consisted of...narratives correlated positively with their reading skill at this age, but narrative quality did not uniquely predict their reading skill 1 year later. study 2...

Journal: Reading and Writing - READ WRIT , vol. 23, no. 6, pp. 627-644, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7084-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7084_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:47:21">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5251405/long-term-effects-of-burning-slash-on-plant-communities-and-arbuscular-mycorrhizae-in-a-semi-arid</link><title>Long-term effects of burning slash on plant communities and arbuscular mycorrhizae in a semi-arid woodland</title><description>* Long-term effects of burning slash on plant communities and arbuscular mycorrhizae in a semi-arid woodland (Citations: 20)

Kristin E. Haskins, Catherine A. Gehring

...along 16 transects in: (i) burned slash pile sites; (ii) interspaces between burned slash piles; (iii) non-burned canopy sites; and (iv) non-burned interspaces. we quantified am colonization of dominant native and exotic plants in burned and non-burned areas. 3. burned areas had significantly fewer understorey plant species than non-burned areas, and exotic species were...

Journal: Journal of Applied Ecology - J APPL ECOL , vol. 41, no. 2, pp. 379-388, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7084-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7084_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:48:29">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/12959446/morphological-awareness-just-more-phonological-the-roles-of-morphological-and-phonological</link><title>Morphological awareness: Just “more phonological”? The roles of morphological and phonological awareness in reading development</title><description>* Morphological awareness: Just “more phonological”? The roles of morphological and phonological awareness in reading development (Citations: 53)

S. HÉLÈNE DEACON, JOHN R. KIRBY

...factors in three aspects of reading development: pseudoword reading, reading comprehension, and single word reading. morphological awareness contributed significantly to pseudoword reading and reading comprehension, after controlling prior measures of reading ability, verbal and nonverbal intelligence...

Journal: Applied Psycholinguistics - APPL PSYCHOLINGUIST , vol. 25, no. 02, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7084-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7084_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:49:34">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/36927481/early-development-of-neurophysiological-processes-involved-in-normal-reading-and-reading</link><title>Early Development of Neurophysiological Processes Involved in Normal Reading and Reading Disability: A Magnetic Source Imaging Study</title><description>* Early Development of Neurophysiological Processes Involved in Normal Reading and Reading Disability: A Magnetic Source Imaging Study (Citations: 15)

Panagiotis G. Simos, Jack M. Fletcher, Shirin Sarkari, Rebecca L. Billingsley, David J. Francis, Eduardo M. Castillo, Ekaterina Pataraia, Carolyn Denton, Andrew C. Papanicolaou

...but later benefited from systematic reading instruction and developed average-range reading skills at the end of...the brain mechanism that supported reading, the majority of high-risk responder children benefited from systematic reading instruction and developed adequate reading abilities....

Journal: Neuropsychology , vol. 19, no. 6, pp. 787-798, 2005</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>