<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7085">Adam rogers music</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:50:44" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7085-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7085_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:50:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57776326/a-poetic-epiphany-explorations-of-aesthetic-forms-of-representation</link><title>A Poetic Epiphany: Explorations of Aesthetic Forms of Representation</title><description>* A Poetic Epiphany: Explorations of Aesthetic Forms of Representation (Citations: 1)

Alexandra L. Adame, Larry M. Leitner, Roger M. Knudson

Alternative forms of representation, such as poetry, are becoming more widely used by qualitative researchers in disciplines such as anthropology, sociology, and psychology. Aesthetic forms of representation highlight the co-constructed nature of the research project, and in this article we will discuss how they can facilitate creative explorations of lived experience in qualitative research. We begin with an example ...

Journal: Qualitative Research in Psychology , vol. 8, no. 4, pp. 370-379, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7085-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7085_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:51:52">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/44787939/point-of-view-is-marching-band-in-step-with-music-education</link><title>Point of View: Is Marching Band in Step with Music Education?</title><description>* Point of View: Is Marching Band in Step with Music Education?

Theresa L. Mason, Ron Moulton, Bryan Burton, Dennis Johnson, George L. Rogers, Richard E. Goodstein, Lemuel Berry, Joseph Marzulli, Lynn H. Wilke, Myron Moss, Gordon W. Adams, Dick Haineshttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=44787939&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=Adam rogers music

Journal: Music Educators Journal , vol. 71, no. 9, 1985</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7085-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7085_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:53:10">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4666328/supporting-music-interaction-and-analysis-with-computers</link><title>Supporting Music Interaction and Analysis with Computers</title><description>* Supporting Music Interaction and Analysis with Computers

Adam Mikeal

...the relationship of computers to music is long and rich, dat- ing back to the earliest years of electronic music experimen- tation and musique concrete...in 1957, max matthews wrote music, the first software application for...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7085-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7085_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:54:23">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57701490/reviews-of-books</link><title>Reviews of Books</title><description>* Reviews of Books

Joseph A. Maiolo, Glyndwr William, Noam J. Zohar, Roger Beaumont, Hans-Friedrich Mueller, John J. Contreni, John H. Munro, David F. Allen, Richard von Glahn, Timothy J. Runyan, Blair B. Kling, Afaf Lutfi al-Sayyid Marsothttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=57701490&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=Adam rogers music

...35.00 (us). reviewed by roger beaumontrobert e. a. palmer. rome...

Journal: International History Review , vol. 21, no. 4, pp. 965-1125, 1999</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7085-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7085_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:55:35">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57701670/reviews-of-books</link><title>Reviews of Books</title><description>* Reviews of Books

Robert Mc C. Adams, Hew Strachan, R. M. Sheldon, Hugh Laracy, Arthur M. Eckstein, Marjorie Chibnall, Roger Collins, Felipe Fernández-Armesto, John Norris, Peter C. Perdue, Mark A. Burkholder, John M. Murrinhttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=57701670&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=Adam rogers music

...65.95 (cdn). reviewed by roger collinsfrancesc relano. the shaping of...watkins. proof through the night: music and the great war. berkeley...

Journal: International History Review , vol. 26, no. 2, pp. 349-466, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7085-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7085_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:56:40">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42478926/books-reviewed</link><title>Books reviewed</title><description>* Books reviewed

Roger Omond, D. N. Beach, Renfrew Christie, Y. Adam, Barry Munslow

...berliner, the soul of mbira, music and traditions of the shona...00)z. cervenka and b. rogers, the nuclear axis—secret collaboration...

Journal: Journal of Southern African Studies - J S AFR STUD , vol. 6, no. 1, pp. 132-137, 1979</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7085-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7085_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:57:49">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/3724393/self-disclosure-in-computer-mediated-communication-the-role-of-self-awareness-and-visual-anonymity</link><title>Self-disclosure in computer-mediated communication: The role of self-awareness and visual anonymity</title><description>* Self-disclosure in computer-mediated communication: The role of self-awareness and visual anonymity (Citations: 187)

Adam N. Joinson

Three studies examined the notion that computer-mediated communication (CMC) can be charac- terised by high levels of self-disclosure. In Study One, significantly higher levels of spontaneous self- disclosure were found in computer-mediated compared to face-to-face discussions. Study Two examined the role of visual anonymity in encouraging self-disclosure during CMC. Visually anonymous participants disclosed significantly ...

Journal: European Journal of Social Psychology - EUR J SOC PSYCHOL , vol. 31, no. 2, pp. 177-192, 2001</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7085-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7085_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 01:59:02">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/60573923/applying-agile-methodstoweapon-weapon-related-software</link><title>Applying Agile MethodstoWeapon/Weapon-Related Software</title><description>* Applying Agile MethodstoWeapon/Weapon-Related Software

D Adams, M Armendariz, M Blackledge, F Campbell, M Cloninger, L Cox, J Davis, M Elliott, K Granger, S Hans, C Kuhn, M Lacknerhttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=60573923&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=Adam rogers music

This white paper provides information and guidance to the Department of Energy (DOE) sites on Agile software development methods and the impact of their application on weapon/weapon-related software development. The purpose of this white paper is to provide an overview of Agile methods, examine the accepted interpretations/uses/practices of these methodologies, and discuss the applicability of Agile ...

Published in 2007.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7085-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7085_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:00:34">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42672999/social-learning-theory-and-music-piracy-the-differential-role-of-online-and-offline-peer-influences</link><title>Social learning theory and music piracy: the differential role of online and offline peer influences</title><description>* Social learning theory and music piracy: the differential role of online and offline peer influences (Citations: 2)

Sameer Hinduja, Jason R. Ingram

...the study of software and music piracy that occurs over the...peer influences on participation in music piracy. results based on data...

Journal: Criminal Justice Studies , vol. 22, no. 4, pp. 405-420, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7085-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7085_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:01:37">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/37002653/auditory-feedback-in-music-performance-the-role-of-transition-based-similarity</link><title>Auditory Feedback in Music Performance: The Role of Transition-Based Similarity</title><description>* Auditory Feedback in Music Performance: The Role of Transition-Based Similarity (Citations: 3)

Peter Q. Pfordresher

...one basis for similarity in musical keyboard performance: matches between sequential...auditory feedback. trained pianists and musically untrained persons produced simple tonal...

Journal: Journal of Experimental Psychology-human Perception and Performance - J EXP PSYCHOL-HUM PERCEP PERF , vol. 34, no. 3, pp. 708-725, 2008</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>