<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7093">What do i need to go fly fishing?</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:51:28" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7093-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7093_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:51:36">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/56602336/prognostic-factors-in-chronic-lymphocytic-leukemia-what-do-we-need-to-know</link><title>Prognostic factors in chronic lymphocytic leukemia—what do we need to know?</title><description>* Prognostic factors in chronic lymphocytic leukemia—what do we need to know?

Paula Cramer, Michael Hallek

...and inexpensive but lack accuracy to predict disease progression and survival...and gives guidance on how to implement novel prognostic tools in the clinical management of cll by applying the criteria of evidence, relevance, and simplicity to the selection of prognostic markers...

Journal: Nature Reviews Clinical Oncology - NAT REV CLIN ONCOL , vol. 8, no. 1, pp. 38-47, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7093-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7093_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:52:53">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/58205704/effluent-trading-to-improve-water-quality-what-do-we-know-today</link><title>Effluent trading to improve water quality: what do we know today?</title><description>* Effluent trading to improve water quality: what do we know today?

Sandra Rousseau

...thirdly there are tradable permits to use or consume water- borne resources, such as fish or the potential energy of...controls, the factory does not need to install abatement technologies to lower the discharge of that...

Published in 2001.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7093-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7093_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:54:00">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48515665/health-of-farmed-fish-its-relation-to-fish-welfare-and-its-utility-as-welfare-indicator</link><title>Health of farmed fish: its relation to fish welfare and its utility as welfare indicator</title><description>* Health of farmed fish: its relation to fish welfare and its utility as welfare indicator

Helmut Segner, Henrik Sundh, Kurt Buchmann, Jessica Douxfils, Kristina Snuttan Sundell, Cédric Mathieu, Neil Ruane, Hilde Toften, Lloyd Vaughan

...conditions modulate health of farmed fish are examined. if fish are subjected to unfavourable husbandry conditions, the resulting...units, thereby providing feasible tools to assess fish welfare under practical farming conditions. as the efforts to improve fish welfare and environmental sustainability lead to increasingly diverse solutions, in particular...

Journal: Fish Physiology and Biochemistry - FISH PHYSIOL BIOCHEM , pp. 1-21</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7093-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7093_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:55:07">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40227689/natural-fishing-experiments-in-marine-reserves-1983-1993-roles-of-life-history-and-fishing</link><title>Natural fishing experiments in marine reserves 1983 – 1993: roles of life history and fishing intensity in family responses</title><description>* Natural fishing experiments in marine reserves 1983 – 1993: roles of life history and fishing intensity in family responses (Citations: 58)

G. R. Russ, A. C. Alcala

...alone was also not sufficient to predict response to fishing. for chaetodontidae, effects of fishing conformed to expectations based on life history and fishing intensity at one island but...with intermediate vulnerability and subjected to intermediate to light fishing (f. scaridae, labridae and mullidae) displayed predictably weak responses to fishing, or counter-intuitive responses (e...

Journal: Coral Reefs - CORAL REEF , vol. 17, no. 4, pp. 399-416, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7093-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7093_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:56:22">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48161016/introduction-to-fish-bioacoustics</link><title>Introduction to Fish Bioacoustics</title><description>* Introduction to Fish Bioacoustics

Richard R. Fay, Arthur N. Popper, Jacqueline F. Webb

...examine all organisms from invertebrates to marine mammals when considering the underwater sound environment. although fish bioacoustics was an important component...history of the world” that: fishes verily have no eares, ne yet any holes to serve for hearing: and yet...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7093-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7093_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:57:31">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/58853414/letter-written-by-dorothy-a-six-clark-to-william-judson-clark-dated-march-15-1945</link><title>Letter Written by Dorothy A. Six Clark to William Judson Clark Dated March 15, 1945</title><description>* Letter Written by Dorothy A. Six Clark to William Judson Clark Dated March 15, 1945

Dorothy A. Six Clark

...field down there. it’s supposed to be awful from what i’ve heard. how do you like air gunnery. i suppose you do a lot. it’s miserable day...when we are together again. what a thing for the army to do. here we’ve practically just been married and what do they do\- separate us. at a time...

Published in 1945.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7093-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7093_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:58:40">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/59525576/return-after-flight-exploring-the-decision-making-process-of-sudanese-war-displaced-people-by</link><title>Return after flight : exploring the decision making process of Sudanese war-displaced people by employing an extended version of the theory of reasoned action</title><description>* Return after flight : exploring the decision making process of Sudanese war-displaced people by employing an extended version of the theory of reasoned action

Uffelen van J. G

...and practice, which are considered to lack responsiveness to the needs, initiatives and strategies of the...country · insecurity makes it difficult to have enough to eat. influential drivers for return were found to be: · food-secure within a...

Published in 2006.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7093-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7093_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 02:59:54">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/59505885/food-insecurity-in-fragile-lands-philippine-cases-through-the-livelihoods-lens</link><title>Food insecurity in fragile lands : Philippine cases through the livelihoods lens</title><description>* Food insecurity in fragile lands : Philippine cases through the livelihoods lens

J. R. Roa

...local businessmen has also contributed to the deterioration, and, in addition, has caused damage to the fish habitat leading to the disappearance of local fishing as an important liveli­hood. in...concerns can be drawn and need to be addressed in order to respond to the persistent food insecurity in...

Published in 2007.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7093-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7093_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:01:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/49322249/risk-based-modelling-of-diffuse-land-use-impacts-from-rural-landscapes-upon-salmonid-fry-abundance</link><title>Risk-based modelling of diffuse land use impacts from rural landscapes upon salmonid fry abundance</title><description>* Risk-based modelling of diffuse land use impacts from rural landscapes upon salmonid fry abundance (Citations: 1)

Sim M. Reaney, A. Louise Heathwaite, Lucy J. Dugdale

...has rarely addressed the extent to which such land covers are hydrologically connected, and hence able to deliver diffuse pollution, to the drainage network. however, there...develop suitable hydrological models, we need to conceptualise the process cascade. to do this, we need to know what matters to the organism being impacted by...

Journal: Ecological Modelling - ECOL MODEL , vol. 222, no. 4, pp. 1016-1029, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7093-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7093_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:02:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11164822/the-old-teacher-in-the-new-classroom-suggestions-for-effective-distance-instruction</link><title>The Old Teacher in the New Classroom: Suggestions for effective distance instruction</title><description>* The Old Teacher in the New Classroom: Suggestions for effective distance instruction (Citations: 1)

Karen HARDIN

...component. one technique we use to provide that comfort level to cameron university instructors is to provide a week of training. we state to the instructors that this week...in the "teacher" mode of "what do i know that you need to know." after the weeklong technology...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>