<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7095">iron in water supply</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:13:54" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7095-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7095_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:14:05">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57487280/contamination-of-local-water-supply-systems-in-suburban-belgrade</link><title>Contamination of local water supply systems in suburban Belgrade</title><description>* Contamination of local water supply systems in suburban Belgrade

Sava Petkovic, Enika Gregoric, Vesna Slepcevic, Srdjan Blagojevic, Bosko Gajic, Igor Kljujev, Branka Žarković, Nevenka Djurovic, Radovan Draskovic

...s inhabitants obtain their drinking water from these water supply systems. the water quality delivered by these local water supply systems is often compromised in terms of microbiological, physical and...residential areas which obtain their water supply from local water supply systems. some possible mitigation measures have been indicated. in the interim period, water must be disinfected continually, and...

Journal: Urban Water Journal - URBAN WATER J , vol. 8, no. 2, pp. 79-92, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7095-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7095_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:15:07">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57271648/removal-of-iron-from-water-supply-punta-gorda-florida</link><title>REMOVAL OF IRON FROM WATER SUPPLY, PUNTA GORDA, FLORIDA</title><description>* REMOVAL OF IRON FROM WATER SUPPLY, PUNTA GORDA, FLORIDA

Charles K. Dodd

Journal: Journal American Water Works Association - J AMER WATER WORK ASSN , vol. 23, no. 1, pp. 77-80, 1931</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7095-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7095_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:16:19">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40494478/contamination-of-water-supplies-by-volcanic-ashfall-a-literature-review-and-simple-impact-modelling</link><title>Contamination of water supplies by volcanic ashfall: A literature review and simple impact modelling</title><description>* Contamination of water supplies by volcanic ashfall: A literature review and simple impact modelling (Citations: 15)

C. Stewart, D. M. Johnston, G. S. Leonard, C. J. Horwell, T. Thordarson, S. J. Cronin

...effects of ashfall on natural waters and water supplies have focused mainly on the consequences of increased levels of turbidity (ash suspended in water), acidity and fluoride, with very...predicting effects of ashfall on water supplies using available information on ash composition.we reviewed reported impacts of historic eruptions on water supplies, drawing on case studies from...

Journal: Journal of Volcanology and Geothermal Research - J VOLCANOL GEOTHERM RES , vol. 158, no. 3, pp. 296-306, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7095-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7095_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:17:30">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/53712571/contamination-of-water-supplies-by-volcanic-ashfall-a-literature-review-and-simple-impact-modelling</link><title>Contamination of water supplies by volcanic ashfall: A literature review and simple impact modelling</title><description>* Contamination of water supplies by volcanic ashfall: A literature review and simple impact modelling

C. Stewart, D. M. Johnston, G. S. Leonard, C. J. Horwell, T. Thordarson, S. J. Cronin

...effects of ashfall on natural waters and water supplies have focused mainly on the consequences of increased levels of turbidity (ash suspended in water), acidity and fluoride, with very...predicting effects of ashfall on water supplies using available information on ash composition. we reviewed reported impacts of historic eruptions on water supplies, drawing on case studies from...

Journal: Journal of Volcanology and Geothermal Research - J VOLCANOL GEOTHERM RES , vol. 158, pp. 296-306, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7095-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7095_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:18:39">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6363026/legionella-pneumophila-in-residential-water-supplies-environmental-surveillance-with-clinical</link><title>Legionella pneumophila in residential water supplies: environmental surveillance with clinical assessment for Legionnaires' disease</title><description>* Legionella pneumophila in residential water supplies: environmental surveillance with clinical assessment for Legionnaires' disease (Citations: 23)

J. E. STOUT, YU V. L, Y. C. YEE, S. VACCARELLO, W. DIVEN, T. C. LEE

...from exposure to legionella pneumophila in residential water systems is uncertain. the residential water supplies of 218 members of the...the presence of legionella antigen in urine. for the immunocompetent hosts, the risk of contracting legionnaires' disease from exposure to contaminated household water supplies in the pittsburgh area appears to...

Published in 1992.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7095-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7095_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:19:50">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42666190/field-observations-of-iron-biofouling-in-water-supply-boreholes</link><title>Field observations of iron biofouling in water supply boreholes</title><description>* Field observations of iron biofouling in water supply boreholes (Citations: 2)

S. F. Tyrrel, P. Howsam

iron biofouling continues to be a significant cause of water supply borehole inefficiency and failure in the uk, yet there are...understanding of the causes of iron biofouling. this is, in part, due to the lack of systematic research into this subject in the uk. this communication outlines...

Journal: Biofouling , vol. 8, no. 1, pp. 65-69, 1994</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7095-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7095_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:21:00">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40206099/environmental-impact-of-drainage-of-dianzi-iron-mine-on-the-groundwater-system-of-the-dawu-water</link><title>Environmental impact of drainage of Dianzi Iron Mine on the groundwater system of the Dawu Water Supply Base</title><description>* Environmental impact of drainage of Dianzi Iron Mine on the groundwater system of the Dawu Water Supply Base

He Keqiang, Xu Guangming

...due to growing water extraction for industry and agriculture, the dawu water supply base, in the east of zibo, china, has been in a state of serious over...the mine draining on the water-supply environment of the dawu water supply base by using the numerical...

Journal: Environmental Earth Sciences - ENVIRON EARTH SCI , vol. 45, no. 8, pp. 1131-1136, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7095-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7095_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:22:07">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40681594/controlling-soluble-iron-and-manganese-in-a-water-supply-reservoir-using-hypolimnetic-oxygenation</link><title>Controlling soluble iron and manganese in a water-supply reservoir using hypolimnetic oxygenation</title><description>* Controlling soluble iron and manganese in a water-supply reservoir using hypolimnetic oxygenation (Citations: 8)

Paul A. Gantzer, Lee D. Bryant, John C. Little

...soluble metals such as iron (fe) and manganese (mn) often reach problematic levels in water-supply reservoirs during summer stratification following...of a hypolimnetic oxygenation system in carvins cove reservoir, a water-supply impoundment managed by the western virginia water authority. during oxygenation, manganese concentrations...

Journal: Water Research - WATER RES , vol. 43, no. 5, pp. 1285-1294, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7095-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7095_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:23:18">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48262562/water-pollution-and-riverbank-filtration-for-water-supply-along-river-nile-egypt</link><title>Water Pollution and Riverbank Filtration for Water Supply Along River Nile, Egypt</title><description>* Water Pollution and Riverbank Filtration for Water Supply Along River Nile, Egypt

Mohamed Shamrukh, Ahmed Abdel-Wahab

...especially when large quantities of water are treated. the two sources of potable water supply in egypt are groundwater and surface water, either from the river nile...are also widespread problems of iron, manganese, nitrate, and fecal coliform bacteria in the groundwater used for drinking water supply. riverbank filtration (rbf) is a water treatment technique that can improve...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7095-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7095_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:24:29">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/24394064/the-prevention-of-dull-shades-due-to-the-presence-of-iron-in-the-dyebath-when-dyeing-with-chrome</link><title>The Prevention of Dull Shades due to the Presence of Iron in the Dyebath, when Dyeing with Chrome Dyes Part I-Iron in the Water Supply</title><description>* The Prevention of Dull Shades due to the Presence of Iron in the Dyebath, when Dyeing with Chrome Dyes Part I-Iron in the Water Supply

C. L. Bird, E. Molloy

Journal: Journal of The Society of Dyers and Colourists - J SOC DYERS COLOUR , vol. 55, no. 11, pp. 560-564, 2008</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>