<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7098">tour moscow</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:30:51" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7098-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7098_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:30:57">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/37685151/foxp3-mrna-levels-are-decreased-in-peripheral-blood-cd4+-lymphocytes-from-hiv-positive-patients</link><title>FOXP3 mRNA Levels are Decreased in Peripheral Blood CD4+ Lymphocytes From HIV-Positive Patients</title><description>* FOXP3 mRNA Levels are Decreased in Peripheral Blood CD4+ Lymphocytes From HIV-Positive Patients (Citations: 35)

Francis Roubinet, Michel Abbal, Patrice Massip, Antoine Blancher

Journal: Jaids-journal of Acquired Immune Deficiency Syndromes - JAIDS , vol. 39, no. 4, pp. 381-385, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7098-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7098_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:32:03">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/14092980/impact-of-graft-mass-on-the-clinical-outcome-of-kidney-transplants</link><title>Impact of Graft Mass on the Clinical Outcome of Kidney Transplants</title><description>* Impact of Graft Mass on the Clinical Outcome of Kidney Transplants (Citations: 12)

Magali Giral, Jean Michel Nguyen, Georges Karam, Michelle Kessler, Bruno Hurault de Ligny, Mattias Buchler, Francois Bayle, Carole Meyer, Yohann Foucher, Marie Laure Martin, Pascal Daguin, Jean Paul Soulillouhttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=14092980&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=tour moscow

The effect of nephronic mass reduction of kidney transplants has not been analyzed specifically in a large cohort. Transplant injuries in cadaver kidney graft may have led to an underestimation of the magnitude of this factor. The aim of this study was to analyze the consequences of kidney mass reduction on transplantation outcome. The weights of 1142 kidney grafts were ...

Published in 2005.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7098-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7098_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:33:05">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/29766620/kidney-and-recipient-weight-incompatibility-reduces-long-term-graft-survival</link><title>Kidney and Recipient Weight Incompatibility Reduces Long-Term Graft Survival</title><description>* Kidney and Recipient Weight Incompatibility Reduces Long-Term Graft Survival (Citations: 6)

Magali Giral, Yohann Foucher, Georges Karam, Yann Labrune, Michelle Kessler, Bruno Hurault de Ligny, Mathias Buchler, Francois Bayle, Carole Meyer, Nathalie Trehet, Pascal Daguin, Karine Renaudinhttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=29766620&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=tour moscow

Long-term function of kidney allografts depends on multiple variables, one of which may be the compatibility in size between the graft and the recipient. Here, we assessed the long-term consequences of the ratio of the weight of the kidney to the weight of the recipient (KwRw ratio) in a multicenter cohort of 1189 patients who received a transplant ...

Journal: Journal of The American Society of Nephrology - J AMER SOC NEPHROL , vol. 21, no. 6, pp. 1022-1029, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7098-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7098_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:34:11">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/12451629/odd-parity-negative-modes-of-einstein-yang-mills-black-holes-and-sphalerons</link><title>Odd-parity negative modes of Einstein-Yang-Mills black holes and sphalerons</title><description>* Odd-parity negative modes of Einstein-Yang-Mills black holes and sphalerons (Citations: 7)

Mikhail S. Volkov, Dmitri V. Gal'tsov

An analytical proof of the existence of negative modes in the odd-parity perturbation sector is given for all known non-Abelian Einstein-Yang-Mills black holes. The significance of the normalizability condition in the functional stability analysis is emphasized. The role of the odd-parity negative modes in the sphaleron interpretation of the Bartnik-McKinnon solutions is discussed.

Journal: Physics Letters B - PHYS LETT B , vol. 341, no. 3, pp. 279-285, 1995</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7098-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7098_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:35:20">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/51239452/black-holes-in-einstein-yang-mills-theory</link><title>Black holes in Einstein-Yang-Mills theory</title><description>* Black holes in Einstein-Yang-Mills theory (Citations: 1)

M. S. Volkov, D. V. Gal'Tsov

The solutions of the self-consistent system of Einstein-Yang-Mills equations with gauge group SU(2) are studied. Analytical and numerical methods are used to construct a family of solutions describing black holes with an essentially non-Abelian gauge structure. This family is described by two parameters: the radius of the event horizon and a discrete number n corresponding ...

Published in 1990.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7098-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7098_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:36:27">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/32164420/rebound-in-complement-dependent-cytotoxicity-and-antibody-dependent-cell-mediated-cytotoxic</link><title>Rebound in complement-dependent cytotoxicity and antibody-dependent cell-mediated cytotoxic activity in primate serum after pig liver perfusion</title><description>* Rebound in complement-dependent cytotoxicity and antibody-dependent cell-mediated cytotoxic activity in primate serum after pig liver perfusion (Citations: 1)

A. Azimzadeh, H. Watier, C. Meyer, J.-M. Guillaumin, J.-P. Beller, R. Kieny, P. Zibolt, K. Boudjema, D. Jaeck, J. Cinqualbre, P. Wolf

HYPERACUTE REJECTION (HAR) of xenograft is initiated by humoral mechanisms including the recipient's xenoreactive natural antibodies (XNA) and complement proteins (C). The role of immunoglobulin M (IgM) XNA in xenograft rejection has been extensively studied and seems essential in C activation.1,2 In vitro, porcine endothelial cells are killed by complement-dependent cytotoxicity (CDC) after the binding of ...

Journal: Transplantation Proceedings - TRANSPLANT PROC , vol. 29, no. 5, pp. 2385-2386, 1997</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7098-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7098_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:37:38">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/54858026/use-of-high-intensity-focused-ultrasound-for-localized-activation-of-thermosensitive-liposomes-for</link><title>Use of high intensity focused ultrasound for localized activation of thermosensitive liposomes for drug delivery</title><description>* Use of high intensity focused ultrasound for localized activation of thermosensitive liposomes for drug delivery

Christophoros Mannaris, Eleni Efthymiou, Jean-Michel Escoffre, Ayache Bouakaz, Vera A. Khokhlova, Sergey A. Ilyin, Michalakis A. Averkiou

Journal: Journal of The Acoustical Society of America - J ACOUST SOC AMER , vol. 129, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7098-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7098_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:38:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/55857392/odd-parity-negative-modes-of-einstein-yang-mills-black-holes-and-sphalerons</link><title>Odd-parity negative modes of Einstein-Yang-Mills black holes and sphalerons</title><description>* Odd-parity negative modes of Einstein-Yang-Mills black holes and sphalerons

M. S. Volkov, D. V. Galtsov

An analytical proof of the existence of negative modes in the odd-parity perturbation sector is given for all known non-Abelian Einstein-Yang-Mills black holes. The significance of the normalizability condition in the functional stability analysis is emphasized. The role of the odd-parity negative modes in the sphaleron interpretation of the Bartnik-McKinnon solutions is discussed.

Journal: Physics Letters B - PHYS LETT B , vol. 341, pp. 279-285, 1995</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7098-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7098_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:39:56">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/56075160/odd-parity-negative-modes-of-einstein-yang-mills-black-holes-and-sphalerons</link><title>Odd-parity negative modes of Einstein-Yang-Mills black holes and sphalerons</title><description>* Odd-parity negative modes of Einstein-Yang-Mills black holes and sphalerons

Mikhail S. Volkov, Dmitri V. Gal'Tsov

An analytical proof of the existence of negative modes in the odd-parity perturbation sector is given for all known non-Abelian Einstein-Yang-Mills black holes. The significance of the normalizability condition in the functional stability analysis is emphasized. The role of the odd-parity negative modes in the sphaleron interpretation of the Bartnik-McKinnon solutions is discussed.

Journal: Physics Letters B - PHYS LETT B , vol. 341, pp. 279-285, 1995</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7098-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7098_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:40:55">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/44788685/the-moscow-sax-quintet-the-jazznost-tour</link><title>The Moscow Sax Quintet: The Jazznost Tour</title><description>* The Moscow Sax Quintet: The Jazznost Tour

Larador Productions

Journal: Music Educators Journal , vol. 77, no. 4, 1990</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>