<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7099">lecture manova</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:42:03" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7099-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7099_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:42:06">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39886052/tertiary-students-knowledge-of-their-own-learning-and-a-solo-taxonomy</link><title>Tertiary students' knowledge of their own learning and a SOLO Taxonomy</title><description>* Tertiary students' knowledge of their own learning and a SOLO Taxonomy (Citations: 17)

Gillian Boulton-Lewis

...869 students and their 21 lecturers in 12 courses in 5 faculties in the queensland university of technology (qut). the students and lecturers were asked to write a...held by tertiary students and lecturers and to use this to describe student knowledge to lecturers as a basis for planning...

Journal: Higher Education - HIGHER EDUC , vol. 28, no. 3, pp. 387-402, 1994</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7099-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7099_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:43:12">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/37439268/interaction-effects-of-teacher-enthusiasm-and-student-notetaking-on-recall-and-recognition-of</link><title>Interaction effects of teacher enthusiasm and student notetaking on recall and recognition of lecture content</title><description>* Interaction effects of teacher enthusiasm and student notetaking on recall and recognition of lecture content (Citations: 2)

Robert A. Stewart

...differences in students’ learning from lecture. three modes of student learning...crossed with two levels of lecturer enthusiasm (less enthusiastic, more enthusiastic) in a 3x2 manova design. dependent variables were simple...

Journal: Communication Research Reports , vol. 6, no. 2, pp. 84-89, 1989</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7099-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7099_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:44:16">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5085270/the-effects-of-strategic-notetaking-on-the-recall-and-comprehension-of-lecture-information-for-high</link><title>The Effects of Strategic Notetaking on the Recall and Comprehension of Lecture Information for High School Students with Learning Disabilities</title><description>* The Effects of Strategic Notetaking on the Recall and Comprehension of Lecture Information for High School Students with Learning Disabilities (Citations: 8)

Joseph R. Boyle, Mary Weishaar

Journal: Learning Disabilities Research and Practice , vol. 16, no. 3, pp. 133-141, 2001</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7099-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7099_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:45:48">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5336854/what-do-they-think-when-we-stack-them-in-a-comparative-analysis-of-student-perceptions-relating-to</link><title>What Do They Think When We Stack Them In? A Comparative Analysis Of Student Perceptions Relating To Large And Small Marketing Subjects</title><description>* What Do They Think When We Stack Them In? A Comparative Analysis Of Student Perceptions Relating To Large And Small Marketing Subjects

Wayne Binne, Wendy Kennedy

...selection, ability to learn and lecture attendance. students expressed a preference for the opportunity to choose from a number of lecture streams available in subjects with...to actively participate in large lectures than in small lecture environments....

Published in 2005.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7099-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7099_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:46:52">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/54762905/restructuring-the-cs-1-classroom-examining-the-effect-of-open-laboratory-based-classes-vs-closed</link><title>Restructuring the CS 1 classroom: Examining the effect of open laboratory-based classes vs. closed laboratory-based classes on Computer Science 1 students' achievement and attitudes toward computers and computer courses</title><description>* Restructuring the CS 1 classroom: Examining the effect of open laboratory-based classes vs. closed laboratory-based classes on Computer Science 1 students' achievement and attitudes toward computers and computer courses

Jean Foster Henderson

...a lab component within the lecture class so that half the class was reserved for lecture and half the class was...a multivariate analysis of variance (manova) via a multiple regression strategy was used to test the study's hypotheses. although the overall manova model was statistically significant, independent...

Published in 2007.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7099-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7099_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:47:46">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/58931197/aids-education-and-adolescent-sexual-self-efficacy-and-behavior</link><title>AIDS education and adolescent sexual self-efficacy and behavior</title><description>* AIDS education and adolescent sexual self-efficacy and behavior

John Sherry

...across the three groups (star, lecture, control). gender differences were also assessed. the dependent variables were analyzed using a multivariate analysis of variance (manova), whereas the data for self...students who were in the lecture and control groups. students in the lecture group displayed higher peer support...

Published in 1997.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7099-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7099_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:48:37">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/36011553/occupational-stress-and-strain-of-female-students-results-of-physiological-behavioral-and</link><title>Occupational stress and strain of female students: results of physiological, behavioral, and psychological monitoring</title><description>* Occupational stress and strain of female students: results of physiological, behavioral, and psychological monitoring (Citations: 13)

Michael Myrtek, Doris Weber, Georg Brügner, Wolfgang Müller

...comparison between typical study (seminar, lecture) and leisure activities (resting, conversation...arousing than studies. two-factorial manovas with the factors ‘stay’ (at...

Journal: Biological Psychology - BIOL PSYCHOL , vol. 42, no. 3, pp. 379-391, 1996</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7099-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7099_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:49:45">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/36916344/perceived-control-type-a-b-behavior-and-quality-of-instruction</link><title>Perceived Control, Type A/B Behavior, and Quality of Instruction</title><description>* Perceived Control, Type A/B Behavior, and Quality of Instruction (Citations: 3)

Raymond P. Perry, Kate Tunna

...then observed a half-hour lecture from either an unexpressive or expressive instructor. after the aptitude test they completed an attribution questionnaire, and after the lecture they took an achievement test...

Journal: Journal of Educational Psychology - J EDUC PSYCHOL , vol. 80, no. 1, pp. 102-110, 1988</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7099-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7099_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:50:59">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39842157/students-explanatory-schemas-and-the-quality-of-college-instruction-some-evidence-for-buffer-and</link><title>Students' explanatory schemas and the quality of college instruction: Some evidence for buffer and compensation effects</title><description>* Students' explanatory schemas and the quality of college instruction: Some evidence for buffer and compensation effects (Citations: 7)

Raymond P. Perry, Dieter J. Schonwetter, Jamie-Lynn Magnusson, C. Ward Struthers

...students then observed a videotaped lecture presented by a low- or...

Journal: Research in Higher Education - RES HIGH EDUC , vol. 35, no. 3, pp. 349-371, 1994</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7099-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7099_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 03:52:11">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/46353988/investigating-the-effectiveness-of-inquiry-instruction-on-the-motivation-of-different-learning</link><title>Investigating the Effectiveness of Inquiry Instruction on the Motivation of Different Learning Styles Students</title><description>* Investigating the Effectiveness of Inquiry Instruction on the Motivation of Different Learning Styles Students (Citations: 7)

Hsiao-Lin Tuan, Chi-Chin Chin, Chi-Chung Tsai, Su-Fey Cheng

...test interview. paired t-test, manova, analytic inductive methods were used...

Journal: International Journal of Science and Mathematics Education , vol. 3, no. 4, pp. 541-566, 2005</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>