<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7102">vlc mac</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:05:16" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7102-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7102_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:05:22">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/51817963/broadcast-of-four-hd-videos-with-led-ceiling-lighting-optical-wireless-mac</link><title>Broadcast of four HD videos with LED ceiling lighting: optical-wireless MAC</title><description>* Broadcast of four HD videos with LED ceiling lighting: optical-wireless MAC

Olivier Bouchet, Pascal Porcon, Eric Gueutier

...suitable for both irc and vlc. the vlc prototype is based on dmt...also present applications for the vlc and irc prototypes and measurement results regarding the mac layer....

Published in 2011.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7102-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7102_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:06:31">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4738413/robust-video-decoding-through-simultaneous-usage-of-residual-source-information-and-mac-layer-crc</link><title>Robust Video Decoding through Simultaneous Usage of Residual Source Information and MAC Layer CRC Redundancy</title><description>* Robust Video Decoding through Simultaneous Usage of Residual Source Information and MAC Layer CRC Redundancy (Citations: 6)

Cédric Marin, Pierre Duhamel, Khaled Bouchireb, Michel Kieffer

...residual source information (related to vlc codes and source characteristics) along with the mac layer crc redundancy in the...

Conference: Global Telecommunications Conference, . GLOBECOM . IEEE - GLOBECOM , pp. 2070-2074, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7102-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7102_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:07:40">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/18403498/mac-hypothesis-in-a-superstring-inspired-model</link><title>Mac hypothesis in a superstring inspired model</title><description>* Mac hypothesis in a superstring inspired model

Norihito Toyota

...e6 model based on the mac hypothesis. we find two kinds...are necessary to cause the mac condensation and two doublet fields...

Journal: Physics Letters B - PHYS LETT B , vol. 199, no. 3, pp. 407-411, 1987</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7102-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7102_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:08:51">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50995948/cross-layer-frame-synchronization-for-h-264-video-over-wimax</link><title>Cross-layer frame synchronization for H.264 video over WIMAX</title><description>* Cross-layer frame synchronization for H.264 video over WIMAX (Citations: 1)

Maria G. Martini, Chaminda T. E. R. Hewage

...several small medium access control (mac) packets may be aggregated to form a mac burst, forwarded to the physical...a mechanism to allow multiple mac protocol data units (pdus) belonging...

Conference: IEEE Workshop on Signal Processing Advances in Wireless Communications - SPAWC , pp. 1-5, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7102-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7102_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:09:50">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50679560/hybrid-wireless-optics-hwo-building-the-next-generation-home-network</link><title>Hybrid wireless optics (HWO): Building the next-generation home network</title><description>* Hybrid wireless optics (HWO): Building the next-generation home network (Citations: 12)

Olivier Bouchet, Mamdouh El Tabach, Mike Wolf, Dominic C. O'Brien, Grahame E. Faulkner, Joachim W. Walewski, Sebastian Randel, Martin Franke, Stefan Nerreter, Klaus-Dieter Langer, Jelena Grubor, Thomas Kamalakis

...wiresrdquo vision. a technology-independent mac layer will control this network...house/apartment, and further, this mac layer will allow the service...

Conference: International Symposium on Communication Systems, Networks and Digital Signal Processing - CNSDSP , 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7102-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7102_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:10:56">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6214238/robust-error-detection-for-h-264-avc-using-relation-based-fragile-watermarking</link><title>Robust Error Detection for H.264/AVC Using Relation Based Fragile Watermarking</title><description>* Robust Error Detection for H.264/AVC Using Relation Based Fragile Watermarking (Citations: 12)

Olivia Nemethova, Gonzalo Calvar Forte, Markus Rupp

...utilizes fragile watermarking applied at mac\- roblock level for the detection of errors in the decoded vlc stream. watermarking based approaches are...

Published in 2006.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7102-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7102_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:12:05">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4418439/an-approach-to-precisely-specifying-the-problem-domain-of-design-patterns</link><title>An approach to precisely specifying the problem domain of design patterns</title><description>* An approach to precisely specifying the problem domain of design patterns (Citations: 9)

Dae-kyoo Kim, Charbel El Khawand

The problem domain of a design pattern describes the problem context in which the pattern can be applied. In general, determining the applicability of a pattern to a particular problem heavily relies on the knowledge and experience the developer has with the pattern. This significantly limits the use of patterns. To address this issue, we propose an approach for rigorously ...

Journal: Journal of Visual Languages and Computing - VLC , vol. 18, no. 6, pp. 560-591, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7102-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7102_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:13:11">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/27759110/boutroux-curves-with-external-field-equilibrium-measures-without-a-minimization-problem</link><title>Boutroux curves with external field: equilibrium measures without a minimization problem</title><description>* Boutroux curves with external field: equilibrium measures without a minimization problem (Citations: 5)

Marco Bertola

...acrobat reader 7 or higher. mac users should also install a...with an external program like vlc or mplayer. all trademarks are...

Published in 2007.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7102-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7102_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:14:21">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/51015158/visible-light-communication-system-enabling-73-mb-s-data-streaming</link><title>Visible-light communication system enabling 73 Mb/s data streaming</title><description>* Visible-light communication system enabling 73 Mb/s data streaming (Citations: 1)

Olivier Bouchet, Pascal Porcon, Mike Wolf, Liane Grobe, Joachim W. Walewski, Stefan Nerreter, Klaus-Dieter Langer, Luz Fernández, Jelena Vucic, Thomas Kamalakis, G. Ntogari, E. Gueutier

...wires” vision. a technology-independent mac layer will control this network...light wireless link including a mac layer protocol adapted to optical...

Conference: IEEE Globecom Workshops - GC Wkshps , 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7102-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7102_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:15:27">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50780636/transparent-and-perceptually-enhanced-jpeg-image-encryption</link><title>Transparent and perceptually enhanced JPEG image encryption</title><description>* Transparent and perceptually enhanced JPEG image encryption (Citations: 1)

Bian Yang, Chong-Qing Zhou, C. Busch, Xia-Mu Niu

...cross-block varied-length codes (vlc) shuffling method perceptually enhanced by a reversible histogram spreading processing, which tends to smoothly re-distribute vlcs among spatial blocks in a...

Conference: International Conference on Digital Signal Processing - DSP , 2009</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>