<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7103">cystic fibrosis treatment</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:16:37" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7103-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7103_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:16:45">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/30443199/long-term-prognosis-of-patients-with-cystic-fibrosis-in-relation-to-early-detection-by-neonatal</link><title>Long term prognosis of patients with cystic fibrosis in relation to early detection by neonatal screening and treatment in a cystic fibrosis centre</title><description>* Long term prognosis of patients with cystic fibrosis in relation to early detection by neonatal screening and treatment in a cystic fibrosis centre (Citations: 50)

J E Dankert-Roelse, G J te Meerman

...birth cohorts of patients with cystic fibrosis was performed at the cystic fibrosis centre in groningen in close...but similar, in favour of treatment at a cystic fibrosis clinic. conclusions--expert management started immediately after an early diagnosis of cystic fibrosis by neonatal screening results in...

Journal: Thorax , vol. 50, no. 7, pp. 712-718, 1995</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7103-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7103_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:17:58">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/30705408/ribotype-analysis-of-pseudomonas-cepacia-from-cystic-fibrosis-treatment-centers</link><title>Ribotype analysis of Pseudomonas cepacia from cystic fibrosis treatment centers†</title><description>* Ribotype analysis of Pseudomonas cepacia from cystic fibrosis treatment centers† (Citations: 32)

J LIPUMA, J MORTENSEN, S DASEN, T EDLIND, D SCHIDLOW, J BURNS, T STULL

Journal: Journal of Pediatrics - J PEDIAT , vol. 113, no. 5, pp. 859-862, 1988</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7103-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7103_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:19:04">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/30276646/nitric-oxide-metabolites-in-cystic-fibrosis-lung-disease</link><title>Nitric oxide metabolites in cystic fibrosis lung disease</title><description>* Nitric oxide metabolites in cystic fibrosis lung disease (Citations: 52)

H Grasemann, I Ioannidis, R P Tomkiewicz, H de Groot, B K Rubin, F Ratjen

...lung tissue of patients with cystic fibrosis, the concentrations of nasal and exhaled no have recently been found to be decreased in cystic fibrosis. this could either be due...and sputum of 18 stable cystic fibrosis patients, 21 cystic fibrosis patients during a pulmonary exacerbation...

Journal: Archives of Disease in Childhood - ARCH DIS CHILD , vol. 78, no. 1, pp. 49-53, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7103-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7103_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:20:11">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/28163038/misidentification-of-burkholderia-cepacia-in-us-cystic-fibrosis-treatment-centers-an-analysis-of</link><title>Misidentification of Burkholderia cepacia in US Cystic Fibrosis Treatment Centers : An Analysis of 1,051 Recent Sputum Isolates</title><description>* Misidentification of Burkholderia cepacia in US Cystic Fibrosis Treatment Centers : An Analysis of 1,051 Recent Sputum Isolates (Citations: 48)

J. D. McMenamin

Journal: Chest , vol. 117, no. 6, pp. 1661-1665, 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7103-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7103_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:21:10">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/241762/designing-an-internet-based-collaborative-environment-for-cystic-fibrosis-treatment</link><title>Designing an Internet-based Collaborative Environment for Cystic Fibrosis Treatment</title><description>* Designing an Internet-based Collaborative Environment for Cystic Fibrosis Treatment (Citations: 3)

Marios Dikaiakos, Costas Christoyiannis, Antonis Papamichalopoulos, Eleni Pouliou, Theodoros Kyprianou, Serafeim Nanas, Ioannis Tsanakas, Antonios Rasidakis, Charalambos Roussos

...technologies in the battle against cystic fibrosis, which is a rare, fatal,genetic dicease. we present some basic facts about the disease, its epidemiologyand treatment conditions in greece and cyprus...of affairs vis-`a-vis cystic fibrosis and the humanand financial resources...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7103-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7103_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:22:11">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/49635067/disposable-versus-reusable-jet-nebulizers-for-cystic-fibrosis-treatment-with-tobramycin</link><title>Disposable versus reusable jet nebulizers for cystic fibrosis treatment with tobramycin</title><description>* Disposable versus reusable jet nebulizers for cystic fibrosis treatment with tobramycin

Laurent Vecellio, Mohamed E. Abdelrahim, Jerome Montharu, Julien Galle, Patrice Diot, Jean-Christophe Dubus

BackgroundJet nebulizers are commonly used to administer aerosolized tobramycin to CF patients. The aim of this study was to assess the performance of disposable jet nebulizers as an alternative to reusable nebulizers such as the Pari LC Plus.

Journal: Journal of Cystic Fibrosis \- J CYST FIBROS , vol. 10, no. 2, pp. 86-92, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7103-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7103_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:23:23">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/30422819/cystic-fibrosis-4-abnormalities-of-airway-epithelial-function-and-the-implications-of-the</link><title>Cystic fibrosis. 4. Abnormalities of airway epithelial function and the implications of the discovery of the cystic fibrosis gene</title><description>* Cystic fibrosis. 4. Abnormalities of airway epithelial function and the implications of the discovery of the cystic fibrosis gene

A W Cuthbert

...of ion transporting abnormalities in cystic fibrosis airway epithelium are now known...the cellular function of the cystic fibrosis transmembrane regulator must now be the major target in research on cystic fibrosis. strategies for treatment based on known cellular and...

Journal: Thorax , vol. 46, no. 2, pp. 124-130, 1991</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7103-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7103_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:24:36">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/24857914/identifying-novel-endpoints-for-cystic-fibrosis-clinical-trials-supported-by-the-cystic</link><title>Identifying Novel Endpoints for Cystic Fibrosis Clinical Trials * * Supported by the Cystic Fibrosis Foundation, the Mike McMorris Cystic Fibrosis Center, Grant #K23 RR018611-02 (NIH/NCRR), and Grant #MO1RR00069, General Clinical Research Centers Program, NCRR, NIH</title><description>* Identifying Novel Endpoints for Cystic Fibrosis Clinical Trials * * Supported by the Cystic Fibrosis Foundation, the Mike McMorris Cystic Fibrosis Center, Grant #K23 RR018611-02 (NIH/NCRR), and Grant #MO1RR00069, General Clinical Research Centers Program, NCRR, NIH

Scott D. Sagel

...clinical and translational research in cystic fibrosis (cf) is hampered by a...candidate anti-inflammatory and antimicrobial treatments. noninvasively obtained biomarkers are especially...

Journal: Advances in Pediatrics , vol. 52, pp. 115-127, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7103-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7103_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:25:46">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/14303698/kolem-nov-ch-l-ebn-ch-postup-zasahuj-c-ch-podstatu-cystick-fibr-zy-je-doplnit-nikoli</link><title>Úkolem nových léčebných postupů, zasahujících podstatu cystické fibrózy, je doplnit, nikoli nahradit, klasickou léčbu této nemoci. Nové léky se zaměřují na ovlivnění iontového transportu a tím vlastností hlenu, potlačení infekce i zánětu. Součástí komplexního léčebného postupu je vyhledávání a léčení komplikací. Obecně se věří, že moderní centralizovaná intenzivní léčba zlepší nejen prognózu ale i kvalitu života nemocných cystickou fibrózou. Klíčová slova: cystická fibróza, terapie infekce, protizánětlivá léčba, pankreatická substituce, nový farmakologický přístup. CURRENT AND FUTURE TREATMENT OF CYSTIC FIBROSIS The aim of new methods in cystic fibrosis treatment is to supplement not to replace classical cystic fibrosis treatment. New methods of therapy are focused on modifying the quality of mucus by means of altered ion transport, suppressing infection and fighting inflamma- tion. Searching for, preventing, and treating complications are important parts of the treatment. There is a g</title><description>* Úkolem nových léčebných postupů, zasahujících podstatu cystické fibrózy, je doplnit, nikoli nahradit, klasickou léčbu této nemoci. Nové léky se zaměřují na ovlivnění iontového transportu a tím vlastností hlenu, potlačení infekce i zánětu. Součástí komplexního léčebného postupu je vyhledávání a léčení komplikací. Obecně se věří, že moderní centralizovaná intenzivní léčba zlepší nejen prognózu ale i kvalitu života nemocných cystickou fibrózou. Klíčová slova: cystická fibróza, terapie infekce, protizánětlivá léčba, pankreatická substituce, nový farmakologický přístup. CURRENT AND FUTURE TREATMENT OF CYSTIC FIBROSIS The aim of new methods in cystic fibrosis treatment is to supplement not to replace classical cystic fibrosis treatment. New methods of therapy are focused on modifying the quality of mucus by means of altered ion transport, suppressing infection and fighting inflamma- tion. Searching for, preventing, and treating complications are important parts of the treatment. There is a g

Jana Bartošová, Libor Fila

Published in 2007.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7103-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7103_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 04:26:53">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/38435020/a-review-of-the-management-of-two-common-clinical-problems-found-in-patients-with-cystic-fibrosis</link><title>A Review of the Management of Two Common Clinical Problems Found in Patients with Cystic Fibrosis: Cystic Fibrosis-Related Diabetes and Poor Growth</title><description>* A Review of the Management of Two Common Clinical Problems Found in Patients with Cystic Fibrosis: Cystic Fibrosis-Related Diabetes and Poor Growth (Citations: 3)

Dana S. Hardin

...background: cystic fibrosis-related diabetes (cfrd) and glucose...

Journal: Hormone Research - HORM RES , vol. 68, no. 5, pp. 113-116, 2007</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>