<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7108">renting car seattle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:04:00" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7108-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7108_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:04:05">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/2463953/a-measurement-study-of-vehicular-internet-access-using-in-situ-wi-fi-networks</link><title>A measurement study of vehicular internet access using in situ Wi-Fi networks</title><description>* A measurement study of vehicular internet access using in situ Wi-Fi networks (Citations: 153)

Vladimir Bychkovsky, Bret Hull, Allen Miu, Hari Balakrishnan, Samuel Madden

...to network clients moving in cars at vehicular speeds? to answer...data also comes from a car in seattle). with a simple caching optimization...

Conference: Mobile Computing and Networking - MOBICOM , pp. 50-61, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7108-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7108_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:05:18">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10242245/n-2-cars-thermometry-and-o-2-lif-concentration-measurements-in-a-flame-under-electrically-induced</link><title>N 2 CARS thermometry and O 2 LIF concentration measurements in a flame under electrically induced microbuoyancy</title><description>* N 2 CARS thermometry and O 2 LIF concentration measurements in a flame under electrically induced microbuoyancy (Citations: 1)

M. J. Papac, D. Dunn-Rankin, C. B. Stipe, D. Lucas

...flows. to facilitate a large range of diagnostics on microgravity flames...coherent anti-stokes raman spectroscopy (cars) temperature measurements to show that...

Journal: Combustion and Flame - COMBUST FLAME , vol. 133, no. 3, pp. 241-254, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7108-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7108_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:06:25">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/12356857/andiamo-a-multiagent-system-to-provide-a-mobile-based-rideshare-service</link><title>ANDIAMO: A Multiagent System to Provide a Mobile-based Rideshare Service</title><description>* ANDIAMO: A Multiagent System to Provide a Mobile-based Rideshare Service

Francesco Sottini, Sameh Abdel-Naby, Paolo Giorgini

...a diverse range of architectures and concepts has been pro- posed by scholars within the theme of car pooling. most of these studies...use of location and available car seats, rideshare systems allow a substantial number of people to share car rides. these systems would, among...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7108-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7108_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:07:25">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/55683909/high-power-density-bipolar-lead-acid-battery-for-electric-vehicle-propulsion</link><title>High power density bipolar lead-acid battery for electric vehicle propulsion</title><description>* High power density bipolar lead-acid battery for electric vehicle propulsion

D. W. Kassekert, A. O. Isenberg, J. T. Brown

...service vehicles and personal commuter cars, with moderate cruising ranges of approximately 30 miles (48...recharge to extend the cruising range. a vehicle mission study was...

Published in 1976.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7108-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7108_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:08:25">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50172333/a-statistical-model-for-dynamic-ridematching-on-the-world-wide-web</link><title>A statistical model for dynamic ridematching on the World Wide Web</title><description>* A statistical model for dynamic ridematching on the World Wide Web (Citations: 4)

D. J. Dailey, D. Meyers

seattle smart traveler (sst) is an...quantifying ride-share matching and car pooling. the model is validated using the sst experimental results, and the model demonstrates that the car-pooling process is a quadratic...

Conference: International Conference on Intelligent Transportation - ITSC , 1999</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7108-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7108_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:09:36">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11631006/regressions-and-cures-of-melanoma-xenografts-following-treatment-with-monoclonal-antibody</link><title>Regressions and Cures of Melanoma Xenografts following Treatment with Monoclonal Antibody ÃŸ-Lactamase Conjugates in Combination with Anticancer Prodrugs</title><description>* Regressions and Cures of Melanoma Xenografts following Treatment with Monoclonal Antibody ÃŸ-Lactamase Conjugates in Combination with Anticancer Prodrugs (Citations: 12)

David E. Kerr, George J. Schreiber, Vivekananda M. Vrudhula, P. Svensson, Karl Erik, Peter D. Senter

Cephalosporin doxorubicin (C-Uox) and 7-(4-carboxybutanamido)- cephalosporin mustard (CCM) are prodrugs that are catalytically con verted by Enterobacter cloacae ÃŸ-lactamase(bL) to the active anticancer agents doxorubicin and phenylenediamine mustard, respectively. Both prodrugs were less cytotoxic to the 3677 human melanoma line than their respective drugs and were activated in an immunologically specific man ner by 96...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7108-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7108_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:10:46">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/47913027/consumer-finances-of-low-income-families</link><title>Consumer Finances of Low-Income Families</title><description>* Consumer Finances of Low-Income Families (Citations: 1)

Steven Garasky, Robert B. Nielsen, Cynthia Needles Fletcher

Serious challenges face families at the bottom of the economic ladder. The difficulties of balancing low incomes against expenditures are exacerbated by a lack of assets and insurance. We examine patterns of family asset ownership and health insurance coverage rates. A review of research focuses on selected dimensions of the financial environment of low-income families: the phenomena of the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7108-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7108_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:11:57">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48747212/a-prospective-study-of-brooding-and-reflection-as-moderators-of-the-relationship-between-stress-and</link><title>A Prospective Study of Brooding and Reflection as Moderators of the Relationship between Stress and Depressive Symptoms in Adolescence</title><description>* A Prospective Study of Brooding and Reflection as Moderators of the Relationship between Stress and Depressive Symptoms in Adolescence

Stephanie Cox, Kristyn Funasaki, Lauren Smith, Amy H. Mezulis

This study examined rumination as a moderator of the relationship between stress and depressive symptoms in a sample of adolescents using a multi-wave prospective design. Stressors were analyzed by domain (independent/dependent and interpersonal/noninterpersonal) and both brooding and reflection subtypes of rumination were examined as moderators. At the baseline assessment, 111 adolescents (ages 14–19) reported rumination and ...

Journal: Cognitive Therapy and Research - COGNITIVE THER RES , pp. 1-10</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7108-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7108_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:13:10">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/634878/design-and-evaluation-of-a-metropolitan-area-multitier-wireless-ad-hoc-network-architecture</link><title>Design and Evaluation of a Metropolitan Area Multitier Wireless Ad Hoc Network Architecture</title><description>* Design and Evaluation of a Metropolitan Area Multitier Wireless Ad Hoc Network Architecture (Citations: 62)

Jorjeta G. Jetcheva, Yih-chun Hu, Santashil Palchaudhuri, Amit Kumar Saha, David B. Johnson

...of city buses in the seattle, washington metropolitan area, on their...

Conference: Workshop on Mobile Computing Systems and Applications - WMCSA , pp. 32-43, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7108-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7108_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:14:22">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4315241/nericell-rich-monitoring-of-road-and-traffic-conditions-using-mobile-smartphones</link><title>Nericell: rich monitoring of road and traffic conditions using mobile smartphones</title><description>* Nericell: rich monitoring of road and traffic conditions using mobile smartphones (Citations: 72)

Prashanth Mohan, Venkata N. Padmanabhan, Ramachandran Ramjee

...vehicles (2-wheelers, 3-wheelers, cars, buses, etc.). to monitor road...

Conference: Conference On Embedded Networked Sensor Systems - SenSys , pp. 323-336, 2008</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>