<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7109">best place to eat pho in new york</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:15:29" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7109-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7109_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:15:34">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/41954508/crustal-structure-of-the-new-york-pennsylvania-area</link><title>Crustal Structure of the New York-Pennsylvania Area</title><description>* Crustal Structure of the New York-Pennsylvania Area (Citations: 6)

Jack Oliver, Robert Kovach, James Dorman

...models show that small variations in elastic properties from place to place may cause significant errors in the determi- nation of total...of crustal structure of the new york-pennsylvania area based largely on seismic information. the new experimental data consist of phase...

Journal: Journal of Geophysical Research , vol. 66, no. 1, pp. 215-225, 1961</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7109-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7109_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:16:44">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40846418/steep-oxygen-isotope-gradients-at-marble-metagranite-contacts-in-the-northwest-adirondack</link><title>Steep oxygen-isotope gradients at marble-metagranite contacts in the northwest Adirondack Mountains, New York, USA: products of fluid-hosted diffusion</title><description>* Steep oxygen-isotope gradients at marble-metagranite contacts in the northwest Adirondack Mountains, New York, USA: products of fluid-hosted diffusion (Citations: 26)

Ian Cartwright, John W. Valley

...whole rock delta18o = 11-12%) in the northwest adirondacks. oxygen- and carbon-isotope fractionations between coexisting minerals in the marbles and the metagranites...which fluid-producing reactions took place and an enhanced porosity was maintained. in the marbles, there is a progressive increase in the percentage of diopside and...

Journal: Earth and Planetary Science Letters - EARTH PLANET SCI LETT , vol. 107, no. 1, pp. 148-163, 1991</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7109-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7109_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:17:48">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6303586/predicting-the-temporal-and-spatial-probability-of-orographic-cloud-cover-in-the-luquillo</link><title>Predicting the temporal and spatial probability of orographic cloud cover in the Luquillo Experimental Forest in Puerto Rico using generalized linear (mixed) models</title><description>* Predicting the temporal and spatial probability of orographic cloud cover in the Luquillo Experimental Forest in Puerto Rico using generalized linear (mixed) models (Citations: 2)

Wei Wu, Charles Hall, Lianjun Zhang

...the area covered by clouds in each pixel on the map” in this paper) at any hour and any place is a function of three...the day until night, apparently in response to the movement of the lifting condensation level. two types of satellite images were available to calibrate our models: the higher...

Journal: Ecological Modelling - ECOL MODEL , vol. 192, no. 3, pp. 473-498, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7109-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7109_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:18:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40917652/urbanization-s-impact-on-sustained-yield-management-as-perceived-by-forestry-professionals-in</link><title>Urbanization's impact on sustained yield management as perceived by forestry professionals in central New York</title><description>* Urbanization's impact on sustained yield management as perceived by forestry professionals in central New York (Citations: 1)

Brandon W. Vickery, René H. Germain, Eddie Bevilacqua

...that population density was the best predictor of reduced commercial harvest opportunity. we applied similar methodologies in central new york to assess urbanization's impact on...urbanization on the forest resource in central new york. unlike other regions of the united states, central new york's growth pattern is characterized...

Journal: Forest Policy and Economics - FOREST POLICY ECON , vol. 11, no. 1, pp. 42-49, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7109-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7109_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:19:42">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/58746109/special-issue-on-applied-neurodynamics-from-neural-dynamics-to-neural-engineering</link><title>Special issue on applied neurodynamics: from neural dynamics to neural engineering</title><description>* Special issue on applied neurodynamics: from neural dynamics to neural engineering

Hillel J Chiel, Peter J Thomas

...is, as we agreed provisionally to say, knowledge which is likely, now or in the comparatively near future, to contribute to the material comfort of mankind...work. mathematicians became increasingly interested in biological problems in general, and in the function of the nervous system in particular, during the latter part...

Journal: Journal of Neural Engineering - J NEURAL ENG , vol. 8, no. 6, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7109-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7109_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:20:49">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/58722202/biodiversity-and-global-health-hubris-humility-and-the-unknown</link><title>Biodiversity and global health—hubris, humility and the unknown</title><description>* Biodiversity and global health—hubris, humility and the unknown

Carolyn Stephens

...and mysteriously night-flowering [1]. new to science, and with so much more to understand, this flower is threatened by deforestation [2]. also in november 2011, a survey of...if the global population chooses to change their view of the planet and their place in it, and to reduce resource consumption to sustainable levels, we do not...

Journal: Environmental Research Letters - ENVIRON RES LETT , vol. 7, no. 1, 2012</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7109-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7109_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:21:52">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/32163289/cornelius-rea-agnew-m-d-and-the-code-of-ethics-of-the-medical-society-of-the-state-of-new-york</link><title>Cornelius Rea Agnew, M.D., and the code of ethics of the medical society of the State of New York</title><description>* Cornelius Rea Agnew, M.D., and the code of ethics of the medical society of the State of New York

Frank W. Newell

...cornelius rea agnew was born in 1830 in new yolzk city to a prominent merchant family. he died there in 1888 of acute appendicitis. agnew...surgeongeneral of the state of new york. when dr. vander poel of kinderhook, new york, resumed that position in 1861 agnew was named director...

Journal: Documenta Ophthalmologica - DOC OPHTHALMOL , vol. 94, no. 1, pp. 179-190, 1997</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7109-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7109_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:22:50">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/60522039/development-and-application-of-improved-techniques-for-the-evaluation-of-electric-energy</link><title>Development and application of improved techniques for the evaluation of electric energy alternatives for New York State</title><description>* Development and application of improved techniques for the evaluation of electric energy alternatives for New York State

Wicks

...of electric generation alternatives for new york state are examined. the development phase combines the best available computer software, computer hardware...condition that forces a shift in traditional planning guidelines in new york state is the extreme increase in oil price and the high...

Published in 1976.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7109-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7109_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:23:57">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/2142581/chase-studies-of-particulate-emissions-from-in-use-new-york-city-vehicles</link><title>Chase Studies of Particulate Emissions from in-use New York City Vehicles</title><description>* Chase Studies of Particulate Emissions from in-use New York City Vehicles (Citations: 101)

Manjula R. Canagaratna, John T. Jayne, David A. Ghertner, Scott Herndon, Quan Shi, Jose L. Jimenez, Philip J. Silva, Paul Williams, Thomas Lanni, Frank Drewnick, Kenneth L. Demerjian, Charles E. Kolbhttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=2142581&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=best place to eat pho in new york

...matter (pm) and gaseous pollutants in urban environments. few studies have characterized both gaseous and pm emissions from individual in-use vehicles under real-world driving conditions. here we describe chase vehicle studies in which on-road emissions from individual vehicles were measured in real time within seconds of...

Journal: Aerosol Science and Technology - AEROSOL SCI TECH , vol. 38, no. 6, pp. 555-573, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7109-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7109_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 05:25:11">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/61315456/district-heating-cooling-potential-in-new-york-city-phase-1-final-report</link><title>District heating/cooling potential in New York City. phase 1. Final report</title><description>* District heating/cooling potential in New York City. phase 1. Final report

G. T. McLoughlin, R. P. Kuo, J. Karol

...most of the property over to new york city more than a decade...hot water will be sold to the new york city housing authority to heat between 3,500 and...

Published in 1983.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>