<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7111">what is the starting salary for a recruiter</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:02:49" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7111-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7111_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:02:57">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/59559802/achtkarspeler-jwg-ers-en-in-de-streekeigen-kultuer-undersyk-nei-de-ynfloed-fan-de-streekeigen</link><title>Achtkarspeler JWG-ers en in de streekeigen kultuer. Undersyk nei de ynfloed fan de streekeigen kultuer fan Achtkarspelen op it h_lden en dragen fan dielnimmers oan de JWG-wet</title><description>* Achtkarspeler JWG-ers en in de streekeigen kultuer. Undersyk nei de ynfloed fan de streekeigen kultuer fan Achtkarspelen op it h_lden en dragen fan dielnimmers oan de JWG-wet

C. H. A. Verhaar

...label of 'jwg client' (not the label, therefore, of a real employee).d) integration5 what is the relevance of the results of the study in the light of human capital theory...and woman was confirmed in the interviews and further detailed. the man is the bread-winner and the place of the woman is in the home, at least if there...

Published in 1997.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7111-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7111_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:03:28">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/59504817/dairy-stock-development-and-milk-production-with-smallholders</link><title>Dairy stock development and milk production with smallholders</title><description>* Dairy stock development and milk production with smallholders

Jong de R

...are in use such as the dutch winter milk price, the town milk price in oceania, and the premium in the usa that increases with the distance from wisconsin.dairy production...desires and financial sacrifices it is prepared to avail for either supporting the working producer or the enjoying consumer. a cashflow from city-have's...

Published in 1996.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7111-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7111_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:03:51">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48213402/are-you-attracted-do-you-intend-to-pursue-a-recruiting-policy-capturing-study</link><title>Are You Attracted? Do You Intend to Pursue? A Recruiting Policy-Capturing Study</title><description>* Are You Attracted? Do You Intend to Pursue? A Recruiting Policy-Capturing Study (Citations: 24)

Lynda Aiman-Smith, Talya N. Bauer, Daniel M. Cable

...this study examines the relative importance of four factors...that factors determining potential job recruits' attraction to an organization may not equate with the factors that prompt job pursuit intentions. using a sample of business students and...

Journal: Journal of Business and Psychology - J BUS PSYCHOL , vol. 16, no. 2, pp. 219-237, 2001</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7111-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7111_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:04:06">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/47821364/the-limits-of-human-endurance-what-is-the-greatest-endurance-performance-of-all-time-which</link><title>The Limits of Human Endurance: What is the Greatest Endurance Performance of All Time? Which Factors Regulate Performance at Extreme Altitude?</title><description>* The Limits of Human Endurance: What is the Greatest Endurance Performance of All Time? Which Factors Regulate Performance at Extreme Altitude? (Citations: 1)

Timothy David Noakes

...performance of all time. interestingly, the dogs that provided the pulling power for norwegian roald amundsen’s team that was the first to reach the south pole, 35 days before...or skeletal muscle hypoxia as is usually argued, but is more likely the result of a process integrated hypoxia and the circulation chapter 0 centrally in...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7111-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7111_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:04:22">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57507026/what-is-the-nature-of-the-self-defining-memories-of-repression-prone-individuals</link><title>What is the Nature of the Self-defining Memories of Repression-prone Individuals?</title><description>* What is the Nature of the Self-defining Memories of Repression-prone Individuals?

Claudia Lardi, Paolo Ghisletta, Martial Van der Linden

the present study investigates the ability to predict various self...between 27 and 43 years) recruited from the general population were analyzed with multilevel models. the main results showed that repression...

Journal: Self and Identity - SELF IDENTITY , vol. 11, no. 4, pp. 492-515, 2012</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7111-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7111_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:04:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57506758/what-is-the-nature-of-the-self-defining-memories-of-repression-prone-individuals</link><title>What Is the Nature of the Self-defining Memories of Repression-prone Individuals?</title><description>* What Is the Nature of the Self-defining Memories of Repression-prone Individuals?

Claudia Lardi, Paolo Ghisletta, Martial Van der Linden

the present study investigates the ability to predict various self...between 27 and 43 years) recruited from the general population were analyzed with multilevel models. the main results showed that repression...

Journal: Self and Identity - SELF IDENTITY , vol. ahead-of-p, no. ahead-of-p, pp. 000-000, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7111-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7111_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:05:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/59288545/veterinary-assistants-salaries-what-is-the-package-worth</link><title>Veterinary assistants' salaries \- what is the package worth?</title><description>* Veterinary assistants' salaries \- what is the package worth?

Christine Shield

...one earlier this year, investigating the salaries earned by veterinary graduates in their first job. the aim has been to give...they may be used as a starting point in salary negotiations between employer and employee. in this article, christine shield presents some of the findings....

Published in 1997.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7111-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7111_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:05:38">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48797479/stem-cell-therapy-for-incontinence-where-are-we-now-what-is-the-realistic-potential</link><title>Stem Cell Therapy for Incontinence: Where Are We Now? What is the Realistic Potential?</title><description>* Stem Cell Therapy for Incontinence: Where Are We Now? What is the Realistic Potential?

Charuspong Dissaranan, Michelle A. Cruz, Bruna M. Couri, Howard B. Goldman, Margot S. Damaser

...stem cells and their derivatives for the prevention and treatment of sui has been performed to test the effect of cell source and...before stem cell therapy becomes a possible treatment for sui, although the future of this therapy looks...

Journal: Current Urology Reports , pp. 1-9</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7111-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7111_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:06:08">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/37079455/progeria-syndromes-and-ageing-what-is-the-connection</link><title>Progeria syndromes and ageing: what is the connection?</title><description>* Progeria syndromes and ageing: what is the connection? (Citations: 11)

Christopher R. Burtner, Brian K. Kennedy

...accelerated forms of human ageing. the answer requires a better understanding of the normal ageing process and the molecular pathology underlying these rare...studies of longevity, lead to a hypothesis whereby progeria syndromes accelerate a subset of the pathological changes that together drive the normal ageing process....

Journal: Nature Reviews Molecular Cell Biology - NAT REV MOL CELL BIOL , vol. 11, no. 8, pp. 567-578, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7111-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7111_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-21 14:06:28">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/59573609/een-demografisch-mozaiek-indonesi-1880-1942</link><title>Een demografisch mozaiek, Indonesië 1880-1942</title><description>* Een demografisch mozaiek, Indonesië 1880-1942

A. J. Gooszen

...the number of inhabitants or the size of the area involved in the redivision. this is a serious impediment to the reconstruction of demographic trends.the administrative entities which are used...characterized by inmigration as well. the origin of the inmigrants in the first region is not specified in the census, but the people attracted to the southeastern region are known to...

Published in 1994.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>