<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7118">part time jobs texas city</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:20:53" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7118-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7118_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:20:59">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6910102/many-pediatric-residents-seek-and-obtain-part-time-positions</link><title>Many Pediatric Residents Seek and Obtain Part-time Positions</title><description>* Many Pediatric Residents Seek and Obtain Part-time Positions (Citations: 4)

William L. Cull, Gretchen L. Caspary, Lynn M. Olson

...reported that they applied for part-time positions and 21% actually accepted part-time positions. residents who applied for part-time positions were more likely to report moderate or considerable job search difficulty (part-time: 36%; full-time: 25%). the average starting salary for residents who accepted part-time jobs was almost $34 000 less...

Published in 2010.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7118-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7118_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:22:07">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/58338741/estudio-emp-rico-en-poblaci-n-femenina-sobre-condiciones-de-aceptaci-n-de-empleo-a-tiempo-parcial</link><title>Estudio empírico en población femenina sobre condiciones de aceptación de empleo a tiempo parcial: Un modelo de decisiones múltiples./Empirical Study of the Conditions for Taking a Part Time Job Among Women: A Multiple Decision Model</title><description>* Estudio empírico en población femenina sobre condiciones de aceptación de empleo a tiempo parcial: Un modelo de decisiones múltiples./Empirical Study of the Conditions for Taking a Part Time Job Among Women: A Multiple Decision Model

C. SAURINA CANALS, M. SAEZ ZAFRA

...year old, on working half time shifts. in the empirical analysis...of a medium-size catalan city. our main findings suggest that...

Published in 2004.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7118-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7118_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:23:21">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57223796/influences-of-trait-negative-affect-and-situational-similarity-on-correlation-and-convergence-of</link><title>Influences of Trait Negative Affect and Situational Similarity on Correlation and Convergence of Work Attitudes and Job Stress Perceptions Across Two Jobs</title><description>* Influences of Trait Negative Affect and Situational Similarity on Correlation and Convergence of Work Attitudes and Job Stress Perceptions Across Two Jobs

John Schaubroeck, Timothy A. Judge, Lewis A. Taylor

...separate organization. correlations of corresponding job attitudes and perceived stressors across the two jobs were signtjicant,. but not of high magnitude. for both job stressors and work attitudes, trait...correlated more strongly with full-time job attitudes than with part-time job attitudes. we discuss implications for...

Journal: Journal of Management - J MANAGE , vol. 24, no. 4, pp. 553-576, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7118-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7118_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:24:24">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39736197/part-time-work-and-the-gender-division-of-labor</link><title>Part-Time Work and the Gender Division of Labor</title><description>* Part-Time Work and the Gender Division of Labor (Citations: 8)

Gretchen Webber, Christine Williams

...care arrangements when they work part-time. three factors emerged as most important in understanding how part-time work can shape mothers’ experiences of the gender division of labor: pathway to part-time work, work location, and work schedule. depending on these factors, part-time work may be experienced as...

Journal: Qualitative Sociology - QUAL SOCIOL , vol. 31, no. 1, pp. 15-36, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7118-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7118_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:25:39">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42654777/an-investigation-into-the-inter-relationship-among-work-family-and-part-time-education-in-hong-kong</link><title>An investigation into the inter-relationship among work, family and part-time education in Hong Kong</title><description>* An investigation into the inter-relationship among work, family and part-time education in Hong Kong

Humphry Hung, Reuben Mondejar

part-time tertiary education at both undergraduate and graduate levels are becoming more and more popular. in pursuing part-time studies, students must use their...about 500 postgraduate and undergraduate part-time university students (who had full-time jobs) in hong kong were surveyed...

Journal: Journal of Vocational Education &amp; Training , vol. 53, no. 4, pp. 561-576, 2001</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7118-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7118_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:26:56">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/29720381/part-time-physicians-prevalent-connected-and-satisfied</link><title>Part-Time Physicians…Prevalent, Connected, and Satisfied</title><description>* Part-Time Physicians…Prevalent, Connected, and Satisfied (Citations: 9)

Hilit F. Mechaber, Rachel B. Levine, Linda Baier Manwell, Marlon P. Mundt, Mark Linzer

...care workforce is evolving and part-time practice is increasing. the objective of this work is to determine the relationship between part-time status, workplace conditions, and physician...and trust. responses compared by part-time and full-time physician status; 2-part regression analyses assessed outcomes associated with part-time status. of 751 physicians contacted...

Journal: Journal of General Internal Medicine - J GEN INTERN MED , vol. 23, no. 3, pp. 300-303, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7118-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7118_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:28:16">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/44556967/mothers-in-good-and-bad-part-time-jobsdifferent-problems-same-results</link><title>Mothers in “Good” and “Bad” Part-time JobsDifferent Problems, Same Results</title><description>* Mothers in “Good” and “Bad” Part-time JobsDifferent Problems, Same Results (Citations: 6)

Gretchen Webber, Christine Williams

part-time work schedules are a popular...women in professional and secondary part-time jobs, drawing on 60 in-depth interviews with mothers working in such “good” and “bad” jobs. we find that mothers at...

Journal: Gender &amp; Society - GENDER SOC , vol. 22, no. 6, pp. 752-777, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7118-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7118_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:29:30">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5503365/school-students-and-part-time-work</link><title>School students and part-time work</title><description>* School students and part-time work (Citations: 1)

Lyn Robinson

...combine study at school with part-time employment outside of school hours has been widely observed, although estimates of how many school students have jobs vary greatly. furthermore, while the...incidence of students who have part-time jobs during the school year - is...

Published in 1996.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7118-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7118_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:30:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48506182/jobs-for-mothers-married-women-s-labor-force-reentry-and-part-time-temporary-employment-in-japan</link><title>Jobs for Mothers: Married Women's Labor Force Reentry and Part-Time, Temporary Employment in Japan</title><description>* Jobs for Mothers: Married Women's Labor Force Reentry and Part-Time, Temporary Employment in Japan (Citations: 3)

Wei-hsin Yu

...japan and their concentration in part-time or temporary employment. existing explanations attribute women's concentration in part-time employment too narrowly to supply...women and the demand for part-time workers have increased, but these conditions channel middle-aged women into part-time or temporary employment only when...

Journal: Sociological Forum - SOCIOL FORUM , vol. 17, no. 3, pp. 493-523, 2002</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7118-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7118_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:31:38">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42663216/higher-education-students-in-part-time-work-in-a-chinese-city</link><title>Higher education students in part-time work in a Chinese city</title><description>* Higher education students in part-time work in a Chinese city

Keith Morrison

...this article discusses students taking part-time work whilst studying higher education...negative aspects and outcomes of part-time work by he students. the paper reviews literature on he students working part-time in the uk and the...

Journal: Evaluation &amp; Research in Education , vol. 22, no. 2-4, pp. 121-144, 2009</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>