<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7119">chocolate photo</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:32:54" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7119-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7119_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:32:57">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/35715246/c-l-mcneil-editor-chocolate-in-mesoamerica-a-cultural-history-of-cacao-university-press-of</link><title>C.L. McNeil, Editor, Chocolate in Mesoamerica (A Cultural History of Cacao), University Press of Florida, USA (2006) 21 Chapters, in four parts, 542 pp., 91 Photos b &amp; w, 97 drawings and maps and 14 tables, Hard cover, Price: $75, ISBN 13: 978-0-8130-2953-8</title><description>* C.L. McNeil, Editor, Chocolate in Mesoamerica (A Cultural History of Cacao), University Press of Florida, USA (2006) 21 Chapters, in four parts, 542 pp., 91 Photos b &amp; w, 97 drawings and maps and 14 tables, Hard cover, Price: $75, ISBN 13: 978-0-8130-2953-8

A ANDRADECETTO

Journal: Journal of Ethnopharmacology - J ETHNOPHARMACOL , vol. 115, no. 2, pp. 336-336, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7119-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7119_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:34:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/13704463/photo</link><title>PHOTO</title><description>* PHOTO

ROBERT A. HAMILTON, N. JOHN SCHMITT

...and black merlins. the featured photo on the back cover shows...two birds in the featured photo). adult males of columbarius are...

Published in 2000.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7119-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7119_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:35:15">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48398939/automatic-optosensing-device-based-on-photo-induced-fluorescence-for-determination-of-piceid-in</link><title>Automatic optosensing device based on photo-induced fluorescence for determination of piceid in cocoa-containing products</title><description>* Automatic optosensing device based on photo-induced fluorescence for determination of piceid in cocoa-containing products

Lucía Molina-García, Antonio Ruiz-Medina, Maria Luisa Fernández-de Córdova

...cocoa-containing products by using photo-induced fluorescence and the aid...piceid in cocoa powder, dark chocolate and milk chocolate. the quantification limits were 1...

Journal: Analytical and Bioanalytical Chemistry - ANAL BIOANAL CHEM , vol. 399, no. 2, pp. 965-972, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7119-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7119_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:36:31">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6729064/phototrophs-in-high-iron-concentration-microbial-mats-physiological-ecology-of-phototrophs-in-an</link><title>Phototrophs in High-Iron-Concentration Microbial Mats: Physiological Ecology of Phototrophs in an Iron-Depositing Hot Spring</title><description>* Phototrophs in High-Iron-Concentration Microbial Mats: Physiological Ecology of Phototrophs in an Iron-Depositing Hot Spring (Citations: 26)

B. K. PIERSON, M. N. PARENTEAU, B. M. GRIFFIN

...studying the interactions of microbial photo\- synthesis and iron deposition and...

Published in 1999.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7119-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7119_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:37:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4984477/the-electronic-nose-applied-to-dairy-products-a-review</link><title>The electronic nose applied to dairy products: a review</title><description>* The electronic nose applied to dairy products: a review (Citations: 78)

S. Ampuero, J. O. Bosset

The state-of-the-art and current trends in the development of “aroma” analysis with electronic noses are reviewed with special reference to applications to dairy-products. Some of the reported problems with electronic noses have recently been reduced, e.g. the correction/reduction of signal drift, the influence of humidity and temperature. New promising and reproducible sensor manufacturing techniques ...

Journal: Sensors and Actuators B-chemical - SENSOR ACTUATOR B-CHEM , vol. 94, no. 1, pp. 1-12, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7119-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7119_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:38:57">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5322146/murine-hermansky-pudlak-syndrome-genes-regulators-of-lysosome-related-organelles</link><title>Murine Hermansky-Pudlak syndrome genes: regulators of lysosome-related organelles</title><description>* Murine Hermansky-Pudlak syndrome genes: regulators of lysosome-related organelles (Citations: 75)

Wei Li, Michael E. Rusiniak, Sreenivasulu Chintala, Rashi Gautam, Edward K. Novak, Richard T. Swank

Summary Inthemouse,atleast16genesregulatevesicletrafficking to specialized lysosome-related organelles, including platelet dense granules and melanosomes. Fourteen of these genes have been identified by positional cloning. All 16 mouse mutants are models for the genetically heterogeneoushumandisease,Hermansky-PudlakSyn- drome (HPS). Five HPS genes encode known vesicle trafficking proteins. Nine genes are novel, are found only in higher eukaryotes and encode members of ...

Journal: Bioessays , vol. 26, no. 6, pp. 616-628, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7119-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7119_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:40:16">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6781239/an-experimental-evaluation-of-a-group-versus-computer-based-intervention-to-improve-food-portion</link><title>An experimental evaluation of a group- versus computer-based intervention to improve food portion size estimation skills</title><description>* An experimental evaluation of a group- versus computer-based intervention to improve food portion size estimation skills (Citations: 8)

Guadalupe Xochitl Ayala

The ability to accurately estimate and measure food portion sizes is important for preventing and treating obesity. This study describes the development, implementation and evaluation of a group- versus computer-based intervention to improve food portion estimation abilities using real food and food models. A convenience sample of 76 women was randomly assigned to one of three conditions: computer training, ...

Published in 2006.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7119-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7119_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:41:29">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/32687969/enos-activation-induced-by-a-polyphenol-rich-grape-skin-extract-in-porcine-coronary-arteries</link><title>eNOS Activation Induced by a Polyphenol-Rich Grape Skin Extract in Porcine Coronary Arteries</title><description>* eNOS Activation Induced by a Polyphenol-Rich Grape Skin Extract in Porcine Coronary Arteries (Citations: 11)

Socorro Vanesca Frota Madeira, Cyril Auger, Eric Anselm, Marta Chataigneau, Thierry Chataigneau, Roberto Soares de Moura, Valérie B. Schini-Kerth

Background/Aims: Drinking red wine is associated with a decreased mortality from coronary heart diseases. This study examined whether polyphenols contained in a grape skin extract (GSE) triggered the endothelial formation of nitric oxide (NO) and investigated the underlying mechanism. Methods: Vascular reactivity was assessed in organ chambers using porcine coronary artery rings in the presence of indomethacin (a cyclooxygenase ...

Journal: Journal of Vascular Research - J VASC RES , vol. 46, no. 5, pp. 406-416, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7119-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7119_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:42:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/36732968/counterfactual-and-mental-state-reasoning-in-children-with-autism</link><title>Counterfactual and Mental State Reasoning in Children with Autism</title><description>* Counterfactual and Mental State Reasoning in Children with Autism (Citations: 6)

Cathy M. Grant, Kevin J. Riggs, Jill Boucher

The contributions of counterfactual conditional reasoning (CCR), belief understanding, and inferential reasoning to the performance of children with autism (CWA) on standard false belief tasks were investigated. To assess the roles of these three factors, we compared the performance of CWA on physical-state CCR tasks (which do not require either an understanding of belief or inferential reasoning); on Wellman ...

Journal: Journal of Autism and Developmental Disorders - J AUTISM DEV DISORD , vol. 34, no. 2, pp. 177-188, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7119-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7119_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:43:59">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42620897/focus-groups-with-young-people-a-participatory-approach-to-research-planning</link><title>Focus groups with young people: a participatory approach to research planning</title><description>* Focus groups with young people: a participatory approach to research planning (Citations: 2)

Anna Bagnoli, Andrew Clark

In this paper we present our experiences of conducting focus groups with young people as part of a participatory approach to research design and participant recruitment. The research is a prospective, 10-year, qualitative, longitudinal project investigating young people's daily lives, relationships, and identities, and the ways these change over time. It adopts a multi-method approach in which ...

Journal: Journal of Youth Studies - J YOUTH STUD , vol. 13, no. 1, pp. 101-119, 2010</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>