<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7125">psychological effects of obesity in children</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:51:49" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7125-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7125_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:51:53">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/37065312/quality-of-life-in-a-clinical-sample-of-obese-children</link><title>Quality of life in a clinical sample of obese children</title><description>* Quality of life in a clinical sample of obese children (Citations: 22)

A R Hughes, K Farewell, D Harris, J J Reilly

...their parents; to assess differences in quality of life between the obese clinical sample and healthy control children.design:pairwise comparison of obese children matched for age, gender and...5).conclusions:hrqol is impaired in clinical samples of obese children compared to lean children, but the degree of impairment is likely to be...

Journal: International Journal of Obesity \- INT J OBESITY , vol. 31, no. 1, pp. 39-44, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7125-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7125_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:53:05">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/56554120/effect-of-body-mass-index-reduction-on-serum-hepcidin-levels-and-iron-status-in-obese-children</link><title>Effect of body mass index reduction on serum hepcidin levels and iron status in obese children</title><description>* Effect of body mass index reduction on serum hepcidin levels and iron status in obese children

A. Amato, N. Santoro, P. Calabro, A. Grandone, D. W. Swinkels, L. Perrone, E Miraglia del Giudice

...deficiency has been linked to obesity. hepcidin is the main regulator of iron homeostasis and is higher in obese children compared to controls. to gain insight into the link between obesity and hepcidin, we performed an intervention study in 15 obese children. these children were subjected to a 6...

Journal: International Journal of Obesity \- INT J OBESITY , vol. 34, no. 12, pp. 1772-1774, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7125-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7125_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:54:19">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39202693/health-related-quality-of-life-in-a-clinical-sample-of-obese-children-and-adolescents</link><title>Health-related quality of life in a clinical sample of obese children and adolescents</title><description>* Health-related quality of life in a clinical sample of obese children and adolescents

Afsane Riazi, Sania Shakoor, Isobel Dundas, Christine Eiser, Sheila A McKenzie

...is known about the impact of obesity on health-related quality of life (hrqol) in children and adolescents from mixed-ethnic samples. the purpose of this study was to: 1) measure hrqol in a mixed-ethnic clinical sample of obese children and adolescents, 2) compare hrqol assessments in obese participants and healthy controls, and...

Journal: Health and Quality of Life Outcomes - HEALTH QUAL LIFE OUTCOMES , vol. 8, no. 1, pp. 134-6, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7125-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7125_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:55:22">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/32631643/medical-care-of-obese-children-and-adolescents</link><title>Medical care of obese children and adolescents</title><description>* Medical care of obese children and adolescents (Citations: 6)

Thomas Reinehr, Martin Wabitsch, Werner Andler, Peter Beyer, Antje Böttner, Annette Chen-Stute, Carmen Fromme, Olaf Hampel, Klaus M. Keller, Uwe Kilian, Hilde Kolbe, Thomas Lob-Corziliushttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=32631643&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=psychological effects of obesity in children

...2000 up to march 2003, of whom 1985 were treated in outpatient institutions and 1852 in rehabilitation institutions. of these children, 10% were overweight, 37% obese...and documented were low (measurement of blood pressure 43%, lipids 40%, glucose metabolism 21%). in the subgroup of obese children who were screened for cardiovascular...

Journal: European Journal of Pediatrics - EUR J PEDIAT , vol. 163, no. 6, pp. 308-312, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7125-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7125_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:56:36">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/37064479/predictors-to-success-in-outpatient-training-in-obese-children-and-adolescents</link><title>Predictors to success in outpatient training in obese children and adolescents</title><description>* Predictors to success in outpatient training in obese children and adolescents (Citations: 45)

T Reinehr, K Brylak, U Alexy, M Kersting, W Andler

...course and behaviour therapy for children and their parents.subjects: a total of 75 obese children (age 7–15 y; standard duration scores of body mass index(sds-bmi...to change their behaviour (changes in weight status, number of attempts at therapy, participation in exercise groups), somatic characteristics (bmi of children and family members, gender, age...

Journal: International Journal of Obesity \- INT J OBESITY , vol. 27, no. 9, pp. 1087-1092, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7125-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7125_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:57:42">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/59212852/promoting-physical-activity-among-overweight-and-obese-children-a-randomised-controlled-trial</link><title>Promoting physical activity among overweight and obese children: a randomised controlled trial comparing a physical activity program, a dietary program and a combined physical activity plus dietary program</title><description>* Promoting physical activity among overweight and obese children: a randomised controlled trial comparing a physical activity program, a dietary program and a combined physical activity plus dietary program

Dylan P. Cliff

...strategies. physical inactivity is implicated in the aetiology of obesity, however, published experimental trials evaluating interventions designed to promote physical activity in overweight and obese children have been compromised by the...follow-up, illustrating its efficacy in the treatment of obesity and related behavioural and psychosocial outcomes in children. as such, effectiveness trials are warranted to examine...

Published in 2008.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7125-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7125_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:58:41">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/32629268/changes-in-fat-mass-fat-free-mass-and-aerobic-fitness-in-severely-obese-children-and-adolescents</link><title>Changes in fat mass, fat-free mass and aerobic fitness in severely obese children and adolescents following a residential treatment programme</title><description>* Changes in fat mass, fat-free mass and aerobic fitness in severely obese children and adolescents following a residential treatment programme (Citations: 17)

Benedicte Deforche, Ilse De Bourdeaudhuij, Patrick Debode, Freddy Vinaimont, Andrew P. Hills, Stefanie Verstraete, Jacques Bouckaert

...paediatric centre zeepreventorium. treatment consisted of moderate dietary restriction, physical activity and psychological support. this study was a clinical observation of 20 severely obese children and adolescents (8 boys and...conclusion: a moderate dietary restriction in combination with physical activity and psychological support in severely obese children and adolescents is effective in decreasing body fat and improving...

Journal: European Journal of Pediatrics - EUR J PEDIAT , vol. 162, no. 9, pp. 616-622, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7125-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7125_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 06:59:59">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/56554262/teasing-and-social-rejection-among-obese-children-enrolling-in-family-based-behavioural-treatment</link><title>Teasing and social rejection among obese children enrolling in family-based behavioural treatment: effects on psychological adjustment and academic competencies</title><description>* Teasing and social rejection among obese children enrolling in family-based behavioural treatment: effects on psychological adjustment and academic competencies

T Gunnarsdottir, U Njardvik, A S Olafsdottir, L W Craighead, R Bjarnason

...was to determine the prevalence of psychological maladjustment (emotional and behavioural problems), low academic competencies and teasing/social rejection among obese icelandic children enrolling in a family-based behavioural treatment...and weight, demographics and measures of children's psychological adjustment, academic competencies, teasing/social rejection and physical activity were collected from children, parents and teachers. parental depression...

Journal: International Journal of Obesity \- INT J OBESITY , vol. 36, no. 1, pp. 35-44, 2012</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7125-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7125_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:01:11">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48777687/inpatient-treatment-of-obese-children-a-multicomponent-programme-without-stringent-calorie</link><title>Inpatient treatment of obese children: a multicomponent programme without stringent calorie restriction</title><description>* Inpatient treatment of obese children: a multicomponent programme without stringent calorie restriction (Citations: 19)

Caroline Braet, Ann Tanghe, Patrick De Bode, Hilde Franckx, Myriam Van Winckel

...case-control study describes the effect of an inpatient multicomponent treatment programme for obese children and adolescents on their weight and psychological well being. we studied 38...a valuable treatment option for obese children, with a lasting effect up to 14 months post-treatment. nevertheless, more research is needed to characterise those children who regain weight after treatment...

Journal: European Journal of Pediatrics - EUR J PEDIAT , vol. 162, no. 6, pp. 391-396, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7125-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7125_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:02:18">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/38405774/randomized-controlled-comparison-of-two-cognitive-behavioral-therapies-for-obese-children-mother</link><title>Randomized Controlled Comparison of Two Cognitive Behavioral Therapies for Obese Children: Mother versus Mother-Child Cognitive Behavioral Therapy</title><description>* Randomized Controlled Comparison of Two Cognitive Behavioral Therapies for Obese Children: Mother versus Mother-Child Cognitive Behavioral Therapy (Citations: 12)

Simone Munsch, Binia Roth, Tanja Michael, Andrea Hans Meyer, Esther Biedert, Sandra Roth, Vanessa Speck, Urs Zumsteg, Emanuel Isler, Jürgen Margraf

...or for a combined treatment of parents and children. children’s percent overweight, the body mass index of their mothers, and behavioral and psychological problems of children and mothers were assessed. results...of the two treatments. further, psychological well-being of both mothers and children can be improved in a cbt for obese children and their parents. future studies...

Journal: Psychotherapy and Psychosomatics - PSYCHOTHER PSYCHOSOM , vol. 77, no. 4, pp. 235-246, 2008</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>