<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7127">which cities surround long beach ca</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:04:47" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7127-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7127_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:04:51">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/13278988/20th-ieee-acm-international-conference-on-automated-software-engineering-ase-2005-november-7-11</link><title>20th IEEE/ACM International Conference on Automated Software Engineering (ASE 2005), November 7-11, 2005, Long Beach, CA, USA</title><description>* 20th IEEE/ACM International Conference on Automated Software Engineering (ASE 2005), November 7-11, 2005, Long Beach, CA, USA

David F. Redmiles, Thomas Ellman, Andrea Zisman

Conference: Automated Software Engineering - ASE , 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7127-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7127_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:06:02">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/51458907/near-surface-structure-and-faults-of-the-long-beach-california-area-as-determined-from</link><title>Near-Surface Structure and Faults of the Long Beach, California Area as Determined from High-Resolution Seismic Reflection and Refraction Imaging</title><description>* Near-Surface Structure and Faults of the Long Beach, California Area as Determined from High-Resolution Seismic Reflection and Refraction Imaging

M. R. Goldman, R. D. Catchings, G. Gandhok, D. Ponti

...reflection/refraction surveys in the city of long beach, ca in the summer of 2000...of clay and sand layers which form a long-wavelength (hundreds of meters) fold...

Published in 2002.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7127-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7127_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:07:20">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6382467/exploring-rippled-scour-depressions-offshore-huntington-beach-ca</link><title>EXPLORING RIPPLED SCOUR DEPRESSIONS OFFSHORE HUNTINGTON BEACH, CA</title><description>* EXPLORING RIPPLED SCOUR DEPRESSIONS OFFSHORE HUNTINGTON BEACH, CA

Eleyne L. Phillips, Curt D. Storlazzi, Peter Dartnell

...within rsds and on the surrounding seafloor were calculated from photography...

Published in 2007.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7127-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7127_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:08:23">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11961603/effect-of-pregnancy-as-a-risk-factor-for-breast-cancer-inbrca1-brca2-mutation-carriers</link><title>Effect of pregnancy as a risk factor for breast cancer inBRCA1/BRCA2 mutation carriers</title><description>* Effect of pregnancy as a risk factor for breast cancer inBRCA1/BRCA2 mutation carriers (Citations: 52)

Carey A. Cullinane, Jan Lubinski, Susan L. Neuhausen, Parviz Ghadirian, Henry T. Lynch, Claudine Isaacs, Barbara Weber, Pal Moller, Kenneth Offit, Charmaine Kim-Sing, Eitan Friedman, Susan Randallhttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=11961603&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=which cities surround long beach ca

...vs. nulli­ tive factors have long been known to be important...is: todd cancer center at long beach was no significant increase in the risk of breast cancer among memorial medical center, long beach, ca. brca2 carriers older than 50...

Journal: International Journal of Cancer - INT J CANCER , vol. 117, no. 6, pp. 988-991, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7127-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7127_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:09:41">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/15279811/organizational-challenges-in-developing-one-of-the-nationwide-health-information-network-trial</link><title>Organizational Challenges in Developing One of the Nationwide Health Information Network Trial Implementation Awardees</title><description>* Organizational Challenges in Developing One of the Nationwide Health Information Network Trial Implementation Awardees

Aram Dobalian, Maria L. Claver, Joshua M. Pevnick, Harris R. Stutman, Alan Tomines, Paul Fu Jr

...information network (nhin) site in long beach, ca during its first year of operation. the long beach network for health (lbnh) focused...

Journal: Journal of Medical Systems , vol. 34, no. 3, pp. 1-8</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7127-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7127_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:10:54">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40735576/assessment-of-hospital-and-police-ascertainment-of-automobile-versus-childhood-pedestrian-and</link><title>Assessment of hospital and police ascertainment of automobile versus childhood pedestrian and bicyclist collisions</title><description>* Assessment of hospital and police ascertainment of automobile versus childhood pedestrian and bicyclist collisions (Citations: 16)

Preet K Dhillon, Amy S Lightstone, Corinne Peek-Asa, Jess F Kraus

...different characteristics of a collision, which reflects differences in case finding...motor vehicle collision in the city of long beach, ca, between january 1, 1992 and...

Journal: Accident Analysis and Prevention - ACCID ANAL PREVENT , vol. 33, no. 4, pp. 529-537, 2001</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7127-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7127_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:12:04">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/52887620/methodology-for-estimating-tsunami-induced-hazard-for-ports-along-california-coastline</link><title>Methodology for Estimating Tsunami Induced Hazard for Ports Along California Coastline</title><description>* Methodology for Estimating Tsunami Induced Hazard for Ports Along California Coastline

Burak Uslu, Vasily V. Titov, Marie C. Eble, Utku Kanoglu

...are operated separately by the cities of long beach and los angeles. due to...ports of los angeles and long beach. in coastal engineering 2006---proceedings of the 30th international conference, san diego, ca, 3-8 december 2006, 1616...

Published in 2010.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7127-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7127_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:13:21">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/54680796/methodology-for-estimating-tsunami-induced-hazard-for-ports-along-california-coastline</link><title>Methodology for Estimating Tsunami Induced Hazard for Ports Along California Coastline</title><description>* Methodology for Estimating Tsunami Induced Hazard for Ports Along California Coastline

B. U. Uslu, V. V. Titov, M. C. Eble, U. Kanoglu

...are operated separately by the cities of long beach and los angeles. due to...ports of los angeles and long beach. in coastal engineering 2006---proceedings of the 30th international conference, san diego, ca, 3-8 december 2006, 1616...

Published in 2009.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7127-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7127_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:14:35">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5935435/measuring-and-modeling-repeat-and-near-repeat-burglary-effects</link><title>Measuring and Modeling Repeat and Near-Repeat Burglary Effects</title><description>* Measuring and Modeling Repeat and Near-Repeat Burglary Effects (Citations: 3)

M. B. Short, M. R. D’Orsogna, P. J. Brantingham, G. E. Tita

...data. parsing burglary data from long beach, ca according to different counting methods...for repeat burglary events in long beach by fitting our data to...

Journal: Journal of Quantitative Criminology - J QUANT CRIMINOL , vol. 25, no. 3, pp. 325-339, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7127-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7127_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:16:00">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11449033/studies-of-the-48-bp-repeat-polymorphism-of-thedrd4-gene-in-impulsive-compulsive-addictive</link><title>Studies of the 48 bp repeat polymorphism of theDRD4 gene in impulsive, compulsive, addictive behaviors: Tourette syndrome, ADHD, pathological gambling, and substance abuse</title><description>* Studies of the 48 bp repeat polymorphism of theDRD4 gene in impulsive, compulsive, addictive behaviors: Tourette syndrome, ADHD, pathological gambling, and substance abuse (Citations: 95)

David E. Comings, Nancy Gonzalez, Shijuan Wu, Radhika Gade, Donn Muhleman, Gerard Saucier, Patrick Johnson, Ray Verde, Richard J. Rosenthal, Henry R. Lesieur, Loreen J. Rugle, Warren B. Millerhttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=11449033&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=which cities surround long beach ca

Prior studies have reported an association between the presence of the 7 repeat allele of the 48 bp repeat polymorphism of the third cytoplasmic loop of the dopamine D4 receptor gene (DRD4) and novelty seeking behaviors, attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD), Tourette syndrome (TS), pathological gambling, and substance abuse. However, other studies have failed to replicate some of these observations. ...

Journal: American Journal of Medical Genetics - AMER J MED GENET , vol. 88, no. 4, pp. 358-368, 1999</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>