<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7132">massachusetts general hospital jobs</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:43:50" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7132-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7132_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:43:55">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/892713/history-of-the-development-of-medical-information-systems-at-the-laboratory-of-computer-science-at</link><title>History of the development of medical information systems at the Laboratory of Computer Science at Massachusetts General Hospital</title><description>* History of the development of medical information systems at the Laboratory of Computer Science at Massachusetts General Hospital (Citations: 7)

G. Octo Barnett

...laboratory of computer science at massachusetts general hospital, i have found it equally...wave of optimism and enthusiasm generated by beguiling promises of an immediately available total hospital computer system has passed. now...

Conference: History of Medical Informatics - HMI , pp. 43-49, 1987</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7132-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7132_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:45:23">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/29677687/the-uses-of-shadowing-the-doctor-and-patient</link><title>The uses of shadowing the doctor—and patient</title><description>* The uses of shadowing the doctor—and patient (Citations: 1)

John D. Stoeckle, Larry Ronan, Carol Ehrlich, David Roberts

...introduction to medicine," at the massachusetts general hospital, shadowing a physician during a...tagging along on office visits, hospital rounds, and perhaps home visits is meant to show what practice is, "the doctor's job." the traditional focus is professional...

Journal: Journal of General Internal Medicine - J GEN INTERN MED , vol. 8, no. 10, pp. 561-563, 1993</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7132-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7132_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:46:33">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/13161513/the-effects-of-particulate-air-pollution-on-daily-deaths-a-multi-city-case-crossover-analysis</link><title>The effects of particulate air pollution on daily deaths: a multi-city case crossover analysis</title><description>* The effects of particulate air pollution on daily deaths: a multi-city case crossover analysis (Citations: 27)

J Schwartz, L Punnett, A Seidler, A Nienhaus, T Bernhardt, T Kauppinen, A-L Elo, L Frölich, J Dekker, C Bigert, K Klerdal, N Hammarhttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=13161513&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=massachusetts general hospital jobs

Journal: Occupational and Environmental Medicine - OCCUP ENVIRON MEDICINE , vol. 61, no. 12, pp. 956-961, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7132-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7132_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:47:42">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/30008172/the-work-impact-of-dysthymia-in-a-primary-care-population</link><title>The work impact of dysthymia in a primary care population</title><description>* The work impact of dysthymia in a primary care population (Citations: 9)

David A Adler, Julie Irish, Thomas J McLaughlin, Carla Perissinotto, Hong Chang, Maggie Hood, Leueen Lapitsky, William H Rogers, Debra Lerner

...with three health plans in massachusetts, we compared 69 patients diagnosed...loss due to on-the-job performance limitations (“presenteeism”). patients with...

Journal: General Hospital Psychiatry - GEN HOSP PSYCHIAT , vol. 26, no. 4, pp. 269-276, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7132-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7132_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:48:43">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/30550012/outcome-of-strategy-training-in-stroke-patients-with-apraxia-a-phase-ii-study</link><title>Outcome of strategy training in stroke patients with apraxia: a phase II study</title><description>* Outcome of strategy training in stroke patients with apraxia: a phase II study (Citations: 10)

C. M. van Heugten, J. Dekker, B. G. Deelman, A. J. van Dijk, J. C. Stehmann-Saris, A. Kinebanian

...at occupational therapy departments in general hospitals, rehabilitation centres and nursing homes...

Journal: Clinical Rehabilitation - CLIN REHABIL , vol. 12, no. 3, pp. 216-225, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7132-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7132_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:49:53">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6536428/burnout-caring-for-the-caregivers</link><title>Burnout: Caring for the Caregivers</title><description>* Burnout: Caring for the Caregivers (Citations: 11)

RICHARD T. P ENSON, FIONA L. DIGNAN, GEORGE P. C ANELLOS, CAROL L. PICARD, THOMAS J. LYNCH

...schwartz, a cancer patient at massachusetts general hospital (mgh), founded the kenneth b...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7132-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7132_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:51:05">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48426124/pflegepersonal-in-psychiatrisch-psychosomatischen-konsiliar-liaison-diensten</link><title>Pflegepersonal in psychiatrisch-psychosomatischen Konsiliar-Liaison-Diensten</title><description>* Pflegepersonal in psychiatrisch-psychosomatischen Konsiliar-Liaison-Diensten

Angelika Rießland-Seifert, Zuzana Höcher, Susanne Erbert

...and psychosocial care needs in general hospitals require adequate structures of care...especially important because of their job profile, and because they serve...

Journal: Psychosomatik Und Konsiliarpsychiatrie , vol. 1, no. 1, pp. 40-46, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7132-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7132_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:52:11">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/14903376/identification-and-analysis-of-functional-elements-in-1-of-the-human-genome-by-the-encode-pilot</link><title>Identification and analysis of functional elements in 1% of the human genome by the ENCODE pilot project</title><description>* Identification and analysis of functional elements in 1% of the human genome by the ENCODE pilot project (Citations: 839)

Ewan Birney, John A. Stamatoyannopoulos, Anindya Dutta, Roderic Guigó, Thomas R. Gingeras, Elliott H. Margulies, Zhiping Weng, Michael Snyder, Emmanouil T. Dermitzakis, Robert E. Thurman, Michael S. Kuehn, Christopher M. Taylorhttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=14903376&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=massachusetts general hospital jobs

...we report the generation and analysis of functional data...

Journal: Nature , vol. 447, no. 7146, pp. 799-816, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7132-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7132_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:53:26">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/34843722/urbanisation-as-a-risk-indicator-for-psychiatric-admission</link><title>Urbanisation as a risk indicator for psychiatric admission</title><description>* Urbanisation as a risk indicator for psychiatric admission (Citations: 5)

J. Peen, J. Dekker

...all first admissions to dutch general psychiatric hospitals and psychiatric teaching clinics in...

Journal: Social Psychiatry and Psychiatric Epidemiology - SOC PSYCHIAT PSYCHIAT EPIDEM , vol. 38, no. 9, pp. 535-538, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7132-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7132_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 07:54:33">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/34781545/psychometric-properties-of-the-korean-version-of-the-job-content-questionnaire-data-from-health</link><title>Psychometric properties of the Korean version of the job content questionnaire: data from health care workers</title><description>* Psychometric properties of the Korean version of the job content questionnaire: data from health care workers (Citations: 9)

Ki-Do Eum, Jian Li, Hyung-Joon Jhun, Jong-Tae Park, Sang-Woo Tak, Robert Karasek, Sung-Il Cho

...scales, namely, decision latitude, psychological job demand, social support, job insecurity, and macro-level decision latitude from the korean version of the job content questionnaire (k-jcq), as...and low levels of psychological job demand and job insecurity were significantly associated with high level of job satisfaction. higher self-identity through...

Journal: International Archives of Occupational and Environmental Health - INT ARCH OCCUP ENVIR HEALTH , vol. 80, no. 6, pp. 497-504, 2007</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>