<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7136">Soccer trick</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:18:40" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7136-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7136_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:18:42">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/59234784/international-recognition-for-notre-dame-s-soccer-superstar</link><title>International recognition for Notre Dame’s soccer superstar</title><description>* International recognition for Notre Dame’s soccer superstar

Leigh Dawson

...game to begin his own soccer coaching company called d10 football. with a focus on fine-tuning basic soccer skills in young players, such...if his aspirations of playing soccer professionally aren’t realised. through the practicum component of his degree at notre dame, he also offers his soccer expertise to the perth glory...

Published in 2012.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7136-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7136_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:19:32">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4486663/round-robin-scheduling-a-survey</link><title>Round robin scheduling - a survey</title><description>* Round robin scheduling - a survey (Citations: 36)

Rasmus V. Rasmussen, Michael A. Trick

This paper presents a comprehensive survey on the literature considering round robin tour- naments. The terminology used within the area has been modifled over time and today it is highly inconsistent. By presenting a coherent explanation of the various notions we hope that this paper will help to obtain a unifled terminology. Furthermore, we outline the contributions presented during the ...

Journal: European Journal of Operational Research - EJOR , vol. 188, no. 3, pp. 617-636, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7136-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7136_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:20:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4595210/scheduling-the-belgian-soccer-league</link><title>Scheduling the Belgian Soccer League</title><description>* Scheduling the Belgian Soccer League (Citations: 11)

Dries R. Goossens, Frits C. R. Spieksma

...countries, the interest for belgian soccer has increased over the last years. this paper describes our expe- riences in scheduling the highest belgian soccer league. we describe how we...

Journal: Interfaces , vol. 39, no. 2, pp. 109-118, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7136-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7136_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:21:55">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4306895/scheduling-the-brazilian-soccer-tournament-with-fairness-and-broadcast-objectives</link><title>Scheduling the Brazilian Soccer Tournament with Fairness and Broadcast Objectives</title><description>* Scheduling the Brazilian Soccer Tournament with Fairness and Broadcast Objectives (Citations: 4)

Celso C. Ribeiro, Sebastián Urrutia

...the brazilian soccer tournament is organized every year by the brazilian soccer confederation. its major sponsor is...

Conference: Practice and Theory of Automated Timetabling - PATAT , pp. 147-157, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7136-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7136_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:22:53">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48269259/soccer-schedules-in-europe-an-overview</link><title>Soccer schedules in Europe: an overview</title><description>* Soccer schedules in Europe: an overview

Dries R. Goossens, Frederik Spieksma

...schedules used in 25 european soccer competitions for the season 2008...quite some diversity in european soccer schedules, and that current schedules...

Journal: Journal of Scheduling - SCHEDULING , pp. 1-11, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7136-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7136_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:24:05">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4306900/a-branch-and-cut-algorithm-for-scheduling-the-highly-constrained-chilean-soccer-tournament</link><title>A Branch-and-Cut Algorithm for Scheduling the Highly-Constrained Chilean Soccer Tournament</title><description>* A Branch-and-Cut Algorithm for Scheduling the Highly-Constrained Chilean Soccer Tournament (Citations: 2)

Thiago F. Noronha, Celso C. Ribeiro, Guillermo Durán, Sebastian Souyris, Andres Weintraub

...the chilean soccer championship follows the structure of...

Conference: Practice and Theory of Automated Timetabling - PATAT , pp. 174-186, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7136-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7136_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:25:15">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/2377/wiener-soccer-and-its-generalization</link><title>WIENER SOCCER AND ITS GENERALIZATION</title><description>* WIENER SOCCER AND ITS GENERALIZATION (Citations: 2)

YULIY BARYSHNIKOV

...of the ball in a soccer game is modelled by the...

Published in 1996.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7136-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7136_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:26:22">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/2794579/branch-and-cut-for-a-real-life-highly-constrained-soccer-tournament-scheduling-problem</link><title>Branch-and-cut for a real-life highly constrained soccer tournament scheduling problem</title><description>* Branch-and-cut for a real-life highly constrained soccer tournament scheduling problem (Citations: 5)

Guillermo Duran, Thiago F. Noronha, Celso C. Ribeiro, Sebastian Souyris, Andres Weintraub

,Department of Industrial Engineering, University of Chile, Republica 701, Santiago, Chile.,Department of Computer Science, Catholic University of Rio de Janeiro, Rua Marqu?es de S?ao Vicente 225, Rio de Janeiro, RJ 22453-900, Brazil.,Department of Computer Science, Universidade Federal Fluminense, Rua Passo da P'atria 156, Niter'oi, RJ 24210-240, Brazil. gduran@dii. uchile. cl, ftfn,...

Published in 2006.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7136-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7136_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:27:33">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/56924397/development-of-monocular-vision-system-for-depth-estimation-in-mobile-robot-robot-soccer</link><title>Development of monocular vision system for depth estimation in mobile robot — Robot soccer</title><description>* Development of monocular vision system for depth estimation in mobile robot — Robot soccer

M. N. A. Wahab, N. Sivadev, K. Sundaraj

...paper also will show the trick on how to solve the...

Published in 2011.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7136-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7136_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 08:28:35">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/711573/a-new-algorithm-for-ball-recognition-using-circle-hough-transform-and-neural-classifier</link><title>A new algorithm for ball recognition using circle Hough transform and neural classifier</title><description>* A new algorithm for ball recognition using circle Hough transform and neural classifier (Citations: 40)

Tiziana D'orazio, Cataldo Guaragnella, Marco Leo, Arcangelo Distante

...in this work is the soccer game. in the sequences ofsoccer...positive has been found. some tricks like background subtraction and ball...

Journal: Pattern Recognition - PR , vol. 37, no. 3, pp. 393-408, 2004</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>