<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7141">Cambridge must do</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:04:39" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7141-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7141_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:04:42">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/51544231/symbolical-logic</link><title>Symbolical Logic</title><description>* Symbolical Logic

Hugh McColl

...sciences, gonville and caius college, cambridge) must be my excuse for troubling...

Journal: Nature , vol. 24, no. 606, pp. 124-126, 1881</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7141-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7141_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:05:51">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/37405258/diagnosing-prosopagnosia-effects-of-ageing-sex-and-participant-stimulus-ethnic-match-on-the</link><title>Diagnosing prosopagnosia: Effects of ageing, sex, and participant–stimulus ethnic match on the Cambridge Face Memory Test and Cambridge Face Perception Test</title><description>* Diagnosing prosopagnosia: Effects of ageing, sex, and participant–stimulus ethnic match on the Cambridge Face Memory Test and Cambridge Face Perception Test (Citations: 10)

Devin C. Bowles, Elinor McKone, Amy Dawel, Bradley Duchaine, Romina Palermo, Laura Schmalzl, Davide Rivolta, C. Ellie Wilson, Galit Yovel

...the cambridge face memory test (cfmt) and cambridge face perception test (cfpt) have...which norms for these tasks must take into account ageing, sex...

Journal: Cognitive Neuropsychology - COGNITIVE NEUROPSYCHOL , vol. 26, no. 5, pp. 423-455, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7141-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7141_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:07:02">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/51420634/the-structure-and-evolution-of-normal-galaxies-proceedings-of-the-advanced-study-institute</link><title>The structure and evolution of normal galaxies; Proceedings of the Advanced Study Institute, Cambridge University, Cambridge, England), August 3-15, 1980</title><description>* The structure and evolution of normal galaxies; Proceedings of the Advanced Study Institute, Cambridge University, Cambridge, England), August 3-15, 1980

S. M. Fall, D. Lynden-Bell

...general properties of galaxies which must be explained, the photometric and...

Published in 1981.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7141-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7141_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:08:10">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10340514/that-this-house-calls-upon-the-barnett-government-to-provide-guaranteed-four-year-funding-staffing</link><title>That this house calls upon the Barnett government to provide guaranteed four-year funding, staffing and support to the School Volunteer Program, which does an excellent job supporting schools across Western Australia. I am very pleased that this very important motion — Point of Order Mr R.F. JOHNSON: I do not want to interrupt the member for Mandurah, but I think that I am right in saying that the member in whose name the motion stands must move the motion. The member has not done that. The ACTING SPEAKER (Mr J.M. Francis): The member for Rockingham's name is on the notice paper. Mr M. McGOWAN: I seek your guidance, Mr Speaker. The member for Mandurah does not necessarily have to be the lead speaker. I am happy to speak first or later in the debate. Whatever is in accordance with the standing orders is fine with me. Mr R.F. JOHNSON: I have always understood that the motion must be moved by the member in whose name the motion stands. I think the member for Mandurah can move it on behalf</title><description>* That this house calls upon the Barnett government to provide guaranteed four-year funding, staffing and support to the School Volunteer Program, which does an excellent job supporting schools across Western Australia. I am very pleased that this very important motion — Point of Order Mr R.F. JOHNSON: I do not want to interrupt the member for Mandurah, but I think that I am right in saying that the member in whose name the motion stands must move the motion. The member has not done that. The ACTING SPEAKER (Mr J.M. Francis): The member for Rockingham's name is on the notice paper. Mr M. McGOWAN: I seek your guidance, Mr Speaker. The member for Mandurah does not necessarily have to be the lead speaker. I am happy to speak first or later in the debate. Whatever is in accordance with the standing orders is fine with me. Mr R.F. JOHNSON: I have always understood that the motion must be moved by the member in whose name the motion stands. I think the member for Mandurah can move it on behalf

David Templeman, Rob Johnson, Acting Speaker, Eric Ripper, Lisa Baker, Chris Tallentire, Andrew Waddell, Janine Freeman, Paul Papalia, Elizabeth Constable, Paul Miles, Colin Barnetthttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=10340514&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=Cambridge must do</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7141-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7141_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:09:16">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/43261358/review-dante-gabriel-rossetti-and-the-game-that-must-be-lost-jerome-mcgann-dante-gabriel</link><title>Review: Dante Gabriel Rossetti and the Game that Must be Lost * Jerome McGann: Dante Gabriel Rossetti and the Game that Must be Lost</title><description>* Review: Dante Gabriel Rossetti and the Game that Must be Lost * Jerome McGann: Dante Gabriel Rossetti and the Game that Must be Lost

R. Frith

Journal: Cambridge Quarterly , vol. 32, no. 1, pp. 81-85, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7141-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7141_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:10:25">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/29016684/ganges-cambridge-chicago-edinburgh-cambridge-values-and-public-health</link><title>Ganges, Cambridge, Chicago, Edinburgh, Cambridge... Values and Public Health</title><description>* Ganges, Cambridge, Chicago, Edinburgh, Cambridge... Values and Public Health (Citations: 1)

Michael Marmot

...pause. krishna argues that he must do his duty regardless of the...health for example, or by doing the right thing such as...

Journal: European Journal of Epidemiology - EUR J EPIDEMIOL , vol. 20, no. 10, pp. 809-812, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7141-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7141_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:11:33">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/51349161/book-review-structures-in-the-universe-by-exact-methods-formation-evolutions-interactions</link><title>BOOK REVIEW: Structures in the Universe by Exact Methods: Formation, Evolutions, Interactions (Cambridge Monographs on Mathematical Physics) Structures in the Universe by Exact Methods: Formation, Evolutions, Interactions (Cambridge Monographs on Mathematical Physics)</title><description>* BOOK REVIEW: Structures in the Universe by Exact Methods: Formation, Evolutions, Interactions (Cambridge Monographs on Mathematical Physics) Structures in the Universe by Exact Methods: Formation, Evolutions, Interactions (Cambridge Monographs on Mathematical Physics)

Krzysztof Bolejko, Andrzej Krasinski, Charles Hellaby, Marie-Noëlle Célérier

...and consequently the copernican principle) must be properly challenged and revisited...

Journal: Classical and Quantum Gravity - CLASS QUANTUM GRAVITY , vol. 27, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7141-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7141_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:12:40">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/12788847/the-haskell-98-foreign-function-interface-1-0-an-addendum-to-the-haskell-98-report</link><title>The Haskell 98 Foreign Function Interface 1.0 An Addendum to the Haskell 98 Report</title><description>* The Haskell 98 Foreign Function Interface 1.0 An Addendum to the Haskell 98 Report (Citations: 5)

Manuel Chakravarty, Marcin Kowalczyk, Simon Marlow, Cambridge Erik Meijer, Simon Peyton Jones, Cambridge Alastair Reid, Malcolm Wallace</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7141-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7141_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:13:28">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/13031606/l-ac-uk-department-of-engineering-uni-v-ersity-of-cambridge-t-rumpington-street-cb2-1pz</link><title>l.ac.uk Department of Engineering, Uni v ersity of Cambridge, T rumpington Street, CB2 1PZ Cambridge, U.K. md283@eng.cam.ac .uk Department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering, Uni v ersity of Melbourne, V ictoria 3010 Australia. a.doucet@ee.mu.o z.au</title><description>* l.ac.uk Department of Engineering, Uni v ersity of Cambridge, T rumpington Street, CB2 1PZ Cambridge, U.K. md283@eng.cam.ac .uk Department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering, Uni v ersity of Melbourne, V ictoria 3010 Australia. a.doucet@ee.mu.o z.au

C. Andrieu

the frequencies, moduli and real poles instead of a standard model on the AR coef ficients as it mak es more sense from a physical vie wpoint. Second, optimal estimation in v olv es solving a comple x optimal filtering problem which does not ad- mit an y closed-form solution. W e propose a ne w particle filtering scheme ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7141-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7141_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:14:18">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39814714/third-world-debt-must-grow</link><title>Third world debt must grow</title><description>* Third world debt must grow

Malcolm Crawford, Cambridge Grove

Approximately 60 percent of the debt owed by the World's Developing Countries is to the international banks. The author gives an economic analysis of the situation and concludes that real growth for the less developed countries (LDCs) will justify further increased borrowing.

Journal: The Environmentalist , vol. 6, no. 3, pp. 219-226, 1986</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>