<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7144">can headphones cause hearing loss</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:27:13" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7144-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7144_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:27:18">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4912743/is-poor-frequency-modulation-detection-linked-to-literacy-problems-a-comparison-of-speciwc-reading</link><title>Is poor frequency modulation detection linked to literacy problems? A comparison of speciWc reading disability and mild to moderate sensorineural hearing loss</title><description>* Is poor frequency modulation detection linked to literacy problems? A comparison of speciWc reading disability and mild to moderate sensorineural hearing loss (Citations: 1)

L. F. Halliday, D. V. M. Bishop

...widely recognised as often being caused by phonological processing problems, avecting...children with mild to moderate hearing loss (snh group) and 16 age...

Published in 2006.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7144-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7144_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:28:14">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/25247723/aspirin-can-cause-hearing-loss</link><title>Aspirin can cause hearing loss</title><description>* Aspirin can cause hearing loss

Unknown

Journal: Reactions Weekly , vol. &amp;NA;, no. 464, 1993</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7144-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7144_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:29:14">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/34289945/thegjb2-mutation-r75q-can-cause-nonsyndromic-hearing-loss-dfna3-or-hereditary-palmoplantar</link><title>TheGJB2 mutation R75Q can cause nonsyndromic hearing loss DFNA3 or hereditary palmoplantar keratoderma with deafness</title><description>* TheGJB2 mutation R75Q can cause nonsyndromic hearing loss DFNA3 or hereditary palmoplantar keratoderma with deafness (Citations: 6)

Delphine Feldmann, Françoise Denoyelle, Hélène Blons, Stanislas Lyonnet, Natalie Loundon, Isabelle Rouillon, Smail Hadj-Rabia, Christine Petit, Rémy Couderc, Eréa-Noel Garabédian, Sandrine Marlin

Journal: American Journal of Medical Genetics Part A - AM J MED GENET PART A , vol. 137A, no. 2, pp. 225-227, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7144-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7144_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:30:21">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/32971846/audioprofile-directed-screening-identifies-novel-mutations-in-kcnq4-causing-hearing-loss-at-the</link><title>Audioprofile-directed screening identifies novel mutations in KCNQ4 causing hearing loss at the DFNA2 locus</title><description>* Audioprofile-directed screening identifies novel mutations in KCNQ4 causing hearing loss at the DFNA2 locus (Citations: 3)

Michael S. Hildebrand, Dylan Tack, Sarah J. McMordie, Adam DeLuca, In Ae Hur, Carla Nishimura, Patrick Huygen, Thomas L. Casavant, Richard J. H. Smith

...families segregating autosomal dominant sensorineural hearing loss presents a significant challenge. to...pore and audiogene audioprofile analysis can effectively prioritize genes for mutation screening in small families segregating high-frequency autosomal dominant sensorineural hearing loss. audiogene software will be made...

Journal: Genetics in Medicine - GENET MED , vol. 10, no. 11, pp. 797-804, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7144-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7144_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:31:19">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/47667799/tinnitus-and-hearing-loss</link><title>Tinnitus and Hearing Loss</title><description>* Tinnitus and Hearing Loss

Giovanna Baracca, Luca Del Bo, Umberto Ambrosetti

...and one of the major causes of permanent sensorineural hearing loss. (b)  administration of ototoxic drugs can cause hearing loss, tinnitus, and vertigo or dizziness...decrease) in cochlear blood perfusion can lead to cochlear damage with hearing loss and tinnitus. (f)  abrupt change in barometric pressure (barotraumas) can cause damage to the cochlea and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7144-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7144_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:32:16">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/33908638/progressive-hearing-loss-and-increased-susceptibility-to-noise-induced-hearing-loss-in-mice</link><title>Progressive Hearing Loss and Increased Susceptibility to Noise-Induced Hearing Loss in Mice Carrying a Cdh23 but not a Myo7a Mutation</title><description>* Progressive Hearing Loss and Increased Susceptibility to Noise-Induced Hearing Loss in Mice Carrying a Cdh23 but not a Myo7a Mutation (Citations: 21)

Ralph H. Holme, Karen P. Steel

...to contribute to noise-induced hearing loss. mice homozygous for null mutations...the first gene known to cause deafness in the human population to be linked with predisposition to noise-induced hearing loss....

Journal: Jaro-journal of The Association for Research in Otolaryngology - JARO , vol. 5, no. 1, pp. 66-79, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7144-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7144_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:33:21">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/47756540/mutations-in-the-calcium-binding-motifs-of-cdh23-and-the-35delg-mutation-in-gjb2-cause-hearing-loss</link><title>Mutations in the calcium-binding motifs of CDH23 and the 35delG mutation in GJB2 cause hearing loss in one family</title><description>* Mutations in the calcium-binding motifs of CDH23 and the 35delG mutation in GJB2 cause hearing loss in one family (Citations: 11)

Arjan P. de Brouwer, Ronald J. Pennings, Marjolijn Roeters, Peter Van Hauwe, Lisa M. Astuto, Lies H. Hoefsloot, Patrick L. Huygen, Bellinda van den Helm, Julie M. Bork, William J. Kimberling, Frans P. Cremers, Cor W. Cremershttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=47756540&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=can headphones cause hearing loss

...autosomal recessive non-syndromic childhood hearing loss (dfnb). failure to demonstrate linkage...suggested genetic heterogeneity for the hearing loss in this family. this heterogeneity...

Journal: Human Genetics - HUM GENET , vol. 112, no. 2, pp. 156-163, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7144-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7144_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:34:37">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/59325789/improvement-in-neonatal-hearing-loss-following-treatment-with-thyroxin</link><title>Improvement in neonatal hearing loss following treatment with thyroxin</title><description>* Improvement in neonatal hearing loss following treatment with thyroxin

V M Hickson

...association of thyroid problems and hearing loss to elucidate an explanation for the improvement in hearing when hypothyroidism was treated.resultsthe sensorineural hearing loss in two babies showed an...s syndrome is a known cause of hearing loss associated with thyroid dysfunction in which hearing loss is not thought to respond...

Journal: Archives of Disease in Childhood - ARCH DIS CHILD , vol. 96, no. 1, pp. A31-A32, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7144-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7144_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:35:34">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/34648295/progressive-hearing-loss-and-recurrent-sudden-sensorineural-hearing-loss-associated-with-gjb2</link><title>Progressive hearing loss, and recurrent sudden sensorineural hearing loss associated with GJB2 mutations - phenotypic spectrum and frequencies of GJB2 mutations in Austria</title><description>* Progressive hearing loss, and recurrent sudden sensorineural hearing loss associated with GJB2 mutations - phenotypic spectrum and frequencies of GJB2 mutations in Austria (Citations: 17)

Andreas R. Janecke, Almut Hirst-Stadlmann, Barbara Günther, Barbara Utermann, Thomas Müller, Judith Löffler, Gerd Utermann, Doris Nekahm-Heis

...26) are the most common cause of hearing loss (hl) in different populations, and...patients with non-syndromic sensorineural hearing loss for gjb2 mutations. causative gjb2 mutations were identified in...

Journal: Human Genetics - HUM GENET , vol. 111, no. 2, pp. 145-153, 2002</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7144-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7144_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:36:38">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/14142156/hearing-screening-in-older-adults-a-brief-hearing-loss-screener</link><title>Hearing Screening in Older Adults: A Brief Hearing Loss Screener</title><description>* Hearing Screening in Older Adults: A Brief Hearing Loss Screener

Kathleen Demers

...older have some degree of hearing loss. hearing loss related to normal aging is the most common cause, but other risk factors include...and diseases that affect sensorineural hearing. hearing loss can lead to miscommunication, social withdrawal...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>