<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7146">why do leaves fall</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:38:41" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7146-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7146_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:38:44">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39888477/amphibious-fish-why-do-they-leave-water</link><title>Amphibious fish: why do they leave water?</title><description>* Amphibious fish: why do they leave water? (Citations: 17)

M. D. J. Sayer, J. Davenport

...insight into the reasons for leaving and eventually abandoning the aquatic habitat. amphibious fishes today leave the water for a variety...

Journal: Reviews in Fish Biology and Fisheries - REV FISH BIOL FISHERIES , vol. 1, no. 2, pp. 159-181, 1991</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7146-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7146_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:39:49">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40151094/selective-oviposition-by-a-leaf-miner-in-response-to-temporal-variation-in-abscission</link><title>Selective oviposition by a leaf miner in response to temporal variation in abscission</title><description>* Selective oviposition by a leaf miner in response to temporal variation in abscission (Citations: 30)

Thomas L. Bultman, Stanley H. Faeth

...following tagged mined and unmined leaves revealed that peripheral leaves fall sooner than central leaves and that more cameraria mining peripheral leaves die due to abscission than those mining central leaves. we discuss factors that might influence interactions between leaf miners and abscission of the host-leaves they attack....

Journal: Oecologia , vol. 69, no. 1, pp. 117-120, 1986</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7146-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7146_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:40:59">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4993259/autumn-leaves-seen-through-herbivore-eyes</link><title>Autumn leaves seen through herbivore eyes</title><description>* Autumn leaves seen through herbivore eyes (Citations: 10)

Thomas F. Döring, Marco Archetti, Jim Hardie

why leaves of some trees turn red in autumn has puzzled biologists for decades, as just before leaf fall the pigments causing red coloration...attractive to aphids than green leaves, whereas yellow leaves are much more attractive. we conclude that, while active avoidance of red leaves by aphids is unlikely, red...

Journal: Proceedings of The Royal Society B: Biological Sciences , vol. 276, no. 1654, pp. 121-127, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7146-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7146_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:42:10">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40154965/paradoxical-selective-feeding-on-a-low-nutrient-diet-why-do-mangrove-crabs-eat-leaves</link><title>Paradoxical selective feeding on a low-nutrient diet: why do mangrove crabs eat leaves?</title><description>* Paradoxical selective feeding on a low-nutrient diet: why do mangrove crabs eat leaves? (Citations: 49)

Martin W. Skov, Richard G. Hartnoll

...this is surprising, since mangrove leaves have high tannin contents and...mangroves, and investigated whether burrow leaves had c, n or c/n values significantly different from those of senescent leaves. leaves were found in n. meinerti...

Journal: Oecologia , vol. 131, no. 1, pp. 1-7, 2002</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7146-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7146_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:43:18">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/55272407/retention-of-leaves-by-deciduous-trees</link><title>Retention of Leaves by Deciduous Trees</title><description>* Retention of Leaves by Deciduous Trees

P. T

...concerning the retention of their leaves by young beeches, i beg...case there is no reason why the leaves should fall off for a considerable time...

Journal: Nature , vol. 66, no. 1698, pp. 56-56, 1902</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7146-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7146_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:44:26">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42251471/getting-off-the-escalator-a-study-of-scots-out-migration-from-a-global-city-region</link><title>Getting off the escalator? A study of Scots out-migration from a global city region</title><description>* Getting off the escalator? A study of Scots out-migration from a global city region (Citations: 2)

Allan Findlay, Colin Mason, Richard Harrison, Donald Houston, David McCollum

...labour market. the authors ask why scots are leaving the uk’s main escalator region...findlay et al and ask why people would leave a global city offering good...

Journal: Environment and Planning A - ENVIRON PLAN A , vol. 40, no. 9, pp. 2169-2185, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7146-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7146_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:45:22">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/35718265/take-some-days-off-why-don-t-you</link><title>Take some days off, why don’t you?</title><description>* Take some days off, why don’t you? (Citations: 3)

John Douglas Skåtun

...a model of endogenous sick leave in the presence of endemic infectious diseases. the prevalence rate elasticity with respect to sick leave is unity, when workers are...to the healthy workers. sick leave pay is greater than the healthy working wage. the contracted sick leave period falls with: the external disease transmission...

Journal: Journal of Health Economics - J HEALTH ECON , vol. 22, no. 3, pp. 379-402, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7146-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7146_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:46:25">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/53518566/sugar-maple-phenology-anthocyanin-production-during-leaf-senescence</link><title>Sugar Maple Phenology: Anthocyanin Production During Leaf Senescence</title><description>* Sugar Maple Phenology: Anthocyanin Production During Leaf Senescence

E. Lindgren, B. Rock

...anthocyanin, is synthesized in the fall as chlorophyll slowly degrades. remote sensing data from landsat during fall senescence can help investigate this...will help answer the question, "why do leaves turn red?" one hypothesis is that this pigment acts as a photoprotectant and screens leaves from uv light. it is...

Published in 2007.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7146-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7146_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:47:23">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48172709/remnant-trees-and-the-conservation-of-biodiversity-in-costa-rican-pastures</link><title>Remnant trees and the conservation of biodiversity in Costa Rican pastures</title><description>* Remnant trees and the conservation of biodiversity in Costa Rican pastures (Citations: 63)

C. A. Harvey, W. A. Haber

...interviews with farmers to determine why they leave trees in pastures and how...farmers mentioned 19 reasons for leaving trees in pastures. of these...

Journal: Agroforestry Systems - AGROFOREST SYST , vol. 44, no. 1, pp. 37-68, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7146-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7146_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:48:21">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10517218/sense-of-community-stress-levels-and-discrepancy-between-ideal-perceptions-and-actual-experiences</link><title>Sense of community, stress levels, and discrepancy between ideal perceptions and actual experiences in retaining first year students Research Report 2007-04</title><description>* Sense of community, stress levels, and discrepancy between ideal perceptions and actual experiences in retaining first year students Research Report 2007-04

Marcia J. Belcheir

...there are many reasons students leave college, this study delves into the emotional/psychological side of why students may leave. these issues may be particularly...is available for them without leaving their homes and jobs. what then may cause these students to leave? one reason may be that...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>