<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7147">breast cancer review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:49:22" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7147-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7147_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:49:26">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11176735/tamoxifen-and-breast-density-in-women-at-increased-risk-of-breast-cancer</link><title>Tamoxifen and Breast Density in Women at Increased Risk of Breast Cancer</title><description>* Tamoxifen and Breast Density in Women at Increased Risk of Breast Cancer (Citations: 66)

Jack Cuzick, Jane Warwick, Elizabeth Pinney, Ruth M. L. Warren, Stephen W. Duffy

...density changes are associated with breast cancer risk are unclear. we investigated mammographic breast density in healthy women with an increased risk of breast cancer at baseline and during 54...group) at high risk for breast cancer, from the international breast cancer intervention study i, a trial of tamoxifen for breast cancer prevention. breast density measurements, at baseline and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7147-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7147_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:50:28">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/31005659/predictors-of-perceived-breast-cancer-risk-and-the-relation-between-perceived-risk-and-breast</link><title>Predictors of perceived breast cancer risk and the relation between perceived risk and breast cancer screening: a meta-analytic review</title><description>* Predictors of perceived breast cancer risk and the relation between perceived risk and breast cancer screening: a meta-analytic review (Citations: 80)

Maria C Katapodi, Kathy A Lee, Noreen C Facione, Marylin J Dodd

...variables as predictors of perceived breast cancer risk and the relationship between perceived risk and breast cancer screening. statistical relationships, weighted for...perceived risk influences adherence to breast self-examination. women who perceived a higher breast cancer risk were more likely to...

Journal: Preventive Medicine - PREV MED , vol. 38, no. 4, pp. 388-402, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7147-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7147_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:51:27">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/29063051/adjuvant-dietary-fat-intake-reduction-in-postmenopausal-breast-cancer-patient-management</link><title>Adjuvant dietary fat intake reduction in postmenopausal breast cancer patient management</title><description>* Adjuvant dietary fat intake reduction in postmenopausal breast cancer patient management (Citations: 28)

Rowan T. Chlebowski, David Rose, I. Marilyn Buzzard, George L. Blackburn, William Insull, Mary Grosvenor, Robert Elashoff, Ernst L. Wynder

...outcome of patients with resected breast cancer. the rationale supporting evaluation of dietary fat reduction in the management of patients with localized breast cancer is based on: (1) epidemiologic...outcome in patients with established breast cancer; (3) effects of weight gain (especially that associated with adjuvant chemotherapy) on breast cancer clinical outcome; (4)in vivo...

Journal: Breast Cancer Research and Treatment - BREAST CANCER RES TREAT , vol. 20, no. 2, pp. 73-84, 1991</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7147-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7147_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:52:27">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6912536/lower-category-benign-breast-disease-and-the-risk-of-invasive-breast-cancer</link><title>Lower-Category Benign Breast Disease and the Risk of Invasive Breast Cancer</title><description>* Lower-Category Benign Breast Disease and the Risk of Invasive Breast Cancer (Citations: 29)

Jiping Wang, Joseph R. Costantino, Elizabeth Tan-Chiu, D. Lawrence Wickerham, Soonmyung Paik, Norman Wolmark

...background: the risk of invasive breast cancer associated with benign breast disease (bbd) other than atypical hyper- plasia and in situ breast cancer, especially with nonprolif- erative diagnosis...bbd, of whom 47 developed breast cancer, and of the 9931 women without lc-bbd, 291 developed breast cancer. the rr of breast cancer for women with lc-bbd...

Journal: Obstetrical &amp; Gynecological Survey - OBSTET GYNECOL SURV , vol. 59, no. 8, pp. 590-592, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7147-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7147_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:53:14">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/30383217/health-related-quality-of-life-in-breast-cancer-patients-a-bibliographic-review-of-the-literature</link><title>Health-related quality of life in breast cancer patients: A bibliographic review of the literature from 1974 to 2007</title><description>* Health-related quality of life in breast cancer patients: A bibliographic review of the literature from 1974 to 2007 (Citations: 46)

Ali Montazeri

...measure quality of life in breast cancer patients. the european organization for research and treatment of cancer core cancer quality of life questionnaire (eortc...on quality of life in breast cancer patients. these papers have made a considerable contribution to improving breast cancer care, although their exact benefit...

Journal: Journal of Experimental &amp; Clinical Cancer Research - J EXP CLIN CANCER RES , vol. 27, no. 1, pp. 32-31, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7147-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7147_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:54:18">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48307095/exposures-in-childhood-adolescence-and-early-adulthood-and-breast-cancer-risk-a-systematic-review</link><title>Exposures in Childhood, Adolescence and Early Adulthood and Breast Cancer Risk: a Systematic Review of the Literature</title><description>* Exposures in Childhood, Adolescence and Early Adulthood and Breast Cancer Risk: a Systematic Review of the Literature (Citations: 39)

Mona Okasha, Peter McCarron, David Gunnell, George Davey Smith

...the relationship between birthweight and breast cancer, to suggest that in utero events are related to breast cancer risk in adulthood. strong evidence...or adolescence and risk of breast cancer. the evidence to suggest an association between physical activity in early life and breast cancer risk is convincing from case...

Journal: Breast Cancer Research and Treatment - BREAST CANCER RES TREAT , vol. 78, no. 2, pp. 223-276, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7147-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7147_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:55:19">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39167333/host-microenvironment-in-breast-cancer-development-inflammatory-cells-cytokines-and-chemokines-in</link><title>Host microenvironment in breast cancer development: Inflammatory cells, cytokines and chemokines in breast cancer progression - reciprocal tumor–microenvironment interactions</title><description>* Host microenvironment in breast cancer development: Inflammatory cells, cytokines and chemokines in breast cancer progression - reciprocal tumor–microenvironment interactions (Citations: 51)

A Ben-Baruch

...a comprehensive overview of breast cancer development and progression suggests that...on their potential involvement in breast cancer development and progression....

Journal: Breast Cancer Research - BREAST CANCER RES , vol. 5, no. 1, pp. 31-6, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7147-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7147_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:56:15">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/29075699/the-effect-of-environment-on-breast-cancer-risk</link><title>The Effect of Environment on Breast Cancer Risk</title><description>* The Effect of Environment on Breast Cancer Risk (Citations: 41)

YvonneMarie Coyle

...explain a large proportion of breast cancer incidence. known risk factors for breast cancer, which are related to the...the effects of metals on breast cancer risk. studies suggest that circadian rhythm disruption is linked with breast cancer, but too few studies have...

Journal: Breast Cancer Research and Treatment - BREAST CANCER RES TREAT , vol. 84, no. 3, pp. 273-288, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7147-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7147_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:57:08">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/29080972/racial-and-ethnic-disparities-in-breast-cancer-rates-by-age-naaccr-breast-cancer-project</link><title>Racial and ethnic disparities in breast cancer rates by age: NAACCR Breast Cancer Project</title><description>* Racial and ethnic disparities in breast cancer rates by age: NAACCR Breast Cancer Project (Citations: 26)

Sue A. Joslyn, Mary L. Foote, Kiumarss Nasseri, Steven S. Coughlin, Holly L. Howe

...examine age-specific rates of breast cancer incidence among racial and ethnic...

Journal: Breast Cancer Research and Treatment - BREAST CANCER RES TREAT , vol. 92, no. 2, pp. 97-105, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7147-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7147_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 09:58:11">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/29097062/depression-quality-of-life-and-breast-cancer-a-review-of-the-literature</link><title>Depression, quality of life and breast cancer: a review of the literature</title><description>* Depression, quality of life and breast cancer: a review of the literature (Citations: 39)

M. Reich, A. Lesur, C. Perdrizet-Chevallier

...is misdiagnosed and undertreated among breast cancer population. risk factors for depression...relation between stress, immunity and cancer occurrence or even mortality. breast cancer survivors report a higher prevalence...

Journal: Breast Cancer Research and Treatment - BREAST CANCER RES TREAT , vol. 110, no. 1, pp. 9-17, 2008</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>