<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7154">stones satisfaction</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:52:46" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7154-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7154_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:52:51">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/33113000/is-suprapubic-cystostomy-an-optimal-urinary-management-in-high-quadriplegics</link><title>Is Suprapubic Cystostomy an Optimal Urinary Management in High Quadriplegics?</title><description>* Is Suprapubic Cystostomy an Optimal Urinary Management in High Quadriplegics? (Citations: 14)

T. Mitsui, K. Minami, T. Furuno, H. Morita, T. Koyanagi

...symptomatic genitourinary infection and urinary stone. satisfaction with urinary management was also...of daily activities, and overall satisfaction showed no significant difference between the two groups.conclusion: except for bladder stones, spc is a valuable option...

Journal: European Urology - EUR UROL , vol. 38, no. 4, pp. 434-438, 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7154-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7154_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:54:02">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/37374606/the-mediating-role-of-communication-satisfaction-in-relational-demography-a-study-in-macao-sar</link><title>The mediating role of communication satisfaction in relational demography – a study in Macao, SAR context</title><description>* The mediating role of communication satisfaction in relational demography – a study in Macao, SAR context

Ka Wai Chan, Jia Jun Wu

...of an underlying attribute – communication satisfaction. the results demonstrate that communication satisfaction fully mediates the relationship between hometown diversity and satisfaction with a supervisor. hometown diversity acts as a stepping stone to increase satisfaction at the beginning of the...

Journal: Asia Pacific Business Review , vol. 15, no. 4, pp. 547-564, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7154-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7154_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:55:08">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5308120/repeated-job-quits-stepping-stones-or-learning-about-quality</link><title>Repeated Job Quits: Stepping stones or learning about quality?</title><description>* Repeated Job Quits: Stepping stones or learning about quality? (Citations: 1)

Anne C. Gielen

...gains and higher overall job satisfaction, many workers quit once again...quits serve as a stepping stone to more satisfaction at work....

Published in 2009.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7154-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7154_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:56:29">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/58325201/repeated-job-quits-stepping-stones-or-learning-about-quality</link><title>Repeated Job Quits: Stepping Stones or Learning about Quality?</title><description>* Repeated Job Quits: Stepping Stones or Learning about Quality?

Anne C. Gielen

...gains and higher overall job satisfaction, many workers quit once again...quits serve as a stepping stone to more satisfaction at work....

Published in 2008.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7154-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7154_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:57:44">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/58145006/repeated-job-quits-stepping-stones-or-learning-about-quality</link><title>Repeated Job Quits: Stepping stones or learning about quality?</title><description>* Repeated Job Quits: Stepping stones or learning about quality?

Gielen Anne C

...of job quits and job satisfaction illustrate that the labor market ischaracterized by elements of both explanations. more specifically, a variancedecomposition shows that the stepping stone model explains 80 percent ofrepeated...quits serve as a stepping stone to more satisfaction atwork....

Published in 2008.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7154-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7154_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 10:59:02">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/2383772/the-satisfaction-with-life-scale</link><title>The Satisfaction With Life Scale</title><description>* The Satisfaction With Life Scale (Citations: 2473)

Ed Diener, ROBERT A. EMMONS, Randy Larsen, Sharon Griffin

...scale to measure global life satisfaction, the satisfaction with life scale (swls). among...identified: positive affect, overall life satisfaction. as tatarkiewicz negative affect, and life satisfaction (an- (1976) wrote, ". . .happiness requires...

Journal: Journal of Personality Assessment - J PERSONAL ASSESS , vol. 49, no. 1, pp. 71-75, 1985</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7154-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7154_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:00:11">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/29293025/does-stone-dimension-affect-the-effectiveness-of-ureteroscopic-lithotripsy-in-distal-ureteral</link><title>Does stone dimension affect the effectiveness of ureteroscopic lithotripsy in distal ureteral stones?</title><description>* Does stone dimension affect the effectiveness of ureteroscopic lithotripsy in distal ureteral stones? (Citations: 2)

Volkan Tuğcu, Ali İhsan Taşcı, Emin Özbek, Bekir Aras, Levent Verim, Levent Gürkan

...patients were grouped according to stone dimension; 193 patients with stones smaller than 1 cm being group...the treatment of distal ureteral stones was independent of stone dimension. however, the operative time was longer and the rate of perforation was higher in stones with a diameter ≥1 cm. on...

Journal: International Urology and Nephrology - INT UROL NEPHROL , vol. 40, no. 2, pp. 269-275, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7154-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7154_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:01:16">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57336934/fairness-perceptions-and-satisfaction-with-components-of-pay-satisfaction</link><title>Fairness perceptions and satisfaction with components of pay satisfaction</title><description>* Fairness perceptions and satisfaction with components of pay satisfaction

I. M. Jawahar, Thomas H. Stone

...distributive justice was related to satisfaction with pay level, procedural justice to satisfaction with benefits, raises and pay...managers' ability to influence pay satisfaction. hr policies and managers' behaviors can influence pay satisfaction as much or more than...

Journal: Journal of Managerial Psychology - J MANAG PSYCHOL , vol. 26, no. 4, pp. 297-312, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7154-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7154_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:02:20">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/36782024/the-effects-of-the-ability-to-choose-the-type-of-human-resources-system-on-perceptions-of-invasion</link><title>The Effects of the Ability to Choose the Type of Human Resources System on Perceptions of Invasion of Privacy and System Satisfaction</title><description>* The Effects of the Ability to Choose the Type of Human Resources System on Perceptions of Invasion of Privacy and System Satisfaction (Citations: 2)

Kimberly M. Lukaszewski, Dianna L. Stone, Eugene F. Stone-Romero

...of invasion of privacy and satisfaction with the human resource system...in organizations, and enhancing employee satisfaction with human resource services. implications...

Journal: Journal of Business and Psychology - J BUS PSYCHOL , vol. 23, no. 3, pp. 73-86, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7154-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7154_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:03:26">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/37833925/on-the-transferability-of-traditional-satisfaction-theory-to-non-traditional-employment</link><title>On the transferability of “traditional” satisfaction theory to non-traditional employment relationships: temp agency work satisfaction</title><description>* On the transferability of “traditional” satisfaction theory to non-traditional employment relationships: temp agency work satisfaction (Citations: 5)

Nicole Torka, Birgit Schyns

...sources of temp agency work satisfaction and discuss whether or not these sources differ from those well-known to traditional satisfaction research (i.e. those appropriate...in the paper conclude that satisfaction theory is transferable to temp agency workers, but that future satisfaction research should include less studied...

Journal: Employee Relations , vol. 29, no. 5, pp. 440-457, 2007</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>