<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7161">dodge caliber</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:39:31" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7161-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7161_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:39:33">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6614549/theoretical-studies-of-impulse-propagation-in-serotonergic-axons</link><title>Theoretical studies of impulse propagation in serotonergic axons</title><description>* Theoretical studies of impulse propagation in serotonergic axons (Citations: 3)

Melvyn D. Goldfinger, V. R. Roettger, John C. Pearson

...finite-difference approximation (cooley and dodge 1966). first-order differential equations...

Journal: Biological Cybernetics , vol. 66, no. 5, pp. 399-406, 1992</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7161-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7161_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:40:32">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/2591495/a-model-of-spike-initiation-in-neocortical-pyramidal-neurons</link><title>A Model of Spike Initiation in Neocortical Pyramidal Neurons</title><description>* A Model of Spike Initiation in Neocortical Pyramidal Neurons (Citations: 116)

Zachary F. Mainen, John R. Huguenard, Terrence J. Sejnowski

Summary Neocortical pyramidal cells possess voltage-depend- ent dendritic sodium channels that promote propaga- tion of action potentials into the dendritic tree but para- doxically may fail to originate dendritic spikes. A biophysical model was constructed to reconcile these observations with known anatomical and physioiogi- cai properties. When dendritic and somatic sodium channel densities compatible with electrophysiologi- cal measurements were ...

Journal: Nature , 1995</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7161-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7161_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 11:41:25">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/32683158/a-novel-rat-model-of-carotid-artery-stenting-for-the-understanding-of-restenosis-in-metabolic</link><title>A Novel Rat Model of Carotid Artery Stenting for the Understanding of Restenosis in Metabolic Diseases</title><description>* A Novel Rat Model of Carotid Artery Stenting for the Understanding of Restenosis in Metabolic Diseases (Citations: 30)

Aloke V. Finn, Herman K. Gold, Anita Tang, Deena K. Weber, Thomas N. Wight, Allen Clermont, Renu Virmani, Frank D. Kolodgie

The effects of risk modifiers such as diabetes, obesity and hypertension on vascular healing after stent deployment are largely unknown, because of a lack of an appropriate animal model to study. Since many inbred strains of rats expressing these phenotypes are available, we validated a carotid artery model of in-stent restenosis in the rat. A detailed histomorphometric analysis was ...

Journal: Journal of Vascular Research - J VASC RES , vol. 39, no. 5, pp. 414-425, 2002</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>