<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7165">vice president residence</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:09:47" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7165-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7165_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:09:53">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/12345956/spring-2009-dean-s-list-students-from-springfield-springfield-residents-who-have-been-named-to</link><title>Spring 2009 Dean's List Students (from Springfield) Springfield residents who have been named to the Dean's List for the Spring 2009 semester at Springfield Technical Community College have been announced by Vice President for Academic Affairs Stephen H. Keller. The Dean's List is published each semester to recognize above-average academic performance. Students carrying a full-time course load of 12 or more semester hours of college-level courses, who achieve a quality point average of 3.3 or above, are placed on the Dean's List. Students honored on the list include Idairis Acevedo-Pagan</title><description>* Spring 2009 Dean's List Students (from Springfield) Springfield residents who have been named to the Dean's List for the Spring 2009 semester at Springfield Technical Community College have been announced by Vice President for Academic Affairs Stephen H. Keller. The Dean's List is published each semester to recognize above-average academic performance. Students carrying a full-time course load of 12 or more semester hours of college-level courses, who achieve a quality point average of 3.3 or above, are placed on the Dean's List. Students honored on the list include Idairis Acevedo-Pagan

Bruce Adams, Ajoke Adesina, Olufunmito Aina, Victoria Aina, Lawrence Akers, Marian Ako-Brew, Peter Alicea, Kiryl Alsheuski, Jamal Amimi, Samantha Aquino, Maria Aristud, Whitney Asantehttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=12345956&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=vice president residence</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7165-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7165_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:10:37">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/49517338/federal-grants-and-the-flight-to-the-suburbs-1-1-an-example-of-what-we-have-in-mind-is-the</link><title>Federal grants and the flight to the suburbs 1 1 An example of what we have in mind is the “liveability” agenda pursued by Vice-President Al Gore</title><description>* Federal grants and the flight to the suburbs 1 1 An example of what we have in mind is the “liveability” agenda pursued by Vice-President Al Gore

Akram Temimi, Manfred Dix

...services, it would persuade affluent residents to stay in the city...

Journal: The Quarterly Review of Economics and Finance , vol. 41, no. 4, pp. 533-543, 2001</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7165-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7165_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:11:28">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/918527/new-wine-in-old-skins-or-was-all-this-ferment-really-necessary</link><title>New wine in old skins, or, was all this ferment really necessary?</title><description>* New wine in old skins, or, was all this ferment really necessary?

Sally Webster

...and computing, headed by a vice president, to which both administrative and...of service, because the new vice president could combine and rearrange staffs from two computing units (administrative and academic).furthermore, the vice president convened a campus-wide committee...

Conference: SIGUCCS Conference on User Services , pp. 139-144, 1988</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7165-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7165_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:12:23">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42059034/sky-and-ocean-joined-the-u-s-naval-observatory-1830-2000</link><title>Sky and Ocean Joined-The U.S. Naval Observatory 1830-2000</title><description>* Sky and Ocean Joined-The U.S. Naval Observatory 1830-2000

Bill Carter

...as the location of the vice president's residence. asked to search their memories...

Journal: Eos, Transactions American Geophysical Union , vol. 84, no. 23, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7165-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7165_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:13:11">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/28591819/infection-control-programs-at-children-s-hospitals-a-description-of-structures-and-processes</link><title>Infection control programs at children’s hospitals: A description of structures and processes</title><description>* Infection control programs at children’s hospitals: A description of structures and processes (Citations: 9)

Shirley Girouard, Gail Levine, Kathy Goodrich, Stephanie Jones, Harry Keyserling, Mobeen Rathore, Craig Rubens, Evelyn Williams, William Jarvis

...responsibility for the ic program resided with the medical director (21%); vice president for patient care (18%); quality...

Journal: American Journal of Infection Control - AMER J INFECT CONTROL , vol. 29, no. 3, pp. 145-151, 2001</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7165-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7165_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:13:54">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/892713/history-of-the-development-of-medical-information-systems-at-the-laboratory-of-computer-science-at</link><title>History of the development of medical information systems at the Laboratory of Computer Science at Massachusetts General Hospital</title><description>* History of the development of medical information systems at the Laboratory of Computer Science at Massachusetts General Hospital (Citations: 7)

G. Octo Barnett

...4k with active user programs residing the one of the 2k...thesis of tony gorry (now vice president for institutional development of baylor...

Conference: History of Medical Informatics - HMI , pp. 43-49, 1987</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7165-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7165_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:14:49">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/892727/the-background-of-internist-i-and-qmr</link><title>The background of INTERNIST I and QMR</title><description>* The background of INTERNIST I and QMR (Citations: 3)

J. D. Myers

...of harvard university, established by president james bryant conant in the...supervision by a dean or vice-president. thus the position allows maximal...

Conference: History of Medical Informatics - HMI , pp. 195-197, 1987</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7165-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7165_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:15:36">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57920495/involving-health-care-workers-in-screening-for-alcohol-problems</link><title>Involving Health Care Workers in Screening for Alcohol Problems</title><description>* Involving Health Care Workers in Screening for Alcohol Problems (Citations: 3)

Barbara S McCrady, Stephanie S. Richter, Thomas J. Morgan, John Slade, Carl Pfeifer

...told by the director of residency training or by the vice-president for nursing to administer it...of patients). surgeons and surgical residents recorded alcohol-related information on 30% of their patients. residents were more likely to interview...

Journal: Journal of Addictive Diseases - J ADDICT DIS , vol. 15, no. 3, pp. 45-58, 1996</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7165-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7165_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:16:26">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/58936083/5th-annual-mccarthy-residency-keynote-the-experiences-of-a-humanitarian-crusader-in-a-chaotic</link><title>5th Annual McCarthy Residency Keynote: "The Experiences of a Humanitarian Crusader in a Chaotic World"</title><description>* 5th Annual McCarthy Residency Keynote: "The Experiences of a Humanitarian Crusader in a Chaotic World"

John Chromy

...our annual mccarthy scholar in residency running from monday, march 19th...john chromy as our distinguished resident. mr. chromy is currently serving as the vice president of the cooperating housing foundation...

Published in 2012.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7165-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7165_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:17:15">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/60501978/gulf-coast-resid-processor-succeeds-with-long-range-planning</link><title>Gulf Coast resid processor succeeds with long range planning</title><description>* Gulf Coast resid processor succeeds with long range planning

M. Zanotti, F. Potter, R. Gonzalez

...between martin p. zanotti, executive vice president of valero energy corp. and...special or specifically focused on resid processors, valero's mexican joint...

Published in 2009.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>