<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7167">aluminium extrusion</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:19:07" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7167-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7167_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:19:10">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/26491021/static-and-dynamic-axial-crushing-of-square-thin-walled-aluminium-extrusions</link><title>Static and dynamic axial crushing of square thin-walled aluminium extrusions</title><description>* Static and dynamic axial crushing of square thin-walled aluminium extrusions (Citations: 55)

M. Langseth, O. S. Hopperstad

...behaviour of square thin-walled aluminium extrusions in alloy aa6060 subjected to...

Journal: International Journal of Impact Engineering - INT J IMPACT ENG , vol. 18, no. 7, pp. 949-968, 1996</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7167-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7167_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:19:54">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/26495661/static-crushing-of-square-aluminium-extrusions-with-aluminium-foam-filler</link><title>Static crushing of square aluminium extrusions with aluminium foam filler</title><description>* Static crushing of square aluminium extrusions with aluminium foam filler (Citations: 45)

A. G. Hanssen, M. Langseth, O. S. Hopperstad

...study the behaviour of square aluminium extrusions filled with aluminium foam under quasi-static loading...

Journal: International Journal of Mechanical Sciences - INT J MECH SCI , vol. 41, no. 8, pp. 967-993, 1999</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7167-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7167_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:20:44">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/26491376/static-and-dynamic-crushing-of-square-aluminium-extrusions-with-aluminium-foam-filler</link><title>Static and dynamic crushing of square aluminium extrusions with aluminium foam filler</title><description>* Static and dynamic crushing of square aluminium extrusions with aluminium foam filler (Citations: 56)

A. G. Hanssen, M. Langseth, O. S. Hopperstad

...of triggered, square 80×80mm2 aa6060 aluminium extrusions filled with aluminium foam under both quasi-static...were the foam density, the extrusion wall strength and the extrusion wall thickness. previously proposed design...

Journal: International Journal of Impact Engineering - INT J IMPACT ENG , vol. 24, no. 4, pp. 347-383, 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7167-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7167_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:21:36">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/26491260/crashworthiness-of-aluminium-extrusions-validation-of-numerical-simulation-effect-of-mass-ratio</link><title>Crashworthiness of aluminium extrusions: validation of numerical simulation, effect of mass ratio and impact velocity</title><description>* Crashworthiness of aluminium extrusions: validation of numerical simulation, effect of mass ratio and impact velocity (Citations: 46)

M. Langseth, O. S. Hopperstad, T. Berstad

...and dynamic tests on square aluminium extrusions in alloy aa6060 tempers t4...a small trigger in the extrusion side-wall represented the initial geometrical imperfections. the validated model was used to study the response of square aluminium tubes, varying the mass of...

Journal: International Journal of Impact Engineering - INT J IMPACT ENG , vol. 22, no. 9, pp. 829-854, 1999</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7167-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7167_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:22:24">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/26491384/static-and-dynamic-crushing-of-circular-aluminium-extrusions-with-aluminium-foam-filler</link><title>Static and dynamic crushing of circular aluminium extrusions with aluminium foam filler</title><description>* Static and dynamic crushing of circular aluminium extrusions with aluminium foam filler (Citations: 52)

A. G. Hanssen, M. Langseth, O. S. Hopperstad

...behaviour of triggered, circular aa6060 aluminium extrusions filled with aluminium foam under both quasi-static...were the foam density, the extrusion wall strength and the extrusion wall thickness. based on the...

Journal: International Journal of Impact Engineering - INT J IMPACT ENG , vol. 24, no. 5, pp. 475-507, 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7167-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7167_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:23:12">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/26629759/local-buckling-of-square-thin-walled-aluminium-extrusions</link><title>Local buckling of square thin-walled Aluminium extrusions</title><description>* Local buckling of square thin-walled Aluminium extrusions (Citations: 13)

M. Langseth, O. S. Hopperstad

...behaviour of square thin-walled aluminium extrusions in alloy aa6060. the primary variables have been the temper and wall thickness of the extrusions. furthermore, the classical stowell theory...

Journal: Thin-walled Structures - THIN WALL STRUCT , vol. 27, no. 1, pp. 117-126, 1997</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7167-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7167_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:24:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40479377/3d-fem-simulation-of-the-whole-cycle-of-aluminium-extrusion-throughout-the-transient-state-and-the</link><title>3D FEM simulation of the whole cycle of aluminium extrusion throughout the transient state and the steady state using the updated Lagrangian approach</title><description>* 3D FEM simulation of the whole cycle of aluminium extrusion throughout the transient state and the steady state using the updated Lagrangian approach (Citations: 19)

J. Zhou, L. Li, J. Duszczyk

aluminium extrusion involves the generation of free...a result, the simulation of aluminium extrusion performed so far has been...

Journal: Journal of Materials Processing Technology - J MATER PROCESS TECHNOL , vol. 134, no. 3, pp. 383-397, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7167-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7167_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:24:52">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/26933955/a-comprehensive-failure-model-for-crashworthiness-simulation-of-aluminium-extrusions</link><title>A comprehensive failure model for crashworthiness simulation of aluminium extrusions</title><description>* A comprehensive failure model for crashworthiness simulation of aluminium extrusions (Citations: 19)

H. Hooputra, H. Gese, H. Werner

...compression tests of double chamber extrusion components. all studies presented in this paper were carried out on extrusions made from aluminium alloy en aw-7108 t6...

Journal: International Journal of Crashworthiness - INT J CRASHWORTHINESS , vol. 9, no. 5, pp. 449-464, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7167-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7167_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:25:55">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40659451/tribological-simulation-of-aluminium-hot-extrusion</link><title>Tribological simulation of aluminium hot extrusion</title><description>* Tribological simulation of aluminium hot extrusion (Citations: 13)

Thomas Björk, Jens Bergström, Sture Hogmark

...hot extrusion is a very cost efficient method of aluminium forming. one limitation for further...method proved to simulate realistic extrusion conditions. chemical wear dominates the deterioration for the two surface treatments. both in actual extrusion and in the laboratory tests...

Journal: Wear , vol. 224, no. 2, pp. 216-225, 1999</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7167-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7167_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 12:26:57">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/45085988/extrusion-welding-in-aluminium-extrusion</link><title>Extrusion welding in aluminium extrusion</title><description>* Extrusion welding in aluminium extrusion (Citations: 12)

Henry Valberg

Journal: International Journal of Materials &amp; Product Technology - INT J MATER PROD TECHNOL , vol. 17, no. 7, 2002</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>