<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7173"> severed spinal cord</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:30:20" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7173-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7173_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:30:23">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/36455494/the-relationships-among-the-severity-of-spinal-cord-injury-residual-neurological-function-axon</link><title>The relationships among the severity of spinal cord injury, residual neurological function, axon counts, and counts of retrogradely labeled neurons after experimental spinal cord injury</title><description>* The relationships among the severity of spinal cord injury, residual neurological function, axon counts, and counts of retrogradely labeled neurons after experimental spinal cord injury (Citations: 135)

Michael G. Fehlings, Charles H. Tator

...neurological function may persist after spinal cord injury (sci) with survival of...examined in rats with graded severity of clip compression injury of the cord at t1. the rats were...

Journal: Experimental Neurology - EXP NEUROL , vol. 132, no. 2, pp. 220-228, 1995</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7173-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7173_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:31:00">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/28545575/long-term-adaptation-to-electrically-induced-cycle-training-in-severe-spinal-cord-injured</link><title>Long term adaptation to electrically induced cycle training in severe spinal cord injured individuals</title><description>* Long term adaptation to electrically induced cycle training in severe spinal cord injured individuals (Citations: 65)

T Mohr, J L Andersen, F Biering-Sørensen, H Galbo, J Bangsbo, A Wagner, M Kjaer

spinal cord injured (sci) individuals most often...first 2 years after the spinal cord injury. the muscle in the...

Journal: Spinal Cord , vol. 35, no. 1, pp. 1-16, 1997</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7173-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7173_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:31:24">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/24776562/the-relationships-among-the-severity-of-spinal-cord-injury-motor-and-somatosensory-evoked</link><title>The relationships among the severity of spinal cord injury, motor and somatosensory evoked potentials and spinal cord blood flow</title><description>* The relationships among the severity of spinal cord injury, motor and somatosensory evoked potentials and spinal cord blood flow (Citations: 70)

M FEHLINGS, C TATOR, R LINDEN

Journal: Electroencephalography and Clinical Neurophysiology/evoked Potentials Section , vol. 74, no. 4, pp. 241-259, 1989</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7173-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7173_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:31:50">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/38328389/asymptomatic-spinal-cord-lesions-in-clinically-isolated-optic-nerve-brain-stem-and-spinal-cord</link><title>Asymptomatic spinal cord lesions in clinically isolated optic nerve, brain stem, and spinal cord syndromes suggestive of demyelination</title><description>* Asymptomatic spinal cord lesions in clinically isolated optic nerve, brain stem, and spinal cord syndromes suggestive of demyelination (Citations: 36)

J I O’Riordan, N A Losseff, C Phatouros, A J Thompson, I F Moseley, D G MacManus, W I McDonald, D H Miller

...optic nerve, brain stem, or spinal cord. the objectives of the present...gadolinium enhancing lesions in the spinal cord respectively.conclusionthis high incidence of spinal cord lesions emphasises that asymptomatic demyelinating...

Journal: Journal of Neurology Neurosurgery and Psychiatry - J NEUROL NEUROSURG PSYCHIAT , vol. 64, no. 3, pp. 353-357, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7173-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7173_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:32:06">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4187829/spinal-cord-transplants-enhance-the-recovery-of-locomotor-function-after-spinal-cord-injury-at-birth</link><title>Spinal cord transplants enhance the recovery of locomotor function after spinal cord injury at birth</title><description>* Spinal cord transplants enhance the recovery of locomotor function after spinal cord injury at birth (Citations: 41)

E. Kunkel-Bagden, B. S. Bregman

...recovery of motor function after spinal cord injury at birth. embryonic (e14) spinal cord transplants were placed into the site of a spinal cord “over-hemisection” in rat pups...qualitative and quantitative improvements in several parameters of locomotion. spinal cord transplants at the site of neonatal spinal cord injury result in enhanced sparing...

Journal: Experimental Brain Research - EXP BRAIN RES , vol. 81, no. 1, pp. 25-34, 1990</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7173-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7173_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:32:29">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/36456743/basic-fibroblast-growth-factor-bfgf-enhances-functional-recovery-following-severe-spinal-cord</link><title>Basic Fibroblast Growth Factor (bFGF) Enhances Functional Recovery Following Severe Spinal Cord Injury to the Rat</title><description>* Basic Fibroblast Growth Factor (bFGF) Enhances Functional Recovery Following Severe Spinal Cord Injury to the Rat (Citations: 52)

A. G. Rabchevsky, I. Fugaccia, A. F. Turner, D. A. Blades, M. P. Mattson, S. W. Scheff

...that following a moderate contusion spinal cord injury (sci) to rats, subsequent...the injury in bfgf-treated spinal cords versus controls. optical density measurements of astrocyte and microglial cell immunoreactivity in bfgf-treated spinal cords showed that after 6 weeks...

Journal: Experimental Neurology - EXP NEUROL , vol. 164, no. 2, pp. 280-291, 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7173-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7173_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:32:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/28968922/development-of-post-traumatic-cysts-in-the-spinal-cord-of-rats-subjected-to-severe-spinal-cord</link><title>Development of post-traumatic cysts in the spinal cord of rats subjected to severe spinal cord contusion</title><description>* Development of post-traumatic cysts in the spinal cord of rats subjected to severe spinal cord contusion (Citations: 28)

Gabriel Guizar-Sahagun, Israel Grijalva, Ignacio Madrazo, Rebecca Franco-Bourland, Hermelinda Salgado, Antonio Ibarra, Elena Oliva, Armando Zepeda

Journal: Surgical Neurology - SURG NEUROL , vol. 41, no. 3, pp. 241-249, 1994</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7173-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7173_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:33:12">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4220805/fetal-spinal-cord-transplants-support-growth-of-supraspinal-and-segmental-projections-after</link><title>Fetal Spinal Cord Transplants Support Growth of Supraspinal and Segmental Projections after Cervical Spinal Cord Hemisection in the Neonatal Rat</title><description>* Fetal Spinal Cord Transplants Support Growth of Supraspinal and Segmental Projections after Cervical Spinal Cord Hemisection in the Neonatal Rat (Citations: 42)

Pamela S. Diener, Barbara S. Bregman

...cervical spinal cord injury at birth permanently disrupts fore- limb function in goal-directed reaching. transplants of fetal spinal cord tissue permit the development of...rats received a cer- vical spinal cord overhemisection with or without transplanta- tion of fetal spinal cord tissue (embryonic day 14); unoperated...

Published in 1998.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7173-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7173_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:33:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/28573096/increased-production-of-reactive-oxygen-species-contributes-to-motor-neuron-death-in-a-compression</link><title>Increased production of reactive oxygen species contributes to motor neuron death in a compression mouse model of spinal cord injury</title><description>* Increased production of reactive oxygen species contributes to motor neuron death in a compression mouse model of spinal cord injury (Citations: 34)

W Xu, L Chi, R Xu, Y Ke, C Luo, J Cai, M Qiu, D Gozal, R Liu

...neuron apoptosis resulted from compression spinal cord injury.results:ros production was shown to be elevated in the lesioned spinal cord as detected by fluorescent oxidation...expression, were significantly increased after spinal cord injury. lipid peroxidation and nucleic acid oxidation were also elevated in the lesioned spinal cord and motor neurons. cytochrome c...

Journal: Spinal Cord , vol. 43, no. 4, pp. 204-213, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7173-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7173_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:34:29">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/13235099/severe-spinal-cord-involvement-is-a-universal-feature-of-asians-with-multiple-sclerosis-a-joint</link><title>Severe spinal cord involvement is a universal feature of Asians with multiple sclerosis: A joint Asian study</title><description>* Severe spinal cord involvement is a universal feature of Asians with multiple sclerosis: A joint Asian study (Citations: 10)

Heng Thay CHONG, Patrick CK LI, Benjamin ONG, Kwang Ho LEE, Ching Piao TSAI, Bhim S SINGHAL, Naraporn PRAYOORWIWAT, Chong Tin TAN

...of the patient had optic-spinal recurrent and 60% had western...tonic spasm, long segment of spinal cord lesion in mri, and low rate of positive cerebrospinal fluid oligoclonal band. severe involvement of spinal cord is thus a universal feature...

Published in 2002.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>