<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7174">seal team 6</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:34:51" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7174-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7174_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:34:53">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40204010/seals-at-sea-modelling-seal-distribution-in-the-german-bight-based-on-aerial-survey-data</link><title>Seals at sea: modelling seal distribution in the German bight based on aerial survey data</title><description>* Seals at sea: modelling seal distribution in the German bight based on aerial survey data

Helena Herr, M. Scheidat, K. Lehnert, U. Siebert

...an important habitat for harbour seals and grey seals. they regularly haul-out on...be relevant predictor variables for seal density. density surface modelling allowed for a depiction of seal distribution in the study area...

Journal: Marine Biology - MAR BIOL , vol. 156, no. 5, pp. 811-820, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7174-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7174_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:35:15">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4918164/observed-prosocial-and-antisocial-behaviors-in-male-soccer-teams-age-differences-across</link><title>Observed Prosocial and Antisocial Behaviors in Male Soccer Teams: Age Differences across Adolescence and the Role of Motivational Variables</title><description>* Observed Prosocial and Antisocial Behaviors in Male Soccer Teams: Age Differences across Adolescence and the Role of Motivational Variables (Citations: 10)

Maria Kavussanu, Alistair R. Seal, Daniel R. Phillips

...and antisocial behaviors in soccer teams, age differences in observed behaviors...group was represented by eight teams. players were filmed during a...

Journal: Journal of Applied Sport Psychology - J APPL SPORT PSYCHOL , vol. 18, no. 4, pp. 326-344, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7174-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7174_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:35:42">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/60605221/environmental-management-waste-management-facility-proxy-waste-lot-profile-6-999-for-building-k-25</link><title>Environmental Management Waste Management Facility Proxy Waste Lot Profile 6.999 for Building K-25 West Wing, East Tennessee Technology Park, Oak Ridge, Tennessee</title><description>* Environmental Management Waste Management Facility Proxy Waste Lot Profile 6.999 for Building K-25 West Wing, East Tennessee Technology Park, Oak Ridge, Tennessee

Rigsby V. P

...lines; (2) process piping; (3) seal exhaust headers; (4) seal exhaust traps; (5) process valves; (6) differential blind multipliers (dbm)/partial...commingled waste lot. on january 6, 2009, a meeting was held with epa, tdec, doe and the team for the sole purpose of...

Published in 2009.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7174-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7174_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:36:00">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/30906018/effects-of-script-based-role-play-in-cardiopulmonary-resuscitation-team-training</link><title>Effects of script-based role play in cardiopulmonary resuscitation team training</title><description>* Effects of script-based role play in cardiopulmonary resuscitation team training

Sung Phil Chung, Junho Cho, Yoo Seok Park, Hyung Goo Kang, Chan Woong Kim, Keun Jeong Song, Hoon Lim, Gyu Chong Cho

...of educational intervention for cpr team training. fourteen teams, each consisting of five members...in dynamics (c: 9.1±12.6 vs s: 7.4±13.7, p=0.715), performance (c: 5.5±11.4 vs s: 4.7±9.6, p=0.838) and total...

Journal: Emergency Medicine Journal - EMERG MED J , vol. 28, no. 8, pp. 690-694, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7174-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7174_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:36:30">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/60599920/dismantling-of-radium226-coal-level-gauges-encountered-problems-and-how-to-solve</link><title>Dismantling of Radium226 Coal Level Gauges: Encountered Problems and How to Solve</title><description>* Dismantling of Radium226 Coal Level Gauges: Encountered Problems and How to Solve

M. Punnachaiya, P. Nuanjan, K. Moombansao, T. Sawangsri, P. Pruantonsai, K. Srichom

...the 2 mci (20 pieces), 6 mci (20 pieces) and 6.6 mci (30 pieces) of ra...conditioning period, each of the 6 mci and 6.6 mci sources were dismantled and...

Published in 2006.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7174-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7174_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:36:57">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/33934053/electrothermal-bipolar-vessel-sealing-device-vs-ultrasonic-coagulating-shears-in-laparoscopic</link><title>Electrothermal bipolar vessel sealing device vs. ultrasonic coagulating shears in laparoscopic colectomies: a comparative study</title><description>* Electrothermal bipolar vessel sealing device vs. ultrasonic coagulating shears in laparoscopic colectomies: a comparative study (Citations: 17)

Roberto Campagnacci, Angelo de Sanctis, Maddalena Baldarelli, Massimiliano Rimini, Giovanni Lezoche, Mario Guerrieri

...clips, and electrothermal bipolar vessel sealing (ebvs) are currently used according...hospital stay (5.2 vs. 6.1, 6.5 vs. 7.1, and 6.8 vs 7.3 days...

Journal: Surgical Endoscopy and Other Interventional Techniques - SURG ENDOSC , vol. 21, no. 9, pp. 1526-1531, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7174-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7174_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:37:22">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39205773/a-multidisciplinary-primary-care-team-consultation-in-a-socio-economically-deprived-community-an</link><title>A multidisciplinary primary care team consultation in a socio-economically deprived community: An exploratory randomised controlled trial</title><description>* A multidisciplinary primary care team consultation in a socio-economically deprived community: An exploratory randomised controlled trial

Wai-Sun Chan, David L Whitford, Ronan Conroy, David Gibney, Brid Hollywood

...of a lengthened multi-disciplinary team consultation in primary care in...intervention and control groups after 6 months and 12 months in all of the measured outcomes. conclusions: the new lengthened multi-disciplinary team consultation did not have any...

Journal: BMC Health Services Research - BMC HEALTH SERV RES , vol. 11, no. 1, pp. 15-8, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7174-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7174_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:37:44">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40203581/foraging-behaviour-of-sympatric-antarctic-and-subantarctic-fur-seals-does-their-contrasting</link><title>Foraging behaviour of sympatric Antarctic and subantarctic fur seals: does their contrasting duration of lactation make a difference?</title><description>* Foraging behaviour of sympatric Antarctic and subantarctic fur seals: does their contrasting duration of lactation make a difference? (Citations: 1)

Sebastián P. Luque, John P. Y. Arnould, Edward H. Miller, Yves Cherel, Christophe Guinet

...subantarctic (a. tropicalis, sfs) fur seals were compared at iles crozet...diving behaviour differed between fur seal species. ofts were more frequent...

Journal: Marine Biology - MAR BIOL , vol. 152, no. 1, pp. 213-224, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7174-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7174_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:38:03">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/60599919/conditioning-of-the-4-curies-radium226-sealed-radiation-source-in-thailand</link><title>Conditioning of the 4 Curies Radium226 Sealed Radiation Source in Thailand</title><description>* Conditioning of the 4 Curies Radium226 Sealed Radiation Source in Thailand

M. Punnachaiya, T. Sawangsri, P. Wanabongse, P. Pruantonsai, P. Nunjan, A. Phattanasub, N. Ya-Anant, S. Thiangtrongjit

...curies radium-226 (ra-226) sealed radiation source using as a...and budgetary supports, comprised of 6 operational steps: the surface dose...

Published in 2006.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7174-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7174_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:38:40">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/33898456/bipolar-vessel-sealing-increases-operative-safety-in-laparoscopic-assisted-vaginal-hysterectomy</link><title>Bipolar vessel sealing increases operative safety in laparoscopic-assisted vaginal hysterectomy</title><description>* Bipolar vessel sealing increases operative safety in laparoscopic-assisted vaginal hysterectomy (Citations: 1)

Kazem Nouri, Johannes Ott, Maurus Demmel, Regina Promberger, Johannes C. Huber, Klaus Mayerhofer

...with and without bipolar vessel sealing (bvs) using the ligasure™ device...05); 15 out of 251 (6.0%) patients were found to...

Journal: Archives of Gynecology and Obstetrics - ARCH GYNECOL OBSTET , vol. 283, no. 1, pp. 91-95, 2011</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>