<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7176"> weather in nyc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:42:29" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7176-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7176_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:42:30">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11980727/forecast-issues-in-the-urban-zone-report-of-the-10th-prospectus-development-team-of-the-u-s</link><title>Forecast Issues in the Urban Zone: Report of the 10th Prospectus Development Team of the U.S. Weather Research Program</title><description>* Forecast Issues in the Urban Zone: Report of the 10th Prospectus Development Team of the U.S. Weather Research Program (Citations: 20)

Walter F. Dabberdt, Jeremy Hales, Steven Zubrick, Andrew Crook, Witold Krajewski, J. Christopher Doran, Cynthia Mueller, Clark King, Ronald N. Keener, Robert Bornstein, David Rodenhuis, Paul Kocinhttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=11980727&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query= weather in nyc

...the short-term prediction of weather and air quality in urban forecast zones. weather has special and significant impacts...u.s. population who live in major urban areas. it is recognized that urban users have different weather information needs than do their...

Journal: Bulletin of The American Meteorological Society - BULL AMER METEOROL SOC , vol. 81, no. 9, 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7176-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7176_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:42:54">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57509840/weather-effects-on-earnings-response-coefficients-international-evidence</link><title>Weather effects on earnings response coefficients: international evidence</title><description>* Weather effects on earnings response coefficients: international evidence

Chien-Ju Lu, Chen-Lung Chin, Yuanchen Chang

...with unexpected earnings and with weather measures. investors in some countries respond more negatively...we also find an asymmetric weather effect that is more significant for bad earnings announcements, on average. moreover, the extent of this weather effect is less for countries...

Journal: Asia-pacific Journal of Accounting &amp; Economics - ASIA-PAC J ACCOUNT ECON , vol. ahead-of-p, no. ahead-of-p, pp. 1-19, 2012</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7176-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7176_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:43:24">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/54659833/wind-field-measurements-for-the-mitigation-of-airborne-health-threats-in-a-complex-urban-environment</link><title>Wind field measurements for the mitigation of airborne health threats in a complex urban environment</title><description>* Wind field measurements for the mitigation of airborne health threats in a complex urban environment

Mark Arend, David Santoro, Sameh Abdelazim, Fred Moshary, Sam Ahmed

...urban dispersion program (udp) resulted in the strategic placement of weather instruments in new york city (nyc) and the transition of some...winds above city building tops. in order to extend the observational capabilities of the nyc metnet, a cost effective portable...

Published in 2009.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7176-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7176_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:43:42">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/52213391/one-hundred-years-of-new-york-city-s</link><title>One Hundred Years of New York City's</title><description>* One Hundred Years of New York City's

J. E. Rosenthal, K. M. Knowlton, C. Rosenzweig, R. Goldberg, P. L. Kinney

...a heat island effect existing in nyc, with mean temperatures in the nycp station generally higher...century between the mean temperature in nyc and its surrounding rural areas, and this difference increased over the twentieth century. there was a significant decrease in the monthly and seasonal variability...

Published in 2003.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7176-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7176_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:44:09">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/52141074/modeling-ozone-plumes-observed-downwind-of-new-york-city-over-the-north-atlantic-ocean-during-the</link><title>Modeling ozone plumes observed downwind of New York City over the North Atlantic Ocean during the ICARTT field campaign</title><description>* Modeling ozone plumes observed downwind of New York City over the North Atlantic Ocean during the ICARTT field campaign

S.-H. Lee, S.-W. Kim, G. J. Frost, S. A. McKeen, O. R. Cooper, F. Flocke, J. S. Holloway, J. A. Neuman, T. Ryerson, C. J. Senff, A. L. Swanson, A. M. Thompson

...chemical transformation of the simulated nyc urban plumes using wrf-chem results showed that the pollutants can be efficiently transported in (isentropic) layers in the lower atmosphere (&lt;2...decoupling by cessation of turbulence in the stable mbl. the o3 mixing ratio in the nyc urban plumes remained at 80...

Journal: Atmospheric Chemistry and Physics Discussions , vol. 11, pp. 14031-14089, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7176-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7176_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:44:31">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/55342274/modeling-ozone-plumes-observed-downwind-of-new-york-city-over-the-north-atlantic-ocean-during-the</link><title>Modeling ozone plumes observed downwind of New York City over the North Atlantic Ocean during the ICARTT field campaign</title><description>* Modeling ozone plumes observed downwind of New York City over the North Atlantic Ocean during the ICARTT field campaign

S.-H. Lee, S.-W. Kim, G. J. Frost, S. A. McKeen, O. R. Cooper, F. Flocke, J. S. Holloway, J. A. Neuman, T. Ryerson, C. J. Senff, A. L. Swanson, A. M. Thompson

...chemical transformation of the simulated nyc urban plumes using wrf-chem results showed that the pollutants can be efficiently transported in (isentropic) layers in the lower atmosphere (&lt;2...decoupling by cessation of turbulence in the stable mbl. the o3 mixing ratio in the nyc urban plumes remained at 80...

Journal: Atmospheric Chemistry and Physics - ATMOS CHEM PHYS , vol. 11, pp. 7375-7397, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7176-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7176_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:44:52">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10408121/urban-heat-islands-and-summertime-convective-thunderstorms-in-atlanta-three-case-studies</link><title>Urban heat islands and summertime convective thunderstorms in Atlanta: three case studies</title><description>* Urban heat islands and summertime convective thunderstorms in Atlanta: three case studies (Citations: 94)

Robert Bornstein, Qinglu Lin

...data from both 27 sites in the atlanta mesonet surface meteorological network and eight national weather service sites were analyzed for...shown that new york city (nyc) effects summer daytime thunderstorm formation and/or movement. that study found that during nearly calm regional flow conditions, the nyc uhi initiates convective activity. moving...

Journal: Atmospheric Environment - ATMOS ENVIRON , vol. 34, no. 3, pp. 507-516, 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7176-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7176_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:45:25">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/55813520/forecasting-for-new-york-city-and-its-surroundings-with-emphasis-on-sea-surface-temperature-s</link><title>Forecasting for New York City and its Surroundings, with Emphasis on Sea-Surface Temperature's Effect on Sea Breezes and Other Coastal Circulations that Influence Air Quality</title><description>* Forecasting for New York City and its Surroundings, with Emphasis on Sea-Surface Temperature's Effect on Sea Breezes and Other Coastal Circulations that Influence Air Quality

J. C. Knievel, D. L. Rife, J. A. Grim

...responders, and anyone else interested in the challenges of predicting transport and dispersion in urban settings. the research applications...focused on new york city (nyc) and its urban and suburban surroundings. the system is based on the weather research and forecasting (wrf) model...

Published in 2008.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7176-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7176_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:45:45">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48394570/mesoscale-aspects-of-the-urban-heat-island-around-new-york-city</link><title>Mesoscale aspects of the Urban Heat Island around New York City</title><description>* Mesoscale aspects of the Urban Heat Island around New York City (Citations: 26)

S. D. Gedzelman, S. Austin, R. Cermak, N. Stefano, S. Partridge, S. Quesenberry, D. A. Robinson

...uhi) of new york city (nyc) is performed using a mesoscale network of weather stations. in all seasons the uhi switches on rapidly in late afternoon and shuts down...dawn. it averages about 4 °c in summer and autumn and 3 °c in winter and spring. it is...

Journal: Theoretical and Applied Climatology - THEOR APPL CLIMATOL , vol. 75, no. 1, pp. 29-42, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7176-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7176_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:46:06">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/56113877/the-new-york-city-research-initiative-a-model-for-undergraduate-and-high-school-student-research</link><title>The New York City Research Initiative: A Model for Undergraduate and High School Student Research in Earth and Space Sciences and Space Technology</title><description>* The New York City Research Initiative: A Model for Undergraduate and High School Student Research in Earth and Space Sciences and Space Technology

F. Scalzo, J. Frost, B. E. Carlson, P. Marchese, C. Rosenzweig, S. A. Austin, D. M. Peteet, L. Druyan, M. Fulakeza, S. Gaffin, H. Baruh, S. Deckerhttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=56113877&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query= weather in nyc

...and rain effects, decadal changes in aerosol and asthma, variations in salinity and river discharge in the hudson river estuary, environmental change in the hudson estuary wetlands, verification...developed for nor'easters, solar weather and tropical cyclone activity, tropospheric and stratospheric ozone investigation in metropolitan nyc, aerosol optical depth through use...

Published in 2010.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>