<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7215">squamous cell carcinoma</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:10:13" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7215-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7215_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:10:18">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/32595325/oesophageal-squamous-cell-carcinoma-i-a-critical-review-of-surgery</link><title>Oesophageal squamous cell carcinoma: I. A critical review of surgery</title><description>* Oesophageal squamous cell carcinoma: I. A critical review of surgery (Citations: 344)

Richard Earlam, J. R. Cunha-Melo

Journal: British Journal of Surgery - BRIT J SURG , vol. 67, no. 6, pp. 381-390, 1980</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7215-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7215_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:10:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/15139065/a-role-for-sunlight-in-skin-cancer-uv-induced-p53-mutations-in-squamous-cell-carcinoma</link><title>A role for sunlight in skin cancer: UV-induced p53 mutations in squamous cell carcinoma</title><description>* A role for sunlight in skin cancer: UV-induced p53 mutations in squamous cell carcinoma (Citations: 578)

D. E. Brash, J. A. Rudolph, J. A. Simon, A. Lin, G. J. McKenna, H. P. Baden, J. Ponten

...major epidemiologic risk factor for squamous cell carcinoma of the skin. of the...14/24 (58%) of invasive squamous cell carcinomas of the skin contain mutations...

Journal: Proceedings of The National Academy of Sciences - PNAS , vol. 88, no. 22, pp. 10124-10128, 1991</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7215-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7215_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:14:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5282164/radiotherapy-plus-cetuximab-for-squamous-cell-carcinoma-of-the-head-and-neck</link><title>Radiotherapy plus Cetuximab for Squamous-Cell Carcinoma of the Head and Neck</title><description>* Radiotherapy plus Cetuximab for Squamous-Cell Carcinoma of the Head and Neck (Citations: 954)

James A. Bonner, Paul M. Harari, Jordi Giralt, Nozar Azarnia, Dong M. Shin, Roger B. Cohen, Christopher U. Jones, Ranjan Sur, David Raben, Jacek Jassem, Roger Ove, Merrill S. Kieshttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=5282164&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=squamous cell carcinoma

Journal: New England Journal of Medicine - N ENGL J MED , vol. 354, no. 6, pp. 567-578, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7215-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7215_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:14:27">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/31642407/pretreatment-oxygenation-predicts-radiation-response-in-advanced-squamous-cell-carcinoma-of-the</link><title>Pretreatment oxygenation predicts radiation response in advanced squamous cell carcinoma of the head and neck</title><description>* Pretreatment oxygenation predicts radiation response in advanced squamous cell carcinoma of the head and neck (Citations: 372)

Marianne Nordsmark, Marie Overgaard, Jens Overgaard

...background and purpose: hypoxic tumor cells are known to be relatively...and radiation response in advanced squamous cell carcinomas of head and neck.methods...

Journal: Radiotherapy and Oncology - RADIOTHER ONCOL , vol. 41, no. 1, pp. 31-39, 1996</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7215-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7215_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:17:10">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/30252593/oxygen-distribution-in-squamous-cell-carcinoma-metastases-and-its-relationship-to-outcome-of</link><title>Oxygen distribution in squamous cell carcinoma metastases and its relationship to outcome of radiation therapy</title><description>* Oxygen distribution in squamous cell carcinoma metastases and its relationship to outcome of radiation therapy (Citations: 253)

Robert A. Gatenby, Howard B. Kessler, Jay S. Rosenblum, Lawrence R. Coia, Philip J. Moldofsky, William H. Hartz, George J. Broder

Journal: International Journal of Radiation Oncology Biology Physics - INT J RADIAT ONCOL BIOL PHYS , vol. 14, no. 5, pp. 831-838, 1988</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7215-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7215_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:19:25">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/30048944/postoperative-concurrent-radiotherapy-and-chemotherapy-for-high-risk-squamous-cell-carcinoma-of-the</link><title>Postoperative Concurrent Radiotherapy and Chemotherapy for High-Risk Squamous-Cell Carcinoma of the Head and Neck</title><description>* Postoperative Concurrent Radiotherapy and Chemotherapy for High-Risk Squamous-Cell Carcinoma of the Head and Neck (Citations: 476)

Jay S. Cooper, Thomas F. Pajak, Arlene A. Forastiere, John Jacobs, Bruce H. Campbell, Scott B. Saxman, Julie A. Kish, Harold E. Kim, Anthony J. Cmelak, Marvin Rotman, Mitchell Machtay, John F. Ensleyhttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=30048944&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=squamous cell carcinoma

Journal: New England Journal of Medicine - N ENGL J MED , vol. 350, no. 19, pp. 1937-1944, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7215-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7215_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:23:12">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/30230942/distribution-of-cervical-lymph-node-metastases-from-squamous-cell-carcinoma-of-the-upper</link><title>Distribution of cervical lymph node metastases from squamous cell carcinoma of the upper respiratory and digestive tracts</title><description>* Distribution of cervical lymph node metastases from squamous cell carcinoma of the upper respiratory and digestive tracts (Citations: 262)

Robert Lindberg

Journal: Cancer , vol. 29, no. 6, pp. 1446-1449, 1972</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7215-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7215_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:25:20">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6828690/epidermal-growth-factor-receptor-blockade-with-c225-modulates-proliferation-apoptosis-and</link><title>Epidermal Growth Factor Receptor Blockade with C225 Modulates Proliferation, Apoptosis, and Radiosensitivity in Squamous Cell Carcinomas of the Head and Neck1</title><description>* Epidermal Growth Factor Receptor Blockade with C225 Modulates Proliferation, Apoptosis, and Radiosensitivity in Squamous Cell Carcinomas of the Head and Neck1 (Citations: 241)

Shyh-Min Huang, Jonathan M. Bock, Paul M. Harari

...clonal antibody c225 on proliferation, cell cycle phase distribution, apoptosis, and radiosensitivity in squamous cell carcinoma (scc) cell lines derived from head and...c225 treatment induces accumulation of cells in g1, which is accompanied by a 2-3-fold decrease in the percentage of cells in s phase. c225 exposure...

Published in 1999.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7215-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7215_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:27:12">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/30149972/a-radiation-therapy-oncology-group-rtog-phase-iii-randomized-study-to-compare-hyperfractionation</link><title>A radiation therapy oncology group (RTOG) phase III randomized study to compare hyperfractionation and two variants of accelerated fractionation to standard fractionation radiotherapy for head and neck squamous cell carcinomas: first report of RTOG 9003</title><description>* A radiation therapy oncology group (RTOG) phase III randomized study to compare hyperfractionation and two variants of accelerated fractionation to standard fractionation radiotherapy for head and neck squamous cell carcinomas: first report of RTOG 9003 (Citations: 396)

Karen K. Fu, Thomas F. Pajak, Andy Trotti, Christopher U. Jones, Sharon A. Spencer, Theodore L. Phillips, Adam S. Garden, John A. Ridge, Jay S. Cooper, K. Kian Ang

Purpose: The optimal fractionation schedule for radiotherapy of head and neck cancer has been controversial. The objective of this randomized trial was to test the efficacy of hyperfractionation and two types of accelerated fractionation individually against standard fractionation.Methods and Materials: Patients with locally advanced head and neck cancer were randomly assigned to receive radiotherapy delivered with: 1) standard fractionation ...

Journal: International Journal of Radiation Oncology Biology Physics - INT J RADIAT ONCOL BIOL PHYS , vol. 48, no. 1, pp. 7-16, 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7215-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7215_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:29:36">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/3409165/molecular-assessment-of-histopathologi-cal-staging-in-squamous-cell-carcinoma-of-the-head-and-neck</link><title>Molecular assessment of histopathologi-cal staging in squamous-cell carcinoma of the head and neck</title><description>* Molecular assessment of histopathologi-cal staging in squamous-cell carcinoma of the head and neck (Citations: 263)

Ja Brennan, L Mao, Rh Hruban

Published in 1995.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>