<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7217">who was lincolns vice president</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:53:15" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7217-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7217_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:53:16">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/63170/in-search-of-owners-lessons-of-experience-with-privatization-and-corporate-governance-in</link><title>In Search of Owners: Lessons of Experience with Privatization and Corporate Governance in Transition Economies</title><description>* In Search of Owners: Lessons of Experience with Privatization and Corporate Governance in Transition Economies (Citations: 5)

Cheryl W. Gray

...the chief economist and senior vice president, development economics --- was produced as a background paper...

Published in 1999.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7217-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7217_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:54:15">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10036597/presidential-address-john-parkes</link><title>PRESIDENTIAL ADDRESS: JOHN PARKES</title><description>* PRESIDENTIAL ADDRESS: JOHN PARKES

J. P. PARKES

...john parkes was born in marton, went to...on council and as secretary, vice-president, and president. feral goats: designing solutions for...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7217-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7217_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:56:45">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42775922/the-tug-of-war-between-cash-flow-and-institutional-values-in-a-college-seminary-merger</link><title>The Tug-of-War Between Cash Flow and Institutional Values in a College-Seminary Merger</title><description>* The Tug-of-War Between Cash Flow and Institutional Values in a College-Seminary Merger

ASBJORN OSLAND, MARK ANKENY

...institutional perspective and resource dependency was evident in how fru dealt with its seminary during the time of the case study (1996–2002). the seminary was clearly christian and had lost...in the perspective of the president, vice president for academic affairs, and the board, the seminary was categorized as an adult program...

Journal: Journal of Research on Christian Education , vol. 16, no. 1, pp. 103-123, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7217-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7217_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:58:54">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57675992/gender-and-student-reception-of-a-seminary-s-dominant-messages</link><title>Gender and Student Reception of a Seminary's Dominant Messages</title><description>* Gender and Student Reception of a Seminary's Dominant Messages

Timothy D. Lincoln

Theological schools seek to educate both women and men to serve the church and promote the study of religion. This education involves constant messaging through multiple channels. This article explores the central messages received by theological students at one free-standing Presbyterian seminary in the United States. Women commonly reported two messages, a message about community (relationships between students) and ...

Journal: Christian Higher Education , vol. 11, no. 3, pp. 205-218, 2012</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7217-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7217_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:59:53">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6334225/developmental-and-genetic-determinants-of-leadership-role-occupancy-among-women</link><title>Developmental and Genetic Determinants of Leadership Role Occupancy Among Women</title><description>* Developmental and Genetic Determinants of Leadership Role Occupancy Among Women (Citations: 17)

Richard D. Arvey, Zhen Zhang, Bruce J. Avolio, Robert F. Krueger

...variance in leadership role occupancy was associated with heritability. the 2...only the work experience factor was significantly related to leadership role...

Journal: Journal of Applied Psychology - J APPL PSYCHOL , vol. 92, no. 3, pp. 693-706, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7217-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7217_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:02:33">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5672362/working-with-generation-d-adopting-and-adapting-to-cultural-learning-and-change</link><title>Working with Generation-D: adopting and adapting to cultural learning and change</title><description>* Working with Generation-D: adopting and adapting to cultural learning and change (Citations: 6)

Win Shih, Martha Allen

Purpose – The paper aims to discuss the expectations and needs of Generation Y students for higher education specifically targeting issues relating to libraries and library management. Design/methodology/approach – The paper provides a brief overview of Generation Y personality traits and characteristics. This is followed by a discussion of organizational culture, explaining how to effectively adapt to meet the expectations ...

Journal: Library Management , vol. 28, no. 1/2, pp. 89-100, 2007</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>