<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7218">edward kennedy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:04:09" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7218-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7218_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:04:10">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57599414/a-pentadic-analysis-of-senator-edward-kennedy-s-address-to-the-people-of-massachusetts-july-25</link><title>A pentadic analysis of senator Edward Kennedy's address to the people of massachusetts, July 25, 1969</title><description>* A pentadic analysis of senator Edward Kennedy's address to the people of massachusetts, July 25, 1969 (Citations: 25)

David A. Ling

...examination was made of senator edward kennedy's address of july 25, 1969. that analysis suggests that the speech depicted kennedy as the victim of a...

Journal: Communication Studies , vol. 21, no. 2, pp. 81-86, 1970</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7218-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7218_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:05:30">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5666036/multi-hop-whistler-mode-elf-vlf-signals-and-triggered-emissions-excited-by-the-haarp-hf-heater</link><title>Multi-hop whistler-mode ELF/VLF signals and triggered emissions excited by the HAARP HF heater</title><description>* Multi-hop whistler-mode ELF/VLF signals and triggered emissions excited by the HAARP HF heater (Citations: 25)

M. Golkowski, D. L. Carpenter, N. Reddell, R. C. Moore, T. F. Bell, E. Paschal, P. Kossey, E. Kennedy, S. Z. Meth

Modulated heating of the lower ionosphere with the HAARP HF heater is used to excite 1-2 kHz signals observed on a ship-borne receiver in the geomagnetic conjugate hemisphere after propagating as ducted whistler-mode signals. These 1-hop signals are believed to be amplified, and are accompanied by triggered emissions. Simultaneous observations near (~30 km) HAARP show 2-...

Journal: Geophysical Research Letters - GEOPHYS RES LETT , vol. 312, no. 24, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7218-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7218_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:09:45">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42039923/the-wind-haarp-experiment-initial-results-of-high-power-radiowave-interactions-with-space-plasmas</link><title>The WIND-HAARP experiment: Initial results of high power radiowave interactions with space plasmas</title><description>* The WIND-HAARP experiment: Initial results of high power radiowave interactions with space plasmas (Citations: 16)

P. Rodriguez, E. J. Kennedy, M. J. Keskinen, C. L. Siefring, Sa. Basu, M. McCarrick, J. Preston, M. Engebretson, M. L. Kaiser, M. D. Desch, K. Goetz, J.-L. Bougerethttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=42039923&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=edward kennedy

Results from the first science experiment with the new HF Active Auroral Research Program (HAARP) in Alaska are reported. The objective was to study the effects of space plasmas on high power radiowave transmission to high altitudes in the magnetosphere. Reception was done by the NASA/WIND satellite. The data suggest that structured space plasmas along the propagation path impose ...

Journal: Geophysical Research Letters - GEOPHYS RES LETT , vol. 25, no. 3, pp. 257-260, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7218-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7218_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:12:45">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/28258488/the-concentration-of-glucosamine-in-normal-and-pathological-sera</link><title>THE CONCENTRATION OF GLUCOSAMINE IN NORMAL AND PATHOLOGICAL SERA</title><description>* THE CONCENTRATION OF GLUCOSAMINE IN NORMAL AND PATHOLOGICAL SERA (Citations: 12)

D. H. Clarke, E. M. Kennedy

Journal: Journal of Clinical Investigation - J CLIN INVEST , vol. 17, no. 2, pp. 173-178, 1938</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7218-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7218_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:13:28">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11514240/cluster-observations-of-lower-hybrid-waves-excited-at-high-altitudes-by-electromagnetic-whistler</link><title>CLUSTER observations of lower hybrid waves excited at high altitudes by electromagnetic whistler mode signals from the HAARP facility</title><description>* CLUSTER observations of lower hybrid waves excited at high altitudes by electromagnetic whistler mode signals from the HAARP facility (Citations: 15)

T. F. Bell, M. Platino, J. S. Pickett, P. A. Kossey, E. J. Kennedy

Journal: Geophysical Research Letters - GEOPHYS RES LETT , vol. 31, no. 6, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7218-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7218_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:16:30">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/12479685/25-years-of-results-linear-technology-corporation-2006-annual-report</link><title>25 Years of Results Linear Technology Corporation 2006 Annual Report</title><description>* 25 Years of Results Linear Technology Corporation 2006 Annual Report

Robert H. Swanson, Robert Dobkin, Eugene Tanaka, Michael Hertzberg, Robert Scott, Julia Brown, Donald Lewis, Guy Hoover, Phillip Hernandez, Keith Bray, James Williams, Elizabeth Kooyhttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=12479685&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=edward kennedy</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7218-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7218_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:17:26">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5850883/demeter-observations-of-elf-waves-injected-with-the-haarp-hf-transmitter</link><title>DEMETER observations of ELF waves injected with the HAARP HF transmitter</title><description>* DEMETER observations of ELF waves injected with the HAARP HF transmitter (Citations: 13)

M. Platino, T. F. Bell, M. Parrot, E. J. Kennedy

Modulated HF heating of the auroral electrojet is used to inject ELF signals into the magnetosphere that are observed on the low altitude DEMETER spacecraft. The HF heater is a component of the High-Frequency Active Auroral Research Program (HAARP) facility in Gakona, Alaska, (located at L ~ 4.9). Simultaneous observations of all six components of the ELF electromagnetic fields ...

Journal: Geophysical Research Letters - GEOPHYS RES LETT , vol. 331, no. 16, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7218-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7218_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:20:49">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5829097/subionospheric-vlf-observations-of-transmitter-induced-precipitation-of-inner-radiation-belt</link><title>Subionospheric VLF observations of transmitter-induced precipitation of inner radiation belt electrons</title><description>* Subionospheric VLF observations of transmitter-induced precipitation of inner radiation belt electrons (Citations: 27)

M. Golkowski, M. K. Casey, R. C. Moore, W. Peter, P. Kulkarni, P. Kossey, E. Kennedy, S. Meth, P. Smit

Ionospheric effects of energetic electron precipitation induced by controlled injection of VLF signals from a ground based transmitter are observed via subionospheric VLF remote sensing. The 21.4 kHz NPM transmitter in Lualualei, Hawaii is keyed ON-OFF in 30 minute periodic sequences. The same periodicity is observed in the amplitude and phase of the sub ionospherically propagating signals of ...

Journal: Geophysical Research Letters - GEOPHYS RES LETT , vol. 340, no. 2, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7218-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7218_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:21:25">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5980859/elf-waves-generated-by-modulated-hf-heating-of-the-auroral-electrojet-and-observed-at-a-ground</link><title>ELF waves generated by modulated HF heating of the auroral electrojet and observed at a ground distance of ∼4400 km</title><description>* ELF waves generated by modulated HF heating of the auroral electrojet and observed at a ground distance of ∼4400 km (Citations: 15)

R. C. Moore, T. F. Bell, E. J. Kennedy

(1) We present calibrated measurements of ELF waves generated by modulated HF heating of the auroral electrojet by the High frequency Active Auroral Research Program (HAARP) HF transmitter in Gakona, Alaska, and detected after propagating more than 4400 km in the Earth-ionosphere waveguide to Midway Atoll. The magnitude of the 2125 Hz wave received at Midway Atoll is consistent ...

Journal: Journal of Geophysical Research , vol. 112, no. A5, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7218-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7218_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:24:25">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/45897386/cluster-observations-of-elf-vlf-signals-generated-by-modulated-heating-of-the-lower-ionosphere-with</link><title>Cluster observations of ELF/VLF signals generated by modulated heating of the lower ionosphere with the HAARP HF transmitter</title><description>* Cluster observations of ELF/VLF signals generated by modulated heating of the lower ionosphere with the HAARP HF transmitter (Citations: 14)

M. Platino, T. F. Bell, J. Pickett, E. J. Kennedy, J. G. Trotignon, J. L. Rauch, P. Canu

Journal: Annales Geophysicae , vol. 22, no. 7, pp. 2643-2653, 2004</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>