<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7235">silicone roof coatings</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:32:07" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7235-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7235_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:32:08">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/60510709/in-situ-thermal-performance-of-app-modified-bitumen-roof-membranes-coated-with-reflective-coatings</link><title>In situ thermal performance of APP modified bitumen roof membranes coated with reflective coatings</title><description>* In situ thermal performance of APP modified bitumen roof membranes coated with reflective coatings

J. D. Carlson, T. L. Smith, J. E. Christian

...polypropylene (app) modified bitumen membrane roof systems and four reflective coatings began in 1991. this long...app modified bitumen membranes (both coated and uncoated), the comparative performance of coating application soon after membrane installation versus preweathering, coating performance, and aspects of recoating...

Published in 1992.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7235-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7235_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:35:45">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/60558373/in-situ-thermal-performance-of-app-modified-bitumen-roof-membranes-coated-with-reflective-coatings</link><title>In situ thermal performance of APP modified bitumen roof membranes coated with reflective coatings</title><description>* In situ thermal performance of APP modified bitumen roof membranes coated with reflective coatings

J. D. Carlson, T. L. Smith, J. E. Christian

...polypropylene (app) modified bitumen membrane roof systems and four reflective coatings began in 1991. this long...app modified bitumen membranes (both coated and uncoated), the comparative performance of coating application soon after membrane installation versus preweathering, coating performance, and aspects of recoating...

Published in 1992.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7235-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7235_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:38:32">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50001460/amorphous-silicon-alloy-based-roof-integrated-photovoltaic-systems</link><title>Amorphous silicon alloy-based roof integrated photovoltaic systems</title><description>* Amorphous silicon alloy-based roof integrated photovoltaic systems (Citations: 1)

P. Nath, C. Vogeli, A. Singh, J. Call

...used to deposit tandem amorphous silicon alloy solar cells onto thin...can be integrated into building roofs. the module is fabricated by laminating the large area amorphous silicon on stainless steel solar cell...

Conference: World Conference on Photovoltaic Energy Conversion - WCPEC , 1994</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7235-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7235_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:42:25">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/60698948/performance-evaluation-of-a-sustainable-and-energy-efficient-re-roofing-technology-using-field-test</link><title>PERFORMANCE EVALUATION OF A SUSTAINABLE AND ENERGY EFFICIENT RE-ROOFING TECHNOLOGY USING FIELD-TEST DATA</title><description>* PERFORMANCE EVALUATION OF A SUSTAINABLE AND ENERGY EFFICIENT RE-ROOFING TECHNOLOGY USING FIELD-TEST DATA

Kaushik Biswas, William A Miller, Phillip W Childs, Jan Kosny, Scott Kriner

...to each other. the leftmost roof is the conventional shingle roof, followed by the metal panel roof incorporating the cool-roof coating, and third from left is...and 7. the metal panel roof consists of three metal panels with the cool-roof coating; in further discussion this is...

Published in 2011.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7235-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7235_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:45:15">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/27181182/adhesion-of-weatherproofing-coatings-to-hcfc141b-blown-spray-foam</link><title>Adhesion of Weatherproofing Coatings to HCFC141b Blown Spray Foam</title><description>* Adhesion of Weatherproofing Coatings to HCFC141b Blown Spray Foam

R. C. Parker, L. B. Bement

...applied to the sprayed-on roof. these coatings are usually elastomeric acrylics, silicones or urethanes. selection of the coating nor mally lies with the...also play a role in coating selection. regardless of the coating type, however, the foam/coating package must meet building codes...

Journal: Journal of Building Physics - J BUILD PHYS , vol. 18, no. 1, pp. 70-80, 1994</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7235-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7235_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:45:39">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/41178437/coloured-paints-based-on-iron-oxide-and-silicon-oxide-coated-flakes-of-aluminium-as-the-pigment</link><title>Coloured paints based on iron oxide and silicon oxide coated flakes of aluminium as the pigment, for energy efficient paint: optical and thermal experiments</title><description>* Coloured paints based on iron oxide and silicon oxide coated flakes of aluminium as the pigment, for energy efficient paint: optical and thermal experiments (Citations: 4)

G. B. Smith, A. Gentle, P. D. Swift, A. Earp, N. Mronga

...energy efficient coloured paint coatings utilising flaky aluminium pigment with...layer (fe2o3 on sio2) interference coatings are optically and thermally characterised. similar pigments with coatings on flaky dielectric particles and...

Journal: Solar Energy Materials and Solar Cells - SOLAR ENERG MATER SOLAR CELLS , vol. 79, no. 2, pp. 179-197, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7235-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7235_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:48:54">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/60027544/experimental-polyurethane-foam-puf-roofing-systems-iii-naval-station-roosevelt-roads-puerto</link><title>Experimental polyurethane foam (PUF) roofing systems. III. Naval Station, Roosevelt Roads, Puerto Rico, and Naval Facility, Cape Hatteras, North Carolina. Interim report, September 1978March 1984</title><description>* Experimental polyurethane foam (PUF) roofing systems. III. Naval Station, Roosevelt Roads, Puerto Rico, and Naval Facility, Cape Hatteras, North Carolina. Interim report, September 1978March 1984

S. R. Conklin, D. A. Zarate, R. L. Alumbaugh

...of the housing units were coated with acrylic and silicone coating systems, but urethane/hypalon, modified urethane, and butyl/hypalon elastomeric coating systems were also used. the roofing system installed on the galley at cape hatteras was acrylic elastomer coated puf roof applied over a modified bitumen...

Published in 1986.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7235-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7235_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:50:51">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/55288161/influence-of-the-reactor-wall-composition-on-radicals-densities-and-total-pressure-in-cl2</link><title>Influence of the reactor wall composition on radicals' densities and total pressure in Cl2 inductively coupled plasmas: II. During silicon etching</title><description>* Influence of the reactor wall composition on radicals' densities and total pressure in Cl2 inductively coupled plasmas: II. During silicon etching

G. Cunge, N. Sadeghi, R. Ramos

...etching a 200 mm diameter silicon wafer. the pure cl2 plasma is operated in well prepared chamber wall coating with a thin film of...of the reactor wall's coatings on these mole fractions is studied systematically. we show that the reactor wall coatings have a huge influence on...

Journal: Journal of Applied Physics - J APPL PHYS , vol. 102, no. 9, pp. 3305-093305, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7235-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7235_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:54:05">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/56178185/experimental-polyurethane-foam-roof-systems-part-2</link><title>Experimental polyurethane foam roof systems, part 2</title><description>* Experimental polyurethane foam roof systems, part 2

R. L. Alumbaugh, J. R. Keeton, E. F. Humm

...butlerib-type metal decks, the roof divided into five approximately equal areas, and the puf protected with five different elastomeric coating systems. three of the coating systems were damaged by hailstones...the initial installation. the current coatings include two of the original coating systems - a plural component silicone and a single component silicone \- and those applied over the...

Published in 1983.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7235-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7235_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:57:56">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/60047936/experimental-polyurethane-foam-roof-systems-ii-technical-note-oct-75jul-81</link><title>Experimental polyurethane foam roof systems - II. Technical note Oct 75Jul 81</title><description>* Experimental polyurethane foam roof systems - II. Technical note Oct 75Jul 81

R. L. Alumbaugh, J. R. Keeton, E. F. Humm

...butlerib-type metal decks, the roof divided into five approximately equal areas, and the puf protected with five different elastomeric coating systems. three of the coating systems were damaged by hailstones...the initial installation. the current coatings include two of the original coating systems - a plural component silicone and a single component silicone \- and those applied over the...

Published in 1983.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>