<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7250">collagen vascular disease</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:02:15" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7250-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7250_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:02:17">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/28762099/the-histopathologic-spectrum-of-palisaded-neutrophilic-and-granulomatous-dermatitis-in-patients</link><title>The histopathologic spectrum of palisaded neutrophilic and granulomatous dermatitis in patients with collagen vascular disease</title><description>* The histopathologic spectrum of palisaded neutrophilic and granulomatous dermatitis in patients with collagen vascular disease (Citations: 64)

P. Chu

Journal: Archives of Dermatology - ARCH DERMATOL , vol. 130, no. 10, pp. 1278-1283, 1994</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7250-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7250_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:06:00">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/33848632/methotrexate-induced-papular-eruption-in-patients-with-rheumatic-diseases-a-distinctive-adverse</link><title>Methotrexate-induced papular eruption in patients with rheumatic diseases: A distinctive adverse cutaneous reaction produced by methotrexate in patients with collagen vascular diseases</title><description>* Methotrexate-induced papular eruption in patients with rheumatic diseases: A distinctive adverse cutaneous reaction produced by methotrexate in patients with collagen vascular diseases (Citations: 13)

E. Goerttler, H. Kutzner, H. H. Peter, L. Requena

...with rheumatoid arthritis and other collagen vascular diseases, mainly as an immunosuppressive and...patients with acute bouts of collagen vascular diseases who were receiving methotrexate therapy...

Journal: Journal of The American Academy of Dermatology - J AMER ACAD DERMATOL , vol. 40, no. 5, pp. 702-707, 1999</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7250-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7250_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:09:41">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10718521/fibroblastic-foci-in-usual-interstitial-pneumonia-idiopathic-versus-collagen-vascular-disease</link><title>Fibroblastic Foci in Usual Interstitial Pneumonia Idiopathic versus Collagen Vascular Disease</title><description>* Fibroblastic Foci in Usual Interstitial Pneumonia Idiopathic versus Collagen Vascular Disease (Citations: 26)

Kevin R. Flaherty, Thomas V. Colby, William D. Travis, Galen B. Toews, Jeanette Mumford, Susan Murray, Victor J. Thannickal, Ella A. Kazerooni, Barry H. Gross, Joseph P. Lynch, Fernando J. Martinez

...between patients with idiopathic and collagen\- usual interstitial pneumonia (nine with collagen vascular disease) vascular associated pulmonary fibrosis (21-24...abnormalities, and radiographic findings (3). collagen vascular disease-associated usual interstitial pneumonia patients were excluded if they were found to have a disease other have fewer fibroblastic foci...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7250-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7250_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:10:40">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/30425863/interstitial-pulmonary-fibrosis-with-and-without-associated-collagen-vascular-disease-results-of-a</link><title>Interstitial pulmonary fibrosis with and without associated collagen vascular disease: results of a two year follow up</title><description>* Interstitial pulmonary fibrosis with and without associated collagen vascular disease: results of a two year follow up (Citations: 23)

C Agustí, A Xaubet, J Roca, A G Agustí, R Rodriguez-Roisin

...interstitial pulmonary fibrosis is a disease with a highly variable clinical...the "lone" form of the disease (lipf) and those with associated collagen vascular disorders (aipf), were studied separately...

Journal: Thorax , vol. 47, no. 12, pp. 1035-1040, 1992</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7250-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7250_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:11:44">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6769390/pulmonary-hypertension-in-collagen-vascular-disease</link><title>Pulmonary hypertension in collagen vascular disease</title><description>* Pulmonary hypertension in collagen vascular disease (Citations: 19)

M. M. Hoeper

...but often overlooked complication in collagen,vascular,disease. the understanding,of the,development...variables in patients with several collagen vascular diseases and pulmonary,arterial hypertension. continuous...

Journal: European Respiratory Journal - EUR RESP J , vol. 19, no. 3, pp. 571-576, 2002</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7250-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7250_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:13:52">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/33895101/patients-with-collagen-vascular-disease-and-dyspnea-the-value-of-gallium-scanning-and</link><title>Patients with collagen vascular disease and dyspnea. The value of gallium scanning and bronchoalveolar lavage in predicting response to steroid therapy and clinical outcome</title><description>* Patients with collagen vascular disease and dyspnea. The value of gallium scanning and bronchoalveolar lavage in predicting response to steroid therapy and clinical outcome (Citations: 12)

N. B. Greene, A. M. Solinger, R. P. Baughman

...patients with collagen vascular disease with or without pulmonary symptoms...assessing progressive pulmonary fibrosis in collagen vascular disease....

Journal: Chest , vol. 91, no. 5, pp. 698-703, 1987</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7250-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7250_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:15:25">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/30764432/cardiovascular-lesions-in-collagen-vascular-diseases</link><title>Cardiovascular lesions in collagen-vascular diseases</title><description>* Cardiovascular lesions in collagen-vascular diseases (Citations: 9)

Victor J. Ferrans, E. René Rodríguez

...in association with the various collagen-vascular diseases are described. in rheumatoid arthritis...is uncommon except when the disease is related to mucinous adenocarcinoma...

Journal: Heart and Vessels - HEART VESSELS , vol. 1, no. S1, pp. 256-261, 1985</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7250-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7250_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:17:21">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/29325387/cardiac-tumours-simulating-collagen-vascular-disease</link><title>Cardiac tumours simulating collagen vascular disease</title><description>* Cardiac tumours simulating collagen vascular disease (Citations: 8)

A P Fitzpatrick, J G Lanham, D V Doyle

...cardiac tumours can mimic collagen vascular disease and they are often accompanied...that a spectrum of different collagen vascular diseases was diagnosed and treated before...

Journal: Heart , vol. 55, no. 6, pp. 592-595, 1986</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7250-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7250_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:18:21">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/30381108/collagen-vascular-diseases-and-radiation-therapy-a-critical-review</link><title>Collagen vascular diseases and radiation therapy: a critical review</title><description>* Collagen vascular diseases and radiation therapy: a critical review (Citations: 13)

Bart De Naeyer, Gert De Meerleer, Sabine Braems, Luc Vakaet, John Huys

...the impression that patients with collagen vascular disease tolerate radiotherapy less well than...to determine whether patients with collagen vascular diseases have a greater risk of severe radiation therapy complications, than those without a collagen vascular disease. however, most of the publications...

Journal: International Journal of Radiation Oncology Biology Physics - INT J RADIAT ONCOL BIOL PHYS , vol. 44, no. 5, pp. 975-980, 1999</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7250-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7250_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:20:28">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/31570132/maternal-collagen-vascular-disease-associated-with-fetal-heart-block-and-degenerative-changes-of</link><title>Maternal collagen vascular disease associated with fetal heart block and degenerative changes of the atrioventricular valves</title><description>* Maternal collagen vascular disease associated with fetal heart block and degenerative changes of the atrioventricular valves (Citations: 6)

H. S. Weber, J. L. Myers

...heart block associated with maternal collagen vascular disease and sjögren's antibody. serial...

Journal: Pediatric Cardiology - PEDIAT CARDIOL , vol. 15, no. 4, pp. 204-206, 1994</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>