<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7258">swahili dishes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:24:45" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7258-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7258_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:24:46">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10448323/malindi-kenya-the-resilience-of-an-ancient-african-architectural-system</link><title>MALINDI, KENYA - THE RESILIENCE OF AN ANCIENT AFRICAN ARCHITECTURAL SYSTEM</title><description>* MALINDI, KENYA - THE RESILIENCE OF AN ANCIENT AFRICAN ARCHITECTURAL SYSTEM

Gerald Steyn

...as a port for game fishing. but historians know malindi as a swahili city-state dating from the...in transforming the early linear swahili house into the contemporary swahili house with its central corridor...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7258-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7258_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:25:33">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42623845/converting-to-rice-urbanization-islamization-and-crops-on-pemba-island-tanzania-ad-700-1500</link><title>Converting to rice: urbanization, Islamization and crops on Pemba Island, Tanzania, ad 700–1500</title><description>* Converting to rice: urbanization, Islamization and crops on Pemba Island, Tanzania, ad 700–1500 (Citations: 3)

Sarah C. Walshaw

...farmers of eastern africa's swahili coast engaged in a mixed economy, including fishing, animal husbandry and trade in...

Journal: World Archaeology , vol. 42, no. 1, pp. 137-154, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7258-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7258_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:27:56">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/47591230/rituals-of-consumption-and-the-politics-of-feasting-on-the-eastern-african-coast-ad-700-1500</link><title>Rituals of Consumption and the Politics of Feasting on the Eastern African Coast, AD 700–1500</title><description>* Rituals of Consumption and the Politics of Feasting on the Eastern African Coast, AD 700–1500 (Citations: 1)

Jeffrey Fleisher

...historically, the swahili of the eastern african coast...feasting in the more distant swahili past, ad 700–1500, in...

Journal: Journal of World Prehistory , vol. 23, no. 4, pp. 195-217, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7258-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7258_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:29:15">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6131100/archaeological-approaches-to-east-africa-s-changing-seascapes</link><title>Archaeological approaches to East Africa's changing seascapes</title><description>* Archaeological approaches to East Africa's changing seascapes (Citations: 10)

Colin Breen

...on and complement the existing 'swahili' or coastal archaeology research traditions...

Journal: World Archaeology , vol. 35, no. 3, pp. 469-489, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7258-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7258_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:29:53">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4955732/process-based-models-for-port-evolution-and-wreck-site-formation-at-mombasa-kenya</link><title>Process-based models for port evolution and wreck site formation at Mombasa, Kenya</title><description>* Process-based models for port evolution and wreck site formation at Mombasa, Kenya (Citations: 3)

Rory Quinn, Wes Forsythe, Colin Breen, Donal Boland, Athman Lali Omar

...resource in the area comprises fish traps and shipwrecks. physical processes...

Journal: Journal of Archaeological Science - J ARCHAEOL SCI , vol. 34, no. 9, pp. 1449-1460, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7258-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7258_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:32:40">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/47680023/larvicidal-antimicrobial-and-brine-shrimp-activities-of-extracts-from-cissampelos-mucronata-and</link><title>Larvicidal, antimicrobial and brine shrimp activities of extracts from Cissampelos mucronata and Tephrosia villosa from coast region, Tanzania</title><description>* Larvicidal, antimicrobial and brine shrimp activities of extracts from Cissampelos mucronata and Tephrosia villosa from coast region, Tanzania

Ramadhani S O Nondo, Zakaria H Mbwambo, Abdul W Kidukuli, Ester M Innocent, Matobola J Mihale, Paul Erasto, Mainen J Moshi

...toxic to both livestock and fish. the results further suggest that...

Journal: BMC Complementary and Alternative Medicine - BMC COMPLEMENT ALTERN MED , vol. 11, no. 1, pp. 1-7, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7258-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7258_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:33:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11906306/unplanned-tourism-development-in-sub-saharan-africa-with-special-reference-to-kenya</link><title>Unplanned Tourism Development in Sub-Saharan Africa with Special Reference to Kenya</title><description>* Unplanned Tourism Development in Sub-Saharan Africa with Special Reference to Kenya (Citations: 3)

Isaac Sindiga

In sub-Saharan Africa tourism has developed without planning. Three decades of such development increased tourist arrivals and foreign exchange receipts but led to serious environmental and socio-cultural problems and the degradation of the tourism product. This paper examines the development of tourism in sub-Saharan Africa using the Kenya example. After a period of unplanned expansion, Kenya's ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7258-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7258_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:35:03">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5539983/improving-the-livelihoods-of-women-in-the-developing-world-selected-perceptions-of-women-s</link><title>Improving the Livelihoods of Women in the Developing World: Selected Perceptions of Women's Self-Help Groups in Western Kenya</title><description>* Improving the Livelihoods of Women in the Developing World: Selected Perceptions of Women's Self-Help Groups in Western Kenya (Citations: 3)

Billy A. Jivetti, M. Craig Edwards

Development specialists agree that poverty in developing countries is a multidimensional phenomenon. The United Nations (2001) reported that the poorest of the world's poor are women. The Kenyan Government recognizes that poverty is area specific and interventions aimed at creating employment and reducing poverty must be localized. In Kenya, "women's self- help groups" have become popular avenues through ...

Published in 2008.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7258-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7258_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:38:04">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6919789/variation-in-testosterone-levels-and-male-reproductive-effort-insight-from-a-polygynous-human</link><title>Variation in testosterone levels and male reproductive effort: Insight from a polygynous human population</title><description>* Variation in testosterone levels and male reproductive effort: Insight from a polygynous human population (Citations: 6)

Alexandra Alvergne, Charlotte Faurie, Michel Raymond

Recent evidence suggests that, in humans, variations in testosterone (T) levels between men reflect their differential allocation in mating versus parenting efforts. However, most studies have been conducted in urbanized, monogamous populations, making generalizations from them questionable. This study addresses the question of whether indicators of male reproductive effort are associated with variations in salivary T levels in a polygynous ...

Journal: Hormones and Behavior - HORMONE BEHAV , vol. 56, no. 5, pp. 491-497, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7258-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7258_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:40:12">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40095651/social-neuroendocrinology</link><title>Social neuroendocrinology</title><description>* Social neuroendocrinology (Citations: 2)

Sari M. van Anders, Neil V. Watson

In this paper we provide a critical review of research concerned with social/environmental mechanisms that modulate human neuroendocrine function. We survey research in four behavioral systems that have been shaped through evolution: competition, partnering, sex, and pregnancy/parenting. Generally, behavioral neuroendocrine research examines how hormones affect behavior. Instead, we focus on approaches that emphasize the effects of behavioral states ...

Journal: Human Nature-an Interdisciplinary Biosocial Perspective - HUM NATURE-INT BIOSOC PERSPEC , vol. 17, no. 2, pp. 212-237, 2006</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>