<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7260">iowa girls high school basketball</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:01:40" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7260-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7260_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:01:42">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6812303/traumatic-brain-injury-in-high-school-athletes</link><title>Traumatic Brain Injury in High School Athletes</title><description>* Traumatic Brain Injury in High School Athletes (Citations: 112)

John W. Powell, Kim D. Barber-Foss

...cases; wrestling, 128 (10.5%); girls' soccer, 76 (6.2%); boys' soccer, 69 (5.7%); girls' bas- ketball, 63 (5.2%); boys' basketball, 51 (4.2%); softball, 25...for wrestling, 1.14 for girls' soccer, 1.04 for girls' basketball, 0.92 for boys' soccer, 0.75 for boys' basketball, 0.46 for softball, 0...

Published in 1999.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7260-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7260_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:04:13">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/28964033/incidence-of-injury-in-texas-girls-high-school-basketball</link><title>Incidence of Injury in Texas Girls' High School Basketball</title><description>* Incidence of Injury in Texas Girls' High School Basketball (Citations: 45)

Eduardo Gomez, Jesse C. DeLee, William C. Farney

...the incidence of injury in girl's varsity bas ketball to characterize injury demographics in high school athletics. we defined a reportable...4a and 5a texas public high schools that employed full-time certified athletic train ers. the 890 student athletes from 80 schools ranged in age from 14...

Journal: American Journal of Sports Medicine - AMER J SPORT MED , vol. 24, no. 5, pp. 684-687, 1996</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7260-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7260_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:07:00">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57119364/sex-related-injury-patterns-among-selected-high-school-sports</link><title>Sex-Related Injury Patterns Among Selected High School Sports</title><description>* Sex-Related Injury Patterns Among Selected High School Sports (Citations: 6)

John W. Powell, Kim D. Barber-Foss

...the incidence of injuries for girls participating in high school sports is greater than that...they were listed on the school's varsity team roster for boys' or girls' basketball, boys' or girls' soccer, boys' baseball, or girls' softball. injuries and opportunities for...

Journal: American Journal of Sports Medicine - AMER J SPORT MED , vol. 28, no. 3, pp. 385-391, 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7260-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7260_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:08:29">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/59059932/project-adventure-activities-and-team-cohesion-of-girls-high-school-basketball-players</link><title>Project Adventure activities and team cohesion of girls high school basketball players</title><description>* Project Adventure activities and team cohesion of girls high school basketball players

Melodee Yoko Kiyota

Published in 2006.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7260-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7260_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:10:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/13356087/approval-of-agenda-chairman-campbell-requested-additions-to-the-agenda-as-follows-item-viii-f</link><title>APPROVAL OF AGENDA: Chairman Campbell requested additions to the agenda as follows: Item VIII. F. School Nurses, G. Recommendation for Non-renewal of Teachers, H. Approval of Architectural and Engineering Services. On a motion by Mr. Kindle, seconded by Mr. Sampson, all members voting aye, the board approved the agenda including the additions as requested. PRESENTATION OF GATE CITY HIGH SCHOOL GIRLS BASKETBALL TEAM RESOLUTION: Chairman Campbell requested that Mrs. Loretta Q. Page, Clerk of the Board, read the Gate City High School Girls Basketball Team Resolution as follows</title><description>* APPROVAL OF AGENDA: Chairman Campbell requested additions to the agenda as follows: Item VIII. F. School Nurses, G. Recommendation for Non-renewal of Teachers, H. Approval of Architectural and Engineering Services. On a motion by Mr. Kindle, seconded by Mr. Sampson, all members voting aye, the board approved the agenda including the additions as requested. PRESENTATION OF GATE CITY HIGH SCHOOL GIRLS BASKETBALL TEAM RESOLUTION: Chairman Campbell requested that Mrs. Loretta Q. Page, Clerk of the Board, read the Gate City High School Girls Basketball Team Resolution as follows

Lowell S. Campbell, Joe D. Meade, David T. Kindle, Glenn M. McMurray, E. Virgil, James B. Scott, Darryl E. Johnson, C. Dean Foster, Loretta Q. Page, Karen C. Linkous, Deputy Clerk, Johnny Trenthttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=13356087&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=iowa girls high school basketball

Published in 2006.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7260-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7260_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:11:42">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/28981064/the-epidemiology-of-us-high-school-basketball-injuries-2005-2007</link><title>The Epidemiology of US High School Basketball Injuries, 2005-2007</title><description>* The Epidemiology of US High School Basketball Injuries, 2005-2007 (Citations: 17)

Laurel A. Borowski, Ellen E. Yard, Sarah K. Fields, R. Dawn Comstock

...from 100 nationally representative us high schools via reporting information online.results: high school basketball players sustained 1518 injuries during...2.31). the most common girls' injury requiring surgery was knee ligament sprains (47.9%).conclusion: high school basketball injury patterns vary by gender...

Journal: American Journal of Sports Medicine - AMER J SPORT MED , vol. 36, no. 12, pp. 2328-2335, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7260-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7260_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:12:25">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42403240/the-influence-of-athlete-sex-context-and-performance-on-high-school-basketball-coaches-use-of</link><title>The Influence of Athlete Sex, Context, and Performance on High School Basketball Coaches' Use of Regret Messages During Competition</title><description>* The Influence of Athlete Sex, Context, and Performance on High School Basketball Coaches' Use of Regret Messages During Competition (Citations: 1)

Paul D. Turman

Journal: Communication Education - COMMUN EDUC , vol. 56, no. 3, pp. 333-353, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7260-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7260_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:14:40">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/25355497/an-epidemiological-investigation-on-an-outbreak-of-bacillus-cereus-food-poisoning-in-a-girls-high</link><title>An Epidemiological Investigation on an Outbreak of Bacillus Cereus Food Poisoning in a Girls' High School in Sangju-si, Korea, 2008</title><description>* An Epidemiological Investigation on an Outbreak of Bacillus Cereus Food Poisoning in a Girls' High School in Sangju-si, Korea, 2008

Hyun-Dong Lee, Sun-Ok Lee, Hyun-Sul Lim, Kyoung-Chan Lee, Kyu-Jin Chang, Young-A Kang

Journal: Korean Journal of Epidemiology , vol. 30, no. 2, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7260-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7260_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:15:29">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/28214658/gender-specific-injury-patterns-in-high-school-varsity-basketball</link><title>Gender-Specific Injury Patterns in High School Varsity Basketball</title><description>* Gender-Specific Injury Patterns in High School Varsity Basketball (Citations: 14)

DEBRA A. ZILLMER, JOHN W. POWELL, JOHN P. ALBRIGHT

Journal: Journal of Womens Health - J WOMENS HEALTH , vol. 1, no. 1, pp. 69-76, 1992</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7260-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7260_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:19:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39367689/high-school-employment-school-performance-and-college-entry</link><title>High school employment, school performance, and college entry</title><description>* High school employment, school performance, and college entry (Citations: 1)

Chanyoung Lee, Peter F. Orazem

...cumulative work histories during the high school years affect probability of dropout, high school academic performance, and the probability...academic year does not affect high school academic performance. however, increased high school work intensity raises the likelihood of completing high school but lowers the probability of...

Published in 2010.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>