<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7263">hospital acquired pneumonia</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:47:48" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7263-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7263_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:47:49">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/29020199/community-and-hospital-acquired-pneumonia-associated-with-chlamydia-twar-infection-demonstrated</link><title>Community and hospital-acquired pneumonia associated with Chlamydia TWAR infection demonstrated serologically</title><description>* Community and hospital-acquired pneumonia associated with Chlamydia TWAR infection demonstrated serologically (Citations: 38)

J. T. Grayston

Journal: Archives of Internal Medicine - ARCH INTERN MED , vol. 149, no. 1, pp. 169-173, 1989</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7263-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7263_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:50:57">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/34399136/hospital-acquired-pneumonia-overview-of-the-current-state-of-the-art-for-prevention-and-control</link><title>Hospital-acquired pneumonia: Overview of the current state of the art for prevention and control</title><description>* Hospital-acquired pneumonia: Overview of the current state of the art for prevention and control (Citations: 30)

R. P. Wenzel

hospital-acquired pneumonia affects at least 250,000...the true bacterial etiology of hospital-acquired pneumonia utilizing reliable techniques that bypass...

Journal: European Journal of Clinical Microbiology &amp; Infectious Diseases - EUR J CLIN MICROBIOL INFECT D , vol. 8, no. 1, pp. 56-60, 1989</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7263-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7263_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:54:00">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/29004346/bacteriology-of-hospital-acquired-pneumonia</link><title>Bacteriology of hospital-acquired pneumonia</title><description>* Bacteriology of hospital-acquired pneumonia (Citations: 81)

J. G. Bartlett

Journal: Archives of Internal Medicine - ARCH INTERN MED , vol. 146, no. 5, pp. 868-871, 1986</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7263-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7263_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:55:39">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6882371/a-prospective-comparison-of-nursing-home-acquired-pneumonia-with-community-acquired-pneumonia</link><title>A prospective comparison of nursing home acquired pneumonia with community acquired pneumonia</title><description>* A prospective comparison of nursing home acquired pneumonia with community acquired pneumonia (Citations: 42)

W. S. Lim, J. T. MacFarlane

...prospective comparison of nursing home acquired pneumonia with community acquired pneumonia. w.s. lim, j.t. macfarlane. #ers journals ltd 2001. abstract: nursing home acquired pneumonia (nhap) is thought to be clinically distinct from community acquired pneumonia (cap). this observation, based on...

Journal: European Respiratory Journal - EUR RESP J , vol. 18, no. 2, pp. 362-368, 2001</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7263-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7263_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:57:41">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/28243569/hospital-acquired-pneumonia-methicillin-resistance-and-intensive-care-unit-admission</link><title>Hospital-acquired pneumonia: methicillin resistance and intensive care unit admission</title><description>* Hospital-acquired pneumonia: methicillin resistance and intensive care unit admission (Citations: 16)

Jean-Yves Fagon, Jean-Michel Maillet, Ana Novara

...although epidemiologic investigations of hospital-acquired pneumonia have certain intrinsic limitations because...most frequent cause of nosocomial pneumonia in hospitals in both europe and the united states among patients in general hospital units as well as in...

Journal: American Journal of Medicine - AMER J MED , vol. 104, no. 5, pp. 17S-23S, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7263-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7263_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:00:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11611057/guidelines-for-the-management-of-hospital-acquired-pneumonia-in-the-uk-report-of-the-working-party</link><title>Guidelines for the management of hospital-acquired pneumonia in the UK: Report of the Working Party on Hospital-Acquired Pneumonia of the British Society for Antimicrobial Chemotherapy</title><description>* Guidelines for the management of hospital-acquired pneumonia in the UK: Report of the Working Party on Hospital-Acquired Pneumonia of the British Society for Antimicrobial Chemotherapy (Citations: 34)

R. G. Masterton, A. Galloway, J. Armstrong, E. Brown, J. Cleverley, P. Dilworth, C. Fry, A. D. Gascoigne, Alan Knox, D. Nathwani, R. Spencer, M. Wilcox

Journal: Journal of Antimicrobial Chemotherapy - J ANTIMICROB CHEMOTHER , vol. 62, no. 1, pp. 5-34, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7263-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7263_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:02:08">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/28114864/a-prospective-randomized-comparison-of-an-in-line-heat-moisture-exchange-filter-and-heated-wire</link><title>A Prospective, Randomized Comparison of an In-Line Heat Moisture Exchange Filter and Heated Wire Humidifiers: Rates of Ventilator-Associated Early-Onset (Community-Acquired) or Late-Onset (Hospital-Acquired) Pneumonia and Incidence of Endotracheal Tube Occlusion</title><description>* A Prospective, Randomized Comparison of an In-Line Heat Moisture Exchange Filter and Heated Wire Humidifiers: Rates of Ventilator-Associated Early-Onset (Community-Acquired) or Late-Onset (Hospital-Acquired) Pneumonia and Incidence of Endotracheal Tube Occlusion (Citations: 53)

O. C. Kirton, B. DeHaven, J. Morgan, O. Morejon, J. Civetta

Journal: Chest , vol. 112, no. 4, pp. 1055-1059, 1997</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7263-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7263_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:03:17">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10317219/outcomes-of-patients-hospitalized-with-community-acquired-health-care-associated-and</link><title>Outcomes of Patients Hospitalized With Community-Acquired, Health Care-Associated, and Hospital-Acquired Pneumonia</title><description>* Outcomes of Patients Hospitalized With Community-Acquired, Health Care-Associated, and Hospital-Acquired Pneumonia (Citations: 23)

Mario Venditti, Marco Falcone, Salvatore Corrao, Giuseppe Licata, Pietro Serra</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7263-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7263_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:06:20">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11187805/hospital-acquired-pneumonia-guidelines-in-europe-a-review-of-their-status-and-future-development</link><title>Hospital-acquired pneumonia guidelines in Europe: a review of their status and future development</title><description>* Hospital-acquired pneumonia guidelines in Europe: a review of their status and future development (Citations: 16)

R. Masterton, D. Craven, J. Rello, M. Struelens, N. Frimodt-Moller, J. Chastre, A. Ortqvist, G. Cornaglia, H. Lode, H. Giamarellou, M. J. M. Bonten, H. Eraksoyhttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=11187805&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=hospital acquired pneumonia

...hospital-acquired pneumonia (hap) is the most common healthcare-acquired infection contributing to death. effective...

Journal: Journal of Antimicrobial Chemotherapy - J ANTIMICROB CHEMOTHER , vol. 60, no. 2, pp. 206-213, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7263-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7263_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:09:32">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11877108/defining-treating-and-preventing-hospital-acquired-pneumonia-european-perspective</link><title>Defining, treating and preventing hospital acquired pneumonia: European perspective</title><description>* Defining, treating and preventing hospital acquired pneumonia: European perspective (Citations: 21)

Antoni Torres, Santiago Ewig, Harmut Lode, Jean Carlet

...remain in the management of hospital acquired pneumonia (hap), and ventilation-acquired pneumonia (vap), three european societies, european...

Journal: Intensive Care Medicine - INTENS CARE MED , vol. 35, no. 1, pp. 9-29, 2009</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>