<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7303">what causes itchy feet</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:22:10" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7303-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7303_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:22:11">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/35455346/bites-by-australian-mygalomorph-spiders-araneae-mygalomorphae-including-funnel-web-spiders</link><title>Bites by Australian mygalomorph spiders (Araneae, Mygalomorphae), including funnel-web spiders (Atracinae) and mouse spiders (Actinopodidae: Missulena spp)</title><description>* Bites by Australian mygalomorph spiders (Araneae, Mygalomorphae), including funnel-web spiders (Atracinae) and mouse spiders (Actinopodidae: Missulena spp) (Citations: 4)

Geoffrey K Isbister, Mike R Gray

...on distal limbs (hands and feet). local effects included severe pain (53%), puncture marks (61%) and bleeding (27%), local redness (33%). itchiness did not occur. the following...proportion of funnel-web bites cause severe effects. mouse spider bites are unlikely to cause major envenoming but the clinical...

Journal: Toxicon , vol. 43, no. 2, pp. 133-140, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7303-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7303_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:24:50">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39169673/a-study-on-cercarial-dermatitis-in-khuzestan-province-south-western-iran</link><title>A study on cercarial dermatitis in Khuzestan province, south western Iran</title><description>* A study on cercarial dermatitis in Khuzestan province, south western Iran (Citations: 5)

Ali Farahnak, Mostafa Essalat

...swimmer's itch' is an itchy inflammatory response to the penetration...pruritic maculopapular rash on their feet, hands or other parts of...

Journal: BMC Public Health , vol. 3, no. 1, pp. 35-4, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7303-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7303_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:27:37">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10821130/dyshidrotic-eczema-relevance-to-the-immune-response-in-situ</link><title>Dyshidrotic eczema: relevance to the immune response in situ</title><description>* Dyshidrotic eczema: relevance to the immune response in situ

Ana Maria Abreu Velez, Frank J. Pinto, Michael S. Howard

...presented a chronic five-year, itchy vesicular/blistering rash involving her hands and feet. a lesional skin biopsy was...

Published in 2009.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7303-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7303_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:30:17">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/47971259/darier-s-disease</link><title>Darier’s Disease</title><description>* Darier’s Disease

Marimar Saez-De-Ocariz, Luz Orozco-Covarrubias, Carola Durán-McKinster, Ramón Ruiz-Maldonado

...may be severe, with widespread itchy malodorous crusted plaques, painful erosions...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7303-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7303_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:33:21">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6217747/nerve-growth-factor-regulates-nociception-in-human-health-and-disease</link><title>Nerve growth factor regulates nociception in human health and disease</title><description>* Nerve growth factor regulates nociception in human health and disease (Citations: 28)

P. ANAND

In this review, evidence is marshalled for the hypothesis that nerve growth factor (NGF) regulates nociception in human health and disease. The data from humans complement the studies of NGF in animal inflammatory pain models described else- where in this issue. An attempt is made to unify the role of NGF in inflammatory and neuropathic hyperalgesia. Although largely speculative at ...

Published in 1995.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>