<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7320">cayenne pepper plants</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:01:14" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7320-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7320_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:01:15">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/33314875/treatment-of-spasmodic-cholera-by-cayenne-pepper-and-brandy</link><title>TREATMENT OF SPASMODIC CHOLERA BY CAYENNE PEPPER AND BRANDY</title><description>* TREATMENT OF SPASMODIC CHOLERA BY CAYENNE PEPPER AND BRANDY

G PLANT

Journal: Lancet , vol. 52, no. 1302, 1848</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7320-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7320_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:03:59">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/41381953/mixtures-of-plant-growth-promoting-rhizobacteria-for-induction-of-systemic-resistance-against</link><title>Mixtures of plant growth-promoting rhizobacteria for induction of systemic resistance against multiple plant diseases</title><description>* Mixtures of plant growth-promoting rhizobacteria for induction of systemic resistance against multiple plant diseases (Citations: 45)

Kanchalee Jetiyanon, Joseph W Kloepper

...ralstonia solanacearum, anthracnose of long cayenne pepper (capsicum annuum var. acuminatum) caused...mixtures reduced anthracnose of long cayenne pepper, and 7 mixtures reduced damping...

Journal: Biological Control - BIOL CONTROL , vol. 24, no. 3, pp. 285-291, 2002</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7320-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7320_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:06:03">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5739059/induced-systemic-resistance-and-promotion-of-plant-growth-by-bacillus-spp</link><title>Induced Systemic Resistance and Promotion of Plant Growth by Bacillus spp</title><description>* Induced Systemic Resistance and Promotion of Plant Growth by Bacillus spp (Citations: 147)

Joseph W. Kloepper, Choong-Min Ryu, Shouan Zhang

...field trials on tomato, bell pepper, muskmelon, watermelon, sugar beet, tobacco, arabidopsis sp., cucumber, loblolly pine, and two tropical crops (long cayenne pepper and green kuang futsoi). protection...for disease protection on soybean. plant growth-promoting rhizobacteria (pgpr) are among the various groups of plant-associated microorganisms that can elicit plant defenses (28). in concert with...

Journal: Phytopathology , vol. 94, no. 11, pp. 1259-1266, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7320-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7320_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:06:48">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/59230366/toward-the-synthesis-of-cay1-an-antifungal-steroidal-saponin</link><title>Toward the Synthesis of CAY1, an Antifungal Steroidal Saponin</title><description>* Toward the Synthesis of CAY1, an Antifungal Steroidal Saponin

Katharine Bowdy

...from the fruit of the cayenne pepper plant in 0.1% yield. in...

Published in 2007.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7320-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7320_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:07:23">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/41876261/effect-of-genotype-explant-and-medium-on-in-vitro-regeneration-of-red-pepper</link><title>Effect of genotype, explant and medium on in vitro regeneration of red pepper</title><description>* Effect of genotype, explant and medium on in vitro regeneration of red pepper (Citations: 23)

T. Christopher, M. V. Rajam

...in vitro plant regeneration was achieved incapsicum praetermissum, c. baccatum andc. annuum cvs. g4, bhiwapuri sweet pepper, cayenne pepper and hybrid pepper. shoots were induced from hypocotyl...

Journal: Plant Cell Tissue and Organ Culture - PLANT CELL TISSUE ORGAN CULT , vol. 46, no. 3, pp. 245-250, 1996</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7320-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7320_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:08:08">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10197563/broad-spectrum-protection-against-several-pathogens-by-pgpr-mixtures-under-field-conditions-in</link><title>Broad-Spectrum Protection Against Several Pathogens by PGPR Mixtures Under Field Conditions in Thailand</title><description>* Broad-Spectrum Protection Against Several Pathogens by PGPR Mixtures Under Field Conditions in Thailand (Citations: 29)

Kanchalee Jetiyanon, William D. Fowler, Joseph W. Kloepper

...under field conditions in thailand. plant dis. 87:1390- 1394. prior greenhouse experiments showed that four mixtures of plant growth-promoting rhizobacte- ria (pgpr...induced systemic resistance in several plants against different plant pathogens. based on these findings...

Journal: Plant Disease - PLANT DIS , vol. 87, no. 11, pp. 1390-1394, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7320-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7320_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:10:35">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/12671719/preliminary-studies-on-sweet-pepper-and-chili</link><title>PRELIMINARY STUDIES ON SWEET PEPPER AND CHILI</title><description>* PRELIMINARY STUDIES ON SWEET PEPPER AND CHILI

ZHENG JIN-RONG

...divided between "sweet" and "hot" peppers. the sweet pepper is relatively non-pungent with thick flesh. chili, or, the hot pepper is pungent and is an...the total chili and sweet pepper planting area is now 989,000 hectares (1). chili and sweet pepper also play an important role...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7320-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7320_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:11:42">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/12402638/first-year-results-of-a-whitebark-pine-seed-planting-trial-near-baker-city-or</link><title>First Year Results of a Whitebark Pine Seed Planting Trial Near Baker City, Or</title><description>* First Year Results of a Whitebark Pine Seed Planting Trial Near Baker City, Or

John W. Schwandt, Diana F. Tomback, Robert E. Keane

...throughout most of its range. planting seedlings to restore whitebark pine...to reduce rodent predation (thiram, cayenne pepper, and caging). the results after...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7320-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7320_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:14:10">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57972480/effects-of-three-commercially-available-plant-growth-regulators-and-one-plant-growth-enhancer-on</link><title>Effects of Three Commercially Available Plant Growth Regulators and One Plant Growth Enhancer on Pepper (Capsicum annuum L.) Yield and Pigment Content</title><description>* Effects of Three Commercially Available Plant Growth Regulators and One Plant Growth Enhancer on Pepper (Capsicum annuum L.) Yield and Pigment Content

R. Scott Van Pelt, Thomas W. Popham

...commercially available plant growth regulators (pgr) and plant growth enhancers (pge) may be...the production of paprika and cayenne cultivars of pepper (capsicum annuum l.). three pgrs and one pge were foliarly applied to several production pepper fields in the pecos river...

Published in 2002.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7320-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7320_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:17:04">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10663401/inheritance-of-resistance-to-meloidogyne-incognita-race-2-in-the-hot-pepper-cultivar-carolina</link><title>Inheritance of resistance to Meloidogyne incognita race 2 in the hot pepper cultivar Carolina Cayenne (Capsicum annuum L.)</title><description>* Inheritance of resistance to Meloidogyne incognita race 2 in the hot pepper cultivar Carolina Cayenne (Capsicum annuum L.)

Fausto de Souza-Sobrinho, Wilson Roberto Maluf, Luiz A. A. Gomes

...in brazil and worldwide. the pepper species capsicum annuum includes both hot and sweet peppers; very little emphasis has been placed on breeding sweet peppers for nematode resistance. we report...race 2 in the hot pepper cultivar carolina cayenne. the hot pepper cv. caro- lina cayenne was used as seed parent and the sweet pepper cv. agronomico-8 was used...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>