<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7326">volcanoe eruption</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:14:51" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7326-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7326_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:14:52">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4023840/tungurahua-volcano-ecuador-structure-eruptive-history-and-hazards</link><title>Tungurahua Volcano, Ecuador: structure, eruptive history and hazards</title><description>* Tungurahua Volcano, Ecuador: structure, eruptive history and hazards (Citations: 49)

Minard L Hall, Claude Robin, Bernardo Beate, Patricia Mothes, Michel Monzier

...of ecuador's most active volcanoes, is made up of three...another catastrophic debris flow. the eruptive activity of the present volcano (tungurahua iii) has rebuilt the...

Journal: Journal of Volcanology and Geothermal Research - J VOLCANOL GEOTHERM RES , vol. 91, no. 1, pp. 1-21, 1999</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7326-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7326_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:15:21">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40159464/anatomy-of-1986-augustine-volcano-eruptions-as-recorded-by-multispectral-image-processing-of</link><title>Anatomy of 1986 Augustine volcano eruptions as recorded by multispectral image processing of digital AVHRR weather satellite data</title><description>* Anatomy of 1986 Augustine volcano eruptions as recorded by multispectral image processing of digital AVHRR weather satellite data (Citations: 24)

Rick E Holaske, William I. Rose

...7 april 1986 depict the eruptive activity of augustine volcano, located 280 km sw of...broadly applicable to analyzing explosive eruption clouds. the small scale of the augustine activity (column heights of 2–13 km and eruption rates of 2x106–8x107 metric...

Journal: Bulletin of Volcanology - BULL VOLCANOL , vol. 53, no. 6, pp. 420-435, 1991</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7326-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7326_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:18:31">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/41984796/motion-of-kilauea-volcano-during-sustained-eruption-from-the-puu-oo-and-kupaianaha-vents-1983-1991</link><title>Motion of Kilauea Volcano During Sustained Eruption From the Puu Oo and Kupaianaha Vents, 1983–1991</title><description>* Motion of Kilauea Volcano During Sustained Eruption From the Puu Oo and Kupaianaha Vents, 1983–1991 (Citations: 32)

Paul T. Delaney, Asta Miklius, Thora Arnadottir, Arnold T. Okamura, Maurice K. Sako

Journal: Journal of Geophysical Research , vol. 98, no. B10, pp. 17801-17820, 1993</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7326-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7326_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:21:53">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/41994481/magma-chambers-modeled-as-cavities-explain-the-formation-of-rift-zone-central-volcanoes-and-their</link><title>Magma chambers modeled as cavities explain the formation of rift zone central volcanoes and their eruption and intrusion statistics</title><description>* Magma chambers modeled as cavities explain the formation of rift zone central volcanoes and their eruption and intrusion statistics (Citations: 65)

Agust Gudmundsson

...is great difference in the eruption and intrusion statistics of the volcanic systems inside and outside the central volcanoes. in the central volcanoes, eruptions are frequent (typically one every...the surface where the central volcano gradually forms. the inverse relationship between eruption frequency and eruption volume, when the central volcano is compared with other parts...

Journal: Journal of Geophysical Research , vol. 103, no. B4, pp. 7401-7412, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7326-05"><link>http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/41165964/volcanism-in-iceland-in-historical-time-volcano-types-eruption-styles-and-eruptive-history</link><title>Volcanism in Iceland in historical time: Volcano types, eruption styles and eruptive history</title><description>* Volcanism in Iceland in historical time: Volcano types, eruption styles and eruptive history (Citations: 62)

T. Thordarson, G. Larsen

...circumstances. it features nearly all volcano types and eruption styles known on earth. the first order grouping of volcanoes is in accordance with recurrence of eruptions on the same vent system...i.e. subaerial, subglacial, submarine).eruptions are broadly grouped into effusive eruptions where &gt;95% of the erupted magma is lava, explosive eruptions if &gt;95% of the...

Journal: Journal of Geodynamics - J GEODYNAMICS , vol. 43, no. 1, pp. 118-152, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7326-06"><link>http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5469844/community-resilience-and-volcano-hazard-the-eruption-of-tungurahua-and-evacuation-of-the-faldas-in</link><title>Community Resilience and Volcano Hazard: The Eruption of Tungurahua and Evacuation of the Faldas in Ecuador</title><description>* Community Resilience and Volcano Hazard: The Eruption of Tungurahua and Evacuation of the Faldas in Ecuador (Citations: 38)

Graham A. Tobin, Linda M. Whiteford

Journal: Disasters , vol. 26, no. 1, pp. 28-48, 2002</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7326-07"><link>http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40492007/the-1982-el-chichon-volcano-eruptions-a-satellite-perspective</link><title>The 1982 El Chichon Volcano eruptions \- A satellite perspective</title><description>* The 1982 El Chichon Volcano eruptions \- A satellite perspective (Citations: 24)

Michael Matson

...3, and april 4, 1982 eruptions of el chichon volcano were detected and monitored using...concluded that the march 28 eruption, the second of two eruptions on april 3, and the april 4 eruption injected material into the stratosphere...

Journal: Journal of Volcanology and Geothermal Research - J VOLCANOL GEOTHERM RES , vol. 23, no. 1-2, pp. 1-10, 1984</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7326-08"><link>http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39978028/on-a-possibility-of-forecasting-of-bezymianny-volcano-eruptions-according-to-seismic-data</link><title>On a possibility of forecasting of bezymianny volcano eruptions according to seismic data</title><description>* On a possibility of forecasting of bezymianny volcano eruptions according to seismic data (Citations: 19)

P. I. Tokarev

Without Abstract

Journal: Bulletin of Volcanology - BULL VOLCANOL , vol. 26, no. 1, pp. 379-386, 1963</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7326-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7326_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:33:41">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40492906/graphical-and-pc-software-analysis-of-volcano-eruption-precursors-according-to-the-materials</link><title>Graphical and PC-software analysis of volcano eruption precursors according to the Materials Failure Forecast Method (FFM)</title><description>* Graphical and PC-software analysis of volcano eruption precursors according to the Materials Failure Forecast Method (FFM) (Citations: 22)

Reinold R. Cornelius, Barry Voight

...failure forecasting method for volcanic eruptions (ffm) analyses the rate of precursory phenomena. time of eruption onset is derived from the...and discussed.several kinds of eruption precursory phenomena, all simulating accelerating...

Journal: Journal of Volcanology and Geothermal Research - J VOLCANOL GEOTHERM RES , vol. 64, no. 3, pp. 295-320, 1995</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7326-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7326_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:35:12">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/2904180/correlations-between-earthquakes-and-large-mud-volcano-eruptions</link><title>Correlations between earthquakes and large mud volcano eruptions</title><description>* Correlations between earthquakes and large mud volcano eruptions (Citations: 32)

R. Mellors, D. Kilb, A. Aliyev, A. Gasanov, G. Yetirmishli

...year catalog (1810-2001) of eruptions from 77 volcanoes in azerbaijan, central asia, supplemented with reports from mud volcano eruptions in japan, romania, pakistan, and...the occurrence of azerbaijan mud volcano eruptions and find that the number of same-day earthquake/eruption pairs is significantly higher than expected if the eruptions and earthquakes are independent poisson...

Journal: Journal of Geophysical Research , vol. 112, no. B4, 2007</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>