<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7328">reduce acne redness</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:37:53" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7328-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7328_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:37:54">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/14124517/fp0029-treatment-of-acne-photodynamic-therapy-and-micropeeling</link><title>FP0029 TREATMENT OF ACNE : PHOTODYNAMIC THERAPY AND MICROPEELING</title><description>* FP0029 TREATMENT OF ACNE : PHOTODYNAMIC THERAPY AND MICROPEELING

S. Motta, D. Kanah, M. Monti

...and micropeeling are effective in reducing mild-moderate acne. ala-pdt promptly reduces inflammatory acne lesions but is scarcely efficient...cases of mild and moderate acne.this new drug-sparing treatment can be considered an advance in treatment of acne....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7328-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7328_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:38:25">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/47919475/5-aminolevulinic-acid-acne-vulgaris</link><title>5-Aminolevulinic Acid: Acne Vulgaris</title><description>* 5-Aminolevulinic Acid: Acne Vulgaris

Amy Forman Taub

...effective than blue light for acne, whereas red light with ala has been...short contact pdt. pdt for acne with 5-ala for the treatment of moderate to severe acne is a very efficacious and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7328-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7328_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:41:11">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10840325/combination-blue-415-nm-and-red-633-nm-led-phototherapy-in-the-treatment-of-mild-to-severe-acne</link><title>Combination blue (415 nm) and red (633 nm) LED phototherapy in the treatment of mild to severe acne vulgaris</title><description>* Combination blue (415 nm) and red (633 nm) LED phototherapy in the treatment of mild to severe acne vulgaris (Citations: 12)

David J. Goldberg, Bruce A. Russell

...thermal, non-laser, phototherapy for acne with a combination of blue and red light has recently attracted attention...dermatologist assessments were similar. severe acne showed a marginally better response than mild acne. side effects were minimal and...

Journal: Journal of Cosmetic and Laser Therapy - J COSMET LASER THER , vol. 8, no. 2, pp. 71-75, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7328-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7328_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:42:44">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10592047/phototherapy-in-the-treatment-of-acne-vulgaris-what-is-its-role</link><title>Phototherapy in the Treatment of Acne Vulgaris What is its Role?</title><description>* Phototherapy in the Treatment of Acne Vulgaris What is its Role? (Citations: 3)

Aikaterini Charakida, Edward D. Seaton, Marietta Charakida, Paul Mouser, Antonias Avgerinos, Antony C. Chu

...a marked effect on inflammatory acne lesions and seems sufficient for the treatment of acne. in addition, the combination of blue-red light radiation seems to be...in the current management of acne vulgaris. acne vulgaris is a chronic disease of the pilosebaceous follicle 1. pathophysiology of acne and is the most common...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7328-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7328_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:43:40">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11122798/acne-phototherapy-with-a-high-intensity-enhanced-narrow-band-blue-light-source-an-open-study</link><title>Acne phototherapy with a high-intensity, enhanced, narrow- band, blue light source: an open study and in vitro investigation</title><description>* Acne phototherapy with a high-intensity, enhanced, narrow- band, blue light source: an open study and in vitro investigation (Citations: 9)

Akira Kawada, Yoshinori Aragane, Hiroko Kameyama, Yoshiko Sangen, Tadashi Tezuka

...patients with mild to moderate acne. an open study was performed in acne patients who were treated twice...irradiation from this light source reduced the number of propionibacterium acnes (p. acnes) , but not staphylococcus epidermidis that were isolated from the acne patients. phototherapy using this blue...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7328-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7328_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:45:21">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/31725945/the-inhibition-of-free-radical-generation-by-human-neutrophils-through-the-synergistic-effects-of</link><title>The inhibition of free radical generation by human neutrophils through the synergistic effects of metronidazole with palmitoleic acid: a possible mechanism of action of metronidazole in rosacea and acne</title><description>* The inhibition of free radical generation by human neutrophils through the synergistic effects of metronidazole with palmitoleic acid: a possible mechanism of action of metronidazole in rosacea and acne (Citations: 23)

H. Akamatsu, M. Oguchi, S. Nishijima, Y. Asada, M. Takahashi, T. Ushijima, Y. Niwa

...not only rosacea but also acne inflammation. yet it is generally considered not to be very effective in inhibiting the growth of anaerobic propionibacterium acnes. we report here our investigation...the anaerobic growth of p. acnes as well as on human...

Journal: Archives of Dermatological Research - ARCH DERMATOL RES , vol. 282, no. 7, pp. 449-454, 1990</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7328-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7328_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:46:06">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/33018383/topical-treatment-in-acne-current-status-and-future-aspects</link><title>Topical Treatment in Acne: Current Status and Future Aspects</title><description>* Topical Treatment in Acne: Current Status and Future Aspects (Citations: 28)

Harald P. M. Gollnick, Andrea Krautheim

...drugs for the treatment of acne vulgaris has been enriched. topical...retinoids are a mainstay in acne treatment since 1962. all-trans...

Journal: Dermatology , vol. 206, no. 1, pp. 29-36, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7328-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7328_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:49:20">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11438179/an-open-study-to-determine-the-efficacy-of-blue-light-in-the-treatment-of-mild-to-moderate-acne</link><title>An open study to determine the efficacy of blue light in the treatment of mild to moderate acne</title><description>* An open study to determine the efficacy of blue light in the treatment of mild to moderate acne (Citations: 19)

C. A. Morton, R. D. Scholefield, C. Whitehurst, J. Birch

...background: the effective management of acne remains a challenge; achieving an...found to be effective in reducing the number of inflamed lesions in subjects with mild to moderate acne. the treatment had little effect...

Journal: Journal of Dermatological Treatment , vol. 16, no. 4, pp. 219-223, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7328-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7328_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:51:12">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/31732308/impaired-water-barrier-function-in-acne-vulgaris</link><title>Impaired water barrier function in acne vulgaris</title><description>* Impaired water barrier function in acne vulgaris (Citations: 16)

Ayako Yamamoto, Kaoruko Takenouchi, Masaaki Ito

...in acne vulgaris, abnormal follicular keratinization is...noticed between patients with mild acne and control subjects. significant differences between patients with both moderate and mild acne and control subjects were noted...

Journal: Archives of Dermatological Research - ARCH DERMATOL RES , vol. 287, no. 2, pp. 214-218, 1995</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7328-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7328_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:52:23">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48089711/suppression-of-aromatase-estrogen-synthetase-by-red-wine-phytochemicals</link><title>Suppression of aromatase (estrogen synthetase) by red wine phytochemicals</title><description>* Suppression of aromatase (estrogen synthetase) by red wine phytochemicals (Citations: 14)

Elizabeth T. Eng, Dudley Williams, Usha Mandava, Nimeer Kirma, Rajeshwar Rao Tekmal, Shiuan Chen

...cartridge (waters co.) separation of red wine extracts under an increasing acetonitrile (acn) gradient found that the most active components were in the 20% acn fraction, in that they inhibited...dose-dependent fashion. the 20% acn active fraction was heat stable and inhibited aromatase in a non-competitive manner. the aromatase-inhibitory action of red wine extracts was also examined...

Journal: Breast Cancer Research and Treatment - BREAST CANCER RES TREAT , vol. 67, no. 2, pp. 133-146, 2001</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>