<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7405">light therapy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:42:25" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7405-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7405_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:42:27">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/37041636/light-therapy-for-seasonal-affective-disorder-a-review-of-efficacy</link><title>Light therapy for Seasonal Affective Disorder A review of efficacy</title><description>* Light therapy for Seasonal Affective Disorder A review of efficacy (Citations: 149)

M TERMAN

Journal: Neuropsychopharmacology , vol. 2, no. 1, pp. 1-22, 1989</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7405-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7405_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:43:50">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/36824567/morning-bright-light-therapy-for-sleep-and-behavior-disorders-in-elderly-patients-with-dementia</link><title>Morning bright light therapy for sleep and behavior disorders in elderly patients with dementia</title><description>* Morning bright light therapy for sleep and behavior disorders in elderly patients with dementia (Citations: 113)

K. Mishima, M. Okawa, Y. Hishikawa, S. Hozumi, H. Hori, K. Takahashi

Journal: Acta Psychiatrica Scandinavica - ACTA PSYCHIAT SCAND , vol. 89, no. 1, pp. 1-7, 1994</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7405-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7405_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:44:32">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/29551187/macrophage-responsiveness-to-light-therapy</link><title>Macrophage responsiveness to light therapy</title><description>* Macrophage responsiveness to light therapy (Citations: 95)

Steve Young, Peter Bolton, Mary Dyson, Wil Harvey, Costas Diamantopoulos

...this study to see if light could stimulate the release of...to the following wavelengths of light: 660 nm, 820 nm, 870...

Journal: Lasers in Surgery and Medicine - LASER SURG MED , vol. 9, no. 5, pp. 497-505, 1989</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7405-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7405_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:45:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/38476076/the-efficacy-of-light-therapy-in-the-treatment-of-mood-disorders-a-review-and-meta-analysis-of-the</link><title>The Efficacy of Light Therapy in the Treatment of Mood Disorders: A Review and Meta-Analysis of the Evidence</title><description>* The Efficacy of Light Therapy in the Treatment of Mood Disorders: A Review and Meta-Analysis of the Evidence (Citations: 113)

R. N. Golden

Journal: American Journal of Psychiatry - AMER J PSYCHIAT , vol. 162, no. 4, pp. 656-662, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7405-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7405_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:48:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/15161477/enzyme-plus-light-therapy-to-repair-dna-damage-in-ultraviolet-b-irradiated-human-skin</link><title>Enzyme plus light therapy to repair DNA damage in ultraviolet-B-irradiated human skin</title><description>* Enzyme plus light therapy to repair DNA damage in ultraviolet-B-irradiated human skin (Citations: 95)

Helger Stege, Len Roza, Arie A. Vink, Markus Grewe, Thomas Ruzicka, Susanne Grether-Beck, Jean Krutmann

...structure after exposure to photoreactivating light. when a dose of uvb...and subsequent exposure to photoreactivating light decreased the number of uvb...

Journal: Proceedings of The National Academy of Sciences - PNAS , vol. 97, no. 4, pp. 1790-1795, 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7405-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7405_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:48:39">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/29428734/combined-8-methoxypsoralen-and-black-light-therapy-of-psoriasis-technique-and-results</link><title>Combined 8-methoxypsoralen and black light therapy of psoriasis TECHNIQUE AND RESULTS</title><description>* Combined 8-methoxypsoralen and black light therapy of psoriasis TECHNIQUE AND RESULTS (Citations: 27)

GERHARD WEBER

Journal: British Journal of Dermatology - BRIT J DERMATOL , vol. 90, no. 3, pp. 317-324, 1974</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7405-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7405_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:50:28">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/29581009/update-on-non-ablative-light-therapy-for-rejuvenation-a-review</link><title>Update on non-ablative light therapy for rejuvenation: A review</title><description>* Update on non-ablative light therapy for rejuvenation: A review (Citations: 48)

Neil S. Sadick

Journal: Lasers in Surgery and Medicine - LASER SURG MED , vol. 32, no. 2, pp. 120-128, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7405-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7405_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:51:20">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/29045883/elevated-plasma-interleukin1-levels-in-humans-following-ultraviolet-light-therapy-for-psoriasis</link><title>Elevated Plasma Interleukin1 Levels in Humans Following Ultraviolet Light Therapy for Psoriasis</title><description>* Elevated Plasma Interleukin1 Levels in Humans Following Ultraviolet Light Therapy for Psoriasis (Citations: 29)

Nellie Konnikov, Stephanie H. Pincus, Charles A. Dinarello

...of patients undergoing chronic uvb therapy. in order to remove plasma...these results demonstrate that uvb therapy induces circulating il-1 and...

Journal: Journal of Investigative Dermatology - J INVEST DERMATOL , vol. 92, no. 2, pp. 235-239, 1989</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7405-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7405_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:53:03">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/35535055/bright-light-therapy-stabilizes-the-antidepressant-effect-of-partial-sleep-deprivation</link><title>Bright light therapy stabilizes the antidepressant effect of partial sleep deprivation</title><description>* Bright light therapy stabilizes the antidepressant effect of partial sleep deprivation (Citations: 49)

Alexander Neumeister, Ralph Goessler, Michael Lucht, Thomas Kapitany, Christian Bamas, Siegfried Kasper

Journal: Biological Psychiatry - BIOL PSYCHIAT , vol. 39, no. 1, pp. 16-21, 1996</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7405-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7405_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:55:00">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6191781/effects-of-tryptophan-depletion-vs-catecholamine-depletion-in-patients-with-seasonal-affective</link><title>Effects of Tryptophan Depletion vs Catecholamine Depletion in Patients With Seasonal Affective Disorder in Remission With Light Therapy</title><description>* Effects of Tryptophan Depletion vs Catecholamine Depletion in Patients With Seasonal Affective Disorder in Remission With Light Therapy (Citations: 59)

Alexander Neumeister, Erick H. Turner, Jefferey R. Matthews, Teodor T. Postolache, Ronald L. Barnett, Manfred Rauh, Rina G. Vetticad, Siegfried Kasper, Norman E. Rosenthal

...of daily 10 000-lux light therapy were enrolled in a double...conclusions: the beneficial effects of light therapy in the treatment of seasonal...

Journal: Archives of General Psychiatry - ARCH GEN PSYCHIAT , vol. 55, no. 6, pp. 524-530, 1998</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>