<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7406">does my child have adhd</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:56:36" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7406-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7406_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:56:37">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/36746382/parent-child-relationships-and-adhd-symptoms-a-longitudinal-analysis</link><title>Parent–Child Relationships and ADHD Symptoms: A Longitudinal Analysis</title><description>* Parent–Child Relationships and ADHD Symptoms: A Longitudinal Analysis (Citations: 16)

Kate J. Lifford, Gordon T. Harold, Anita Thapar

...study examined the relationship between child adhd symptoms and displays of rejection in the parent–child relationship. these relationships were investigated...effects linking mother– and father–child rejection and child adhd symptoms; with adhd symptoms affecting the mother–child relationship and the converse pattern...

Journal: Journal of Abnormal Child Psychology - J ABNORMAL CHILD PSYCHOL , vol. 36, no. 2, pp. 285-296, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7406-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7406_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:59:20">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/36746043/mother-child-interactions-in-adhd-and-comparison-boys-relationships-with-overt-and-covert</link><title>Mother-child interactions in ADHD and comparison boys: Relationships with overt and covert externalizing behavior</title><description>* Mother-child interactions in ADHD and comparison boys: Relationships with overt and covert externalizing behavior (Citations: 39)

Carolyn A. Anderson, Stephen P. Hinshaw, Cassandra Simmel

...and interaction style with the child characterize the development and maintenance of attention-deficit hyperactivity disorder (adhd) as well as its comorbidity...from maternal negativity even with child interactional compliance controlled. differential predictions of noncompliance were revealed in adhd versus comparison families, yet similar...

Journal: Journal of Abnormal Child Psychology - J ABNORMAL CHILD PSYCHOL , vol. 22, no. 2, pp. 247-265, 1994</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7406-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7406_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:00:55">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/29361697/adhd-does-parenting-style-matter</link><title>ADHD: Does Parenting Style Matter?</title><description>* ADHD: Does Parenting Style Matter? (Citations: 5)

Vania Modesto-Lowe, Jeffrey S. Danforth, Donna Brooks

...and 2007 with the keywords adhd and parenting. child adhd elicits high levels of parental...parent's response to the child's adhd symptoms. optimizing parent—child interaction and parental psychiatric status may improve outcomes for both parent and child....

Journal: Clinical Pediatrics - CLIN PEDIAT , vol. 47, no. 9, pp. 865-872, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7406-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7406_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:03:04">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/34436361/a-growth-curve-analysis-of-the-joint-influences-of-parenting-affect-child-characteristics-and</link><title>A Growth Curve Analysis of the Joint Influences of Parenting Affect, Child Characteristics and Deviant Peers on Adolescent Illicit Drug Use</title><description>* A Growth Curve Analysis of the Joint Influences of Parenting Affect, Child Characteristics and Deviant Peers on Adolescent Illicit Drug Use (Citations: 10)

Paulo Pires, Jennifer M. Jenkins

...both effects were significant when child adhd symptoms were taken into account...with drug use, did not have a differential influence over time...

Journal: Journal of Youth and Adolescence - J YOUTH ADOLESCENCE , vol. 36, no. 2, pp. 169-183, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7406-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7406_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:04:19">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/37340998/parent-child-interaction-therapy-for-adhd-a-conceptual-overview-and-critical-literature-review</link><title>Parent-Child Interaction Therapy for ADHD: A Conceptual Overview and Critical Literature Review</title><description>* Parent-Child Interaction Therapy for ADHD: A Conceptual Overview and Critical Literature Review (Citations: 2)

Stephanie M. Wagner, Cheryl B. McNeil

...to school-aged children, preschoolers have not received as much attention in the literature. parent-child interaction therapy (pcit) is an...treatment outcome studies that measured adhd symptoms. the literature demonstrates that children with adhd have been included in pcit research...

Journal: Child &amp; Family Behavior Therapy - CHILD FAM BEHAV THER , vol. 30, no. 3, pp. 231-256, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7406-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7406_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:04:52">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57759051/does-childhood-disability-increase-risk-for-child-abuse-and-neglect</link><title>Does Childhood Disability Increase Risk for Child Abuse and Neglect?</title><description>* Does Childhood Disability Increase Risk for Child Abuse and Neglect?

Rebecca T. Leeb, Rebecca H. Bitsko, Melissa T. Merrick, Brian S. Armour

...are at increased risk for child maltreatment, and parents with disabilities are more likely to perpetrate child abuse and neglect. challenges to...as the ecological model of child maltreatment. one potential pathway from disability to child maltreatment is presented. knowing and understanding the link between disability and child abuse and neglect is an...

Journal: Journal of Mental Health Research in Intellectual Disabilities , vol. 5, no. 1, pp. 4-31, 2012</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7406-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7406_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:07:04">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5481811/pnp4-physician-perceptions-on-the-use-of-medications-for-attention-deficit-hyperactivity-disorder</link><title>PNP4: PHYSICIAN PERCEPTIONS ON THE USE OF MEDICATIONS FOR ATTENTION DEFICIT HYPERACTIVITY DISORDER</title><description>* PNP4: PHYSICIAN PERCEPTIONS ON THE USE OF MEDICATIONS FOR ATTENTION DEFICIT HYPERACTIVITY DISORDER (Citations: 11)

KAREN M. STOCKL, TOM E. HUGHES, MANAL A. JARRAR, KRISTINA SECNIK, AMY R. PERWIEN

...year, compared to children without adhd. 4 the total annual health care costs for children with adhd are estimated to be more...significantly larg- er when a child with adhd is diagnosed with a comorbid...

Journal: Value in Health - VALUE HEALTH , vol. 6, no. 3, pp. 272-272, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7406-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7406_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:08:18">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48168028/how-do-children-with-adhd-mis-manage-their-real-life-dyadic-friendships-a-multi-method</link><title>How Do Children with ADHD (Mis)manage Their Real-Life Dyadic Friendships? A Multi-Method Investigation</title><description>* How Do Children with ADHD (Mis)manage Their Real-Life Dyadic Friendships? A Multi-Method Investigation (Citations: 2)

Sébastien Normand, Barry H. Schneider, Matthew D. Lee, Marie-France Maisonneuve, Sally M. Kuehn, Philippe Robaey

...with comparison children, children with adhd had friends with high levels of adhd and oppositional symptoms; they perceived...in dyads consisting of one child with adhd and one typically developing child, children with adhd were often more dominant than...

Journal: Journal of Abnormal Child Psychology - J ABNORMAL CHILD PSYCHOL , vol. 39, no. 2, pp. 293-305, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7406-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7406_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:10:17">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/47917967/talk-about-school-between-mothers-and-children-with-or-without-adhd</link><title>Talk About School Between Mothers and Children With or Without ADHD</title><description>* Talk About School Between Mothers and Children With or Without ADHD

Cilla H. Stultz, Dorothy Flannagan

...twenty mother-child dyads including a child with attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (adhd) and 20 mother-child dyads containing a child without adhd recorded a conversation about the...assessed. mothers of children with adhd rated their children's behavioral conduct lower than did other mothers, and dyads including children with adhd discussed behavioral conduct more and...

Journal: Journal of Child and Family Studies - J CHILD FAM STUD , vol. 8, no. 4, pp. 425-435, 1999</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7406-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7406_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:10:49">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/34806465/does-brief-clinically-based-intensive-multimodal-behavior-therapy-enhance-the-effects-of</link><title>Does brief, clinically based, intensive multimodal behavior therapy enhance the effects of methylphenidate in children with ADHD?</title><description>* Does brief, clinically based, intensive multimodal behavior therapy enhance the effects of methylphenidate in children with ADHD? (Citations: 13)

Saskia van der Oord, Pier J. M. Prins, Jaap Oosterlaan, Paul M. G. Emmelkamp

...with attention-deficit hyperactivity disorder (adhd) was investigated. method  fifty children with adhd (ages 8–12) were randomized...behavior therapy consisted of a child and parent behavioral therapy and a teacher behavioral training. assessments included parent, teacher and child ratings of adhd symptoms, oppositional and conduct behavior...

Journal: European Child &amp; Adolescent Psychiatry - EUR CHILD ADOLESC PSYCHIATR , vol. 16, no. 1, pp. 48-57, 2007</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>