<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7423">postdoc jobs european university biotech</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:26:00" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7423-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7423_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:26:03">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5518211/economic-networks-what-do-we-know-and-what-do-we-need-to-know</link><title>Economic Networks: What do we know and What do we need to know?</title><description>* Economic Networks: What do we know and What do we need to know? (Citations: 3)

Frank Schweitzer, Giorgio Fagiolo, Didier Sornette, Fernando Vega-Redondo, Douglas R. White

We examine the emergent field of economic networks and explore its ability to shed light on the global and volatile economy where credit, ownership, innovation, invest- ment, and virtually every other economic activity is carried at a scale and scope that respects no geographical, organizational, or political boundaries. In this context, the study of economic networks and their dynamics must ...

Journal: Advances in Complex Systems - ACS , vol. 12, no. 4-5, pp. 407-422, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7423-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7423_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:28:10">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/26134979/the-m&amp;a-dynamics-of-european-science-based-entrepreneurial-firms</link><title>The M&amp;A dynamics of European science-based entrepreneurial firms</title><description>* The M&amp;A dynamics of European science-based entrepreneurial firms (Citations: 2)

Damiano Bonardo, Stefano Paleari, Silvio Vismara

...and other possible determinants. while university affiliation enhanced attractiveness in the eyes of other companies, it negatively affected the propensity for acquisition. we argue that university-based firms do contribute to...process of commercial exploitation of university-research, while the subsequent step...

Journal: Journal of Technology Transfer - J TECHNOL TRANSFER , vol. 35, no. 1, pp. 141-180, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7423-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7423_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:28:52">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/43550056/assessing-the-international-web-connectivity-of-research-groups</link><title>Assessing the international web connectivity of research groups</title><description>* Assessing the international web connectivity of research groups

Mike Thelwall, Xuemei Li, Franz Barjak, Simon Robinson

...and present brief details of european life sciences research groups as...particularly important for attracting overseas job applicants and to promote research...

Journal: Aslib Proceedings - ASLIB PROC , vol. 60, no. 1, pp. 18-31, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7423-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7423_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:29:36">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10613460/high-growth-entrepreneurs-public-policies-and-economic-growth</link><title>High-Growth Entrepreneurs, Public Policies, and Economic Growth</title><description>* High-Growth Entrepreneurs, Public Policies, and Economic Growth (Citations: 14)

Erik Stam, Kashifa Suddle, Jolanda Hessels, André van Stel

The chapter is structured as follows. After starting with a review of the literature on growth ambitions of entrepreneurs and high-growth firms in Sect. 5.2, we will discuss public policy aimed at high-growth firms in general in the third section. Next, high-growth firms in the USA and the Netherlands are evaluated. In the empirical part of ...

Published in 2006.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7423-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7423_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:31:14">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6183234/what-is-the-value-of-entrepreneurship-a-review-of-recent-research</link><title>What is the value of entrepreneurship? A review of recent research</title><description>* What is the value of entrepreneurship? A review of recent research (Citations: 71)

C. Mirjam van Praag, Peter H. Versloot

...secure labor market, higher paid jobs and a greater number of...

Journal: Small Business Economics - SMALL BUS ECON , vol. 29, no. 4, pp. 351-382, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7423-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7423_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:34:45">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57588240/measuring-knowledge-bases-in-swedish-regions</link><title>Measuring Knowledge Bases in Swedish Regions</title><description>* Measuring Knowledge Bases in Swedish Regions

Roman Martin

Within the literature on innovation systems, there are a growing number of scholars emphasizing the importance of differentiated knowledge bases underlying innovation activities. The existing work on knowledge bases is largely grounded on in-depth case studies; while surprisingly little effort has been done so far to operationalize the concept in a more systematic manner. In this article, an attempt ...

Journal: European Planning Studies - EUR PLAN STUD , vol. ahead-of-p, no. ahead-of-p, pp. 1-14, 2012</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7423-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7423_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:35:33">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/7005693/the-unequal-benefits-of-academic-patenting-for-science-and-engineering-research</link><title>The Unequal Benefits of Academic Patenting for Science and Engineering Research</title><description>* The Unequal Benefits of Academic Patenting for Science and Engineering Research (Citations: 3)

Mario Calderini, Chiara Franzoni, Andrea Vezzulli

...the increase of university patents has raised issues of...

Journal: IEEE Transactions on Engineering Management - IEEE TRANS ENG MANAGE , vol. 56, no. 1, pp. 16-30, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7423-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7423_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:37:04">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/12986597/growth-dynamics-of-dedicated-biotechnology-firms-in-transition-economies-evidence-from-the-baltic</link><title>Growth dynamics of dedicated biotechnology firms in transition economies. Evidence from the Baltic countries and Poland</title><description>* Growth dynamics of dedicated biotechnology firms in transition economies. Evidence from the Baltic countries and Poland

Stéphane Malo, Jesper Norus

Countries undergoing the difficult transition from state ownership to market economies have characteristics which are often portrayed by scholars as adverse to the development of SMEs. Others nonetheless suggest that the performance of such firms can be positively influenced by business strategies. To develop a better understanding of the relation between these two seemingly different standpoints, this paper investigates the ...

Journal: Entrepreneurship and Regional Development - ENTREP REG DEV , vol. 21, no. 5-6, pp. 481-502, 2009</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>