<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7425">coloring picture cars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:42:54" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7425-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7425_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:42:55">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50713947/traffic-sign-recognition-using-scale-invariant-feature-transform-and-color-classification</link><title>Traffic sign recognition using Scale Invariant Feature Transform and color classification</title><description>* Traffic sign recognition using Scale Invariant Feature Transform and color classification (Citations: 4)

M. C. Kus, Muhittin Gökmen, S. Etaner-Uyar

...performance are added. those are color inspection by using proposed color classification method and inspecting the...which are found by sift. color classification method finds out true colors of the pixels by applying some classification rules. it is observed that adding color and orientation inspections raises the...

Conference: International Symposium on Computer and Information Sciences - ISCIS , 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7425-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7425_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:44:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/58853518/letter-written-by-dorothy-a-six-clark-to-william-judson-clark-dated-1945</link><title>Letter Written by Dorothy A. Six Clark to William Judson Clark Dated 1945</title><description>* Letter Written by Dorothy A. Six Clark to William Judson Clark Dated 1945

Dorothy A. Six Clark

...was a riot. the funniest picture i’ve seen in a long...when do we get the color pictures? most of the people i...

Published in 1945.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7425-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7425_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:46:38">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4727737/a-method-to-recognize-and-count-leaves-on-the-surface-of-a-river-using-user-s-knowledge-about-color</link><title>A Method to Recognize and Count Leaves on the Surface of a River Using User's Knowledge about Color of Leaves</title><description>* A Method to Recognize and Count Leaves on the Surface of a River Using User's Knowledge about Color of Leaves

Fujio Tsutsumi, Yutaka Tateda

...leaves in recorded video using color and motion features. the color feature is represented by 3 dimensional histogram of a color space. we have developed a...sample data to extract the color feature by the user interface in the same way as coloring a picture. for the motion feature, speed...

Conference: Pacific-Asia Conference on Knowledge Discovery and Data Mining - PAKDD , pp. 203-212, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7425-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7425_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:49:06">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5213234/long-term-expertise-with-artificial-objects-increases-visual-competition-with-early-face</link><title>Long-term Expertise with Artificial Objects Increases Visual Competition with Early Face Categorization Processes</title><description>* Long-term Expertise with Artificial Objects Increases Visual Competition with Early Face Categorization Processes (Citations: 15)

Bruno Rossion, Daniel Collins, Valérie Goffaux, Tim Curran

...visual objects of expertise. in car experts fixating pictures of cars, we observed a large decrease...was much lower when the car and face stimuli were separated...

Journal: Journal of Cognitive Neuroscience , vol. 19, no. 3, pp. 543-555, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7425-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7425_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:50:50">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5923247/mental-imagery-and-aging</link><title>Mental imagery and aging</title><description>* Mental imagery and aging (Citations: 77)

Itiel E. Dror, Stephen M. Kosslyn

...when trying to recall the color of a car, one may create a "mental picture" of the car and "look" at it; or...

Journal: Psychology and Aging - PSYCHOL AGING , vol. 9, no. 1, pp. 90-102, 1994</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7425-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7425_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:52:42">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/36507601/blue-car-red-car-developing-efficiency-in-online-interpretation-of-adjective-noun-phrases</link><title>Blue car, red car: Developing efficiency in online interpretation of adjective–noun phrases</title><description>* Blue car, red car: Developing efficiency in online interpretation of adjective–noun phrases (Citations: 4)

Anne Fernald, Kirsten Thorpe, Virginia A. Marchman

...noun phrases (e.g. blue car) in visual contexts where the adjective was either informative (e.g. blue car paired with red car or red house) or uninformative (e.g. blue car paired with blue house). thirty...

Journal: Cognitive Psychology - COG PSYCHOL , vol. 60, no. 3, pp. 190-217, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7425-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7425_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:53:48">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/51561748/cross-cultural-differences-in-color-preferences-implication-for-international-film-distribution</link><title>Cross-cultural differences in color preferences: implication for international film distribution</title><description>* Cross-cultural differences in color preferences: implication for international film distribution

Kyung Jae Lee

...proposes the necessity of manipulating colors of movie contents to fit diverse audiences around the world. since films are highly color-dependent messages, it is critical...constant guide for the motion picture industry. the film production stage is often disregarded to deliver the appropriate visual color contents for local audience when...

Published in 2002.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7425-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7425_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:55:17">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50915152/the-analysis-on-vehicle-color-evoked-eeg-based-on-erp-method</link><title>The Analysis on Vehicle Color Evoked EEG Based on ERP Method</title><description>* The Analysis on Vehicle Color Evoked EEG Based on ERP Method

Hong Wang, Ningning Zhang

...using the red and blue car pictures. the average response accuracy rate of red car is higher, and the average...brain energy evoked by red car is larger than that of blue car. it is concluded that red car picture statistically tends to explode the...

Conference: International Conference on Bioinformatics and Biomedical Engineering - ICBBE , pp. 1-3, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7425-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7425_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:56:13">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/49149524/erp-evidence-for-the-speed-of-face-categorization-in-the-human-brain-disentangling-the</link><title>ERP evidence for the speed of face categorization in the human brain: Disentangling the contribution of low-level visual cues from face perception</title><description>* ERP evidence for the speed of face categorization in the human brain: Disentangling the contribution of low-level visual cues from face perception (Citations: 2)

Bruno Rossion, Stéphanie Caharel

...sensitivity in the human brain. pictures of faces and of a category of familiar objects (cars), as well as their phase...face-sensitivity – larger response to pictures of faces than cars – at the level of the...

Journal: Vision Research - VISION RES , vol. 51, no. 12, pp. 1297-1311, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7425-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7425_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:56:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50826319/vehicle-retrieval-using-eigen-color-and-multiple-instance-learning</link><title>Vehicle Retrieval Using Eigen Color and Multiple Instance Learning</title><description>* Vehicle Retrieval Using Eigen Color and Multiple Instance Learning (Citations: 1)

Shin-Yu Chen, Jun-Wei Hsieh, Jui-Chen Wu, Yung-Sheng Chen

...images from databases using eigen color and the concept of multiple instance learning. usually, vehicles have various colors and shapes under different viewpoints...no matter what orientations and colors they are. first of all, this paper proposes a novel color transform model, which is global...

Conference: Intelligent Information Hiding and Multimedia Signal Processing - IIH-MSP , 2009</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>