<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7431">navalni trial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:25:15" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7431-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7431_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:25:16">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/26513880/sea-trial-experimental-results-of-fin-rudder-roll-stabilisation</link><title>Sea-trial experimental results of fin/rudder roll stabilisation</title><description>* Sea-trial experimental results of fin/rudder roll stabilisation

M. T. Sharif, G. N. Roberts, R. Sutton

...on full-scale roll stabilisation trials on board a frigate-size royal naval warship. the trials entailed comparing the efficacy of...

Journal: Control Engineering Practice - CONTROL ENG PRACTICE , vol. 3, no. 5, pp. 703-708, 1995</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7431-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7431_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:25:51">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/54981027/infrared-search-and-track-irst-modeling-and-validation</link><title>Infrared search and track (IRST) modeling and validation</title><description>* Infrared search and track (IRST) modeling and validation

Thomas G. Brown, Philippe Lafleur

...test and evaluation in a naval environment. trial data have been used to...

Published in 1994.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7431-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7431_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:26:32">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/49003129/rationale-and-design-of-the-mass-comm-trial-a-randomized-trial-to-compare-percutaneous-coronary</link><title>Rationale and Design of the MASS COMM Trial: A Randomized Trial to Compare Percutaneous Coronary Intervention between MassachusettsHospitals with Cardiac Surgery-On-Site and CommunityHospitalsWithout Cardiac Surgery-On-Site</title><description>* Rationale and Design of the MASS COMM Trial: A Randomized Trial to Compare Percutaneous Coronary Intervention between MassachusettsHospitals with Cardiac Surgery-On-Site and CommunityHospitalsWithout Cardiac Surgery-On-Site

Laura Mauri, Sharon-Lise T. Normand, Michael Pencina, Donald E. Cutlip, Cathy Jeon, Paul Dreyer, Richard E. Kuntz, Donald S. Baim, Alice K. Jacobs

...there have been no randomized trials evaluating whether cardiac surgery services...study design: the mass comm trial (clinicaltrials.gov #nct01116882) is a randomized trial comparing the safety and effectiveness...

Journal: American Heart Journal - AMER HEART J</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7431-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7431_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:27:02">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11871585/combined-clinical-trial-results-of-a-her2-neu-e75-vaccine-for-the-prevention-of-recurrence-in</link><title>Combined Clinical Trial Results of a HER2/neu (E75) Vaccine for the Prevention of Recurrence in High-Risk Breast Cancer Patients: U.S. Military Cancer Institute Clinical Trials Group Study I-01 and I-02</title><description>* Combined Clinical Trial Results of a HER2/neu (E75) Vaccine for the Prevention of Recurrence in High-Risk Breast Cancer Patients: U.S. Military Cancer Institute Clinical Trials Group Study I-01 and I-02 (Citations: 14)

George E. Peoples, Jarrod P. Holmes, Matthew T. Hueman, Elizabeth A. Mittendorf, Asna Amin, Steven Khoo, Zia A. Dehqanzada, Jennifer M. Gurney, Michael M. Woll, Gayle B. Ryan, Catherine E. Storrer, Dianna Craighttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=11871585&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=navalni trial

...conducted two overlapping e75 vaccine trials to prevent recurrence in node...in a dose escalation safety trial and to nn breast cancer...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7431-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7431_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:27:36">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/61239284/initial-field-trials-of-the-site-characterization-and-analysis-penetrometer-system-scaps</link><title>Initial field trials of the site characterization and analysis penetrometer system (SCAPS). Reconnaissance of Jacksonville Naval Air Station waste oil and solvents disposal site. Final report</title><description>* Initial field trials of the site characterization and analysis penetrometer system (SCAPS). Reconnaissance of Jacksonville Naval Air Station waste oil and solvents disposal site. Final report

S. S. Cooper, D. H. Douglas, M. K. Sharp, R. A. Olsen, G. D. Comes

...at the request of the naval facilities engineering command (navfac), southern...wes) conducted the initial field trial of the site characterization and analysis penetrometer system (scaps) at jacksonville naval air station (nas), jacksonville fl...

Published in 1993.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7431-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7431_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:28:07">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48147520/data-collection-in-support-of-the-modelling-of-naval-vessels</link><title>Data Collection in Support of the Modelling of Naval Vessels</title><description>* Data Collection in Support of the Modelling of Naval Vessels

S. Gwynne, L. Filippidis, E. Galea, D. Cooney, P. Boxall

...are to be applied to naval vessels there is a clear requirement to understand the behaviour of well-trained naval personnel interacting with the fixtures...understanding of the performance of naval personnel in warship environments. the trials were designed and conducted by...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7431-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7431_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:28:42">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/30555224/predictive-value-of-diminutive-colonic-adenoma-trial-the-predict-trial</link><title>Predictive value of diminutive colonic adenoma trial: The PREDICT trial</title><description>* Predictive value of diminutive colonic adenoma trial: The PREDICT trial (Citations: 7)

Philip Schoenfeld, Javaid Shad, Eric Ormseth, Walter Coyle, Brooks Cash, James Butler, William Schindler, Walter J. Kikendall, Christopher Furlong, Leslie H. Sobin, Christine M. Hobbs, David Cruesshttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=30555224&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=navalni trial

...with flexible sigmoidoscopy (fs). this trial assessed the predictive value of...in a multicenter, prospective cohort trial, we matched 200 patients with...

Journal: Clinical Gastroenterology and Hepatology - CLIN GASTROENTEROL HEPATOL , vol. 1, no. 3, pp. 195-201, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7431-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7431_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:29:27">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/31685675/combined-clinical-trial-results-of-a-her2-neu-e75-vaccine-for-the-prevention-of-recurrence-in</link><title>Combined Clinical Trial Results of a HER2/neu (E75) Vaccine for the Prevention of Recurrence in High-Risk Breast Cancer Patients: U.S. Military Cancer Institute Clinical Trials Group Study I-01 and I-02</title><description>* Combined Clinical Trial Results of a HER2/neu (E75) Vaccine for the Prevention of Recurrence in High-Risk Breast Cancer Patients: U.S. Military Cancer Institute Clinical Trials Group Study I-01 and I-02 (Citations: 23)

G. E. Peoples, J. P. Holmes, M. T. Hueman, E. A. Mittendorf, A. Amin, S. Khoo, Z. A. Dehqanzada, J. M. Gurney, M. M. Woll, G. B. Ryan, C. E. Storrer, D. Craighttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=31685675&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=navalni trial

Journal: Clinical Cancer Research - CLIN CANCER RES , vol. 14, no. 3, pp. 797-803, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7431-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7431_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:29:54">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5473282/a-self-controlled-trial-to-evaluate-the-use-of-active-hearing-defenders-in-the-engine-rooms-of</link><title>A Self-Controlled Trial to Evaluate the Use of Active Hearing Defenders in the Engine Rooms of Operational Naval Vessels</title><description>* A Self-Controlled Trial to Evaluate the Use of Active Hearing Defenders in the Engine Rooms of Operational Naval Vessels (Citations: 1)

M Ong, J T L Choo

...methods: a blinded, self-controlled trial was conducted among naval servicemen to compare the effectiveness...

Published in 2004.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7431-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7431_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:30:32">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/32108511/standard-versus-ph-adjusted-and-lidocaine-supplemented-radiocolloid-for-patients-undergoing</link><title>Standard versus pH-adjusted and lidocaine supplemented radiocolloid for patients undergoing sentinel-lymph-node mapping and biopsy for early breast cancer (PASSION-P trial): a double-blind, randomised controlled trial</title><description>* Standard versus pH-adjusted and lidocaine supplemented radiocolloid for patients undergoing sentinel-lymph-node mapping and biopsy for early breast cancer (PASSION-P trial): a double-blind, randomised controlled trial (Citations: 2)

Alexander Stojadinovic, George E Peoples, Jennifer S Jurgens, Robin S Howard, Brandi Schuyler, Kyung H Kwon, Leonard R Henry, Craig D Shriver, Chester C Buckenmaier

Journal: Lancet Oncology - LANCET ONCOL , vol. 10, no. 9, pp. 849-854, 2009</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>