<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7434">wellness hotel Maastricht</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:45:14" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7434-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7434_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:45:15">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/37825613/the-effect-of-customer-card-programs-a-comparative-study-in-singapore-and-the-netherlands</link><title>The effect of customer card programs : A comparative study in Singapore and The Netherlands</title><description>* The effect of customer card programs : A comparative study in Singapore and The Netherlands (Citations: 21)

Corine Noordhoff, Pieter Pauwels, Gaby Odekerken-Schröder

...an established phenomenon (e.g. hotel and airline industry). developing this...indeed impact on attitudinal as well as behavioural store loyalty, as...

Journal: International Journal of Service Industry Management - INT J SERVICE IND MANAGEMENT , vol. 15, no. 4, pp. 351-364, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7434-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7434_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:45:59">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10813903/explaining-the-occupational-structure-of-dutch-sectors-of-industry-1988-2002</link><title>Explaining the occupational structure of Dutch sectors of industry, 1988-2002</title><description>* Explaining the occupational structure of Dutch sectors of industry, 1988-2002

Frank Cörvers, Arnaud Dupuy

...of employment shares fit very well to the data for the...the occupational mix in the hotel, catering and commercial services sector as well as in the health care...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7434-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7434_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:46:27">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/47858672/policies-fostering-new-firm-formation-and-self-employment-in-italy</link><title>Policies Fostering New Firm Formation and Self-Employment in Italy</title><description>* Policies Fostering New Firm Formation and Self-Employment in Italy

Martin Carree, Roberta Piergiovanni, Enrico Santarelli, Ingrid Verheul

...local level: manufacturing, construction, commerce, hotels and restaurants, transportation, and financial...entrepreneurship policies and unemployment, as well as other relevant regional factors...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7434-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7434_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:47:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5451726/the-effect-of-customer-card-programs</link><title>The effect of customer card programs</title><description>* The effect of customer card programs

Corine Noordhoff, Pieter Pauwels, Gaby Odekerken-Schroder

...an established phenomenon (e.g. hotel and airline industry). developing this...indeed impact on attitudinal as well as behavioural store loyalty, as...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7434-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7434_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:47:58">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/58071313/growth-factors-of-flemish-enterprises-an-exploratory-study-over-the-period-1993-1997</link><title>Growth factors of flemish enterprises: an exploratory study over the period 1993-1997</title><description>* Growth factors of flemish enterprises: an exploratory study over the period 1993-1997

Eddy Laveren, Arthur Limere, Kathleen Cleeren

...characteristics of the population as well as firm location and firm growth. industry wise, the low growth performance of "wholesale trade, retail trade, hotels, restaurants and pubs, repair" (nace...

Published in 2003.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7434-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7434_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:48:26">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/34410559/service-firms-and-customer-loyalty-programs-a-regulatory-fit-perspective-of-reward-preferences-in</link><title>Service firms and customer loyalty programs: a regulatory fit perspective of reward preferences in a health club setting</title><description>* Service firms and customer loyalty programs: a regulatory fit perspective of reward preferences in a health club setting (Citations: 1)

Ahmad Daryanto, Ko de Ruyter, Martin Wetzels, Paul G. Patterson

...how they are communicated, as well as the congruence between reward...

Journal: Journal of The Academy of Marketing Science - J ACAD MARK SCI , vol. 38, no. 5, pp. 604-616, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7434-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7434_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:49:10">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/41938454/modelling-return-to-work-intervention-strategies-a-method-to-help-target-interventions</link><title>Modelling Return-to-Work Intervention Strategies: A Method to Help Target Interventions</title><description>* Modelling Return-to-Work Intervention Strategies: A Method to Help Target Interventions (Citations: 4)

Catelijne Joling, Peter P. M. Janssen, W. J. N. Groot

The aim of this study is twofold: 1) to investigate the relationship between the probability of receiving an intervention by the occupational physician and the probability of return-to-work (RTW) of sick workers; 2) to explore the use of simultaneous modelling of the intervention and RTW process. Analyses are performed on population level using data from a major longitudinal ...

Journal: Journal of Occupational Rehabilitation - J OCCUP REHABIL , vol. 14, no. 1, pp. 43-62, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7434-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7434_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:50:22">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10474888/knowledge-transfer-and-the-services-sector-in-the-context-of-the-new-economy</link><title>Knowledge Transfer and the Services Sector in the Context of the New Economy</title><description>* Knowledge Transfer and the Services Sector in the Context of the New Economy (Citations: 2)

Robin Cowan, Luc Soete, Oxana Tchervonnava

This paper examines the processes of knowledge transfer in the services sector in the economic reality, increasingly affected by the use of information and communication technologies. An important focus is to explore whether the knowledge transfer channels, traditionally used in manufacturing, can also be made use of in services. To this end, the authors examine the specificity of services with ...

Published in 2001.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>