<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7438">facebook privacy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:00:13" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7438-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7438_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:00:14">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/3083845/facebook-threats-to-privacy</link><title>Facebook: Threats to Privacy</title><description>* Facebook: Threats to Privacy (Citations: 40)

Harvey Jones, Hiram Soltren

...wide variety of information on facebook, but a discussion of the privacy implications of doing so has yet to emerge. we examined how facebook aects privacy, and found serious a ws in the system. privacy on facebook is undermined by three principal...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7438-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7438_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:00:51">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/15259103/facebook-and-online-privacy-attitudes-behaviors-and-unintended-consequences</link><title>Facebook and Online Privacy: Attitudes, Behaviors, and Unintended Consequences</title><description>* Facebook and Online Privacy: Attitudes, Behaviors, and Unintended Consequences (Citations: 15)

Bernhard Debatin, Jennette P. Lovejoy, Ann-Kathrin Horn, Brittany N. Hughes

...this article investigates facebook users' awareness of privacy issues and perceived benefits and risks of utilizing facebook. research found that facebook is deeply integrated in users...the self. however, users reporting privacy invasion were more likely to change privacy settings than those merely hearing about others' privacy invasions. results suggest that this...

Journal: Journal of Computer-mediated Communication - JCMC , vol. 15, no. 1, pp. 83-108, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7438-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7438_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:01:42">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/44813978/facebook-s-privacy-trainwreckexposure-invasion-and-social-convergence</link><title>Facebook's Privacy TrainwreckExposure, Invasion, and Social Convergence</title><description>* Facebook's Privacy TrainwreckExposure, Invasion, and Social Convergence (Citations: 12)

danah boyd

...not all facebook users appreciated the september 2006 launch of the `news feeds' feature. concerned about privacy implications, thousands of users vocalized...forcing the company to implement privacy tools. this essay examines the privacy concerns voiced following these events...

Journal: Convergence: The International Journal of Research Into New Media Technologies , vol. 14, no. 1, pp. 13-20, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7438-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7438_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:02:35">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/14005080/facebook-privacy-settings-who-cares</link><title>Facebook Privacy Settings: Who Cares?</title><description>* Facebook Privacy Settings: Who Cares? (Citations: 11)

Danah Boyd, Eszter Hargittai

...during a year in which facebook's approach to privacy was hotly contested. we also find that both frequency and type of facebook use as well as internet skill are correlated with making modifications to privacy settings. in contrast, we observe few gender differences in how young adults approach their facebook privacy settings, which is notable given...

Journal: First Monday - FIRSTMONDAY , vol. 15, no. 8, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7438-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7438_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:03:09">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4703003/research-ethics-in-the-facebook-era-privacy-anonymity-and-oversight</link><title>Research ethics in the facebook era: privacy, anonymity, and oversight</title><description>* Research ethics in the facebook era: privacy, anonymity, and oversight (Citations: 2)

Nathan Bos, Karrie Karahalios, Marcela Musgrove-chávez, Erika Shehan Poole, John Charles Thomas, Sarita Yardi

Ethical standards for human subjects research have not kept up with new research paradigms. Several research areas are particularly problematic for the CHI community. Online social research is testing the boundaries of public observation, third-party disclosure, and anonymization methods. Furthermore, there are differences in norms about what is and is not ethical among various research disciplines studying the Web. ...

Conference: Computer Human Interaction - CHI , pp. 2767-2770, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7438-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7438_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:03:58">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5884861/privacy-as-information-access-and-illusory-control-the-case-of-the-facebook-news-feed-privacy</link><title>Privacy as information access and illusory control: The case of the Facebook News Feed privacy outcry</title><description>* Privacy as information access and illusory control: The case of the Facebook News Feed privacy outcry (Citations: 7)

Christopher M. Hoadley, Heng Xu, Joey J. Lee, Mary Beth Rosson

...of the most popular sites—facebook.com—introduced the features of...feed features, trig- gered users' privacy concerns. in addition to enhancing our theoretical understanding of privacy issues in the online social...

Journal: Electronic Commerce Research and Applications - ECRA , vol. 9, no. 1, pp. 50-60, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7438-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7438_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:04:37">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/56902572/analyzing-facebook-privacy-settings-user-expectations-vs-reality</link><title>Analyzing facebook privacy settings: user expectations vs. reality</title><description>* Analyzing facebook privacy settings: user expectations vs. reality

Yabing Liu, Krishna P. Gummadi, Balachander Krishnamurthy, Alan Mislove

...online social networking sites like facebook. as a result, the issue of online social network privacy has received significant attention in...of the problem of managing privacy. we deploy a survey, implemented as a facebook application, to 200 facebook users recruited via amazon mechanical...

Published in 2011.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7438-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7438_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:05:31">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/58574549/facebook-and-privacy-it-s-complicated</link><title>Facebook and privacy: it's complicated</title><description>* Facebook and privacy: it's complicated

Maritza Johnson, Serge Egelman, Steven M. Bellovin

...measure users' attitudes toward interpersonal privacy concerns on facebook and measure users' strategies for...do this, we recruited 260 facebook users to install a facebook application that surveyed their privacy concerns, their friend network compositions...

Published in 2012.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7438-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7438_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:06:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/61432517/facebook-in-privacy-breach</link><title>Facebook in Privacy Breach</title><description>* Facebook in Privacy Breach

Emily Steel, Geoffrey A. Fowler

Published in 2010.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7438-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7438_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:06:39">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/44567624/the-pedagogy-of-momus-technologies-facebook-privacy-and-online-intimacy</link><title>The Pedagogy of Momus Technologies: Facebook, Privacy, and Online Intimacy</title><description>* The Pedagogy of Momus Technologies: Facebook, Privacy, and Online Intimacy

M. van Manen

Journal: Qualitative Health Research - QUAL HEALTH RES , vol. 20, no. 8, pp. 1023-1032, 2010</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>