<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7441">barcelona real madrid goal messi</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:22:36" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7441-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7441_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:22:38">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/583739/a-case-of-multiagent-decision-support-using-autonomous-agents-for-urban-traffic-control</link><title>A Case of Multiagent Decision Support: Using Autonomous Agents for Urban Traffic Control</title><description>* A Case of Multiagent Decision Support: Using Autonomous Agents for Urban Traffic Control (Citations: 14)

Sascha Ossowski, José Cuena, Ana García-serrano

...the urban motorway network around barcelona. it shows how different technologies in the area of intelligent agents can be combined to solve this real-world decision support problem: on...

Conference: Ibero-American Conference on AI - IBERAMIA , pp. 100-111, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7441-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7441_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:23:19">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11238532/stromelysin-1-promoter-mutations-impair-gelatinase-b-activation-in-high-microsatellite-instability</link><title>Stromelysin-1 Promoter Mutations Impair Gelatinase B Activation in High Microsatellite Instability Sporadic Colorectal Tumors1</title><description>* Stromelysin-1 Promoter Mutations Impair Gelatinase B Activation in High Microsatellite Instability Sporadic Colorectal Tumors1 (Citations: 1)

Alberto Moran, Pilar Iniesta, Carmen de Juan, Rosa Gonzalez-Quevedo, Andres Sanchez-Pernaute, Eduardo Dõ, Santiago Ramon, Antonio Torres, Jose Luis Balibrea, Manuel Benito

...by the suppressor pathway. the goal of this work was to...3 study was performed by real-time quantitative pcr. mmp-9...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7441-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7441_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:23:52">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50725382/reem-b-an-autonomous-lightweight-human-size-humanoid-robot</link><title>Reem-B: An autonomous lightweight human-size humanoid robot</title><description>* Reem-B: An autonomous lightweight human-size humanoid robot (Citations: 4)

Ricardo Tellez, Francesco Ferro, Sergio Garcia, E. Gomez, Enric Jorge, Dario Mora, D. Pinyol, J. Oliver, O. Torres, J. Velazquez, D. Faconti

...must be designed to perform real-world tasks including dynamic walking...

Conference: IEEE-RAS International Conference on Humanoid Robots - Humanoids , 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7441-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7441_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:24:36">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50901804/dingpos-a-gnss-based-multi-sensor-demonstrator-for-indoor-navigation-preliminary-results</link><title>DINGPOS, a GNSS-based multi-sensor demonstrator for indoor navigation: Preliminary results</title><description>* DINGPOS, a GNSS-based multi-sensor demonstrator for indoor navigation: Preliminary results (Citations: 1)

Giovanni A. Vecchione, Damian Palenzuela, Manuel Toledo, Jose J. Rosales de Caceres, Damien Kubrak, Yves Capelle, Gonzalo Seco, Jose Lopez-Salcedo, Peter Tiley, Angelo Consoli, David Jimenez-Banos, Gustavo Lopez-Risueno

...the goal of this paper is to...its performance and capabilities with real data....

Conference: Position Location and Navigation IEEE Symposium - PLANS , pp. 113-121, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7441-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7441_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:25:38">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/1227967/a-methodological-framework-for-viewpoint-oriented-conceptual-modeling</link><title>A Methodological Framework for Viewpoint-Oriented Conceptual Modeling</title><description>* A Methodological Framework for Viewpoint-Oriented Conceptual Modeling (Citations: 7)

Javier Andrade Garda, Juan Ares Casal, Rafael García Vázquez, Juan Pazos, Santiago Rodríguez Yánez, Andrés Silva

To solve any nontrivial problem, it first needs to be conceptualized, taking into account the individual who has the problem. However, a problem is generally associated with more than one individual, as is usually the case in software development. Therefore, this process has to take into account different viewpoints about the problem and any discrepancies that could arise as a ...

Journal: IEEE Transactions on Software Engineering - TSE , vol. 30, no. 5, pp. 282-294, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7441-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7441_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:26:10">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/51063144/an-improved-way-for-evaluating-competences-a-different-approach-to-project-management-learning</link><title>An improved way for evaluating competences: A different approach to project management learning</title><description>* An improved way for evaluating competences: A different approach to project management learning

E Crespo, A. Gonzalez-Marcos, F. Alba-Elias, M. Castejon-Limas, J. Ordieres-Mere

...along with other activities. the goal of this experience is to...

Conference: Eurocon , 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7441-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7441_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:27:03">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/13274260/feasible-database-querying-using-a-visual-end-user-approach</link><title>Feasible database querying using a visual end-user approach</title><description>* Feasible database querying using a visual end-user approach

Clemente Rafael Borges, José Antonio Macías

...an experiment carried out with real users....

Published in 2010.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7441-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7441_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:27:50">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4677152/genetic-learning-of-fuzzy-reactive-controllers</link><title>Genetic learning of fuzzy reactive controllers</title><description>* Genetic learning of fuzzy reactive controllers

Vicente Matell, Camino Fernfiadez, M. Molina

...the genetic evolution process, a real robot has been used. numerical...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7441-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7441_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:28:16">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5680755/multivariate-curve-resolution-a-possible-tool-in-the-detection-of-intermediate-structures-in</link><title>Multivariate Curve Resolution: A Possible Tool in the Detection of Intermediate Structures in Protein Folding</title><description>* Multivariate Curve Resolution: A Possible Tool in the Detection of Intermediate Structures in Protein Folding (Citations: 5)

J. Mendieta, M. S. Díaz-Cruz, M. Esteban, R. Tauler

Different multivariate data analysis techniques based on factor analysis and multivariate curve resolution are shown for the study of biochemical evolutionary processes like conformational changes and protein folding. Several simulated CD spectral data sets describing different hypothetical protein folding pathways are analyzed and discussed in relation to the feasibility of factor analysis techniques to detect and resolve the number of ...

Journal: Biophysical Journal - BIOPHYS J , vol. 74, no. 6, pp. 2876-2888, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7441-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7441_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:29:05">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11009755/personalized-information-retrieval-based-on-context-and-ontological-knowledge</link><title>Personalized information retrieval based on context and ontological knowledge</title><description>* Personalized information retrieval based on context and ontological knowledge

P. H. M YLONAS, D. V ALLET, P. CASTELLS, M. F ERNANDEZ

Contextmodelinghaslongbeenacknowledgedasakeyaspectinawidevarietyofproblemdomains. In this paper we focus on the combination of contextualization and personalization methods to improve the performance of personalized information retrieval. The key aspects in our proposed approach are (1) the explicit distinction between historic user context and live user context, (2) the use of ontology-driven representations of the domain of discourse, as a common, enriched representational ground ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>