<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7446">cycling on the mont ventoux</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:54:50" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7446-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7446_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:54:51">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/30349125/the-effect-of-supplementation-with-isoflavones-on-plasma-lipids-and-oxidisability-of-low-density</link><title>The effect of supplementation with isoflavones on plasma lipids and oxidisability of low density lipoprotein in premenopausal women</title><description>* The effect of supplementation with isoflavones on plasma lipids and oxidisability of low density lipoprotein in premenopausal women (Citations: 38)

Samir Samman, Philippa M Lyons Wall, Grace S. M Chan, Sarah J Smith, Peter Petocz

...were collected initially and at the end of the second and fourth menstrual cycles for the determination of plasma lipid concentrations and the resistance of ldl to copper...studies are required to clarify the potential effect of isoflavones on hdl metabolism and the interaction with plasma steroid hormones during the menstrual cycle....

Journal: Atherosclerosis , vol. 147, no. 2, pp. 277-283, 1999</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7446-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7446_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:55:31">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/29294721/effect-of-the-menstrual-cycle-oral-contraception-and-pregnancy-on-forearm-blood-flow-venous</link><title>Effect of the menstrual cycle, oral contraception and pregnancy on forearm blood flow, venous distensibility and clotting factors</title><description>* Effect of the menstrual cycle, oral contraception and pregnancy on forearm blood flow, venous distensibility and clotting factors (Citations: 8)

R. Fawer, A. Dettling, D. Weihs, H. Welti, J. L. Schelling

...than in other women during the follicular phase of a normal menstrual cycle. venous distensibility was not affected by...unchanged (a) or increased (b). the oral contraceptive with the high progestagen component appeared to increase venous capacitance and may induce venous stasis, whereas coagulability was particularly...

Journal: European Journal of Clinical Pharmacology - EUR J CLIN PHARMACOL , vol. 13, no. 4, pp. 251-257, 1978</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7446-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7446_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:56:05">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/31361511/longitudinal-quality-of-life-and-quality-adjusted-survival-in-a-randomised-controlled-trial</link><title>Longitudinal quality of life and quality adjusted survival in a randomised controlled trial comparing six months of bolus fluorouracil/leucovorin vs. twelve weeks of protracted venous infusion fluorouracil as adjuvant chemotherapy for colorectal cancer</title><description>* Longitudinal quality of life and quality adjusted survival in a randomised controlled trial comparing six months of bolus fluorouracil/leucovorin vs. twelve weeks of protracted venous infusion fluorouracil as adjuvant chemotherapy for colorectal cancer (Citations: 5)

Ian Chau, Andrew R. Norman, David Cunningham, Tim Iveson, Mark Hill, Tamas Hickish, Fiona Lofts, Duncan Jodrell, Andrew Webb, Diana Tait, Paul J. Ross, Pat Shellitohttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=31361511&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=cycling on the mont ventoux

...or 12 weeks of protracted venous infusion (pvi) 5-fu (n=397). there were significant differences in the deterioration of qol scores at...coinciding with toxicity peak during the first cycle. following week 12, global qol...

Journal: European Journal of Cancer - EUR J CANCER , vol. 41, no. 11, pp. 1551-1559, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7446-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7446_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:56:42">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6564071/a-randomised-comparison-between-6-months-of-bolus-fluorouracil-leucovorin-and-12-weeks-of</link><title>A randomised comparison between 6 months of bolus fluorouracil/leucovorin and 12 weeks of protracted venous infusion fluorouracil as adjuvant treatment in colorectal cancer</title><description>* A randomised comparison between 6 months of bolus fluorouracil/leucovorin and 12 weeks of protracted venous infusion fluorouracil as adjuvant treatment in colorectal cancer (Citations: 33)

I. Chau, A. R. Norman, D. Cunningham, D. Tait, P. J. Ross, T. Iveson, M. Hill, T. Hickish, F. Lofts, D. Jodrell, A. Webb, J. R. Oates

...was no os difference between the two arms, although pvi 5...as significantly less toxicity. based on our results, the probability of 12 weeks of pvi 5-fu being inferior to 6 months of bolus 5-fu/lv...

Journal: Annals of Oncology - ANN ONCOL , vol. 16, no. 4, pp. 549-557, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7446-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7446_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:57:13">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/31408432/suppression-of-heparinization-of-central-venous-catheters-between-cycles-of-chemotherapy</link><title>Suppression of heparinization of central venous catheters between cycles of chemotherapy</title><description>* Suppression of heparinization of central venous catheters between cycles of chemotherapy (Citations: 3)

R. Delva, E. Gamelin, A. Lortholary, P. Maillart, P. Leynia de la Jarrige, C. Girault, J. Guérin, F. Larra

...were followed up for two cycles. if no blockages were present progression to the next step was authorized. if one blockage was observed 5 additional...have their tscs heparinized after the same interval. two blockages (block) after the same interval meant that the previous interval was recorded as the longest tolerable. there were no...

Journal: Supportive Care in Cancer - SUPPORT CARE CANCER , vol. 6, no. 4, pp. 384-388, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7446-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7446_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:57:38">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/59285866/instantaneous-pressure-flow-velocity-relations-of-systemic-venous-return-in-patients-with</link><title>Instantaneous pressure–flow velocity relations of systemic venous return in patients with univentricular circulation</title><description>* Instantaneous pressure–flow velocity relations of systemic venous return in patients with univentricular circulation

R Kaulitz, P Bergman, I Luhmer, T Paul, G Hausdorf

...objectiveto assess the pressure and flow velocity relations and respiratory variability of the systemic venous and hepatic venous return in patients with univentricular...pattern varied according to cardiac cycle and pressure trace. the effects of total cavopulmonary anastomosis on venous return might counteract its other...

Published in 1999.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7446-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7446_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:58:16">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/28069239/home-use-of-impulse-compression-of-the-foot-and-compression-stockings-in-the-treatment-of-chronic</link><title>Home use of impulse compression of the foot and compression stockings in the treatment of chronic venous insufficiency</title><description>* Home use of impulse compression of the foot and compression stockings in the treatment of chronic venous insufficiency (Citations: 4)

Juan I. Arcelus, Joseph A. Caprini, Lakshman R. Sehgal, José J. Reyna

...and 1, 2, and 3 months thereafter. in addition, all patients underwent air plethysmography studies at the same time intervals, including venous volume, venous filling index, ejection fraction, and...lt; .05) compared with baseline. the foot compression devices were well tolerated by all the patients in the study. conclusions: the use of home foot impulse...

Journal: Journal of Vascular Surgery - J VASC SURG , vol. 34, no. 5, pp. 805-811, 2001</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7446-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7446_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:59:04">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/56543260/protracted-venous-infusion-5-fluorouracil-in-combination-with-subcutaneous-interleukin-2-and</link><title>Protracted venous infusion 5-fluorouracil in combination with subcutaneous interleukin-2 and alpha-interferon in patients with metastatic renal cell cancer: a phase II study</title><description>* Protracted venous infusion 5-fluorouracil in combination with subcutaneous interleukin-2 and alpha-interferon in patients with metastatic renal cell cancer: a phase II study (Citations: 1)

M J Allen, M Vaughan, A Webb, S Johnston, P Savage, T Eisen, S Bate, J Moore, R Ahern, M E Gore

...55) patients achieved disease stabilization. the overall median survival was 11 months with a 1-year survival of 45%. the median survival for evaluable patients...of 60% and 40% respectively. the median survival of responding patients was 31 months and the three patients achieving complete response...

Journal: British Journal of Cancer - BRIT J CANCER , vol. 83, no. 8, pp. 980-985, 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7446-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7446_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:59:54">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/31982592/protracted-venous-infusion-5-fluorouracil-in-combination-with-subcutaneous-interleukin-2-and</link><title>Protracted venous infusion 5-fluorouracil in combination with subcutaneous interleukin-2 and alpha-interferon in patients with metastatic renal cell cancer</title><description>* Protracted venous infusion 5-fluorouracil in combination with subcutaneous interleukin-2 and alpha-interferon in patients with metastatic renal cell cancer (Citations: 1)

MJ Allen, M Vaughan, A Webb, S Johnston, P Savage, T Eisen, S Bates, J Morre, R Ahern, ME Gore

...55) patients achieved disease stabilization. the overall median survival was 11 months with a 1-year survival of 45%. the median survival for evaluable patients...of 60% and 40% respectively. the median survival of responding patients was 31 months and the three patients achieving complete response...

Journal: Urologic Oncology-seminars and Original Investigations , vol. 7, no. 2, pp. 83-83, 2002</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7446-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7446_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:00:39">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/13627794/epirubicin-cisplatin-and-protracted-venous-infusion-of-5fluorouracil-for-advanced-gastric</link><title>Epirubicin, Cisplatin, and Protracted Venous Infusion of 5Fluorouracil for Advanced Gastric Carcinoma</title><description>* Epirubicin, Cisplatin, and Protracted Venous Infusion of 5Fluorouracil for Advanced Gastric Carcinoma (Citations: 4)

Eun Kyung Cho, Woon Ki Lee, Soo-Mee Bang, Dong Kyun Park, Yeon-Ho Park, Oh Sang Kwon, Duck Joo Choi, Dong Bok Shin, Jae Hoon Lee, Tae Hoon Lee

...confidence interval, 18-27 weeks). the median survival for all patients was 10 months (95% confidence interval, 6-14 months), with a 1-yr survival...and leukopenia in 3% of the cycles. central venous catheter complications that required line...

Published in 2002.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>