<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7448">running shoes boston</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:07:21" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7448-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7448_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:07:23">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/32684278/finite-element-analysis-of-the-midsole-of-a-running-shoe</link><title>Finite element analysis of the midsole of a running shoe</title><description>* Finite element analysis of the midsole of a running shoe

Michael D'Agati, Zvi Ladin

Journal: Journal of Biomechanics - J BIOMECH , vol. 26, no. 3, pp. 320-320, 1993</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7448-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7448_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:07:59">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/32667074/a-minimum-energy-approach-to-the-design-of-elastic-soles-for-running-shoes</link><title>A minimum energy approach to the design of elastic soles for running shoes</title><description>* A minimum energy approach to the design of elastic soles for running shoes

Perry Y. Li, Zvi Ladin

Journal: Journal of Biomechanics - J BIOMECH , vol. 23, no. 7, pp. 721-721, 1990</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7448-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7448_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:08:26">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/24965177/the-evaluation-of-cleated-shoes-with-the-adolescent-athlete-in-soccer</link><title>The evaluation of cleated shoes with the adolescent athlete in soccer</title><description>* The evaluation of cleated shoes with the adolescent athlete in soccer (Citations: 2)

J. H. Walter, G. K. Ng

...was made between non-cleated shoes and cleated shoes using both the f-scan in-shoe sensor system (tekscan inc., boston ma), and videotape analysis. negative...throughout the stance phase of running in cleated shoes. in negative heel position the...

Journal: The Foot , vol. 12, no. 3, pp. 158-165, 2002</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7448-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7448_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:09:16">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/7014346/the-political-economy-of-kenya-s-crisis</link><title>The Political Economy of Kenya's Crisis</title><description>* The Political Economy of Kenya's Crisis (Citations: 19)

Susanne D. Mueller

Using political economy analysis, this paper discusses three precipitating factors that were ignited by Kenya's 2007 election, which was too close to call beforehand and highly contested afterwards. These factors were: the gradual loss of the state's monopoly of legitimate force and the consequent diffusion of violence; the deliberate weakening of institutions outside the executive in favour of ...

Journal: Journal of Eastern African Studies - J EAST AFR STUD , vol. 2, no. 2, pp. 185-210, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7448-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7448_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:10:25">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/58852218/letter-written-by-leger-morrison-to-miss-blaney-dated-may-30-1943</link><title>Letter Written by Leger Morrison to Miss Blaney Dated May 30, 1943</title><description>* Letter Written by Leger Morrison to Miss Blaney Dated May 30, 1943

Leger Morrison

...rooming with four fellows from boston college, four fellows which i...three minutes late he came running out of the hotel, panting, his shirt unbuttoned and half on, his shoes unlaced, his right hand holding...

Published in 1943.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7448-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7448_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:11:04">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42476291/life-cycle-vs-multiple-path-dependency-in-industrial-districts</link><title>Life Cycle vs. Multiple Path Dependency in Industrial Districts</title><description>* Life Cycle vs. Multiple Path Dependency in Industrial Districts (Citations: 11)

Fiorenza Belussi, Silvia Rita Sedita

The aim of this article is to shed light on the evolutionary process of industrial districts (IDs), evaluating the role of path dependence in their growth trajectories. We intend here to identify the districts' life cycles and the factors that influence the origin, development and maturity stages. Following an evolutionary economics approach, we investigated the path-dependence mechanism behind the ...

Journal: European Planning Studies - EUR PLAN STUD , vol. 17, no. 4, pp. 505-528, 2009</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>