<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7450">thailand individual travel</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:18:42" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7450-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7450_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:18:43">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57922420/estimating-the-recreational-value-of-pakistan-s-largest-freshwater-lake-to-support-sustainable</link><title>Estimating the recreational value of Pakistan's largest freshwater lake to support sustainable tourism management using a travel cost model</title><description>* Estimating the recreational value of Pakistan's largest freshwater lake to support sustainable tourism management using a travel cost model

Tehmina Mangan, Roy Brouwer, Heman Das Lohano, Ghulam Mustafa Nangraj

...value is estimated using an individual travel cost model. randomly selected visitors are interviewed during peak season about their recreational travel behavior and perception of lake conditions. key issues in travel cost modeling are addressed, including...

Journal: Journal of Sustainable Tourism - J SUSTAIN TOUR , vol. ahead-of-p, no. ahead-of-p, pp. 1-14, 2012</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7450-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7450_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:19:12">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39201628/pfge-lior-serotype-and-antimicrobial-resistance-patterns-among-campylobacter-jejuni-isolated-from</link><title>PFGE, Lior serotype, and antimicrobial resistance patterns among Campylobacter jejuni isolated from travelers and US military personnel with acute diarrhea in Thailand, 1998-2003</title><description>* PFGE, Lior serotype, and antimicrobial resistance patterns among Campylobacter jejuni isolated from travelers and US military personnel with acute diarrhea in Thailand, 1998-2003 (Citations: 2)

Oralak Serichantalergs, Piyarat Pootong, Anders Dalsgaard, Ladaporn Bodhidatta, Patricia Guerry, David R Tribble, Sinn Anuras, Carl J Mason

...major diarrheal pathogens among adult travelers. to study the epidemiology of c. jejuni in adult travelers and u.s. military personnel with acute diarrhea in thailand from 1998-2003, strains of...jejuni isolates were obtained from travelers (n = 46) and u.s. military personnel (n = 266) in thailand who were experiencing acute diarrhea...

Journal: Gut Pathogens - Gut Pathog , vol. 2, no. 1, pp. 15-11, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7450-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7450_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:19:53">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42558146/middle-class-travel-patterns-predispositions-and-attitudes-and-present-day-transport-policy-in</link><title>Middle‐class Travel Patterns, Predispositions and Attitudes, and Present‐day Transport Policy in Bangkok, Thailand</title><description>* Middle‐class Travel Patterns, Predispositions and Attitudes, and Present‐day Transport Policy in Bangkok, Thailand

Wanpen Charoentrakulpeeti, Edsel Sajor, Willi Zimmermann

...literature particularly focusing on middle‐class travel patterns, predispositions and transport policy...following findings: (1) that middle‐class travel behaviour is characterized by a high dependence on private motor vehicle travel and ‘inward commuting’; (2) that...

Journal: Transport Reviews - TRANSP REV , vol. 26, no. 6, pp. 693-712, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7450-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7450_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:20:33">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5554992/hepatitis-e-seroconversion-in-united-states-travelers-abroad</link><title>HEPATITIS E SEROCONVERSION IN UNITED STATES TRAVELERS ABROAD</title><description>* HEPATITIS E SEROCONVERSION IN UNITED STATES TRAVELERS ABROAD (Citations: 3)

WINNIE W. OOI, JOHN M. GAWOSKI, PATRICE O. YARBOUGH, GEORGE A. PANKEY

...before and 6 weeks after traveling. samples obtained 6 months after traveling were available for 211 travelers. igg and igm antibodies to...whom such samples were available. travel destinations were diverse: thailand, china, russia, and peru. these data are consistent with an infection acquired while traveling. none of the seropositive subjects...

Published in 1999.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7450-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7450_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:21:15">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/24716362/antibiotics-for-travelers-what-s-good-and-what-s-not</link><title>Antibiotics for travelers: What’s good and what’s not</title><description>* Antibiotics for travelers: What’s good and what’s not (Citations: 4)

Kathryn N. Suh, Jay S. Keystone

...the risk for illness during travel. health problems during travel are common. although many medical problems that travelers incur are noninfectious in origin...bacterial and parasitic infections in travelers. this article reviews antibiotics of particularly high utility to travelers, with emphasis on selected agents...

Journal: Current Infectious Disease Reports , vol. 6, no. 1, pp. 13-21, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7450-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7450_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:21:44">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57552437/social-structure-and-psychographic-explanations-of-destination-preference-of-australians-travel-to</link><title>Social Structure and Psychographic Explanations of Destination Preference of Australians' Travel to South-East Asia</title><description>* Social Structure and Psychographic Explanations of Destination Preference of Australians' Travel to South-East Asia (Citations: 1)

Uraiporn Kattiyapornpong, Kenneth E. Miller

...psychographic variables and preference for travel to asia by australians. differences in preference for travel to specific south-east asian destinations, namely, malaysia, singapore and thailand, are explained using psychographic explanatory...different ways to constrain/enable travel preference for asia. this means there are differences in the socio-demographic and psychographic profiles of travelers who prefer specific destinations within...

Journal: Asia Pacific Journal of Tourism Research , vol. 16, no. 1, pp. 39-56, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7450-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7450_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:22:16">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57963787/chinese-urban-mature-travelers-motivation-and-constraints-by-decision-autonomy</link><title>CHINESE URBAN MATURE TRAVELERS' MOTIVATION AND CONSTRAINTS BY DECISION AUTONOMY</title><description>* CHINESE URBAN MATURE TRAVELERS' MOTIVATION AND CONSTRAINTS BY DECISION AUTONOMY (Citations: 2)

Cathy H. C. Hsu, Soo K. Kang

...motivation of 800 chinese mature travelers residing in metropolitan areas based on travelers' decision autonomy in planning domestic...analysis. significant relationships among mature travelers' trip autonomy, motivation, and constraints contributed to the understanding of urban mature travelers in china....

Journal: Journal of Travel &amp; Tourism Marketing , vol. 26, no. 7, pp. 703-721, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7450-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7450_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:22:58">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6404875/current-situation-and-status-of-long-tailed-macaques-macaca-fascicularis-in-thailand</link><title>Current Situation and Status of Long-tailed Macaques (Macaca fascicularis) in Thailand</title><description>* Current Situation and Status of Long-tailed Macaques (Macaca fascicularis) in Thailand

SUCHINDA MALAIVIJITNOND, YUZURU HAMADA

...most frequently encountered primate in thailand. they are currently considered at...needed. we sent questionnaires throughout thailand to a total of 7,410 sub-districts, and received 1,417 (19.12%) replies. we traveled to the sub-districts from...

Published in 2008.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7450-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7450_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:23:58">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40669532/commuters-attitudes-towards-travel-demand-management-in-bangkok</link><title>Commuters' attitudes towards travel demand management in Bangkok</title><description>* Commuters' attitudes towards travel demand management in Bangkok (Citations: 8)

Kumares C. Sinha, S. Waqar Haider, Yordphol Tanaboriboon

...to investigate the effect of individual socio-economic characteristics on these...1210 daily commuters in bangkok, thailand. among four broad categories of...

Journal: Transport Policy - TRANSP POLICY , vol. 4, no. 3, pp. 161-170, 1997</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7450-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7450_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:24:26">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/24996857/pleasure-and-pain-medical-travel-in-asia</link><title>Pleasure and pain: Medical travel in Asia</title><description>* Pleasure and pain: Medical travel in Asia (Citations: 16)

A. Whittaker

...termed ‘medical tourism’ or medical travel, is a growing industry being aggressively marketed across asia. this paper explores the industry development in four countries: thailand, india, malaysia, and singapore, providing...

Journal: Global Public Health , vol. 3, no. 3, pp. 271-290, 2008</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>