<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7451">buy animal farm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:24:47" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7451-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7451_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:24:48">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4824914/guarding-against-the-trojan-horse-practical-biosecurity-measures-for-dairy-farms</link><title>Guarding Against the 'Trojan Horse': Practical Biosecurity Measures for Dairy Farms</title><description>* Guarding Against the 'Trojan Horse': Practical Biosecurity Measures for Dairy Farms

Dale A. Moore

...s veterinarian prior to buying animals. √ never bring in animals without knowing their vaccination history. √ never buy animals from a herd that has mixed origin cattle. √ transport animals in clean vehicles. √ have a control program for outside animals which could spread disease (rodents...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7451-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7451_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:25:37">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/12224558/strategi-pemberdayaan-usaha-kecil-dan-menengah-sektor-pertanian-dalam-mendukung-sektor-pariwisata</link><title>STRATEGI PEMBERDAYAAN USAHA KECIL DAN MENENGAH SEKTOR PERTANIAN DALAM MENDUKUNG SEKTOR PARIWISATA DI PROVINSI BALI</title><description>* STRATEGI PEMBERDAYAAN USAHA KECIL DAN MENENGAH SEKTOR PERTANIAN DALAM MENDUKUNG SEKTOR PARIWISATA DI PROVINSI BALI

IDA BAGUS, KETUT SURYA

...identify how tourism stimulates the farming sub sector. (2) to identify...sub-sectors such as agriculture, animal farming, forestry, and fish farming. the plant sub sector is...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7451-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7451_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:25:59">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/53263261/waste-of-fertilizers</link><title>Waste of Fertilizers</title><description>* Waste of Fertilizers

G. W. Cooke

...efficiency of the fertilizers they buy. animal and crop wastes contain most...and in handling and applying animal wastes. further improvement should result from more research on the farming cycles involving plant nutrients and...

Published in 1977.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7451-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7451_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:26:38">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10138683/poverty-credit-and-microcredit-in-rural-china</link><title>Poverty, credit and microcredit in rural China</title><description>* Poverty, credit and microcredit in rural China (Citations: 2)

Jonathan Unger

...to support the individual families' farming. they initially gave priority to...duration to enable families to buy agricultural inputs at the start of the growing season or to buy animals for fattening and quick resale...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7451-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7451_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:27:19">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/47511169/m-canisation-productivit-du-travail-et-risques-le-cas-du-burkina-faso</link><title>Mécanisation, productivité du travail et risques : le cas du Burkina Faso</title><description>* Mécanisation, productivité du travail et risques : le cas du Burkina Faso (Citations: 2)

Guy Faure

...rise in monetary incomes per farm for small animal traction farms an particulaly for large animal traction farms and motorized farms. the monetary incomes per person largely increase when farmers get animal traction but they increase just a little when farmers buy a tractor. the naturals risks...

Published in 1994.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7451-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7451_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:27:48">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/34785053/prevalence-of-fishborne-zoonotic-parasites-in-important-cultured-fish-species-in-the-mekong-delta</link><title>Prevalence of fishborne zoonotic parasites in important cultured fish species in the Mekong Delta, Vietnam</title><description>* Prevalence of fishborne zoonotic parasites in important cultured fish species in the Mekong Delta, Vietnam (Citations: 20)

Pham Cu Thien, Anders Dalsgaard, Bui Ngoc Thanh, Annette Olsen, K. Darwin Murrell

...small-scale integrated vegetable–aquaculture–animal husbandry farming (vac) systems were also examined...

Journal: Parasitology Research - PARASITOL RES , vol. 101, no. 5, pp. 1277-1284, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7451-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7451_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:28:39">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10518054/challenges-of-animal-traction-research-and-development-in-west-and-central-africa-at-the-eve-of-the</link><title>Challenges of animal traction research and development in West and Central Africa at the eve of the 21st Century</title><description>* Challenges of animal traction research and development in West and Central Africa at the eve of the 21st Century

Michel Havard, Aboubakar Njoya, Roland Pirot, Eric Vall, Betty Wampfler

...for farmers is how to buy draught animals and improve animal traction use, as animal teams are a power source...challenges have changed as regards animal traction. previously the objective of development structures was to introduce the technique in the farming systems. they provided farmers with...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7451-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7451_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:29:09">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40331869/the-conservation-impact-of-commercial-wildlife-farming-of-porcupines-in-vietnam</link><title>The conservation impact of commercial wildlife farming of porcupines in Vietnam</title><description>* The conservation impact of commercial wildlife farming of porcupines in Vietnam (Citations: 2)

Emma G. E. Brooks, Scott I. Roberton, Diana J. Bell

...province of son la. although farm owners are obliged by law to propagate stock solely from farm-bred animals, 58% of farm owners admitted purchasing wild founder stock, with at least 19% continuing to buy wild individuals. despite the number of farms, the primary demand on them is to supply other farms, and wild meat restaurants were...

Journal: Biological Conservation - BIOL CONSERV , vol. 143, no. 11, pp. 2808-2814, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7451-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7451_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:30:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/43541392/consumer-perception-of-organic-food-production-and-farm-animal-welfare</link><title>Consumer perception of organic food production and farm animal welfare</title><description>* Consumer perception of organic food production and farm animal welfare (Citations: 75)

Gemma C. Harper, Aikaterini Makatouni

...food trends: organic food and animal welfare. the results indicate that...in relation to standards of animal welfare, play a significant influencing...

Journal: British Food Journal - BR FOOD J , vol. 104, no. 3/4/5, pp. 287-299, 2002</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7451-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7451_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:30:44">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/41907047/effectiveness-of-strategic-anthelmintic-treatments-in-the-control-of-gastrointestinal-nematodes-and</link><title>Effectiveness of strategic anthelmintic treatments in the control of gastrointestinal nematodes and Fasciola gigantica in cattle in Iringa region, Tanzania</title><description>* Effectiveness of strategic anthelmintic treatments in the control of gastrointestinal nematodes and Fasciola gigantica in cattle in Iringa region, Tanzania (Citations: 2)

J. D. Keyyu, N. C. Kyvsgaard, J. Monrad, A. A. Kassuku

...from three large-scale dairy farms, four traditional farms and nine small-scale dairy farms were randomly selected. the selected animals on each farm were ear tagged and allocated...respectively compared to untreated control animals (p &lt; 0.001). two and four strategic treatments per year significantly reduced the proportion of animals passing fasciola eggs in faeces...

Journal: Tropical Animal Health and Production - TROP ANIM HEALTH PROD , vol. 41, no. 1, pp. 25-33, 2009</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>