<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7453">pc 2 games reviews</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:32:13" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7453-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7453_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:32:15">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4241719/heuristic-evaluation-for-games-usability-principles-for-video-game-design</link><title>Heuristic evaluation for games: usability principles for video game design</title><description>* Heuristic evaluation for games: usability principles for video game design (Citations: 37)

David Pinelle, Nelson Wong, Tadeusz Stach

...developed the heuristics by analyzing pc game reviews from a popular gaming website, and the review set covered 108 different games and included 18 from each of 6 major game genres. we analyzed the reviews and identified twelve common classes of usability problems seen in games. we developed ten usability heuristics...

Conference: Computer Human Interaction - CHI , pp. 1453-1462, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7453-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7453_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:32:54">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/12458300/from-gaming-to-training-a-review-of-studies-on-fidelity-immersion-presence-and-buy-in-and-their</link><title>From Gaming to Training: A Review of Studies on Fidelity, Immersion, Presence, and Buy-in and Their Effects on Transfer in PC-Based Simulations and Games</title><description>* From Gaming to Training: A Review of Studies on Fidelity, Immersion, Presence, and Buy-in and Their Effects on Transfer in PC-Based Simulations and Games (Citations: 6)

Amy L. Alexander, Tad Brunyé, Jason Sidman, Shawn A. Weil</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7453-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7453_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:33:25">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/47635112/hospital-management-games-a-taxonomy-and-extensive-review</link><title>Hospital management games: a taxonomy and extensive review</title><description>* Hospital management games: a taxonomy and extensive review (Citations: 1)

Markus Kraus, Marion S. Rauner, Sigrun Schwarz

...hospital management games have gained importance in better...the main characteristics of these games from an operations research (or) perspective. hospital management games model the complex decision making...

Journal: Central European Journal of Operations Research , vol. 18, no. 4, pp. 567-591, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7453-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7453_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:34:04">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/44669181/software-reviews-the-other-side-a-global-conflict-resolution-game-publisher-tom-snyder</link><title>Software Reviews : THE OTHER SIDE: A Global Conflict Resolution Game Publisher: Tom Snyder Productions, Inc., 123 Mt. Auburn St., Cambridge, MA 02138 (telephone: 617-876-5841) Year of Publication: 1985 Materials: One instructor's guide, two player's guides, game and backup diskettes, two map/game boards, two erasable markers Price: $69.95 Machine Specificity: Apple II+, IIe, IIc (48K), (Version 2.0 also IBM PC and compatibles, Tandy 1000) System Requirements: One computer (or two computers connected by cable or modem), one disk drive per computer, color or monochrome monitor Effectiveness: Fair User-Friendliness: Fair Documentation: Fair</title><description>* Software Reviews : THE OTHER SIDE: A Global Conflict Resolution Game Publisher: Tom Snyder Productions, Inc., 123 Mt. Auburn St., Cambridge, MA 02138 (telephone: 617-876-5841) Year of Publication: 1985 Materials: One instructor's guide, two player's guides, game and backup diskettes, two map/game boards, two erasable markers Price: $69.95 Machine Specificity: Apple II+, IIe, IIc (48K), (Version 2.0 also IBM PC and compatibles, Tandy 1000) System Requirements: One computer (or two computers connected by cable or modem), one disk drive per computer, color or monochrome monitor Effectiveness: Fair User-Friendliness: Fair Documentation: Fair

M. S. Soroos

Journal: Social Science Computer Review \- SOC SCI COMPUT REV , vol. 4, no. 2, pp. 246-247, 1986</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7453-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7453_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:34:36">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4751876/using-genres-to-customize-usability-evaluations-of-video-games</link><title>Using genres to customize usability evaluations of video games</title><description>* Using genres to customize usability evaluations of video games (Citations: 10)

David Pinelle, Nelson Wong, Tadeusz Stach

...video games are varied, with vastly different visual layouts and interaction styles; however, most games that share a common genre...we coded usability problems in reviews of 108 commercial video games. the review set included 18 games from each of six major game genres. we statistically analyzed the...

Published in 2008.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7453-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7453_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:35:29">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39237260/design-and-evaluation-of-player-experience-of-a-location-based-mobile-game</link><title>Design and evaluation of player experience of a location-based mobile game</title><description>* Design and evaluation of player experience of a location-based mobile game

Tara Carrigy, Katsiaryna Naliuka, Natasa Paterson, Mads Haahr

...of a location-based mobile game set in dublin, ireland in...the concept of immersion in gaming and then review related work before presenting the...

Conference: Nordic Conference on Human-Computer Interaction - NORDICHI , pp. 92-101, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7453-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7453_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:36:07">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42402579/software-reviews</link><title>Software reviews</title><description>* Software reviews

Barbara J. Kidneigh, Vicki S. Freimuth, Suzanne McCorkle, Wenden W. Waite

...48011 (313) 258–5566 ibm pc/pc/xt 64k (96k w. dos 2.0)/and apple $59.99sensible...number.version 3.1 ibm pc, xt (compatibles) 128 k memory color monitor 2 disc drives $697.00 plus...

Journal: Communication Education - COMMUN EDUC , vol. 35, no. 3, pp. 313-323, 1986</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7453-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7453_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:36:46">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39364872/gender-and-race-representation-in-casual-games</link><title>Gender and Race Representation in Casual Games</title><description>* Gender and Race Representation in Casual Games

Donghee Yvette Wohn

...sample (n=200) of casual games retrieved from the websites of the largest five casual game distributors. study 2 looks at the most popular games on websites of the same...studies of gender representation in game characters: this paper suggests that sampling methodology and the relatively new trend of casual games excluded this subset of games from prior research. implications are...

Journal: Sex Roles , vol. 65, no. 3-4, pp. 1-10, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7453-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7453_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:37:19">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4710489/usability-heuristics-for-networked-multiplayer-games</link><title>Usability heuristics for networked multiplayer games</title><description>* Usability heuristics for networked multiplayer games (Citations: 7)

David Pinelle, Nelson Wong, Tadeusz Stach, Carl Gutwin

...networked multiplayer games must support a much wider variety of interactions than single-player games because networked games involve communication and coordination between...and evaluation of networked multiplayer games. the new heuristics were identified by analyzing problem reports from 382 reviews of networked pc games, covering six main genres. we...

Conference: International Conference on Supporting Group Work - GROUP , pp. 169-178, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7453-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7453_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:37:55">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4700426/the-vmatrix-equi-ping-game-server-placement-for-pre-arranged-first-person-shooter-multiplayer</link><title>The vMatrix: Equi-Ping Game Server Placement For Pre-Arranged First-Person-Shooter Multiplayer Matches</title><description>* The vMatrix: Equi-Ping Game Server Placement For Pre-Arranged First-Person-Shooter Multiplayer Matches

Amr Awadallah, Mendel Rosenblum

...important for first person shooter games (fps), which are a class of interactive games that is very sensitive to...using microsoft's popular halo pc game, we show that this solution does not degrade the game performance and does not require...

Conference: ACS/IEEE International Conference on Computer Systems and Applications , pp. 633-640, 2006</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>