<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7457">the music man lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:46:46" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7457-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7457_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:46:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/71271/towards-a-digital-library-of-popular-music</link><title>Towards a digital library of popular music</title><description>* Towards a digital library of popular music (Citations: 65)

David Bainbridge, Craig G. Nevill-Manning, Ian H. Witten, Lloyd A. Smith, Rodger J. McNab

...a comprehensive digital library of musical material, including popular music. we have devel- oped new ways of collecting musical material, accessing it through searching...work with different representations of music: facsimile images of scores, the internal representation of a music editing program, page images typeset by a music edi- tor, midi files, audio...

Conference: Digital Libraries - DL , pp. 161-169, 1999</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7457-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7457_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:47:19">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/13280811/music-lyrics-composition-system-considering-user-s-image-and-music-genre</link><title>Music/Lyrics Composition System Considering User's Image and Music Genre</title><description>* Music/Lyrics Composition System Considering User's Image and Music Genre

Takehisa Onisawa, Chisa Nakamura

...section starts. this section composes music fitting lyrics generated by the lyric composing section using the music composition system. and this section generates melody and backing patterns according to music genres. the section presents combinations of lyrics and 16 measures music. a subject evaluates each combination of lyrics and music whether it fits his/her...

Conference: IEEE International Conference on Systems, Man, and Cybernetics - SMC , pp. 1764-1769, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7457-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7457_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:47:50">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/2510185/automatic-lyrics-alignment-for-cantonese-popular-music</link><title>Automatic lyrics alignment for Cantonese popular music</title><description>* Automatic lyrics alignment for Cantonese popular music (Citations: 8)

Chi Hang Wong, Wai Man Szeto, Kin Hong Wong

...everyday functionalities: temporal synchronization of the written text and its corresponding musical phrase. our goal is to automate the process of lyrics alignment, a procedure which, to...designed for cantonese, in which the contour of the musical melody and the tonal contour of the lyrics must match perfectly. with this...

Journal: Multimedia Systems - MMS , vol. 12, no. 4-5, pp. 307-323, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7457-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7457_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:48:37">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50858462/automatic-music-mood-detection-through-musical-structure-analysis</link><title>Automatic Music Mood Detection through Musical Structure Analysis</title><description>* Automatic Music Mood Detection through Musical Structure Analysis

Jong In Lee, Dong-Gyu Yeo, Byeong Man Kim, Hae-Yeoun Lee

...such manual approaches correctly detect the mood, their manual intervention makes their application for new music difficult. moreover, the mood variation in music makes their application more difficult...an automatic method to classify the music mood. after the music is segmented into groups having...

Conference: International Symposium on Computer Science and its Applications - CSA , 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7457-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7457_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:49:21">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/2166195/automatic-lyrics-alignment-on-popular-music</link><title>Automatic Lyrics Alignment on Popular Music</title><description>* Automatic Lyrics Alignment on Popular Music

Chi Hang Wong, Kin Hong Wong, Wai Man Szeto

Conference: Computers and Their Applications - CATA , pp. 385-390, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7457-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7457_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:49:48">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10263442/stand-by-your-man-redneck-woman-towards-a-historical-view-of-country-music-gender-roles</link><title>STAND BY YOUR MAN, REDNECK WOMAN: TOWARDS A HISTORICAL VIEW OF COUNTRY MUSIC GENDER ROLES</title><description>* STAND BY YOUR MAN, REDNECK WOMAN: TOWARDS A HISTORICAL VIEW OF COUNTRY MUSIC GENDER ROLES

CENATE PRUITT

...compared to rock and rap music. this thesis proposes research into the topic of country music, specifically the ways which country music songs portray gender. the thesis uses billboard chart data...attention will be focused on the lyrical descriptions of men and women and how their roles are described in the songs....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7457-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7457_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:50:53">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/59109219/modifying-behaviors-of-children-with-autism-the-use-of-musically-adapted-social-stories-in</link><title>Modifying Behaviors of Children with Autism: The Use of Musically Adapted Social Stories in Home-Based Environments</title><description>* Modifying Behaviors of Children with Autism: The Use of Musically Adapted Social Stories in Home-Based Environments

Yuen-man Chan

...a behavioral problem identified by the parents. original music was then composed to incorporate the sentences of the story as lyrics. an abac/acab counterbalanced design...and third components (a) represented the baseline conditions, the second component (b) represented the treatment condition “reading the story,” and the fourth component (c) represented the...

Published in 2005.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7457-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7457_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:51:29">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57766540/queering-informal-pedagogy-sexuality-and-popular-music-in-school</link><title>Queering informal pedagogy: sexuality and popular music in school</title><description>* Queering informal pedagogy: sexuality and popular music in school

Joseph Michael Abramo

...constructed their sexual identity through musical production and reception. the findings suggest that the boys used popular music making to project a sexual...a high tessitura and writing lyrics – that they willingly performed in traditional music ensembles and genres. this questions whether the recent use of popular music pedagogies in formal settings effectively...

Journal: Music Education Research - MUSIC EDUC RES , vol. 13, no. 4, pp. 465-477, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7457-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7457_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:52:15">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/2518022/pattern-recognition-approach-for-music-style-identification-using-shallow-statistical-descriptors</link><title>Pattern Recognition Approach for Music Style Identification Using Shallow Statistical Descriptors</title><description>* Pattern Recognition Approach for Music Style Identification Using Shallow Statistical Descriptors (Citations: 2)

Pedro Ponce De Len, Jos Iesta

...in the field of computer music, pattern recognition algorithms are very relevant for music information retrieval applications. one challenging task in this area is the automatic recognition of musical style, having a number of...

Journal: IEEE Transactions on Systems, Man, and Cybernetics - TSMC , vol. 37, no. 2, pp. 248-257, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7457-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7457_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:52:44">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4415302/generation-of-personalized-music-sports-video-using-multimodal-cues</link><title>Generation of Personalized Music Sports Video Using Multimodal Cues</title><description>* Generation of Personalized Music Sports Video Using Multimodal Cues (Citations: 13)

Jinjun Wang, Engsiong Chng, Changsheng Xu, Hanqing Lu, Qi Tian

...research challenges are addressed, specifically the semantic sports video content extraction and the automatic music video composition. for the first challenge, we propose to...analysis and alignment to detect the semantics of events in broadcast sports video. for the second challenge, we introduce the video-centric and music-centric music video composition schemes and proposed...

Journal: IEEE Transactions on Multimedia - TMM , vol. 9, no. 3, pp. 576-588, 2007</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>