<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7458">rice recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:53:20" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7458-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7458_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:53:21">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11102537/glycemic-and-lipemic-responses-of-selected-spirulina-supplemented-rice-based-recipes-in-normal</link><title>GLYCEMIC AND LIPEMIC RESPONSES OF SELECTED SPIRULINA SUPPLEMENTED RICE-BASED RECIPES IN NORMAL SUBJECTS</title><description>* GLYCEMIC AND LIPEMIC RESPONSES OF SELECTED SPIRULINA SUPPLEMENTED RICE-BASED RECIPES IN NORMAL SUBJECTS (Citations: 1)

Iyer Uma M, Ahmedi Sophia

...50g carbohydrate portions of five rice based recipes namely, plain rice, a combination of rice \- legume (green peas), a combination of rice \- dal (green gram dal and red gram dal) and vegetable pulao (rice and vegetables) with curd. all the recipes were supplemented with 2.5...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7458-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7458_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:54:08">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/14893379/rice-genome-a-recipe-for-revolution</link><title>Rice genome: A recipe for revolution?</title><description>* Rice genome: A recipe for revolution? (Citations: 2)

David Cyranoski

Journal: Nature , vol. 422, no. 6934, pp. 796-798, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7458-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7458_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:54:46">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/41775608/arsenic-in-rice-a-recipe-for-nutrient-loss</link><title>Arsenic in rice: a recipe for nutrient loss</title><description>* Arsenic in rice: a recipe for nutrient loss

Janet Pelley

Journal: Environmental Science &amp; Technology - ENVIRON SCI TECHNOL , vol. 43, no. 21, pp. 8004-8004, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7458-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7458_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:55:24">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40902705/improvement-of-the-breadmaking-quality-of-rice-flour-by-glucose-oxidase</link><title>Improvement of the breadmaking quality of rice flour by glucose oxidase</title><description>* Improvement of the breadmaking quality of rice flour by glucose oxidase (Citations: 39)

Hardeep Singh Gujral, Cristina M Rosell

...bread from rice flour is very difficult to bake as it lacks gluten like proteins but modification of the rice flour proteins with enzymes like...the effect of go on rice flour dough rheology, protein modification and bread quality has been reported. go modified the rice flour proteins by lowering the...

Journal: Food Research International - FOOD RES INT , vol. 37, no. 1, pp. 75-81, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7458-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7458_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:55:59">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/32356694/the-protein-nutritive-value-of-bouza-and-its-ingredients</link><title>The protein nutritive value of bouza and its ingredients</title><description>* The protein nutritive value of bouza and its ingredients

S. R. Morcos, S. M. Hegazi, S. El-Damhougy

...beans and bread, a popular recipe in egypt, increased from 43 to 52 when supplemented withbouza (first day samples), while the rice and lentils recipe was slightly increased from 48...

Journal: European Journal of Nutrition - EUR J NUTR , vol. 14, no. 1, pp. 34-40, 1975</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7458-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7458_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:56:55">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/41822045/biocultural-diversity-in-traditional-rice-based-agroecosystems-indigenous-research-and</link><title>Biocultural diversity in traditional rice-based agroecosystems: indigenous research and conservation of mavo ( Oryza sativa L.) upland rice landraces of eastern Indonesia</title><description>* Biocultural diversity in traditional rice-based agroecosystems: indigenous research and conservation of mavo ( Oryza sativa L.) upland rice landraces of eastern Indonesia (Citations: 2)

Jeanine M. Pfeiffer, Sisilia Dun, Bonafantura Mulawarman, Kevin J. Rice

...and techniques. the centrality of rice in southeast asian agricultural and social systems, contrasted with the significant erosion of rice-based biological and cultural diversity...to the links between traditional rice varieties and indigenous rice-based customs. this study represents the research efforts of rice farmers pertaining to the tado...

Journal: Environment, Development and Sustainability , vol. 8, no. 4, pp. 609-625, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7458-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7458_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:57:28">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48028903/comparative-life-cycle-assessment-of-uses-of-rice-husk-for-energy-purposes</link><title>Comparative life cycle assessment of uses of rice husk for energy purposes</title><description>* Comparative life cycle assessment of uses of rice husk for energy purposes

Jittima Prasara-A, Tim Grant

...2011), the main use of rice husk in thailand is as fuel to generate electricity. however, rice husk can potentially be used...upon the use of the rice husk. conclusions  overall, the option of using rice husk to generate electricity shows benefits over the option of using rice husk to produce cellulosic ethanol...

Journal: International Journal of Life Cycle Assessment - INT J LIFE CYCLE ASSESS , vol. 16, no. 6, pp. 493-502, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7458-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7458_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:58:10">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57900067/reducing-fat-content-of-brazilian-traditional-preparations-does-not-alter-food-acceptance</link><title>Reducing Fat Content of Brazilian Traditional Preparations Does Not Alter Food Acceptance: Development of a Model for Fat Reduction That Conciliates Health and Culture</title><description>* Reducing Fat Content of Brazilian Traditional Preparations Does Not Alter Food Acceptance: Development of a Model for Fat Reduction That Conciliates Health and Culture (Citations: 1)

Verônica Cortez Ginani, Janini Selva Ginani, Raquel Braz Assunção Botelho, Renata Puppin Zandonadi, Rita de Cássia Akutsu, Wilma Maria Coelho Araújo

...tropeiro) and spiced chicken with rice (galinhada) from the southeast region; and carreteiro rice (arroz carreteiro) and ground corn...0.05), except for carreteiro rice and banana pie recipes. in the case of the carreteiro rice, the acceptance of the modified recipe was greater than the standard...

Journal: Journal of Culinary Science &amp; Technology , vol. 8, no. 4, pp. 229-241, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7458-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7458_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:59:09">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/14116413/recipe-name-none-eggs-fish-milk-peanut-tree-nuts-shellfish-soy-wheat-bagel-x-beans-baked-x</link><title>Recipe Name None Eggs Fish Milk Peanut Tree Nuts Shellfish Soy Wheat Bagel X Beans, Baked X</title><description>* Recipe Name None Eggs Fish Milk Peanut Tree Nuts Shellfish Soy Wheat Bagel X Beans, Baked X

Brown Rice Salad, Chicken BBQ Elem, Chicken Teriyaki Elem

Published in 2009.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7458-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7458_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:00:02">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/44599769/indigestible-recipe-rice-chicken-wings-and-international-financial-institutionsor-hunger</link><title>Indigestible Recipe: Rice, Chicken Wings, and International Financial InstitutionsOr Hunger Politics in Haiti</title><description>* Indigestible Recipe: Rice, Chicken Wings, and International Financial InstitutionsOr Hunger Politics in Haiti

Jean-Germain Gros

Food riots in Haiti in early April 2008 brought to the attention of the international community the plight of the Haitians. These events are neither unique to Haiti nor the product of happenstance. Instead, policies imposed on Haiti by international financial institutions (i.e., the World Bank and International Monetary Fund) since the 1980s, such as currency devaluation and trade ...

Journal: Journal of Black Studies - J BLACK STUD , vol. 40, no. 5, pp. 974-986, 2010</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>