<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7460">kobe bryant news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:11:11" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7460-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7460_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:11:12">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57222088/network-news-coverage-of-high-profile-crimes-during-2004-a-study-of-source-use-and-reporter-context</link><title>Network News Coverage of High-Profile Crimes during 2004: A Study of Source use and Reporter Context</title><description>* Network News Coverage of High-Profile Crimes during 2004: A Study of Source use and Reporter Context (Citations: 1)

Serena Carpenter, Stephen Lacy, Frederick Fico

...a study of network news in 2004 found reporting about high-profile crimes (michael jackson, kobe bryant, scott peterson, and martha stewart...other significant stories. morning network news carried the bulk (84%) of high-profile crime stories that were broadcast on network news. the morning high-profile crime...

Journal: Journalism &amp; Mass Communication Quarterly - JOURNALISM MASS COMMUN , vol. 83, no. 4, pp. 901-916, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7460-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7460_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:12:42">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/36774509/prevalence-of-rape-myths-in-headlines-and-their-effects-on-attitudes-toward-rape</link><title>Prevalence of Rape Myths in Headlines and Their Effects on Attitudes Toward Rape</title><description>* Prevalence of Rape Myths in Headlines and Their Effects on Attitudes Toward Rape (Citations: 4)

Renae Franiuk, Jennifer L. Seefelt, Joseph A. Vandello

...a content analysis of online news headlines from us media (n = 555) surrounding the 2003–2004 kobe bryant sexual assault case showed that...a) less likely to think bryant was guilty than those exposed...

Journal: Sex Roles , vol. 58, no. 11, pp. 790-801, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7460-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7460_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:13:19">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5424951/a-new-flux-for-mean-curvature-1-surfaces-in-hyperbolic-3-space-and-applications</link><title>A new flux for mean curvature 1 surfaces in hyperbolic 3-space, and applications</title><description>* A new flux for mean curvature 1 surfaces in hyperbolic 3-space, and applications (Citations: 5)

Wayne Rossman, Masaaki Umehara, Kotaro Yamada

...using the bryant representation, we define a new flux on homology classes of...

Published in 1997.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7460-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7460_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:14:50">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/23288224/new-series-of-potent-opioid-antagonists-containing-the-h-dmt-tic-nh-hexyl-nh-r-motif</link><title>New series of potent δ-opioid antagonists containing the H-Dmt-Tic-NH-hexyl-NH-R motif</title><description>* New series of potent δ-opioid antagonists containing the H-Dmt-Tic-NH-hexyl-NH-R motif

Tingyou Li, Kimitaka Shiotani, Anna Miyazaki, Yoshio Fujita, Yuko Tsuda, Akihiro Ambo, Yusuke Sasaki, Yunden Jinsmaa, Ewa Marczak, Sharon D. Bryant, Lawrence H. Lazarus, Yoshio Okada

...represent the prototype for a new class of structural homologues lacking...m.; salvadori, s.; jinsmaa, y.; bryant, s. d.; lazarus, l. h...

Journal: Bioorganic &amp; Medicinal Chemistry Letters - BIOORG MEDICINAL CHEM LETTER , vol. 15, no. 24, pp. 5517-5520, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7460-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7460_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:16:34">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/23876763/oral-bioavailability-of-a-new-class-of-opioid-receptor-agonists-containing-3-6bis-dmt-nh-ch-2-n</link><title>Oral Bioavailability of a New Class of μ-Opioid Receptor Agonists Containing 3,6Bis[Dmt-NH(CH 2 ) n ]-2(1 H )-pyrazinone with Central-Mediated Analgesia</title><description>* Oral Bioavailability of a New Class of μ-Opioid Receptor Agonists Containing 3,6Bis[Dmt-NH(CH 2 ) n ]-2(1 H )-pyrazinone with Central-Mediated Analgesia (Citations: 3)

Yunden Jinsmaa, Anna Miyazaki, Yoshio Fujita, Tingyou Li, Yutaka Fujisawa, Kimitaka Shiotani, Yuko Tsuda, Toshio Yokoi, Akihiro Ambo, Yusuke Sasaki, Sharon D. Bryant, Lawrence H. Lazarushttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=23876763&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=kobe bryant news

Journal: Journal of Medicinal Chemistry - J MED CHEM , vol. 47, no. 10, pp. 2599-2610, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7460-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7460_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:17:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6987071/characterization-of-densin-180-a-new-brain-specific-synaptic-protein-of-the-o-sialoglycoprotein</link><title>Characterization of Densin-180, a New Brain-Specific Synaptic Protein of the O-Sialoglycoprotein Family</title><description>* Characterization of Densin-180, a New Brain-Specific Synaptic Protein of the O-Sialoglycoprotein Family (Citations: 48)

Michelle L. Apperson, Mary B. Kennedy

We purified an abundant protein of apparent molecular mass 180 kDa from the postsynaptic density fraction of rat forebrain and obtained amino acid sequences of three tryptic peptides generated from the protein. The sequences were used to de- sign a strategy for cloning the cDNA encoding the protein by polymerase chain reaction. The open reading frame of the cDNA encodes ...

Published in 1996.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7460-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7460_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:18:52">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/49040941/endomorphins-and-related-opioid-peptides</link><title>Endomorphins and related opioid peptides</title><description>* Endomorphins and related opioid peptides (Citations: 15)

Yoshio Okada, Yuko Tsuda, Sharon D Bryant, Lawrence H Lazarust

...lead to the development of new therapeutic drugs for controlling pain...

Journal: Vitamins and Hormones Series - VITAMIN HORMONE-ADVAN RES APP , vol. 65, pp. 257-279, 2002</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7460-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7460_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:20:11">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/34679917/several-new-substrates-for-desulfovibrio-vulgaris-strain-marburg-and-a-spontaneous-mutant-from-it</link><title>Several new substrates for Desulfovibrio vulgaris strain Marburg and a spontaneous mutant from it</title><description>* Several new substrates for Desulfovibrio vulgaris strain Marburg and a spontaneous mutant from it (Citations: 3)

Kazuhiro Tanaka

The ability of Desulfovibrio vulgaris strain Marburg (DSM 2119) to oxidize alcohols was surveyed in the presence and absence of hydrogen-scavenging anaerobes, Acetobacterium woodii and Methanospirillum hungatei. In the presence of sulfate, D. vulgaris grew not only on ethanol, 1-propanol, and 1-butanol, but also on isobutanol, 1-pentanol, ethyleneglycol, and 1,3-propanediol. Metabolism of these alcohols ...

Journal: Archives of Microbiology - ARCH MICROBIOL , vol. 155, no. 1, pp. 18-21, 1990</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7460-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7460_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:21:19">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/23290585/design-and-synthesis-of-opioidmimetics-containing-2-6-dimethyl-l-tyrosine-and-a-pyrazinone-ring</link><title>Design and synthesis of opioidmimetics containing 2′,6′-dimethyl- l-tyrosine and a pyrazinone-ring platform</title><description>* Design and synthesis of opioidmimetics containing 2′,6′-dimethyl- l-tyrosine and a pyrazinone-ring platform (Citations: 2)

Kimitaka Shiotani, Tingyou Li, Anna Miyazaki, Yuko Tsuda, Toshio Yokoi, Akihiro Ambo, Yusuke Sasaki, Sharon D. Bryant, Lawrence H. Lazarus, Yoshio Okada

...formation of pyrazinone opioidmimetics and new lead compounds....

Journal: Bioorganic &amp; Medicinal Chemistry Letters - BIOORG MEDICINAL CHEM LETTER , vol. 17, no. 21, pp. 5768-5771, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7460-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7460_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:22:17">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/34679994/fermentation-of-s-citramalate-citrate-mesaconate-and-pyruvate-by-a-gram-negative-strictly</link><title>Fermentation of S -citramalate, citrate, mesaconate, and pyruvate by a gram-negative strictly anaerobic non-spore-former, Formivibrio citricus gen. nov., sp. nov</title><description>* Fermentation of S -citramalate, citrate, mesaconate, and pyruvate by a gram-negative strictly anaerobic non-spore-former, Formivibrio citricus gen. nov., sp. nov (Citations: 1)

Kazuhiro Tanaka, Kazunori Nakamura, Eiichi Mikami

...as a member of a new genus and a new species in the family bacteroidaceae...

Journal: Archives of Microbiology - ARCH MICROBIOL , vol. 155, no. 5, pp. 491-495, 1991</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>