<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7461">navalni trial latest news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:23:43" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7461-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7461_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:23:44">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/47599635/diagnostic-cutoff-points-for-123-i-mibg-myocardial-scintigraphy-in-a-caucasian-population-with</link><title>Diagnostic cutoff points for 123 I-MIBG myocardial scintigraphy in a Caucasian population with Parkinson’s disease</title><description>* Diagnostic cutoff points for 123 I-MIBG myocardial scintigraphy in a Caucasian population with Parkinson’s disease (Citations: 1)

África Muxí, Pilar Paredes, Ignacio Navales, Francesc Valldeoriola, Carles Gaig, Francisco Lomeña, Andres de la Cerda, Oriol Solà, Beatriz Domenech, Eduardo Tolosa, Francesca Pons

Purpose  Molecular imaging with 123I-metaiodobenzylguanidine (MIBG) has been used in Parkinson’s disease (PD), but there is no consensual index to discriminate between normal and PD patients in the Caucasian population. The purpose of this study was to determine diagnostic cutoff points in the quantification of MIBG cardiac uptake in our population of PD patients. We have also calculated the reproducibility ...

Journal: European Journal of Nuclear Medicine and Molecular Imaging - EUR J NUCL MED MOL IMAGING , vol. 38, no. 6, pp. 1139-1146, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7461-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7461_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:24:21">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/47796099/military-applications-human-factors-aspects-of-speech-based-systems</link><title>Military Applications: Human Factors Aspects of Speech-Based Systems</title><description>* Military Applications: Human Factors Aspects of Speech-Based Systems

Jan M. Noyes, Ellen Haas

When considering military applications of speech-based interactive systems, there are some which are specific to the military domain, and some which are more general, for example, office-type applications (dictation, directory and information enquiries; see Jokinen [23]) and training. The emphasis in the chapter is on the more specific military applications although some of the general applications are discussed. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>