<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7468">car change radiator fluid</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:05:31" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7468-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7468_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:05:32">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/49388766/experimental-study-of-heat-transfer-enhancement-using-water-ethylene-glycol-based-nanofluids-as-a</link><title>Experimental study of heat transfer enhancement using water/ethylene glycol based nanofluids as a new coolant for car radiators</title><description>* Experimental study of heat transfer enhancement using water/ethylene glycol based nanofluids as a new coolant for car radiators

S. M. Peyghambarzadeh, S. H. Hashemabadi, S. M. Hoseini, M. Seifi Jamnani

...convection heat transfer in a car radiator is performed to cool circulating fluid which consisted of water or...heat transfer performance of the car radiator have been determined experimentally. liquid flow rate has been changed in the range of 2...

Journal: International Communications in Heat and Mass Transfer - INT COMMUN HEAT MASS TRANS , vol. 38, no. 9, pp. 1283-1290, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7468-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7468_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:06:11">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/12629956/realignmentenhanced-coherent-antistokes-raman-sca-ttering-cars-and-threedimensional-imaging-in</link><title>Realignmentenhanced coherent antiStokes Raman sca ttering (CARS) and threedimensional imaging in anisotropic fluids</title><description>* Realignmentenhanced coherent antiStokes Raman sca ttering (CARS) and threedimensional imaging in anisotropic fluids

Aliaksandr V. Kachynski, Ivan I. Smalyukh

...coherent anti-stokes raman scattering (cars) microscopy to characterize director structures in liquid crystals. we demonstrate that the polarized cars signal in these anisotropic fluids strongly depends on alignment of...via polarized detection of the cars signal and thus for cars polarization microscopy of liquid crystal...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7468-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7468_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:06:51">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6349733/clathrin-independent-pinocytosis-is-induced-in-cells-overexpressing-a-temperature-sensitive-mutant</link><title>Clathrin-independent pinocytosis is induced in cells overexpressing a temperature-sensitive mutant of dynamin</title><description>* Clathrin-independent pinocytosis is induced in cells overexpressing a temperature-sensitive mutant of dynamin (Citations: 149)

Hanna Damke, Takeshi Baba, Alexander M. van der Bliek, Sandra L. Schmid

...coated vesicle formation. dyn ts car\- ries a point mutation, g273d...held at the nonpermissive temperature, fluid phase uptake fully recovers to...

Journal: Journal of Cell Biology - J CELL BIOL , vol. 131, no. 1, pp. 69-80, 1995</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7468-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7468_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:08:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5957515/quartz-exposure-of-the-rat-lung-leads-to-a-linear-dose-response-in-inflammation-but-not-in</link><title>Quartz Exposure of the Rat Lung Leads to a Linear Dose Response in Inflammation but Not in Oxidative DNA Damage and Mutagenicity</title><description>* Quartz Exposure of the Rat Lung Leads to a Linear Dose Response in Inflammation but Not in Oxidative DNA Damage and Mutagenicity (Citations: 16)

Frank Seiler, Bernd Rehn, S. Rehn, Martina Hermann, Joachim Bruch

...mechanisms involved in particle-induced car\- cinogenesis seem to include inflammation...ers in rat bronchoalveolar lavage fluid (balf); on the induction of...

Published in 2001.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7468-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7468_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:08:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/32651486/vasopressin-hypercalciuria-and-aquaporin-the-key-elements-for-impaired-renal-water-handling-in</link><title>Vasopressin, Hypercalciuria and Aquaporin – The Key Elements for Impaired Renal Water Handling in Astronauts?</title><description>* Vasopressin, Hypercalciuria and Aquaporin – The Key Elements for Impaired Renal Water Handling in Astronauts? (Citations: 1)

Christian Drummer, Giovanna Valenti, Massimo Cirillo, Alessandra Perna, Luigi Bellini, Vesselin Nenov, Natale G. De Santo

...in space, indicates that significant changes in renal sodium and water...in detail these components of fluid balance and kidney function in...

Journal: Nephron , vol. 92, no. 3, pp. 503-514, 2002</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7468-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7468_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:10:17">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/51143787/effectiveness-enchancement-of-heat-exchanger-by-using-nanofluids</link><title>Effectiveness enchancement of heat exchanger by using nanofluids</title><description>* Effectiveness enchancement of heat exchanger by using nanofluids

M. Hasanuzzamana, R. Saidur, N. A. Rahim

...heat is transferred from one fluid to other fluids by convection and conduction through...heat transfer coefficient of the fluid. convective heat transfer coefficient of...

Conference: IEEE Conference on Clean Energy and Technology - CET , 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7468-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7468_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:11:22">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5087888/two-color-particle-tracking-velocimetry-and-thermometry</link><title>Two-Color Particle Tracking Velocimetry and Thermometry</title><description>* Two-Color Particle Tracking Velocimetry and Thermometry

A. V. Mikheev, V. M. Zubtsov

...interest in classical and applied fluid mechanics are essentially inseparable from...coherent anti-stokes raman scattering (cars) technique, micron-resolution particle image...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7468-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7468_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:12:48">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/12431506/classification-of-cancer-cell-lines-using-an-automated-two-dimensional-liquid-mapping-method-with</link><title>Classification of Cancer Cell Lines Using an Automated Two-dimensional Liquid Mapping Method with Hierarchical Clustering Techniques</title><description>* Classification of Cancer Cell Lines Using an Automated Two-dimensional Liquid Mapping Method with Hierarchical Clustering Techniques (Citations: 7)

Yanfei Wang, Rong Wu, Kathleen R. Cho, Kerby A. Shedden, Timothy J. Barder, David M. Lubman

...expression of eight ovarian serous car\- cinoma cell lines and three...whereas specific groups of serous car\- cinoma cell lines clustered with...

Journal: Molecular &amp; Cellular Proteomics - MOL CELL PROTEOMICS , vol. 5, no. 1, pp. 43-52, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7468-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7468_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:14:56">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48258336/cancer-morphology-carcinogenesis-and-genetic-instability-a-background</link><title>Cancer morphology, carcinogenesis and genetic instability: a background</title><description>* Cancer morphology, carcinogenesis and genetic instability: a background (Citations: 7)

Leon P. Bignold, B. L. D. Coghlan, H. P. A. Jersmann

...to mal-distribution and other changes of chromosomes occurring during mitosis...the carcinogenic effects of ionising radiations, of certain chemicals and of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7468-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7468_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:16:30">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/32027458/perspectives-of-cellular-and-molecular-neurosurgery</link><title>Perspectives of Cellular and Molecular Neurosurgery</title><description>* Perspectives of Cellular and Molecular Neurosurgery (Citations: 3)

Manfred Westphal, Peter Mc L. Black

...present therapies like surgery and radiation are able to treat. specific...which surgery, conventional chemotherapy and radiation have to offer. whereas the...

Journal: Journal of Neuro-oncology - J NEURO-ONCOL , vol. 70, no. 2, pp. 255-269, 2004</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>