<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7473">noise canceling head phones</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:38:42" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7473-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7473_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:38:43">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/59510259/personalized-multi-channel-headphone-sound-reproduction-based-on-active-noise-cancellation</link><title>Personalized multi-channel headphone sound reproduction based on active noise cancellation</title><description>* Personalized multi-channel headphone sound reproduction based on active noise cancellation

DWE Schobben, RM Aarts

Published in 2005.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7473-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7473_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:39:51">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5628855/adaptive-audio-noise-cancellation-with-spartan-3e</link><title>Adaptive Audio Noise Cancellation with Spartan 3E</title><description>* Adaptive Audio Noise Cancellation with Spartan 3E (Citations: 1)

Joe Blomer, Dave Rolkosky

...prediction and cancellation of the noise source and one used in a novel manner to compensate for a feedback channel from the cancellation speaker to...absorb the energy from some noise source. also, some means may be used to channel the noise to some other position where...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7473-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7473_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:40:39">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50908400/the-multidimensional-characterization-of-active-noise-cancelation-headphone-perception</link><title>The multidimensional characterization of active noise cancelation headphone perception</title><description>* The multidimensional characterization of active noise cancelation headphone perception

Nick Zacharov, Jesper Ramsgaard, Guillaume Le Ray, Chris Vigandt Jørgensen

...with the application of active noise cancelation (anc) technologies to headphones. in this popular application, both noise cancelation performance is evaluated in noise &amp; also the impact on...format recording over a 5-channel loudspeaker setup in an anechoic chamber to anc headphones placed on a head &amp;amp...

Conference: International Workshop on Quality of Multimedia Experience, QoMEx - QoMEX , 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7473-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7473_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:41:55">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/27053320/a-0-8-v-2-6-mw-88-db-dual-channel-audio-delta-sigma-d-a-converter-with-headphone-driver</link><title>A 0.8 V, 2.6 mW, 88 dB Dual-Channel Audio Delta-Sigma D/A Converter With Headphone Driver</title><description>* A 0.8 V, 2.6 mW, 88 dB Dual-Channel Audio Delta-Sigma D/A Converter With Headphone Driver

Kyehyung Lee, Qingdong Meng, Tetsuro Sugimoto, Koichi Hamashita, Kaoru Takasuka, Seiji Takeuchi, Un-Ku Moon, Gabor C. Temes

...dac with integrated on-chip headphone driver. the dual-channel operation in digital section was efficiently realized with a time-interleaved single-channel hardware and extra registers. using...requires only one opamp per channel for the d/a conversion, low-pass filtering, and driving the headphone. two prototype ics (separate digital...

Journal: IEEE Journal of Solid-state Circuits - IEEE J SOLID-STATE CIRCUITS , vol. 44, no. 3, pp. 916-927, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7473-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7473_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:43:34">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50667242/a-1-3mw-per-channel-103db-snr-stereo-audio-dac-with-class-d-headphones-amplifier-in-65nm-cmos</link><title>A 1.3mW per-channel 103dB SNR stereo audio DAC with class-D headphones amplifier in 65nm CMOS</title><description>* A 1.3mW per-channel 103dB SNR stereo audio DAC with class-D headphones amplifier in 65nm CMOS (Citations: 1)

Yong-Hee Lee, Chun-Kyun Seok, Bong-Joo Kim, Seung-Bin You, Wang-Seup Yeum, Ho-Jin Park, Young-Hyun Jun, Bai-Sun Kong, Jae-Whui Kim

...is applied to minimize switching noise and nonlinearity in the class...only 1.3-mw per channel from a 2.5-v...

Conference: Symposium on VLSI Circuits - VLSIC , 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7473-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7473_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:44:17">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/51231131/comparison-of-speech-intelligibility-scores-for-direct-listening-and-headphone-playback</link><title>Comparison of speech intelligibility scores for direct listening and headphone playback</title><description>* Comparison of speech intelligibility scores for direct listening and headphone playback

John S. Bradley, Hiroshi Sato, Bradford N. Gover, Natalie York

...scores from direct listening and headphone playback were compared to validate the use of headphone playback for investigating the effects...times and 4 signal-to-noise ratios were used. by recording these conditions with an acoustical mannequin, headphone playback of the same conditions...

Journal: Journal of The Acoustical Society of America - J ACOUST SOC AMER , vol. 117, pp. 2465-2466, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7473-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7473_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:45:49">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4773267/a-spectral-conversion-approach-to-single-channel-speech-enhancement</link><title>A Spectral Conversion Approach to Single-Channel Speech Enhancement</title><description>* A Spectral Conversion Approach to Single-Channel Speech Enhancement (Citations: 6)

Athanasios Mouchtaris, Jan Van Der Spiegel, Paul Mueller, Panagiotis Tsakalides

...a novel method for single-channel speech enhancement is proposed, which...to two well-known single channel enhancement methods, namely the iterative...

Journal: IEEE Transactions on Audio, Speech &amp; Language Processing - TASLP , vol. 15, no. 4, pp. 1180-1193, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7473-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7473_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:47:37">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/46523008/effects-of-isolated-and-combined-exposures-to-whole-body-vibration-and-noise-on-auditory-event</link><title>Effects of isolated and combined exposures to whole-body vibration and noise on auditory-event related brain potentials and psychophysical assessment</title><description>* Effects of isolated and combined exposures to whole-body vibration and noise on auditory-event related brain potentials and psychophysical assessment (Citations: 1)

Helmut Seidel, Ralph Bliithner, Janos Martin, Gerhard Menzel, Rudolf Panuska, Peter Ullsperger

...db, 50 ms; given by headphones at a regular interstimulus interval...detection task and intensity of noise by means of cross-modality matching (cmm). vibration-synchronous activity in the electrocardiogram was eliminated by a subtraction-technique. noise caused an attenuation of the...

Published in 1992.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7473-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7473_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:48:58">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6075403/a-stereo-transmission-technique-using-pdm-data-and-synchronized-clock-channels</link><title>A Stereo Transmission Technique Using PDM Data and Synchronized Clock Channels</title><description>* A Stereo Transmission Technique Using PDM Data and Synchronized Clock Channels

Yasuyuki Matsuya, Takahiro Mesuda

...pdm) for digital wireless audio headphone systems. the main feature of the proposed technique is the use of two channels for transmission: the pdm data channel and the synchronized clock channel. this technique improves receiver characteristics to a noise floor of -80db and a...

Journal: Ieice Transactions - IEICE , vol. 92-A, no. 2, pp. 456-458, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7473-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7473_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:49:55">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10895610/active-noise-control-at-high-frequencies</link><title>ACTIVE NOISE CONTROL AT HIGH FREQUENCIES</title><description>* ACTIVE NOISE CONTROL AT HIGH FREQUENCIES

Erkan Kaymak, Mark Atherton, Ken Rotter, Brian Millar

...that can benefit from active noise control (anc) such as in...environment; in which dental drill noise is commonly off-putting for...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>