<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7475">software consultant work at home</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:59:41" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7475-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7475_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:59:43">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11324895/few-rural-general-practitioners-use-the-internet-frequently-in-regard-to-patient-care</link><title>Few rural general practitioners use the Internet frequently in regard to patient care</title><description>* Few rural general practitioners use the Internet frequently in regard to patient care (Citations: 4)

Ron Janes, Bruce Arroll, Stephen Buetow, Gregor Coster, Ross McCormick, Iain Hague

...89.0%) reported computer availability at work when consulting, but even more had access to a computer at home (97.1%, p&lt;0...or more times a week at work (6.9%) or home (8.6%) in regard to patients. of those with internet access at work, 27.0% had broadband (fast...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7475-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7475_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:01:05">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/2909317/creating-change-a-review-of-the-impact-of-design-and-technology-in-schools-in-england</link><title>Creating Change? A Review of the Impact of Design and Technology in Schools in England</title><description>* Creating Change? A Review of the Impact of Design and Technology in Schools in England (Citations: 3)

Valerie Wilson, Marlene Harris

...england. these findings are summarized at the end of each section...h c i co ltd, software consultants, scotland. ...

Published in 2004.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7475-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7475_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:01:43">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4947816/imaging-technologies-for-avoiding-back-pain-at-work-imaging-technologies-for-avoiding-back-pain-at</link><title>Imaging technologies for avoiding back pain at work Imaging technologies for avoiding back pain at work Imaging technologies for avoiding back pain at work Imaging technologies for avoiding back pain at work</title><description>* Imaging technologies for avoiding back pain at work Imaging technologies for avoiding back pain at work Imaging technologies for avoiding back pain at work Imaging technologies for avoiding back pain at work

L. Engels, T. Leloup, N. Warzée

...system aims rehabilitation exercises performed at home but can also take place...have to perform physical exercises at home between two consultations. the patient cannot profit of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7475-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7475_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:02:19">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/55010350/obituary-albert-g-petschek-1928-2004</link><title>Obituary: Albert G. Petschek, 1928-2004</title><description>* Obituary: Albert G. Petschek, 1928-2004

Stirling A. Colgate, Rolfe G. Petschek, Larry D. Libersky

...tech to spend three years at science, systems and software, a scientific consulting firm in san diego california...those with whom he interacted at new mexico tech. of his 69 published works, 39 were published in collaboration with stirling colgate. colgate, at that time new mexico tech...

Published in 2005.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7475-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7475_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:04:00">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/639563/centering-on-the-student-computer-user-the-evolution-of-a-peer-training-program-at-the-university</link><title>Centering on the student computer user (the evolution of a peer training program at the University of Maryland)</title><description>* Centering on the student computer user (the evolution of a peer training program at the University of Maryland)

Marie A. Zannis, Deborah Mateik

...students to use wam (workstations at maryland) public computing labs and acquainting them with some workstation software. one class, however, teaches remote...peer training staff available to consult with students working on term papers and projects...

Conference: SIGUCCS Conference on User Services , pp. 427-433, 1990</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7475-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7475_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:05:36">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39246856/entering-the-ada-systems-design-and-coding-market</link><title>Entering the Ada systems design and coding market</title><description>* Entering the Ada systems design and coding market

P. J. Mayer

...and concretely confirm our perceptions.at each step in the process we were looking at what value was being added...scrupulously avoid being hardware and software “brokers” collecting fees for merely placing products with customers. we consider ourselves as partners with our clients and work to enhance their businesses with...

Published in 1988.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7475-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7475_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:06:58">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/12053122/automatic-preventive-control-for-work-posture-in-front-of-a-visual-display-terminal</link><title>AUTOMATIC PREVENTIVE CONTROL FOR WORK POSTURE IN FRONT OF A VISUAL DISPLAY TERMINAL</title><description>* AUTOMATIC PREVENTIVE CONTROL FOR WORK POSTURE IN FRONT OF A VISUAL DISPLAY TERMINAL

L. Engels, T. Leloup, N. Warzée

...system aims rehabilitation exercises performed at home but can also take place...have to perform physical exercises at home between two consultations. the patient cannot profit of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7475-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7475_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:07:39">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57210043/abstracts-of-research-oral-and-poster-presentations-at-the-2011-ilca-conference</link><title>Abstracts of Research Oral and Poster Presentations at the 2011 ILCA Conference</title><description>* Abstracts of Research Oral and Poster Presentations at the 2011 ILCA Conference

Stephanie Santana, Radha Sadacharan, Emily Sanchez, Gregory Makrigiorgos, Xena Grossman, Anne Merewood, Shadia Riad El Guindy, Azza H. Ahmed, Oluwaseun Taiwo Esan, Bridget Omisore, Carol Traa, Florence Omekarahttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=57210043&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=software consultant work at home

...were baby-friendly. however, staff at 644 hospitals (53%) incorrectly said their hospitals were baby-friendly. by contrast, staff at all 41 baby-friendly hospitals...records indicated solids were started at 2 months, but at 1 year, the mother recalled starting at 6 months). on average, incorrect...

Journal: Journal of Human Lactation - J HUM LACT , vol. 28, no. 1, pp. 77-85, 2012</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7475-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7475_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:09:26">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/59196895/improving-pediatric-cardiology-consultation-methods-by-introducing-digital-interactive-3-d-heart</link><title>Improving Pediatric Cardiology Consultation Methods by Introducing Digital Interactive 3-D Heart Models: A Proof of Concept Study</title><description>* Improving Pediatric Cardiology Consultation Methods by Introducing Digital Interactive 3-D Heart Models: A Proof of Concept Study

Adam Verigan

...a certain congenital heart defect. consultation education methods and materials may include verbal descriptions, two-dimensional (2-d) heart diagrams, and take-home pamphlets. because the human heart...of the situation. in this work a method to improve patient consultation is outlined. heart model segmentation...

Published in 2007.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7475-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7475_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:10:34">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4349941/an-integrated-approach-to-supporting-interaction-evolution-in-home-care-systems</link><title>An integrated approach to supporting interaction evolution in home care systems</title><description>* An integrated approach to supporting interaction evolution in home care systems (Citations: 9)

Tony Mcbryan, Marilyn Rose Mcgee-lennon, Philip D. Gray

...addresses this issue in the home care domain by integrating methods for interaction re- quirements engineering with system support for turning those requirements into a working configuration. both the methods and...of change - 'interaction evolution' in home care. we present the key features of our approach using a home care scenario and consider our...

Conference: International Conference on Pervasive Technologies Related to Assistive Environments - PETRA , pp. 45-8, 2008</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>