<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7478">protect kids online</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:33:26" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7478-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7478_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:33:27">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/58896483/trust-safety-security-framing-eu-kids-online-policy-recommendations-within-the-digital-agenda</link><title>Trust, Safety, Security: Framing EU Kids Online Policy Recommendations within the Digital Agenda for Europe</title><description>* Trust, Safety, Security: Framing EU Kids Online Policy Recommendations within the Digital Agenda for Europe

Brian ONeill

...people, the risks they experience online, and the impact on children when they encounter difficulties. this paper seeks to locate eu kids online policy recommendations within the overarching...in their approach to the online world, also have significant concerns regarding the availability of quality online content, trust, security, misuse of personal data and online support services. this paper outlines...

Published in 2011.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7478-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7478_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:34:39">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/58917057/australian-children-s-experiences-of-parents-online-mediation</link><title>Australian children’s experiences of parents’ online mediation</title><description>* Australian children’s experiences of parents’ online mediation

Lelia Green, John Hartley, Catharine Lumby, Danielle Brady

...the work of the "eu kids online" network funded by the ec...context of the mediation and online protection practices adopted by their parents...

Published in 2011.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7478-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7478_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:35:32">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57823779/playing-with-porn-greek-children-s-explorations-in-pornography</link><title>Playing with porn: Greek children's explorations in pornography</title><description>* Playing with porn: Greek children's explorations in pornography

Liza Tsaliki

...research findings of the greek kids go online project and the eu kids online i network research on children and online technologies in europe, funded by...and 17 with pornographic texts online, and parental perceptions of these...

Journal: Sex Education , vol. 11, no. 3, pp. 293-302, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7478-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7478_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:36:20">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11912572/virtual-playgrounds-and-buddybots-a-data-minefield-for-tweens</link><title>Virtual Playgrounds and Buddybots: A Data-Minefield for Tweens</title><description>* Virtual Playgrounds and Buddybots: A Data-Minefield for Tweens (Citations: 1)

Valerie Steeves, Ian R. Kerr

...to purchase been able to protect children's privacy in the online product. environment. we also examine...that the vision tices can protect kids from the invasive nature of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7478-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7478_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:37:09">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/58896360/promoting-children-s-interests-on-the-internet-regulation-and-the-emerging-evidence-base-of-risk</link><title>Promoting Children’s Interests on the Internet: Regulation and the Emerging Evidence Base of Risk and Harm</title><description>* Promoting Children’s Interests on the Internet: Regulation and the Emerging Evidence Base of Risk and Harm

Brian ONeill, Sonia Livingstone

...advocacy for child protection online has tended to flow against...of the interests of children online has met with significant challenges, and child protection measures are frequently viewed as...

Published in 2010.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7478-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7478_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:37:34">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/58958700/an-implementation-of-accountable-anonymity</link><title>An implementation of accountable anonymity</title><description>* An implementation of accountable anonymity

Leonardo Aguilera

...should be equally important as protecting the anonymity of legitimate users...child pornography, pedophiles chatting with kids online or any other illegal activity...

Published in 2011.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7478-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7478_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:38:19">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/285365/online-investors-do-the-slow-die-first</link><title>Online Investors: Do the Slow Die First?</title><description>* Online Investors: Do the Slow Die First? (Citations: 126)

Brad M. Barber, Terrance Odean

...switched from phone-based to online trading during the 1990s. those who switch to online trading perform well prior to going online, beating the market by more...and reduction in performance of online investors. (the giant) tortoise lives longer than any other animal. collier's encyclopedia "online trading is like the old...

Journal: SSRN Electronic Journal , 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7478-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7478_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:38:51">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/1826655/cool-hunting-the-kids-digital-playground-datamining-and-the-privacy-debates-in-children-s-online</link><title>Cool Hunting the Kids' Digital Playground: Datamining and the Privacy Debates in Children's Online Entertainment Sites</title><description>* Cool Hunting the Kids' Digital Playground: Datamining and the Privacy Debates in Children's Online Entertainment Sites (Citations: 2)

Grace Chung, Sara M. Grimes

...management,practices ,found ,within ,children’s online entertainment sites. although the increasing...provisions, explicating the administration of online gaming,community ,information ,infrastructures reveals...

Conference: Hawaii International Conference on System Sciences - HICSS , pp. 194a-194a, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7478-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7478_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:39:40">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11647704/kids-and-teens-e-privacy-at-stake</link><title>Kids' and teens' e-privacy at stake?</title><description>* Kids' and teens' e-privacy at stake?

Michel Walrave

...union (e.g. european data protection directive (95/46/ec)). institutions have made specific recommendations to protect children online (e.g. the belgian privacy...observed and recommendations applied, an online questionnaire was developed to analyse 294 belgian websites mainly targeting kids and teens. this analysis shows...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7478-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7478_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:40:57">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42685002/click-here-kids</link><title>Click here, Kids!</title><description>* Click here, Kids!

Xiaomei Cai, Xiaoquan Zhao

...were analyzed. results revealed an online advertising world for children that is both tempting and confusing. moreover, protection of children's privacy is not ideal on advertisers' websites. in all, online advertising raises challenging fairness and privacy issues. better protection of children on the web...

Journal: Journal of Children and Media , vol. 4, no. 2, pp. 135-154, 2010</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>