<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7479">dunbar number social networks</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:42:12" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7479-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7479_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:42:14">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/27631884/being-rational-or-aggressive-a-revisit-to-dunbar-s-number-in-online-social-networks</link><title>Being Rational or Aggressive? A Revisit to Dunbar's Number in Online Social Networks</title><description>* Being Rational or Aggressive? A Revisit to Dunbar's Number in Online Social Networks

Jichang Zhao, Junjie Wu, Guannan Liu, Ke Xu, Guoqing Chen

...revisit to the well-known dunbar's number in online social networks. our main research contributions are...affect the evolution of online social networks. finally, we show the potential use of our findings in viral marketing and privacy management in online social networks....

Journal: Computing Research Repository - CORR , vol. abs/1011.1, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7479-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7479_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:43:29">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6631962/defining-friendworks-communication-perspective-on-social-networks-types</link><title>Defining Friendworks; Communication perspective on Social networks Types</title><description>* Defining Friendworks; Communication perspective on Social networks Types

Orit Ben-Narush

...as a new term in social networks studies. a friendwork is a network of friends. it is a specific case of an interpersonal social network. naming this seemingly well known...focus on one segment within social networks stimulates a wider discussion regarding the different subgroups within social networks. other subgroups also discussed in...

Published in 2009.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7479-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7479_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:44:19">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/51101466/a-model-for-the-generation-of-social-network-graphs</link><title>A model for the generation of social network graphs</title><description>* A model for the generation of social network graphs

Marco Conti, Andrea Passarella, Fabio Pezzoni

...we present and evaluate a social network model which exploits fundamental results coming from the social anthropology literature. specifically, our model...average, known properties of ego networks such as the size, the composition and the hierarchical structure. keywords-social networks; ego networks; model; of the information (i...

Conference: Workshop on Wireless Mobile Multimedia - WOWMOM , 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7479-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7479_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:45:52">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/3758019/social-network-size-in-humans</link><title>Social network size in humans</title><description>* Social network size in humans (Citations: 92)

R. A. Hill, R. I. M. Dunbar

...this paper examines social network size in contemporary western society based on the exchange of christmas cards. maximum network size averaged 153.5 individuals, with a mean network size of 124.9 for...

Journal: Human Nature-an Interdisciplinary Biosocial Perspective - HUM NATURE-INT BIOSOC PERSPEC , vol. 14, no. 1, pp. 53-72, 2003</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7479-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7479_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:46:56">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/41069200/perspective-taking-and-memory-capacity-predict-social-network-size</link><title>Perspective-taking and memory capacity predict social network size</title><description>* Perspective-taking and memory capacity predict social network size (Citations: 20)

James Stiller, R. I. M. Dunbar

...human social networks typically consist of a hierarchically...two different levels within human social networks (support cliques and sympathy groups). we show that the size of an individual's support clique (the number of individual's in the...

Journal: Social Networks \- SOC NETWORKS , vol. 29, no. 1, pp. 93-104, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7479-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7479_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:47:46">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/49513643/ventromedial-prefrontal-volume-predicts-understanding-of-others-and-social-network-size</link><title>Ventromedial prefrontal volume predicts understanding of others and social network size</title><description>* Ventromedial prefrontal volume predicts understanding of others and social network size

Penelope A. Lewis, Roozbeh Rezaie, Rachel Brown, Neil Roberts, R. I. M. Dunbar

...belief states, is associated with social network size and that social group size is correlated with frontal lobe volume across primate species (the social brain hypothesis). given this, we...understanding of the constraints limiting social cognition and social network size in humans, as well...

Journal: Neuroimage , vol. 57, no. 4, pp. 1624-1629, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7479-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7479_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:48:26">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4264674/mobile-social-networking-based-on-mobile-internet-and-ubiquitous-web-services</link><title>Mobile Social Networking Based on Mobile Internet and Ubiquitous Web Services</title><description>* Mobile Social Networking Based on Mobile Internet and Ubiquitous Web Services (Citations: 2)

Yung Bok Kim

...for online social networking service in the ubiquitous computing and networking environment, a ubiquitous web service...domain names, especially for mobile social networking. as convenient user interface for accessing a web service for a social community, instead of long url...

Conference: Human-Computer Interaction - HCI , pp. 536-545, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7479-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7479_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:48:52">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40210987/social-network-theory-in-the-behavioural-sciences-potential-applications</link><title>Social network theory in the behavioural sciences: potential applications</title><description>* Social network theory in the behavioural sciences: potential applications (Citations: 50)

J. Krause, D. P. Croft, R. James

social network theory has made major contributions to our understanding of human social organisation but has found relatively...broad research areas where the networks approach could greatly enhance our understanding of social patterns and processes in animals. the network theory provides a quantitative framework...

Journal: Behavioral Ecology and Sociobiology - BEHAV ECOL SOCIOBIOL , vol. 62, no. 1, pp. 15-27, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7479-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7479_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:49:35">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4159059/social-networks-support-cliques-and-kinship</link><title>Social networks, support cliques, and kinship</title><description>* Social networks, support cliques, and kinship (Citations: 42)

Robin I. M. Dunbar, M. Spoors

...not differ in their total network size, but women have more females and more kin in their networks than men do. kin account for a significantly higher proportion of network members than would be expected by chance. the number of kin in the network increases in proportion to the...

Journal: Human Nature-an Interdisciplinary Biosocial Perspective - HUM NATURE-INT BIOSOC PERSPEC , vol. 6, no. 3, pp. 273-290, 1995</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7479-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7479_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:50:25">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5411450/marginal-contribution-reciprocity-and-equity-in-segregated-groups-bounded-rationality-and</link><title>Marginal contribution, reciprocity and equity in segregated groups: Bounded rationality and self-organization in social networks</title><description>* Marginal contribution, reciprocity and equity in segregated groups: Bounded rationality and self-organization in social networks (Citations: 4)

Alan Kirman, Sheri Markose, Simone Giansante, Paolo Pin

...we study the formation of social networks that are based on local...be altered to obtain segregated social networks as opposed to global components...

Journal: Journal of Economic Dynamics &amp; Control - J ECON DYN CONTROL , vol. 31, no. 6, pp. 2085-2107, 2007</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>