<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7480">phd comics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:51:40" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7480-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7480_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:51:41">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10300049/where-do-new-us-trained-science-engineering-phds-come-from</link><title>Where Do New US-Trained Science-Engineering PhDs come from?</title><description>* Where Do New US-Trained Science-Engineering PhDs come from? (Citations: 9)

Richard B. Freeman, Emily Jin, Chia-Yu Shen

...us trained science and engineering phds changed markedly between the late 1960s-1970s to the 1990s-early 2000s. in 1966, 71% of science and engineering phd graduates were us-born males...most of the growth in phds was in less prestigious smaller doctorate programs. the undergraduate origins of bachelor's obtaining science and engineering phds changed only modestly among us...

Published in 2004.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7480-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7480_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:52:58">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10901092/in-search-of-appropriate-measurement-the-case-of-case-studies-in-preparation-of-phd-dissertation</link><title>IN SEARCH OF APPROPRIATE MEASUREMENT: THE CASE OF CASE STUDIES In preparation of PhD dissertation work "Where the Wings Come From? Emerging countries in the structure of the global aerospace industry</title><description>* IN SEARCH OF APPROPRIATE MEASUREMENT: THE CASE OF CASE STUDIES In preparation of PhD dissertation work "Where the Wings Come From? Emerging countries in the structure of the global aerospace industry

Dániel Vértesy

...and it is perfectly understandable. phd research is no exception to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7480-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7480_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:53:57">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50835899/introduction-of-ethical-subject-in-re-designed-phd-level-computer-education-curriculum-a-teaching</link><title>Introduction of Ethical Subject in Re-designed PhD-level Computer Education Curriculum: A Teaching Experience Driven in Thailand</title><description>* Introduction of Ethical Subject in Re-designed PhD-level Computer Education Curriculum: A Teaching Experience Driven in Thailand

Nidapan Sureerattanan

...faculty of technical education. almost phd students come from teacher profession. human resource...development of ethical subject in phd-level computer education curriculum at...

Conference: International Conference on Computer Technology and Development - ICCTD , 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7480-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7480_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:55:27">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/11444307/monolingual-monologue-regional-issues-of-professional-communication-from-pacific-health-dialog</link><title>Monolingual monologue: regional issues of professional communication from Pacific Health Dialog</title><description>* Monolingual monologue: regional issues of professional communication from Pacific Health Dialog

SITALEKI A. FINAU, GREGORY J. DEVER, ESETA FINAU, VICTOR YANO

...the pacific health dialog (phd) is a journal of community health and clinical medicine with a pacific. focus. a analysis of all nine phd issues from 1994 to 1998...the expenditure and the balance comes from a 'labour of love' from many people. despite this, phd continues to grow. the development of phd has demonstrated that a partici...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7480-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7480_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:57:13">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5216158/phd-job-market-professional-trajectories-and-incentives-during-the-phd</link><title>PhD job market: professional trajectories and incentives during the PhD</title><description>* PhD job market: professional trajectories and incentives during the PhD (Citations: 51)

V. Mangematin

...students to invest in a phd and for phd supervisors to hire phd students. after a theoretical analysis...the same criteria when it comes to recruiting phd graduates? the analysis shows that trajectories are not flexible and that phd graduates have to choose a...

Journal: Research Policy - RES POLICY , vol. 29, no. 6, pp. 741-756, 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7480-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7480_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:57:46">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/12198219/the-author-of-four-chapbooks-closed-histories-falling-forward-another-random-heart-and-that-we</link><title>the author of four chapbooks: Closed Histories, Falling Forward, Another Random Heart, and That We Come to a Consensus, a collaboration with the poet Noah Eli Gordon. She is adjunct faculty at Naropa University teaching prose workshops and literature seminars. Veglahn is also a PhD candidate at Denver University and is the current Associate Editor of the Denver Quarterly</title><description>* the author of four chapbooks: Closed Histories, Falling Forward, Another Random Heart, and That We Come to a Consensus, a collaboration with the poet Noah Eli Gordon. She is adjunct faculty at Naropa University teaching prose workshops and literature seminars. Veglahn is also a PhD candidate at Denver University and is the current Associate Editor of the Denver Quarterly

Keith Abbott, Reed Bye, Sara Veglahn</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7480-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7480_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:58:46">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/14257652/let-s-face-it-it-s-not-all-that-difficult-to-start-a-fitness-routine-after-all-most-of-us-have</link><title>Let's face it: it's not all that difficult to start a fitness routine. After all, most of us have done it more than once. The trouble, of course, comes with sticking with it. All too often, our initial enthusiasm and energy wanes, we get distracted by other things going on in our lives, or we don't think we're seeing results quickly enough -- and we throw in the towel. Yet many people do manage to hang in there, and would no sooner skip their regular workout than their morning shower. What's their secret? A recent study by researcher Diane Klein, PhD, shed some light on the subject. Long-term exercisers (who had been working out for an average of 13 years) were asked to rank what motivated them to keep up with their regimes. Their answers might surprise you. The exercisers were not as concerned with powerful pecs and awesome abs as they were with feeling good and being healthy. Here's how the study participants ranked their motivators</title><description>* Let's face it: it's not all that difficult to start a fitness routine. After all, most of us have done it more than once. The trouble, of course, comes with sticking with it. All too often, our initial enthusiasm and energy wanes, we get distracted by other things going on in our lives, or we don't think we're seeing results quickly enough -- and we throw in the towel. Yet many people do manage to hang in there, and would no sooner skip their regular workout than their morning shower. What's their secret? A recent study by researcher Diane Klein, PhD, shed some light on the subject. Long-term exercisers (who had been working out for an average of 13 years) were asked to rank what motivated them to keep up with their regimes. Their answers might surprise you. The exercisers were not as concerned with powerful pecs and awesome abs as they were with feeling good and being healthy. Here's how the study participants ranked their motivators

Leanna Skarnulis, Louise Chang

• Fitness • Feelings of well-being • Pep and energy • Enjoyment of the exercise • Making exercise a priority • Sleeping better • Feeling alert • Being relaxed • Weight management • Appearance So, once you have your priorities in the right place, how can you become one of the fitness faithful? WebMD has compiled 10 tips for ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7480-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7480_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:00:00">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42857550/book-review-a-century-of-doctorates-data-analyses-of-growth-and-change-u-s-phd-s-their</link><title>Book Review:A Century of Doctorates: Data Analyses of Growth and Change: U. S. PhD's--Their Numbers, Origins, Characteristics, and the Institutions from Which They Come National Research Council, Lindsey R. Harmon</title><description>* Book Review:A Century of Doctorates: Data Analyses of Growth and Change: U. S. PhD's--Their Numbers, Origins, Characteristics, and the Institutions from Which They Come National Research Council, Lindsey R. Harmon

P. Thomas Carroll

Journal: Isis , vol. 71, no. 2, 1980</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7480-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7480_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:00:36">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/36843480/the-hunt-job-hunting-for-the-phd-psychologist</link><title>The hunt: Job hunting for the PhD psychologist</title><description>* The hunt: Job hunting for the PhD psychologist

Baron Perlman

...also exhilarating experiences in a phd psychologist's life comes when he or she searches...

Journal: American Psychologist - AMER PSYCHOL , vol. 31, no. 4, pp. 298-302, 1976</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7480-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7480_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:01:30">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10387447/information-knowledge-and-social-networks-is-a-new-buzzword-coming-up-paper-to-be-presented-for</link><title>Information, knowledge and social networks: is a new buzzword coming up?♣ Paper to be presented for the DRUID PhD Conference, Aalborg, Denmark January 16 -18, 2003</title><description>* Information, knowledge and social networks: is a new buzzword coming up?♣ Paper to be presented for the DRUID PhD Conference, Aalborg, Denmark January 16 -18, 2003

Lorenzo Cassi

The analysis of social networks has recently become a central issue in industrial organisation. A growing literature has started to show the importance of social networks in the economy, above all to explain labour mobility and the actual production of innovation. I argue that using such concepts and analytical tools requires a deep understanding of what is meant by knowledge ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>