<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7482">popular twitter stars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:08:01" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7482-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7482_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:08:02">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6607453/ranking-mechanisms-in-twitter-like-forums</link><title>Ranking mechanisms in twitter-like forums</title><description>* Ranking mechanisms in twitter-like forums (Citations: 5)

Anish Das Sarma, Atish Das Sarma, Sreenivas Gollapudi, Rina Panigrahy

...reviews such as thumb and star ratings. we compare mechanisms where...ity (5), which is a twitter-like forum but items (i.e., tweets in twitter) are rated by using comparisons...

Conference: Web Search and Data Mining - WSDM , pp. 21-30, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7482-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7482_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:09:15">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39248296/topical-semantics-of-twitter-links</link><title>Topical semantics of twitter links</title><description>* Topical semantics of twitter links

Michael J. Welch, Uri Schonfeld, Dan He, Junghoo Cho

twitter, a micro-blogging platform with...focused on the "follow" relationship. twitter's data offers additional implicit...

Conference: Web Search and Data Mining - WSDM , pp. 327-336, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7482-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7482_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:10:54">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50924324/micro-blog-social-network-analysis-digu-network-as-an-example</link><title>Micro-Blog Social Network Analysis: "Digu" Network as an Example</title><description>* Micro-Blog Social Network Analysis: "Digu" Network as an Example

Che Li-mei, Wei Yun-gang, Sun Bo, Qiu Qian, Zhan Nai-xin

...research hotspot. micro-blogs like twitter, taotao, digu are very popular large-scale communication social networks...lot. finally we discuss the "star effect" caused by star nodes....

Conference: International Symposium on Information Engineering and Electronic Commerce - IEEC , 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7482-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7482_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:11:41">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/51972715/engaging-the-public-in-the-citizen-science-globe-at-night-campaign</link><title>Engaging the Public in the Citizen Science GLOBE at Night Campaign</title><description>* Engaging the Public in the Citizen Science GLOBE at Night Campaign

Constance E. Walker, R. T. Sparks, S. M. Pompea

...the emphasis in the international star-hunting campaign, globe at night...to promote the campaign via popular social media, globe at night created facebook and twitter pages. to increase participation in...

Published in 2011.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7482-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7482_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:12:06">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39364090/practical-recommendations-on-crawling-online-social-networks</link><title>Practical Recommendations on Crawling Online Social Networks</title><description>* Practical Recommendations on Crawling Online Social Networks

Minas Gjoka, Maciej Kurant, Carter T. Butts, Athina Markopoulou

Our goal in this paper is to develop a practical framework for obtaining a uniform sample of users in an online social network (OSN) by crawling its social graph. Such a sample allows to estimate any user property and some topological properties as well. To this end, ﬁrst, we consider and compare several candidate crawling techniques. Two approaches that can ...

Journal: IEEE Journal on Selected Areas in Communications - JSAC , vol. 29, no. 9, pp. 1872-1892, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7482-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7482_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:12:48">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39266436/two-of-a-kind-or-the-ratings-game-adaptive-pairwise-preferences-and-latent-factor-models</link><title>Two of a Kind or the Ratings Game? Adaptive Pairwise Preferences and Latent Factor Models</title><description>* Two of a Kind or the Ratings Game? Adaptive Pairwise Preferences and Latent Factor Models

Suhrid Balakrishnan, Sumit Chopra

While latent factor models are built using ratings data, which is typically assumed static, the ability to incorporate different kinds of subsequent user feedback is an important asset. For instance, the user might want to provide additional information to the system in order to improve his personal recommendations. To this end, we examine a novel scheme for efficiently learning (or ...

Conference: IEEE International Conference on Data Mining - ICDM , pp. 725-730, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7482-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7482_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:13:34">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48808300/role-of-context-awareness-for-demand-response-mechanisms</link><title>Role of Context-Awareness for Demand Response Mechanisms</title><description>* Role of Context-Awareness for Demand Response Mechanisms

Pari Delir Haghighi, Shonali Krishnaswamy

Recently due to major changes in the structure of electricity industry and the rising costs of power generation, many countries have realized the potential and benefits of smart metering systems and demand response programs in balancing between the supply and the demand. DR mechanisms are capable of controlling the user energy consumption according to load conditions and providing effective energy ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>