<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7483">facebook paying?</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:14:42" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7483-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7483_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:14:43">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39231891/are-separate-interfaces-inherently-unequal-an-evaluation-with-blind-users-of-the-usability-of-two</link><title>Are separate interfaces inherently unequal?: an evaluation with blind users of the usability of two interfaces for a social networking platform</title><description>* Are separate interfaces inherently unequal?: an evaluation with blind users of the usability of two interfaces for a social networking platform

Brian Wentz, Jonathan Lazar

...has also been suggested by facebook and anecdotal user comments that the mobile interface (hereafter referred to as "facebook mobile") for the application is...interface (hereafter referred to as "facebook desktop") for individuals who use screen readers to access the facebook interface from their computers. this...

Published in 2011.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7483-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7483_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:15:51">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/56920666/howdy-pardner-on-free-to-play-sociability-and-rhythm-design-in-frontierville</link><title>Howdy pardner!: on free-to-play, sociability and rhythm design in FrontierVille</title><description>* Howdy pardner!: on free-to-play, sociability and rhythm design in FrontierVille

Heikki Tyni, Olli Sotamaa, Saara Toivonen

...popularity social games played on facebook have so far gained relatively little interest among academic game researchers. a close reading of the facebook game frontierville aims to provide...examines how also the non-paying players are affected by the...

Published in 2011.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7483-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7483_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:16:49">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39232888/theatre-at-my-desk</link><title>Theatre at my desk</title><description>* Theatre at my desk

Sheetal Chaudhary, Ankit Jhunjhunwala, Swaraj Acharya, Snehal Bodke, Rohan Dalvi

...server which would verify the paying details and start streaming the...users to automatically update their facebook and twitter status. this status...

Published in 2010.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7483-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7483_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:17:25">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57536970/literacy-lite-in-barbiegirls</link><title>Literacy‐lite in BarbieGirls</title><description>* Literacy‐lite in BarbieGirls

Victoria Carrington, Katherine Hodgetts

...such as bebo.com and facebook, virtual worlds have emerged as...more often and staying longer. paying attention to the kinds of...

Journal: British Journal of Sociology of Education - BRIT J SOCIOL EDUC , vol. 31, no. 6, pp. 671-682, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7483-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7483_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:18:30">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42562396/civic-engagement-pedagogy-and-information-technology-on-web-sites-for-youth</link><title>Civic Engagement, Pedagogy, and Information Technology on Web Sites for Youth</title><description>* Civic Engagement, Pedagogy, and Information Technology on Web Sites for Youth (Citations: 9)

Christine Bachen, Chad Raphael, Kathleen-M. Lynn, Kristen McKee, Jessica Philippi

...scholars of political socialization are paying increasing attention to how the...

Journal: Political Communication - POLIT COMMUN , vol. 25, no. 3, pp. 290-310, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7483-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7483_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:19:10">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4198609/social-browsing-&amp;-information-filtering-in-social-media</link><title>Social Browsing &amp; Information Filtering in Social Media</title><description>* Social Browsing &amp; Information Filtering in Social Media (Citations: 1)

Kristina Lerman

...sites (e.g., linkedin and facebook), which allow users to articulate...

Journal: Computing Research Repository - CORR , vol. abs/0710.5, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7483-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7483_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:20:36">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39327162/paradoxical-empowerment-of</link><title>Paradoxical empowerment of</title><description>* Paradoxical empowerment of

Serge Proulx, Lorna Heaton, Mary Jane Kwok Choon, Mélanie Millette

...approach with two case studies: facebook and telabotanica, a platform for...

Journal: New Review of Hypermedia and Multimedia / Hypermedia , vol. 17, no. 1, pp. 9-29, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7483-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7483_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:22:20">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39257223/social-influence-on-being-a-pay-user-in-freemium-based-social-networks</link><title>Social Influence on Being a Pay User in Freemium-based Social Networks</title><description>* Social Influence on Being a Pay User in Freemium-based Social Networks

Hao Wang, Alvin Chin

...connections and interactions with people paying for premium services may, to...

Conference: Advanced Information Networking and Applications - AINA , pp. 526-533, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7483-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7483_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:22:45">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6056757/information-technology-capabilities-for-digital-social-networks</link><title>Information Technology Capabilities for Digital Social Networks</title><description>* Information Technology Capabilities for Digital Social Networks (Citations: 1)

Camille Grange, Izak Benbasat

This paper contributes to the evolving body of knowledge pertaining to the study of digitally-enabled social networks, their usage, and their effects on people, organization, and society. We review the literature on social networks and develop a typology which distinguishes four aspects of digital social networks usage: (i) building and sustaining the network, (ii) observing the network, (iii), extracting ...

Conference: IEEE International Conference on Computational Science and Engineering - CSE , pp. 1054-1059, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7483-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7483_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:23:48">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/4711114/monetizing-the-internet-surely-there-must-be-something-other-than-advertising</link><title>Monetizing the Internet: Surely There Must be Something other than Advertising</title><description>* Monetizing the Internet: Surely There Must be Something other than Advertising (Citations: 1)

Eric K. Clemons

Almost all attempts to monetize internet applications targeted at individuals to date have focused on natural extensions of traditional media or traditional retailing. Most are either some form of consumer-focused advertising or of consumer-focused eCommerce. And yet the net is far more powerful and liberating than traditional media on the one hand, and far more liberating and thus ...

Conference: Hawaii International Conference on System Sciences - HICSS , pp. 1-10, 2009</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>