<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7489">make skull mask</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:48:10" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7489-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7489_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:48:11">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/54026921/robust-fast-automatic-skull-stripping-of-mri-t2-data</link><title>Robust fast automatic skull stripping of MRI-T2 data</title><description>* Robust fast automatic skull stripping of MRI-T2 data

Srinivasan Rajagopalan, Ronald A. Karwoski, Richard Robb

...images before sharing them. this makes the non-trivial skull stripping process all the more...techniques to derive the brain mask. masking the original t2 image with this brain mask strips the skull. by standardizing the intensity of...

Published in 2005.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7489-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7489_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:48:54">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/51544717/a-skull-segmentation-method-for-brain-mr-images-based-on-multiscale-bilateral-filtering-scheme</link><title>A skull segmentation method for brain MR images based on multiscale bilateral filtering scheme</title><description>* A skull segmentation method for brain MR images based on multiscale bilateral filtering scheme

Xiaofeng Yang, Baowei Fei

...automatic segmentation method for the skull on brain mr images for...reciprocal binary sinogram of the skull is obtained for the reconstruction of the skull image. we use the filtered...

Published in 2010.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7489-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7489_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:49:25">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5083951/a-hybrid-approach-to-the-skull-stripping-problem-in-mri</link><title>A hybrid approach to the skull stripping problem in MRI</title><description>* A hybrid approach to the skull stripping problem in MRI (Citations: 207)

F. Ségonne, A. M. Dale, E. Busa, M. Glessner, D. Salat, H. K. Hahn, B. Fischla

...we present a novel skull-stripping algorithm based on a...a smooth surface to the masked volume, allowing the incorporation of geometric constraints into the skull-stripping procedure. a statistical atlas...

Journal: Neuroimage , vol. 22, no. 3, pp. 1060-1075, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7489-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7489_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:50:19">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/13258327/combining-explicitly-mask-image-with-voxel-based-morphometry-for-improving-0-35t-functional-mri</link><title>Combining Explicitly Mask Image with Voxel-Based Morphometry for Improving 0.35T Functional MRI Data Analysis</title><description>* Combining Explicitly Mask Image with Voxel-Based Morphometry for Improving 0.35T Functional MRI Data Analysis

Ping Yang, Hongyu Guo, Yanfa He

...be eliminated by combining explicitly mask image with voxel-based morphometry...surface model as a explicitly mask image, constructs analysis mask and adds it to the...

Conference: International Conference on Image and Graphics - ICIG , pp. 712-715, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7489-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7489_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:51:02">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5702421/the-role-of-polysemy-in-masked-semantic-and-translation-priming</link><title>The role of polysemy in masked semantic and translation priming</title><description>* The role of polysemy in masked semantic and translation priming (Citations: 43)

Matthew Finkbeiner, Kenneth Forster, Janet Nicol, Kumiko Nakamurab

...asymmetry exists in the bilingual masked priming literature in which lexical decision is used: namely, masked primes in the dominant language...this task difference, finding robust masked l2-l1 translation priming in...

Journal: Journal of Memory and Language - J MEM LANG , vol. 51, no. 1, pp. 1-22, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7489-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7489_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:51:51">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/31891323/nonlinear-geometric-warping-of-the-mask-image-a-new-method-for-reducing-misregistration-artifacts</link><title>Nonlinear Geometric Warping of the Mask Image: A New Method for Reducing Misregistration Artifacts in Digital Subtraction Angiography</title><description>* Nonlinear Geometric Warping of the Mask Image: A New Method for Reducing Misregistration Artifacts in Digital Subtraction Angiography (Citations: 5)

Nobushige Hayashi, Toyohiko Sakai, Manabu Kitagawa, Rika Inagaki, Norihiro Sadato, Yasushi Ishii, Yasuhiro Nishimoto, Masato Tanaka, Tetsuya Fukushima, Hiroyuki Komuro, Hisakazu Ogura, Hidenori Kobayashihttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=31891323&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=make skull mask

...fully automatic computerized program. after making differential images with a lapracian...the corresponding roi of the mask image searching for the best position to match itself. each pixel of the mask image was shifted individually following...

Journal: Cardiovascular and Interventional Radiology - CARDIOVASC INTERVEN RADIOL , vol. 21, no. 2, pp. 138-141, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7489-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7489_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:53:26">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/31432323/improve-the-management-of-patients-with-skull-bone-metastases-by-means-of-helical-tomotherapy</link><title>Improve the management of patients with skull bone metastases by means of helical tomotherapy</title><description>* Improve the management of patients with skull bone metastases by means of helical tomotherapy

C. Chargari, Y. M. Kirova, S. Zefkili, F. Campana

...particularly in patients with multiple skull metastases. for those patients, conventional...breast cancer patient with multiple skull bone metastases. in october 2007...

Journal: Supportive Care in Cancer - SUPPORT CARE CANCER , vol. 17, no. 6, pp. 613-615, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7489-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7489_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:54:23">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/60583799/nonlinear-geometric-warping-of-the-mask-image-a-new-method-for-reducing-misregistration-artifacts</link><title>Nonlinear Geometric Warping of the Mask Image: A New Method for Reducing Misregistration Artifacts in Digital Subtraction Angiography</title><description>* Nonlinear Geometric Warping of the Mask Image: A New Method for Reducing Misregistration Artifacts in Digital Subtraction Angiography

Nobushige Hayashi, Toyohiko Sakai, Manabu Kitagawa, Rika Inagaki, Norihiro Sadato, Yasushi Ishii, Yasuhiro Nishimoto, Masato Tanaka, Tetsuya Fukushima, Hiroyuki Komuro, Hisakazu Ogura, Hidenori Kobayashihttp://academic.research.microsoft.com/io.ashx?type=5&amp;id=60583799&amp;selfId1=-1&amp;selfId2=-1&amp;maxNumber=12&amp;query=make skull mask

...fully automatic computerized program. after making differential images with a lapracian...the corresponding roi of the mask image searching for the best position to match itself. each pixel of the mask image was shifted individually following...

Journal: Cardiovascular and Interventional Radiology - CARDIOVASC INTERVEN RADIOL , vol. 21, no. 2, pp. 138-141, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7489-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7489_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:55:00">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/5457969/skull-stripping-magnetic-resonance-brain-images-using-a-model-based-level-set</link><title>Skull-stripping magnetic resonance brain images using a model-based level set</title><description>* Skull-stripping magnetic resonance brain images using a model-based level set (Citations: 30)

Audrey H. Zhuang, Daniel J. Valentino, Arthur W. Toga

...images, commonly referred to as skull stripping, is an important image...the mls algorithm provides robust skull-stripping results, making it a promising tool for...

Journal: Neuroimage , vol. 32, no. 1, pp. 79-92, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7489-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7489_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:56:38">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6326953/the-impact-of-skull-stripping-and-radio-frequency-bias-correction-on-grey-matter-segmentation-for</link><title>The impact of skull-stripping and radio-frequency bias correction on grey-matter segmentation for voxel-based morphometry</title><description>* The impact of skull-stripping and radio-frequency bias correction on grey-matter segmentation for voxel-based morphometry (Citations: 7)

Julio Acosta-Cabronero, Guy B. Williams, João M. S. Pereira, George Pengas, Peter J. Nestorb

...evaluates the application of (i) skull-stripping methods (hybrid watershed algorithm...further assessed using artificial-lesion masks applied to 10 healthy controls...

Journal: Neuroimage , 2007</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>