<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7491">convert wav mp3 program</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:01:28" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7491-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7491_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:01:28">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/3557815/pdf-to-mp3-conversion-an-alternative-method-to-reading-academic-papers</link><title>PDF to MP3 conversion: an alternative method to reading academic papers</title><description>* PDF to MP3 conversion: an alternative method to reading academic papers

Dorian Miller

...the pdf to mp3 project provides alternative access to academic documents for the blind, weak readers and others. using an mp3 player the person listens to...software performs the pdf to mp3 conversion using the python programming language and third party components...

Published in 2003.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7491-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7491_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:02:59">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/32335579/evaluation-of-the-mixing-point-in-tinnitus-sound-therapy-by-a-psychoacoustic-matching-protocol-with</link><title>Evaluation of the Mixing Point in Tinnitus Sound Therapy by a Psychoacoustic Matching Protocol with a Digital Tinnitus Evaluation System</title><description>* Evaluation of the Mixing Point in Tinnitus Sound Therapy by a Psychoacoustic Matching Protocol with a Digital Tinnitus Evaluation System (Citations: 1)

Chii-Yuan Huang, Jiunn-Liang Wu, Chun-Chou Cheng, Yung-Ji Sher, Kao-Chi Chung

Directive counseling and sound therapy have been reported to effectively alleviate tinnitus suffering. Without objective evaluation, researchers doubt the real effect of sound therapy. This study was designed to evaluate the frequency and intensity of the theoretical ‘mixing point’ (MP) in sound therapy and to investigate its relationship with the minimal masking level (MML) of tinnitus. The tinnitus tones of ...

Journal: Orl-journal for Oto-rhino-laryngology and Its Related Specialties - ORL-J OTO-RHINO-LARYNGOL , vol. 68, no. 2, pp. 110-114, 2006</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>