<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7493">islam discussions social media</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:14:48" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7493-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7493_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:14:49">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/13996184/gender-difference-analysis-of-political-web-forums-an-experiment-on-an-international-islamic</link><title>Gender difference analysis of political web forums: An experiment on an international islamic women's forum</title><description>* Gender difference analysis of political web forums: An experiment on an international islamic women's forum

Yulei Zhang, Yan Dang, Hsinchun Chen

...as an important type of social media, the political web forum has become a major communication channel for people to discuss and debate political, cultural and social issues. although the internet has...

Conference: Intelligence and Security Informatics , pp. 61-64, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7493-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7493_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:15:37">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57338240/a-us-academic-library-promotes-pluralism-with-technology</link><title>A US academic library promotes pluralism with technology</title><description>* A US academic library promotes pluralism with technology

Deborah J. Margolis

...was found near the local islamic center in september 2010. design...codes, a public service announcement, social media, web features, and an audio...

Journal: Library Hi Tech News , vol. 28, no. 6, pp. 25-27, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7493-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7493_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:16:35">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42497930/religious-education-conflict-and-diversity-an-exploration-of-young-children-s-perceptions-of-islam</link><title>Religious education, conflict and diversity: an exploration of young children’s perceptions of Islam</title><description>* Religious education, conflict and diversity: an exploration of young children’s perceptions of Islam

Lynn Revell

...in english primary school perceive islam through discussion of islam in the media. the research suggests that pupils are aware of islam as a world religion and...racist or prejudiced views about islam many pupils appeared to perceive islam and muslims as ‘foreign’ and...

Journal: Educational Studies - EDUC STUD , vol. 36, no. 2, pp. 207-215, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7493-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7493_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:18:10">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57781629/islam-and-muslims-in-u-s-public-schools-since-september-11-2001</link><title>Islam and Muslims in U.S. Public Schools Since September 11, 2001</title><description>* Islam and Muslims in U.S. Public Schools Since September 11, 2001

Liz Jackson

...are represented in the mass media in recent years, there has been little exploration of the way muslims and islam are discussed in u.s. public schools. this article considers how muslims and islam are represented in educational standards...

Journal: Religious Education , vol. 106, no. 2, pp. 162-180, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7493-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7493_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:19:41">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57718038/media-institutions-news-organizations-and-the-journalistic-social-role-worldwide-a</link><title>Media Institutions, News Organizations, and the Journalistic Social Role Worldwide: A Cross-National and Cross-Organizational Study of Codes of Ethics</title><description>* Media Institutions, News Organizations, and the Journalistic Social Role Worldwide: A Cross-National and Cross-Organizational Study of Codes of Ethics (Citations: 1)

Itai Himelboim, Yehiel Limor

...journalists and media organizations are often criticized by politicians, the public, and media scholars for not fulfilling their...94 countries to identify journalistic social role as perceived by media organizations. it identified and compared journalistic social roles toward society and toward...

Journal: Mass Communication and Society - MASS COMMUN SOC , vol. 14, no. 1, pp. 71-92, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7493-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7493_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:20:49">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40106534/minority-leadership-science-symbols-and-the-media-the-belgian-islam-debate-and-its-relevance</link><title>Minority leadership, science, symbols, and the media: The Belgian Islam debate and its relevance for other countries in Europe</title><description>* Minority leadership, science, symbols, and the media: The Belgian Islam debate and its relevance for other countries in Europe (Citations: 5)

Johan Leman

...this article discusses the processes that occurred in...the academic community, the great social symbolic events, and the media. it concludes with the political...

Journal: Journal of International Migration and Integration / Revue De L'integration Et De La Migration Internationale , vol. 1, no. 3, pp. 351-372, 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7493-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7493_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:21:19">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42370520/unveiled-sentiments-gendered-islamophobia-and-experiences-of-veiling-among-muslim-girls-in-a</link><title>Unveiled Sentiments: Gendered Islamophobia and Experiences of Veiling among Muslim Girls in a Canadian Islamic School</title><description>* Unveiled Sentiments: Gendered Islamophobia and Experiences of Veiling among Muslim Girls in a Canadian Islamic School (Citations: 12)

Jasmin Zine

...muslim women attending a canadian islamic school speak to the contested notion of gender identity in islam. the narratives situate their various articulations of islamic womanhood in ways that both...who attended a gender-segregated islamic high school in toronto, this discussion allows a deeper understanding of...

Journal: Equity &amp; Excellence in Education , vol. 39, no. 3, pp. 239-252, 2006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7493-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7493_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:22:08">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57591678/vive-la-grande-famille-des-m-dias-tunisiens-media-reform-authoritarian-resilience-and-societal</link><title>‘Vive la grande famille des médias tunisiens’ Media reform, authoritarian resilience and societal responses in Tunisia</title><description>* ‘Vive la grande famille des médias tunisiens’ Media reform, authoritarian resilience and societal responses in Tunisia

Rikke Hostrup Haugbølle, Francesco Cavatorta

...permitted the arrival on the media scene of new social voices and actors that never had the opportunity to discuss taboo topics and this transforms public debate. while political discussions were excluded and political pluralism absent, the new private media managed to challenge previously prevailing...

Journal: The Journal of North African Studies , vol. 17, no. 1, pp. 97-112, 2012</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7493-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7493_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:23:10">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57589217/vive-la-grande-famille-des-m-dias-tunisiens-media-reform-authoritarian-resilience-and-societal</link><title>‘Vive la grande famille des médias tunisiens’ Media reform, authoritarian resilience and societal responses in Tunisia</title><description>* ‘Vive la grande famille des médias tunisiens’ Media reform, authoritarian resilience and societal responses in Tunisia

Rikke Hostrup Haugbølle, Francesco Cavatorta

...permitted the arrival on the media scene of new social voices and actors that never had the opportunity to discuss taboo topics and this transforms public debate. while political discussions were excluded and political pluralism absent, the new private media managed to challenge previously prevailing...

Journal: The Journal of North African Studies , vol. ahead-of-p, no. ahead-of-p, pp. 1-16, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7493-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7493_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:23:58">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42672660/listening-across-difference-media-and-multiculturalism-beyond-the-politics-of-voice</link><title>Listening across difference: Media and multiculturalism beyond the politics of voice</title><description>* Listening across difference: Media and multiculturalism beyond the politics of voice (Citations: 5)

Tanja Dreher

...research and policy on media and cultural diversity routinely emphasize speaking or ‘voice’, whether in mainstream, community or diaspora media. an established tradition also examines...racialization. this paper extends these discussions to focus on questions of ‘listening’. attention to listening provokes important questions about media and multiculturalism: how do media enable or constrain listening across...

Journal: Continuum-journal of Media &amp; Cultural Studies - CONTINUUM-J MEDIA CULT STUD , vol. 23, no. 4, pp. 445-458, 2009</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>