<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7494">cartoons festival</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:25:11" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7494-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7494_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:25:12">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57843023/learning-to-labor-with-handy-manny-immigration-politics-and-the-world-of-work-in-a-children-s</link><title>Learning to labor with Handy Manny: immigration politics and the world of work in a children's cartoon</title><description>* Learning to labor with Handy Manny: immigration politics and the world of work in a children's cartoon

Sean Brayton

...handy manny, a popular disney cartoon featuring a latino handyman. specifically...latina/o signifiers like food, festivals, and a spanish vocabulary, it...

Journal: Social Semiotics , vol. ahead-of-p, no. ahead-of-p, pp. 1-17, 2012</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7494-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7494_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:25:45">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/12922439/situating-machinima-in-the-new-mediascape</link><title>Situating Machinima in the New Mediascape</title><description>* Situating Machinima in the New Mediascape (Citations: 3)

Leo Berkeley

...at the 2005 machinima film festival in new york - i have...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7494-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7494_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:26:20">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42734021/after-effects-or-velvet-revolution</link><title>AFTER EFFECTS, OR VELVET REVOLUTION</title><description>* AFTER EFFECTS, OR VELVET REVOLUTION (Citations: 2)

Lev Manovich

This article is a first part of the series devoted to the analysis of the new hybrid visual language of moving images that emerged during the period 1993–1998. Today this language dominates our visual culture. It can be seen in commercials, music videos, motion graphics, TV graphics, and other types of short non-narrative films and moving image sequences ...

Journal: Artifact: Journal of Virtual Design - Artifact , vol. 1, no. 2, pp. 67-75, 2007</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7494-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7494_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:26:54">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/230414/real-face-communication-in-a-virtual-world</link><title>Real Face Communication in a Virtual World</title><description>* Real Face Communication in a Virtual World (Citations: 2)

Won-sook Lee, Elwin Lee, Nadia Magnenat-thalmann

This paper describes an efficient method to make an individual face for animation from several possible inputs and how to use this result for a realistic talking head communication in a virtual world. We present a method to reconstruct 3D facial model from two orthogonal pictures taken from front and side views. The method is based on extracting features from ...

Conference: Virtual Worlds - VW , pp. 1-13, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7494-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7494_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:28:08">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57563159/the-mediatisation-of-religion-theorising-religion-media-and-social-change</link><title>The mediatisation of religion: Theorising religion, media and social change</title><description>* The mediatisation of religion: Theorising religion, media and social change

Stig Hjarvard

Drawing on recent advances in mediatisation theory, the article presents a theoretical framework for understanding the increased interplay between religion and media. The media have become an important, if not primary, source of information about religious issues, and religious information and experiences become moulded according to the demands of popular media genres. As a cultural and social environment, the media ...

Journal: Culture and Religion , vol. 12, no. 2, pp. 119-135, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7494-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7494_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:28:40">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39782499/climatic-change-communication-changes-over-this-journal-s-first-century</link><title>Climatic change: communication changes over this journal’s first ‘century’</title><description>* Climatic change: communication changes over this journal’s first ‘century’

Ann Henderson-Sellers

Over the century of ‘Climatic Change’ volumes and the 33 years that they span the climate has changed. Here I consider the challenge of interdisciplinary communication to which the first 99 volumes of this journal are dedicated. Have we succeeded and have climatic change researchers shared findings with a broader audience? If this journal has been successful, should the editorial board ...

Journal: Climatic Change , vol. 100, no. 1, pp. 215-227, 2010</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>