<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7496">why IEEE member</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:38:54" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7496-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7496_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:38:56">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/908241/analysis-of-views-of-acm-and-ieee-members-concerning-professionalism-in-the-computing-field</link><title>Analysis of views of ACM and IEEE members concerning professionalism in the computing field</title><description>* Analysis of views of ACM and IEEE members concerning professionalism in the computing field

John D. Longhill

...professional societies. information from the members of these two organizations concerning their views on professionalism in the computer field should be useful in determining why there is still not the...the opinions of acm and ieee members concerning aspects of professionalism in...

Conference: ACM Southeast Regional Conference , pp. 235-239, 1982</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7496-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7496_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:39:50">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50131472/electronic-access-what-ieee-members-say-they-want</link><title>Electronic access: what IEEE members say they want</title><description>* Electronic access: what IEEE members say they want (Citations: 1)

F. T. Andrews, H. Shein, P. Holst

...on a controlled basis for members of technical associations, such as the ieee. the question is, what is it that members want enough to actually use...these results provide insights into why actual usage of online publications has been far less than expected. for example, there are some clues that members want access to more information...

Conference: Proceedings. Socioeconomic Dimensions of Electronic Publishing Workshop - SEDEP , 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7496-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7496_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:40:55">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/27041169/linking-technologists-and-humanitarians</link><title>Linking technologists and humanitarians</title><description>* Linking technologists and humanitarians (Citations: 1)

KARL PERUSICH, HAROLD TEPPER, J. R. B. de Marca, RUSS LEFEVRE, RICHARD BASEIL

...of electrical and electronics engineers (ieee) and the united nations foundation (unf), was initiated in 2007 to provide a structured forum for marshalling ieee members' extensive talent for identifying implementable...technical solutions and sometimes wonder why those solutions are not more...

Journal: IEEE Technology and Society Magazine - IEEE TECHNOL SOC MAG , vol. 28, no. 4, pp. 25-31, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7496-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7496_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:41:20">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50225764/unmanned-air-vehicles-new-challenges-in-design</link><title>Unmanned air vehicles: new challenges in design</title><description>* Unmanned air vehicles: new challenges in design (Citations: 1)

T. J. Cord, S. Newbern

...with a few thoughts on why members of ieee should be interested...

Published in 2001.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7496-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7496_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:41:46">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/3803069/strand-spaces-why-is-a-security-protocol-correct</link><title>Strand Spaces: Why is a Security Protocol Correct?</title><description>* Strand Spaces: Why is a Security Protocol Correct? (Citations: 246)

F. Javier Thayer, Jonathan C. Herzog, Joshua D. Guttman

...our proof methods to explain why the original needham- schroeder protocol...

Conference: IEEE Symposium on Security and Privacy - S&amp;P , pp. 160-171, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7496-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7496_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:42:22">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/10814961/penalized-discriminant-analysis-of-in-situ-hyperspectral-data-for-conifer-species-recognition-bin</link><title>Penalized Discriminant Analysis of In Situ Hyperspectral Data for Conifer Species Recognition Bin Yu, Senior Member, IEEE, I. Michael Ostland, Peng Gong, and Ruiliang Pu</title><description>* Penalized Discriminant Analysis of In Situ Hyperspectral Data for Conifer Species Recognition Bin Yu, Senior Member, IEEE, I. Michael Ostland, Peng Gong, and Ruiliang Pu

B. Yu, M. Ostland, P. Gong, R. Pu

Using in situ hyperspectral measurements collected in the Sierra Nevada Mountains in California, we discriminate six species of conifer trees using a recent, nonparametric statistics technique known as penalized discriminant analysis (PDA). A classification accuracy of 76% is obtained. Our emphasis is on providing an intuitive, geometric description of PDA that makes the advantages of penalization clear. PDA is a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7496-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7496_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:42:58">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/27062069/seeing-remote-team-members-as-leaders-a-study-of-us-scandinavian-teams</link><title>Seeing Remote Team Members as Leaders: A Study of US-Scandinavian Teams</title><description>* Seeing Remote Team Members as Leaders: A Study of US-Scandinavian Teams (Citations: 2)

Saonee Sarker, C. Schneider

...understand the factors that explain why an individual may be considered a leader by team members in other locations. specifically, the...suggests that us and scandinavian members do not use the same criteria for identifying remote team members as leaders and offers a...

Journal: IEEE Transactions on Professional Communication - IEEE Trans. Profess. Commun. , vol. 52, no. 1, pp. 75-94, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7496-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7496_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:43:47">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/50826720/the-history-of-technical-societies-why-and-how-to-do-them</link><title>The History of Technical Societies: Why and How to Do Them</title><description>* The History of Technical Societies: Why and How to Do Them

D. Hochfelder

...organization and discipline accessible to members, historians, and the interested public...difficulty and straitened society budgets): why and how ought technical societies...

Conference: IEEE Conference on the History of Technical Societies - HTS , 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7496-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7496_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:44:41">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/28228780/design-versus-research-in-bme-accreditation-abet-requirements-and-why-research-cannot-substitute</link><title>Design versus research in BME accreditation [ABET requirements and why research cannot substitute for design]</title><description>* Design versus research in BME accreditation [ABET requirements and why research cannot substitute for design]

JOHN D. GASSERT, JOHN D. ENDERLE

...job of an engineering faculty member would be easy. a student...

Journal: IEEE Engineering in Medicine and Biology Magazine - IEEE ENG MED BIOL MAG , vol. 27, no. 2, pp. 80-85, 2008</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7496-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7496_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:45:14">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/1533923/why-do-computer-methods-for-grounding-analysis-produce-anomalous-results</link><title>Why do computer methods for grounding analysis produce anomalous results?</title><description>* Why do computer methods for grounding analysis produce anomalous results? (Citations: 12)

Fermín Navarrina, Ignasi Colominas, Manuel Casteleiro

Grounding systems are designed to guarantee personal security, protection of equipment, and continuity of power supply. Hence, engineers must compute the equivalent resistance of the system and the potential distribution on the earth surface when a fault condition occurs. While very crude approximations were available until the 1970s, several computer methods have been more recently proposed on the basis of ...

Journal: IEEE Transactions on Power Delivery - IEEE TRANS POWER DELIVERY , vol. 18, no. 4, pp. 1192-1202, 2003</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>