<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7498">syria chemical weapons</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:52:58" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7498-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7498_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:52:59">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/2828862/chemical-and-biological-weapons-in-egypt</link><title>Chemical and biological weapons in Egypt</title><description>* Chemical and biological weapons in Egypt (Citations: 6)

Dany Shoham

...ramat gan, israel, specializing in chemical and biological warfare in arab...virology and a monograph on chemical weapons in syria and egypt. w hile egypt...

Journal: The Nonproliferation Review , vol. 5, no. 3, pp. 48-58, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7498-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7498_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:54:08">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57131415/getting-the-middle-east-holdouts-to-join-the-cwc</link><title>Getting the Middle East Holdouts to Join the CWC</title><description>* Getting the Middle East Holdouts to Join the CWC

Eitan Barak

...egypt, israel, and syria have yet to fully embrace the chemical weapons convention, but movement is possible...toward a universal ban on chemical weapons....

Journal: Bulletin of The Atomic Scientists - BULL ATOM SCI , vol. 66, no. 1, pp. 57-62, 2010</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7498-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7498_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:55:35">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/57184818/west-asian-conflicts-and-indian-responses</link><title>West Asian Conflicts and Indian Responses</title><description>* West Asian Conflicts and Indian Responses

Christopher S. Raj

...iranian allegations of iraq using chemical weapons continues. apart from the usual...iran-iraq. while libya and syria strongly support iran in the...

Journal: India Quarterly: A Journal of International Affairs , vol. 41, no. 1, pp. 53-59, 1985</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7498-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7498_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:56:48">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/58896211/irish-intelligence-staff-work-from-kosovo-to-kabul</link><title>Irish Intelligence Staff Work From Kosovo To Kabul</title><description>* Irish Intelligence Staff Work From Kosovo To Kabul

Tom Clonan

...threats, from nuclear, biological and chemical weapons proliferation to the activities, intentions...east including lebanon, israel and syria....

Published in 2006.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7498-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7498_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:57:22">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/37396457/creating-instability-in-dangerous-global-regions-north-korean-proliferation-and-support-to</link><title>Creating Instability in Dangerous Global Regions: North Korean Proliferation and Support to Terrorism in the Middle East and South Asia</title><description>* Creating Instability in Dangerous Global Regions: North Korean Proliferation and Support to Terrorism in the Middle East and South Asia

Bruce E. Bechtol Jr

...proliferation of missiles and other weapons systems used as delivery platforms for chemical (and the production of chemical munitions) or biological weapons, including long-range artillery. evidence...in the nuclear programs of syria, iran, libya, and pakistan and has provided weapons and training to terrorist groups...

Journal: Comparative Strategy , vol. 28, no. 2, pp. 99-115, 2009</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7498-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7498_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:58:41">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/42596721/it-s-time-to-scrap-the-npt</link><title>It's time to scrap the NPT</title><description>* It's time to scrap the NPT (Citations: 5)

Michael Wesley

...one or two additional nuclear weapons states per decade into the...governing the possession of nuclear weapons would help put transnational nuclear smuggling networks out of business and stabilise the inevitable spread of nuclear weapons....

Journal: Australian Journal of International Affairs - AUST J INT AFF , vol. 59, no. 3, pp. 283-299, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7498-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7498_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:00:01">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/43532221/a-us-view-of-terrorism</link><title>A US view of terrorism</title><description>* A US view of terrorism (Citations: 1)

Jack N. Kondrasuk

...cuba, sudan, cuba, libya, and syria are seen as the main countries supporting terrorism. the main terrorist weapons are explosives, guns, biological, chemical, radiological, psychological, and to a...

Journal: Disaster Prevention and Management - DISASTER PREV MANAG , vol. 14, no. 5, pp. 644-656, 2005</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7498-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7498_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:01:02">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48814845/the-gulf-war-and-its-aftermath</link><title>The Gulf War and Its Aftermath</title><description>* The Gulf War and Its Aftermath (Citations: 1)

Simon Wessely

...saudi arabia, egypt, oman, france, syria, kuwait, pakistan, canada, bahrain, morocco...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7498-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7498_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:01:35">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48834749/measurement-of-radionuclides-and-gamma-ray-dose-rate-in-soil-and-transfer-of-radionuclides-from</link><title>Measurement of Radionuclides and Gamma-Ray Dose Rate in Soil and Transfer of Radionuclides from Soil to Vegetation, Vegetable of Some Northern Area of Pakistan Using γ-Ray Spectrometry</title><description>* Measurement of Radionuclides and Gamma-Ray Dose Rate in Soil and Transfer of Radionuclides from Soil to Vegetation, Vegetable of Some Northern Area of Pakistan Using γ-Ray Spectrometry (Citations: 1)

Hasan M. Khan, M. Ismail, Khalid Khan, Perveen Akhter

The analysis of gamma emitters natural radionuclides, i.e., 226Ra, 232Th, and 40K, has been carried out in soil, vegetation, vegetable, and water samples collected from some Northern area of Pakistan, using gamma-ray spectrometry. The γ-ray spectrometry was carried out using high-purity Germanium detector coupled with a computer-based high-resolution multi-channel analyzer. The activity concentrations ...

Journal: Water Air and Soil Pollution - WATER AIR SOIL POLLUT , vol. 219, no. 1, pp. 129-142, 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7498-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7498_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:02:57">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/48214749/botulism</link><title>Botulism</title><description>* Botulism

Jeremy Sobel</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>