<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7499">gold price</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:03:21" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7499-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7499_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:03:22">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/34066250/forecasting-s&amp;p-and-gold-futures-prices-an-application-of-neural-networks</link><title>Forecasting S&amp;P and gold futures prices: An application of neural networks</title><description>* Forecasting S&amp;P and gold futures prices: An application of neural networks (Citations: 46)

Gary Grudnitski, Larry Osburn

Journal: Journal of Futures Markets - J FUTURES MARKETS , vol. 13, no. 6, pp. 631-643, 1993</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7499-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7499_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:04:23">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/3275001/investigating-the-relationship-between-gold-and-silver-prices</link><title>Investigating the Relationship between Gold and Silver Prices</title><description>* Investigating the Relationship between Gold and Silver Prices (Citations: 41)

Álvaro Escribano, Clive W. J. Granger

...the long-run relationship between gold and silver prices. the three main questions addressed...the rates of return of gold and silver. in the three type of relationships that we have analysed between the prices of gold and silver, the dependence is...

Journal: Journal of Forecasting - J FORECASTING , vol. 17, no. 2, pp. 81-107, 1998</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7499-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7499_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:05:20">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/35805435/the-impact-of-gold-price-on-the-value-of-gold-mining-stock</link><title>The impact of gold price on the value of gold mining stock</title><description>* The impact of gold price on the value of gold mining stock (Citations: 21)

Joseph C. P. Shieh

...proportion of assets unrelated to gold price risk. assuming that forward gold prices are the market's unbiased expectations of future spot prices, a model is derived that estimates the theoretical gold price elasticity of gold mining stock. the model shows...

Journal: Review of Financial Economics , vol. 4, no. 2, pp. 125-139, 1995</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7499-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7499_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:05:57">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/36069779/do-macroeconomics-news-releases-affect-gold-and-silver-prices</link><title>Do macroeconomics news releases affect gold and silver prices?</title><description>* Do macroeconomics news releases affect gold and silver prices? (Citations: 18)

Mukesh Chaudhry, Timothy W. Koch

...we document the responses of gold and silver future prices to monthly macroeconomic news releases. both metals respond strongly to the release of capacity utilization. gold also responds strongly to the...the unemployment rate affects both gold and silver, whereas the gross domestic product and ppi have significant effects on gold. weak responses by gold to the release of the...

Journal: Journal of Economics and Business , vol. 52, no. 5, pp. 405-421, 2000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7499-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7499_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:07:05">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/39112857/a-gold-pricing-model</link><title>A gold pricing model</title><description>* A gold pricing model (Citations: 13)

Eugene J Sherman

Journal: Journal of Portfolio Management - J PORTFOLIO MANAGE , vol. 9, no. 3, pp. 68-70, 1983</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7499-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7499_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:08:15">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/36069704/gold-and-commodity-prices-as-leading-indicators-of-inflation-tests-of-long-run-relationship-and</link><title>Gold and commodity prices as leading indicators of inflation: Tests of long-run relationship and predictive performance</title><description>* Gold and commodity prices as leading indicators of inflation: Tests of long-run relationship and predictive performance (Citations: 15)

Saeid Mahdavi, Su Zhou

...we compared the performance of gold and commodity prices as leading indicators of the...of the cpi including commodity prices significantly outperforms a cpi model including the price of gold, but the marginal contribution of...

Journal: Journal of Economics and Business , vol. 49, no. 5, pp. 475-489, 1997</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7499-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7499_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:09:09">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/19458513/low-q-moment-multifractal-analysis-of-gold-price-dow-jones-industrial-average-and-bgl-usd-exchange</link><title>Low q-moment multifractal analysis of Gold price, Dow Jones Industrial Average and BGL-USD exchange rate</title><description>* Low q-moment multifractal analysis of Gold price, Dow Jones Industrial Average and BGL-USD exchange rate (Citations: 18)

K. Ivanova, M. Ausloos

...the assumed multifractal spectrum of gold price, dow jones industrial average (djia...

Journal: European Physical Journal B - EUR PHYS J B , vol. 8, no. 4, pp. 665-669, 1999</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7499-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7499_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:09:50">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/36744577/gold-price-neural-networks-and-genetic-algorithm</link><title>Gold Price, Neural Networks and Genetic Algorithm</title><description>* Gold Price, Neural Networks and Genetic Algorithm (Citations: 10)

Sam Mirmirani, H. C. Li

...explanation of the dynamicpath of price movement over time. therefore, the use of any linear ornon-linear functional form to model the gold price movement is bound to bearbitrary...genetic algorithms is used topredict gold price movement. the results indicate that prices in the past, upto 36 days, strongly affect the gold prices of the future. this confirms...

Journal: Computational Economics - COMPUT ECON , vol. 23, no. 2, pp. 193-200, 2004</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7499-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7499_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:10:27">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40686952/the-crisis-in-south-african-gold-mining</link><title>The crisis in South African gold mining</title><description>* The crisis in South African gold mining (Citations: 6)

Nicoli Nattrass

...ore grades and a stagnant gold price are steadily eroding the economic viability of gold mining in south africa. this...negative effect of the low gold prices—a development which more than...

Journal: World Development - WORLD DEVELOP , vol. 23, no. 5, pp. 857-868, 1995</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7499-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7499_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:11:16">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/18280062/statistical-analysis-of-daily-gold-price-data</link><title>Statistical analysis of daily gold price data</title><description>* Statistical analysis of daily gold price data (Citations: 7)

Terence C. Mills

...the statistical behaviour of daily gold price data from 1971 to 2002...

Journal: Physica A-statistical Mechanics and Its Applications - PHYSICA A , vol. 338, no. 3, pp. 559-566, 2004</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>