<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7503">uki</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:24:15" name="MS Academic" id="FW14-e010"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e010-7503-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7503_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:24:16">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/1521955/a-vlsi-fuzzy-logic-controller-with-reconfigurable-cascadable-architecture</link><title>A VLSI fuzzy logic controller with reconfigurable, cascadable architecture</title><description>* A VLSI fuzzy logic controller with reconfigurable, cascadable architecture (Citations: 133)

HIROY UKI WATANABE, WAYNE D. DETTLOFF, KATHY E. YOUNT

A general-purpose fuzzy logic inference engine for real-time control applications, designed and fabricated in a 1.1-μm, 3.3-V, double-level-metal CMOS technology, is discussed. Up to 102 rules are processed in parallel with a single 688 K transistor device. Features include a dynamically reconfigurable and cascadable architecture, TTL-compatible host interface, laser-programmable redundancy, ...

Journal: IEEE Journal of Solid-state Circuits - IEEE J SOLID-STATE CIRCUITS , vol. 25, no. 2, pp. 376-382, 1990</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7503-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7503_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:25:22">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/37136682/the-role-of-ia-antigens-in-t-cell-activation</link><title>The Role of Ia Antigens in T Cell Activation</title><description>* The Role of Ia Antigens in T Cell Activation (Citations: 31)

David W. Thomas, Uki Yamashita, Ethan M. Shevach

Journal: Immunological Reviews - IMMUNOL REV , vol. 35, no. 1, pp. 97-120, 1977</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7503-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7503_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:25:56">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/15132628/cyclic-amp-an-intracellular-second-messenger-for-interleukin-1</link><title>Cyclic AMP--An Intracellular Second Messenger for Interleukin 1</title><description>* Cyclic AMP--An Intracellular Second Messenger for Interleukin 1 (Citations: 43)

Fumihiko Shirakawa, Uki Yamashita, Marcio Chedid, Steven B. Mizel

We demonstrated that interleukin 1 (IL-1), a potent peptide mediator in immune and inflammatory responses, stimulates the synthesis of cAMP in a variety of IL-1-responsive cell targets. We also showed that cAMP analogs and cAMP-inducing agents can replace IL-1 in the induction of interleukin 2 receptors on lymphocytes as well as in phytohemagglutinin-induced murine ...

Journal: Proceedings of The National Academy of Sciences - PNAS , vol. 85, no. 21, pp. 8201-8205, 1988</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7503-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7503_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:26:22">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/40705475/regulation-of-maturation-and-spawning-of-an-abalone-haliotis-gastropoda-by-external</link><title>Regulation of maturation and spawning of an abalone, Haliotis (Gastropoda) by external environmental factors</title><description>* Regulation of maturation and spawning of an abalone, Haliotis (Gastropoda) by external environmental factors (Citations: 25)

N UKI, S KIKUCHI

Journal: Aquaculture , vol. 39, no. 1-4, pp. 247-261, 1984</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7503-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7503_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:27:05">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/26914992/effect-of-traction-force-distribution-control-on-vehicle-dynamics</link><title>Effect of Traction Force Distribution Control on Vehicle Dynamics</title><description>* Effect of Traction Force Distribution Control on Vehicle Dynamics (Citations: 15)

S. Motoyama, H. Uki

Journal: Vehicle System Dynamics - VEH SYST DYN , vol. 22, no. 5, pp. 455-464, 1993</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7503-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7503_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:27:57">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6991375/cd44-stimulation-induces-integrin-mediated-adhesion-of-colon-cancer-cell-lines-to-endothelial-cells</link><title>CD44 Stimulation Induces Integrin-mediated Adhesion of Colon Cancer Cell Lines to Endothelial Cells by Up-Regulation of Integrins and c-Met and Activation of Integrins1</title><description>* CD44 Stimulation Induces Integrin-mediated Adhesion of Colon Cancer Cell Lines to Endothelial Cells by Up-Regulation of Integrins and c-Met and Activation of Integrins1 (Citations: 42)

Takeshi Fujisaki, Yoshiya Tanaka, Koichi Fujii, Shinichiro Mine, Kazuyoshi Saito, Shinwa Yamada, Uki Yamashita, Tatsuro Irimura, Sumiya Eto

For cancer metastasis, tumor cells present in the circulation must first adhere to the endothelium. Integrins lymphocyte function-associated an- tigen (LFA) 1 and very late antigen 4 play a central role in leukocyte adhesion to the endothelium and subsequent migration into tissues. The majority of tumor cells derived from solid cancers including colorectal cancer do not express suitable adhesion ...

Published in 1999.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7503-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7503_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:29:00">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/32437839/recurrence-of-primary-intracranial-germinomas-after-complete-response-with-radiotherapy-recurrence</link><title>Recurrence of Primary Intracranial Germinomas after Complete Response with Radiotherapy: Recurrence Patterns and Therapy</title><description>* Recurrence of Primary Intracranial Germinomas after Complete Response with Radiotherapy: Recurrence Patterns and Therapy (Citations: 23)

Nobuo Ono, Itsuo Isobe, Jiro Uki, Hideyuki Kurihara, Tsuneo Shimizu, Kazuyuki Kohno

Journal: Neurosurgery , vol. 35, no. 4, 1994</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7503-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7503_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:29:50">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/6566346/production-of-bone-resorbing-activity-corresponding-to-interleukin-la-by-adult-t-cell-leukemia</link><title>Production of Bone-resorbing Activity Corresponding to Interleukin-la by Adult T-Cell Leukemia Cells in Humans1</title><description>* Production of Bone-resorbing Activity Corresponding to Interleukin-la by Adult T-Cell Leukemia Cells in Humans1 (Citations: 12)

Fumihiko Shirakawa, Uki Yamashita, Yoshiya Tanaka, Kennichi Watanaba, Kanji Sato, Joji Haratake, Takashi Fujihira, Susumu Od, Sumiya Eto

The physicochemical properties and relationship of bone-resorbing activity and interleukin 1 (11.-1) produced by adult 1-cell leukemia (All,) cells and cell line were studied in vitro. The culture supernatant of AIL cell line, Ml2, and peripheral blood lymphocytes freshly obtained from ATL patients had both II,-1 activity detected by the stimulation of murine thymocyte-proliferative responses ...

Published in 1988.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7503-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7503_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:30:49">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/26302933/optical-humidity-and-ammonia-gas-sensor-using-calcein-based-films</link><title>Optical humidity and ammonia gas sensor using calcein-based films</title><description>* Optical humidity and ammonia gas sensor using calcein-based films (Citations: 9)

Yoshihiko Sadaoka, Yoshiro Sakai, Yu-uki Murata

Journal: Sensors and Actuators B-chemical - SENSOR ACTUATOR B-CHEM , vol. 13, no. 1-3, pp. 420-423, 1993</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e010-7503-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e010/7503_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:31:35">http://academic.research.microsoft.com/Publication/35922253/biphasic-changes-in-behavioral-endocrine-and-sympathetic-systems-in-adjuvant-arthritis-in-lewis</link><title>Biphasic changes in behavioral, endocrine, and sympathetic systems in adjuvant arthritis in Lewis rats</title><description>* Biphasic changes in behavioral, endocrine, and sympathetic systems in adjuvant arthritis in Lewis rats (Citations: 30)

Hiroaki Tanaka, Yoichi Ueta, Uki Yamashita, Hiroshi Kannan, Hiroshi Yamashita

Adjuvant arthritis (AA) is an experimental model for rheumatoid arthritis, and is induced most easily in inbred Lewis rats by an intradermal injection of heat-killed Mycobacterium tuberculosis (MT) in incomplete Freund's adjuvant. Susceptivity to the arthritis in Lewis rats is thought to be related to a defect in their responses of the hypothalamo-pituitary-adrenal (HPA) axis to ...

Journal: Brain Research Bulletin - BRAIN RES BULL , vol. 39, no. 1, pp. 33-37, 1996</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>