<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7004">z-machine</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:58:52" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7004-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/07/ibm_s_360_50_anniversary/</link><title>Why won't you DIE? IBM's S/360 and its legacy at 50</title><description>Why won't you DIE? IBM's S/360 and its legacy at 50

IBM's System 360 mainframe, celebrating its 50th anniversary on Monday, was more than a just another computer. The S/360 changed IBM just as it changed computing and the technology industry. The digital computers that were to become known as mainframes were already being sold by companies during the 1950s and 1960s - so the S/ …

Gavin Clarke, 07 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7004_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/07/01/ibm_system_360_model_50.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7004-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/12/archaeologic_amstrad_cpc_464/</link><title>You’re NOT fired: The story of Amstrad’s amazing CPC 464</title><description>You’re NOT fired: The story of Amstrad’s amazing CPC 464

It was a home computer that embodied so many contradictions. It was launched months after the British microcomputer boom of the early 1980s had peaked. It was a rush job: the machine that was revealed to the press in the Spring of 1984 hadn’t even existed nine months previously. It was one of the best-produced British micros of …

Tony Smith, 12 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7004_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/01/13/464_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7004-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/03/review_asus_transformer_trio/</link><title>This THREESOME is a HANDFUL: It’s the Asus Transformer Book Trio</title><description>This THREESOME is a HANDFUL: It’s the Asus Transformer Book Trio

No matter what sort of tablet you prefer, be it an iPad or an Android slate, there will be times when you will also need a good old-fashioned Windows laptop too. Asus, which has form when it comes to cooking up strange combo designs - witness the PadFone - obviously thinks that’s the case as the new Transformer Book Trio is both …

Alun Taylor, 03 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7004_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/03/trio_2.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7004-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/03/what_lenovo_ibm_buy_really_means/</link><title>Why IBM's server sell-off is a lightbulb moment</title><description>Why IBM's server sell-off is a lightbulb moment

We’re not even out of January yet and already the UK's tech channel has possibly seen its biggest story of 2014 after IBM sold its low-end server business to Lenovo. The two companies have history, of course, with IBM offloading its profitable-but-not-for-long PC business to the Chinese firm back in 2005. Lenovo did rather well …

Alexandre Mesguich, 03 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7004_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/01/18/lightbulb.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7004-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/31/end_of_year_review_2013/</link><title>Glassholes, snapt**ts, #blabbergasms, selfies and PRISM: The Reg's review of 2013</title><description>Glassholes, snapt**ts, #blabbergasms, selfies and PRISM: The Reg's review of 2013

"Selfie" is the Oxford English Dictionary's word of the year. There's nothing new about a "selfie" - it's a self-portrait - but a perfect storm of social networks and smartphones has given popularity to a word and an act even world leaders feel it's OK to do on really serious occasions. In keeping with a long tradition here at …

Gavin Clarke, 31 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7004_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/03/09/google_glass.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7004-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/26/review_hp_slate_21_tablet/</link><title>HP’s ENORMO-SLAB: The Slate 21 MONSTER tablet</title><description>HP’s ENORMO-SLAB: The Slate 21 MONSTER tablet

Hewlett-Packard’s first attempt at an Android tablet, the Slate 7, was a cheap, wretched and irredeemably awful device. So when I heard that the Palm killer’s follow-up fondleslab was to be a 21-inch affair, my reaction was one of incredulity mixed with foreboding. HP Slate 21 Your new desktop? HP’s Android-based Slate 21 In …

Alun Taylor, 26 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7004_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/26/s21_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7004-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/25/wd_seeing_double_with_twofer_one_drive/</link><title>Flash stash on toppa platta: WD's tasty Black² 1TB combo for LAPTOPS</title><description>Flash stash on toppa platta: WD's tasty Black² 1TB combo for LAPTOPS

WD hopes to whet the appetites of laptop owners and serious gamers who have the need for speed AND capacity: it has launched a 1TB Black spinning disk drive with a 120GB SSD stuffed inside its case. The Black2 has a notebook 2.5-inch disk drive form factor, with a 9.5mm z-height and will bring joy and delight to Windows notebook …

Chris Mellor, 25 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7004_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/10/wd_disk.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7004-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/08/managing_aspergers_techies/</link><title>Techies with Asperger's? Yes, we are a little different...</title><description>Techies with Asperger's? Yes, we are a little different...

Shortly after being told I have Asperger's syndrome, I stood in front of 30-odd people, my work colleagues, telling them I have Asperger’s and what it means to them and to me. Some were like: "Meh, whatever!", some were busy looking their watches: "Is it lunchtime yet?" I could feel my job slowly ebbing away. It was like …

Stuart Burns, 08 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7004_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/07/10/moss_index.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7004-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/03/review_sony_xperia_ultra_z/</link><title>Sony Xperia Z Ultra: The quad-core 2.2GHz MEGA SCREEN PHONDLESLAB</title><description>Sony Xperia Z Ultra: The quad-core 2.2GHz MEGA SCREEN PHONDLESLAB

Two years after Samsung opened the Very Large Phone (VLP™) Pandora’s Box with the original Galaxy Note, Sony has thrown its hat into the ring with the Xperia Z Ultra: a device boasting a 6.4-inch screen and a 2.2GHz quad-core processor. Now I have a pretty wild imagination, especially after a few pints and an injudicious late- …

Alun Taylor, 03 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7004_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/30/uz_11.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7004-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/09/23/round_up_3g_and_4g_tablets/</link><title>Can't fit slab AND mobe in your tight pockets? 10 tablets with built-in 3G/4G</title><description>Can't fit slab AND mobe in your tight pockets? 10 tablets with built-in 3G/4G

If you want a tablet that is always connected to the internet, there are several options to consider. One that involves no extra hardware expense is simply to use your smartphone as a wireless hotspot, routing connections over 3 or 4G - if your chosen mobile network lets you. Another option, which has the advantage of not …

Alun Taylor, 23 Sep 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7004_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/06/18/xtz_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>