<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7009">linkedin engineering</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:24:14" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7009-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/16/where_are_dey_now_gone_to_to_titsup_ville/</link><title>Hic! Storage upstart DEY bought out by Australian wine merchant</title><description>Hic! Storage upstart DEY bought out by Australian wine merchant

Software-defined storage startup DEY Storage has been bought by CloudCentral, an Australian cloud service provider, which has had a DEY storage co-founder as a board advisor for a few months. And it's being bought by a winery. Are we making this up? No, but perhaps we might have drunk too deeply from the Hippocrene. Let's go to …

Chris Mellor, 16 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7009_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/04/15/dromana_bottles.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7009-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/08/cobol_s_360_anniversary/</link><title>The gift of Grace: COBOL's odyssey from Vietnam to the Square Mile</title><description>The gift of Grace: COBOL's odyssey from Vietnam to the Square Mile

Cobol is the language most associated with mainframes, especially the IBM System 360 whose 50th anniversary is being celebrated or at least commemorated this week. But when COBOL was first spawned in the mid-1950s, it wasn’t intended for programmers. It was aimed instead at “accountants and business managers” – basically a Stone …

Dominic Connor, 08 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7009_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/03/09/grace_hopper_419x278.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7009-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/20/java_8_security_multi_core/</link><title>Reality check: Java 8 finally catches a multi-core break</title><description>Reality check: Java 8 finally catches a multi-core break

Two years later than planned, Oracle has made Java ready for a multi-core processor world. The database giant has announced general availability of Java 8, calling it a “major new release”. Java 8 is important because it’s the base spec for Java Enterprise Edition, as well as feeding the free and open-source implementation of …

Gavin Clarke, 20 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7009_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/01/30/java_logo.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7009-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/04/dells_new_research_division/</link><title>Dell's fellow from Big Blue heads up blue sky division</title><description>Dell's fellow from Big Blue heads up blue sky division

A now-private Dell appears to have set up a Research Division headed by IBM import Jai Menon. Menon, a former IBM fellow, joined Dell in October 2012, becoming the chief technology officer at Round Rock. Now several reports, here and here for example, say he has been given the role of big boss of the R &amp; D Division inside Dell …

Chris Mellor, 04 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7009_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/06/cloud_grab.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7009-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/06/virtualised_server_data_sensing_and_analysis/</link><title>Ex-VMware bods start up infrastructure firm, draw 'inspiration' from Google</title><description>Ex-VMware bods start up infrastructure firm, draw 'inspiration' from Google

Big Data analytics techniques play a role in CloudPhysics' instrumentation data-sensing results analysis. Here is the second part of Willem ter Harmsel's interview (click here for part one) with Cloud Physics CEO John Blumenthal, who explains how Cloud Physics takes its cues from Google and LinkedIn. WtH: Is CloudPhysics still …

Willem ter Harmsel, 06 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7009_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/26/google_hummingbird.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7009-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/22/apple_new_pricing_policy_of_free_upgrades/</link><title>Pop OS X Mavericks on your Mac for FREE while you have LUNCH</title><description>Pop OS X Mavericks on your Mac for FREE while you have LUNCH

Apple's latest version of OS X, Mavericks, is now available at the low, low price of zero, zip, zilch. The iLife and iWorks creativity and productivity suites have also been marked down to nothing for buyers of new iOS and Mac hardware. "Today we're going to revolutionize pricing, because the days of spending hundreds of dollars …

Rik Myslewski, 22 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7009_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/27/empty_pockets.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7009-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/03/apple_has_big_ambitions_for_the_small_screen/</link><title>Apple hires streaming vid bloke: Nurse, the corpse of Apple monster telly is twitching again</title><description>Apple hires streaming vid bloke: Nurse, the corpse of Apple monster telly is twitching again

Apple has taken another step towards the introduction of a full-blown big-screen fruity goggle box with the hiring of a cable telly supremo. Jean-Francois Mulé has defected to Cupertino from Cablelabs, a non-profit research body paid for by cable television companies, according to the New York Times. He will join Apple as an …

Jasper Hamill, 03 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7009_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/08/16/apple_television.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7009-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/09/17/20_years_of_the_apple_newton/</link><title>Stylus counsel: The rise and fall of the Apple Newton MessagePad</title><description>Stylus counsel: The rise and fall of the Apple Newton MessagePad

It will forever be remembered as the butt of a-thousand-and-one jokes about its poor handwriting recognition, but Apple’s MessagePad was bold in its conception. Its legacy is ARM’s conquest of the mobile microprocessor world. The company said on 8 August 1993: The Newton MessagePad is the first in a family of communications …

Tony Smith, 17 Sep 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7009_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/16/mp_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7009-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/08/05/the_old_reader_drops_google_refugee_eviction_plan/</link><title>The Old Reader drops Google refugee eviction plan</title><description>The Old Reader drops Google refugee eviction plan

The Old Reader, the RSS reader that drowned in new users after Google switched off its own RSS reader and then decided to boot out those refugees, has reversed its position and will continue to operate as a public service. In a blog post someone called “Ben Wolf” wrote “The application now has a bigger team, significantly more …

Simon Sharwood, 05 Aug 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7009_09_thumb.gif">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/03/15/keep_calm_and_save_google_reader.gif?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7009-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/15/iwatch_ipad_mini_delated_until_2014/</link><title>Apple needs help: iWatch, 'Retina' iPad mini delayed until 2014?</title><description>Apple needs help: iWatch, 'Retina' iPad mini delayed until 2014?

Fanbois may need to revise this year's holiday shopping plans: Apple's long-anticipated iWatch appears to be slipping behind schedule, and so is the "Retina display" iPad mini. A pair of reports say that neither will appear until next year. London's Financial Times reported on Sunday that Apple has been hiring "aggressively" in …

Rik Myslewski, 15 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7009_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/07/15/help_wanted.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>