<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7010">manchester united FC football</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:48:07" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7010-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/07/05/ronaldo_transferred/</link><title>Cristiano Ronaldo on eBay transfer list</title><description>Cristiano Ronaldo on eBay transfer list

As any true Englishman knows, our national football team's traditional crash-and-burn in the World Cup is never as a result of our own shortcomings. Previous top quality excuses have involved excess heat, unexpectedly low atmospheric pressure, the wrong kind of grass on the pitch, players' concerns over the political situation …

Lester Haines, 05 Jul 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7010_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7010-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/03/01/lip_reading_fans/</link><title>Lip-reading footie fans spot racial abuse</title><description>Lip-reading footie fans spot racial abuse

Police are looking into an allegation that a Liverpool player racially abused a Manchester United team member during the two teams' clash at Old Trafford on 22 January, the BBC reports. The tip-off came neither from the player allegedly at the receiving end of the insult, nor from a match official, but rather two deaf footie …

Lester Haines, 01 Mar 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7010_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7010-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/11/22/lfc_lottery_scam/</link><title>Lads from Lagos set up Anfield branch</title><description>Lads from Lagos set up Anfield branch

Fraudsters are posing as representatives of a lottery sponsored by Liverpool Football Club in an attempt to defraud gulliable net users. The spam messages claim that recipients are one of 40 lucky winners to have won £500,000 in a lottery supposedly run by Liverpool FC. The emails say that LFC's financial success exceeded …

John Leyden, 22 Nov 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7010_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/03/chandef3.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7010-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2004/07/15/five_years_ago/</link><title>Man Utd enters free ISP race</title><description>Man Utd enters free ISP race

Today's slurp from the stagnant pool of yesteryear is especially for El Reg hack John "Lips" Leyden, who is noted for being a bit of a Manchester United FC fan. That's the Manchester United who failed to take last season's Premiership title, in case readers had forgotten: Man Utd enters free ISP race By Sean Fleming …

Team Register, 15 Jul 2004</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7010_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7010-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2002/08/05/football_culture_everything_in_between/</link><title>Football. Culture. Everything in between</title><description>Football. Culture. Everything in between

With the kick-off of the football season North of the border last weekend, and the beginning of the Nationwide season next it's high time Site of the Day took a look at the world of football Web sites. Barely a month after the end of the World Cup, what better place to start that Osaka, Japan-based Website Soccerphile.com. A …

John Leyden, 05 Aug 2002</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7010_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7010-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/1999/07/15/man_utd_enters_free_isp/</link><title>Man Utd enters free ISP race</title><description>Man Utd enters free ISP race

They'll be scratching their heads in disbelief in Stretford today as news breaks that Manchester United FC is actually giving something away - for free. The world's largest - and richest - football club (that's the game where you kick the ball with your feet, hence the name football, in case our US readers were getting confused …

Sean Fleming, 15 Jul 1999</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7010_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>