<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7014">Asian culture</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:56:09" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7014-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/28/quotw_ending_march_28/</link><title>'I will not work with Facebook... they seem creepy to me'</title><description>'I will not work with Facebook... they seem creepy to me'

This was the week when Facebook continued to splash the cash, spanking $2bn on Oculus VR just a short while after splaffing $19bn on messaging app WhatsApp. To justify his latest billion-dollar purchase, chief Mark Zuckerberg gushed: Oculus' mission is to enable you to experience the impossible. Their technology opens up the …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 28 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7014_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/13/oculus_rift.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7014-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/18/mh370_airliner_mystery_the_iel_regi_pubdinnerparty_guide/</link><title>MH370 airliner MYSTERY: The El Reg Pub/Dinner-party Guide</title><description>MH370 airliner MYSTERY: The El Reg Pub/Dinner-party Guide

So, the mysterious case of the missing flight MH370. We've mainly stayed out of this - apart from noting that no, the jet wasn't hackjacked using a mobile phone. But naturally we've been poking around a bit to see what we could find out, and it's not completely nothing. Here's what we bring to the party. Some of us know a bit …

Lewis Page, 18 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7014_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/03/18/mh370_teaser.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7014-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/12/archaeologic_amstrad_cpc_464/</link><title>You’re NOT fired: The story of Amstrad’s amazing CPC 464</title><description>You’re NOT fired: The story of Amstrad’s amazing CPC 464

It was a home computer that embodied so many contradictions. It was launched months after the British microcomputer boom of the early 1980s had peaked. It was a rush job: the machine that was revealed to the press in the Spring of 1984 hadn’t even existed nine months previously. It was one of the best-produced British micros of …

Tony Smith, 12 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7014_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/01/13/464_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7014-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/05/dell_makes_economic_sense_kinda/</link><title>A private Dell makes sense. Doesn't mean it'll work, though</title><description>A private Dell makes sense. Doesn't mean it'll work, though

So now that Dell the man has spaffed $24bn (with a little help from his friends) on buying back Dell the company, what is Michael D actually going to do with it? And why has he had to take it private in order to do it? What is there that you cannot do on a public stock exchange that you can do as a private company? The first …

Tim Worstall, 05 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7014_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/06/06/michael_dell_2.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7014-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/10/history_of_magnetic_tape_part_three/</link><title>Video thrilled the radio star: Tracking the history of magnetic tape</title><description>Video thrilled the radio star: Tracking the history of magnetic tape

El Reg's magnetic tape odyssey has covered tape's early beginnings in sound recording in part one and its revolution in computing in part two. In this final part, we look at how film and TV became some of magnetic tape's best customers. The music and computer industries weren’t the only early adopters of magnetic tape. The …

Bob Dormon, 10 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7014_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/10/10/rca_video_recorder_ad2_480.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7014-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/09/27/global_execs_name_apple_most_innovative_company_again/</link><title>Global execs name Apple 'most innovative company' – again</title><description>Global execs name Apple 'most innovative company' – again

When unveiling the soon-to-be-released computer-in-a-can Mac Pro at the company's Worldwide Developers Conference this June, Apple marketing headman Phil Schiller quipped "Can't innovate anymore, my ass," a barb aimed at those observers who accuse Cupertino of having lost its mojo. Global business strategy firm Boston Consulting …

Rik Myslewski, 27 Sep 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7014_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/27/foam_finger.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7014-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/08/30/pure_storage_chasing_flash_array_glory/</link><title>Pure Storage hoovers up $150m in funding, hires ex-Data Domain CEO</title><description>Pure Storage hoovers up $150m in funding, hires ex-Data Domain CEO

Flash array upstart Pure Storage aims to emerge from the herd and pull off a Data Domain, having secured $150m in E-round funding and hired former Data Domain head honcho Frank Slootman, who joins its board as "a key strategic advisor." Pure says the $150m is "the single largest private funding in the history of the enterprise …

Chris Mellor, 30 Aug 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7014_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/purestorage.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7014-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/08/06/lawsuit_claims_infosys_abuses_visas_to_discriminate_against_us_staff/</link><title>Lawsuit: Infosys abuses visas to discriminate against US staff</title><description>Lawsuit: Infosys abuses visas to discriminate against US staff

A class-action lawsuit filed against IT outsourcing firm Infosys claims that the company is systematically abusing the visa system and actively discriminates against hiring US workers for staff position. The lawsuit, filed in US District Court in Eastern Wisconsin by VMware specialist Brenda Koehler, claims that up to 90 per …

Iain Thomson, 06 Aug 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7014_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/06/13/grab_that_cash.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7014-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/29/microsoft_might_yet_win/</link><title>Microsoft haters: You gotta lop off a lot of legs to slay Ballmer's monster</title><description>Microsoft haters: You gotta lop off a lot of legs to slay Ballmer's monster

Contrary to increasingly popular belief, Microsoft is not a “dead” company, nor at immediate risk of collapse. I do, however, believe that Microsoft’s “Windows on the endpoint” monopoly days have passed, that Microsoft’s senior management are aware of this and are actively taking steps to compensate. Similarly, I believe that …

Trevor Pott, 29 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7014_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/07/29/warrior.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7014-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/05/03/data_privacy_cloud_market_asia/</link><title>'Inconsistent' watchdogs throw cloud biz barons into a tizzy</title><description>'Inconsistent' watchdogs throw cloud biz barons into a tizzy

A lack of consistency over the way Asian regulators approach data privacy issues has led to a slow take-up of cloud services by businesses in the region, an expert has said. Hong Kong-based outsourcing contracts expert Peter Bullock of Pinsent Masons, the law firm behind Out-Law.com, said that cloud providers are not offering …

OUT-LAW.COM, 03 May 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7014_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/06/12/pain.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>