<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7025">M/G/1 queue</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:30:06" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7025-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/09/25/java_message_services/</link><title>Programming message services in Java</title><description>Programming message services in Java

Lately I seem to be involved increasingly in systems relying on asynchronous interactions for efficient and effective integration. In these cases, the asynchronous behaviour has been implemented using JMS (or Java Message Service) queues, with message driven beans, and with the underlying message server provided by application …

John Hunt, 25 Sep 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7025_01_thumb.gif">http://regmedia.co.uk/_teaser/75x75/java.gif?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7025-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/06/30/first_apple_iphone_review/</link><title>Apple iPhone</title><description>Apple iPhone

No, Apple didn't send us an iPhone. Newsweek got one. And The Wall Street Journal. And The New York Times. But Jobs and Co. have a very different attitude towards El Reg. We weren't likely to get an official review unit even before our very own Ashlee Vance publicly questioned the sanity of the company's PR staff. We had to wait …

Cade Metz, 30 Jun 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7025_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2007/06/28/iphone_sm.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7025-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/01/16/latters_1601/</link><title>You've left your prints all over that flaming Mac</title><description>You've left your prints all over that flaming Mac

The fire just won't go out. We've tried pouring sand on it, water, throwing blankets at it, but all we got was the odd feeling we'd been on an English seaside holiday. We're talking of course, about the flames licking up the edges of the pages we used to publish any mention of the new phone from that company. You know, the …

Lucy Sherriff, 16 Jan 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7025_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7025-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/12/04/yule_blogs/</link><title>Yuletide Weblog roundup</title><description>Yuletide Weblog roundup

Ah, Christmas! When pubs fill up with inexperienced drinkers to the disapproval of regular sots, when lunchtime turkey sarnies get a blob of cranberry jam and are relaunched as 'Christmas dinner flavour' for a 40p premium, and when the moneyed middle-classes are not ashamed to be seen shopping at Woolworth's. Ah, Christmas! …

Verity Stob, 04 Dec 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7025_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7025-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/12/01/dalek_thespian/</link><title>Candid Dalek shares thesp titbits</title><description>Candid Dalek shares thesp titbits

Do you remember, earlier in the year, there was an episode of Doctor Who where the Dalek stuck its sink plunger through a computer screen and downloaded the entire internet? And then went on to commit suicide? (The Doctor, who inclines towards complex and indeed Lamarckian explanations, diagnosed its depression as being caused …

Verity Stob, 01 Dec 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7025_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7025-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2004/08/05/kodak_kiosk_reply/</link><title>Digital print booths: Kodak addresses your concerns</title><description>Digital print booths: Kodak addresses your concerns

We're obliged to Kodak for getting back to us to answer the questions raised by one reader's recent field test of the Kodak digital print booth as now enjoyed by Boots' customers across the UK. First, there's the matter of payment. Our man on the streets Simon Prentagast noted that you print out your snaps first, then flash the …

Lester Haines, 05 Aug 2004</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7025_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7025-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2003/09/17/verisign_dns_change_broke_my/</link><title>Verisign DNS change broke my HP printer</title><description>Verisign DNS change broke my HP printer

Reg readers have plenty of say about Verisign's controversial move to direct surfers who get lost on the Web to a search site run by the company. Our coverage provoked a large number of letters, almost all hostile, about Versign's audacious typo-squatting land grab. All your Web typos are belong to us Martin Ward is the first …

John Leyden, 17 Sep 2003</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7025_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>