<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7026">keanu reeves films</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:54:01" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7026-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/05/11/worst_film_never/</link><title>Vote now for the worst movie NEVER made</title><description>Vote now for the worst movie NEVER made

The moment has arrived for you, our beloved cinemagoing readers, to vote for the worst movie never made. To recap, we invited submissions for an imaginary nightmare celluloid creation more hideous than this cinematic list of shame - the 10 worst films ever made, according to El Reg readers: Battlefield Earth The Phantom Menace …

Lester Haines, 11 May 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7026_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/01/24/kodak_camera.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7026-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/04/13/movie_compo/</link><title>So what's the worst movie NEVER made?</title><description>So what's the worst movie NEVER made?

Our hunt for the worst movie ever proved highly popular with you, our beloved cinema-going readers, and the list of nominees makes such chilling reading that we began to wonder if it would be possible to shoot a film so atrocious that it would prompt audiences to run screaming from the cinema vowing never again to badmouth …

Lester Haines, 13 Apr 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7026_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7026-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/01/24/matrix_4_5/</link><title>Matrix 4 and 5 in works, threatens Keanu</title><description>Matrix 4 and 5 in works, threatens Keanu

Another two Matrix films may be leaping into cinemas, the Grauniad shrugs. The curiously youthful Keanu Reeves, star of the Matrix trilogy and of an exceptionally lame meme told an audience at the London School of Performing Arts that he may be getting back into Neo's slinky strides once again. Excitable source El Nino told big …

Sarah Bee, 24 Jan 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7026_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7026-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2001/07/26/the_reg_guide_to_hackers/</link><title>The Reg guide to hackers in film</title><description>The Reg guide to hackers in film

Our recent stories about the movie Swordfish, which goes on general release in the UK tomorrow have encouraged us to take a look at the whole hacker-film sub-genre. Hollywood's various attempts to create a convincing portrayal of hacking on celluloid (cracking exists for Tinseltown only in the Marx Brother's Animal Crackers) …

John Leyden, 26 Jul 2001</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7026_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>