<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7027">prefered or preferred</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:05:27" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7027-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/16/punch_and_judy_roundup/</link><title>LOHAN's Punch and Judy show: The big fat round-up</title><description>LOHAN's Punch and Judy show: The big fat round-up

The dust has pretty well settled on the Low Orbit Helium Assisted Navigator (LOHAN) Punch and Judy test flights, and we now present for your further entertainment a round-up of the two missions. Watch Video As you can see from the above timelapse video of the launches last Thursday, we did finally get off the ground after a …

Lester Haines, 16 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7027_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/04/05/punch_judy_team.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7027-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/10/how_to_run_xp_on_new_windows/</link><title>Cheat Win XP DEATH: Little-known tool to save you from the XPocalypse</title><description>Cheat Win XP DEATH: Little-known tool to save you from the XPocalypse

Windows XP's date with destiny has passed. As of Tuesday, Microsoft will NOT be releasing any new security updates. With one in five PCs still running Windows XP, there's a chance you are among those whose computer is now running an unsupported operating system. What now? Doing an in-place upgrade to Windows 7 isn't a good …

Liam Proven, 10 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7027_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/13/zombie.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7027-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/07/byod_cyod_lets_call_whole_thing_off/</link><title>HP exec: 'CYOD' will TEAR APART the IT dept as we know it</title><description>HP exec: 'CYOD' will TEAR APART the IT dept as we know it

Corporations are close to handing staff credit notes to buy or choose their own technology in a trend that will bust classic IT departments and supply chains, HP's top boss for Europe reckons. BYOD has morphed into Choose Your Own Device (CYOD) but the impact will still be just as dramatic, said Herbert Kock, HP's joint head of …

Paul Kunert, 07 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7027_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/17/chain_relationship_channel.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7027-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/07/ibm_s_360_50_anniversary/</link><title>Why won't you DIE? IBM's S/360 and its legacy at 50</title><description>Why won't you DIE? IBM's S/360 and its legacy at 50

IBM's System 360 mainframe, celebrating its 50th anniversary on Monday, was more than a just another computer. The S/360 changed IBM just as it changed computing and the technology industry. The digital computers that were to become known as mainframes were already being sold by companies during the 1950s and 1960s - so the S/ …

Gavin Clarke, 07 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7027_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/07/01/ibm_system_360_model_50.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7027-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/04/willowra_xp_migration_conclusion/</link><title>Deep desert XP-ocalypse averted as Reg man returns</title><description>Deep desert XP-ocalypse averted as Reg man returns

Yesterday was day three of my XP-ocalypse aversion mission to upgrade the PCs at the remote Wirliyatjarrayi Learning Centre. The day started with the dew on the ground and the desert sun struggling to penetrate a low, hazy, layer of cloud. The air was just a tad sticky and I wondered if it might rain. I hoped not: the road to …

Simon Sharwood, 04 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7027_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/04/03/willowra_store.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7027-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/02/poisonous_spiders_first_obstacle_to_xpocalypse_upgrade/</link><title>El Reg's Deep Outback XP upgrade almost foiled by KILLER ARACHNIDS</title><description>El Reg's Deep Outback XP upgrade almost foiled by KILLER ARACHNIDS

Australia's Northern territory, where The Reg is this week doing a Windows XP upgrade at the Wirliyatjarrayi Learning Centre in the remote community of Willowra, is huge and empty. Let's give that statement some dimensions. The United Kingdom covers 243,610 km2 and is home to 63.23 million people. Texas covers 696,241 km2 and …

Simon Sharwood, 02 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7027_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/19/red_back_spider.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7027-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/02/nsw_to_expand_evoting/</link><title>NSW to expand e-voting</title><description>NSW to expand e-voting

New South Wales is set to expand the footprint of electronic voting in its state election, due in 2015, with Spanish vendor Scytl reportedly on the brink of signing a new contract with the state government. Scytl's Java-based electoral software already has a footprint in NSW, since it formed the basis of the state's iVote system …

Richard Chirgwin, 02 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7027_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/04/01/nsw_ivote_logo.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7027-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/01/ulbricht_bitcoin_laundering_charge/</link><title>Money? What money? Lawyer for accused Silk Road boss claims you can't launder Bitcoin</title><description>Money? What money? Lawyer for accused Silk Road boss claims you can't launder Bitcoin

An attorney for Ross Ulbricht, the man accused of masterminding the online drugs marketplace Silk Road, has asked that the money-laundering charges against his client be dropped on the basis that Bitcoin, Silk Road's preferred medium of exchange, doesn't count as money. Ulbricht was arrested in San Francisco in October after a …

Neil McAllister, 01 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7027_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/08/ross_ulbricht.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7027-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/01/public_accounts_committee_attacks_government_broadband_rollout_for_allowing_bt_to_monopolise_project/</link><title>MPs attack BT's 'monopolistic' grip on gov-subsidised £1.2bn rural broadband rollout</title><description>MPs attack BT's 'monopolistic' grip on gov-subsidised £1.2bn rural broadband rollout

The UK government has completely screwed up the deployment of faster internet connections to Brits living in the countryside because it failed to properly address competition concerns as a result of its awarding all its broadband contracts to BT, politicians concluded today. MPs sitting on the public accounts committee published …

Kelly Fiveash, 01 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7027_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/07/26/two_mobiles_man.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7027-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/27/microsoft_office_apps_ipad/</link><title>FINALLY Microsoft releases Office for iPad – but wait there's a CATCH</title><description>FINALLY Microsoft releases Office for iPad – but wait there's a CATCH

Microsoft has, after years of speculation, released some of its Office applications for Apple iPad owners – but you'll need an Office 365 subscription to use them in anything other than a lobotomized form. Nadella Nadella holds his first press conference since taking former CEO Steve Ballmer's crown The Apple App Store now …

Iain Thomson, 27 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7027_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/03/27/nadella.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>