<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7031">Thomas test</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:53:20" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7031-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/07/ibm_s_360_50_anniversary/</link><title>Why won't you DIE? IBM's S/360 and its legacy at 50</title><description>Why won't you DIE? IBM's S/360 and its legacy at 50

IBM's System 360 mainframe, celebrating its 50th anniversary on Monday, was more than a just another computer. The S/360 changed IBM just as it changed computing and the technology industry. The digital computers that were to become known as mainframes were already being sold by companies during the 1950s and 1960s - so the S/ …

Gavin Clarke, 07 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7031_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/07/01/ibm_system_360_model_50.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7031-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/29/unsung_heroes_john_miller_kirkpatrick/</link><title>Britain’s forgotten first home computer pioneer: John Miller-Kirkpatrick</title><description>Britain’s forgotten first home computer pioneer: John Miller-Kirkpatrick

Too few people today remember John Miller-Kirkpatrick, the enthusiastic founder, owner, manager and technical director of Bywood Electronics. He died in December 1978 at the monstrously young age of 32, less than two years before the début of the Sinclair ZX80 and the start of the UK home computing boom – for which he had helped …

Tony Smith, 29 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7031_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/14/jmk_14.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7031-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/21/gpu_accelerators_overrun_green500_list_of_energyefficient_hpc_systems/</link><title>Green supercomputer benchmarks make boffins see red, check blueprints</title><description>Green supercomputer benchmarks make boffins see red, check blueprints

The biannual Green500 list of the most energy-efficient supercomputers has broken new ground in two important ways: for the first time an HPC system broke the 4 gigaflops per watt barrier, and also for the first time all the top 10 systems benefitted from GPU acceleration. Then there's a third bit of note: the benchmarks are …

Rik Myslewski, 21 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7031_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/21/green500_419x278.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7031-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/21/doctor_who_the_right_stuff/</link><title>Dry, cold and volatile: How to survive Mars, and your fellow crew</title><description>Dry, cold and volatile: How to survive Mars, and your fellow crew

What did you want to be when you grew up? Chances are as a follower of Dr Who, you wanted to be a Time lord. While travel in time sadly isn’t on the cards, space travel is becoming a reality with Virgin Galactic’s SpaceShipTwo working through 50-plus rocket-powered test flights to qualify for passenger flights and with the Space …

Dave Wilby, 21 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7031_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/10/09/thomas_presquet_eva_training_with_nasa_photo_esa.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7031-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/01/google_makes_difficult_decision_to_try_to_bring_ec_competition_probe_to_an_end/</link><title>Ad giant Google makes new 'abuse' case offer to EU antitrust cops</title><description>Ad giant Google makes new 'abuse' case offer to EU antitrust cops

Google appeared to confess today that it had given up fighting the European Commission and its rivals in the search business over claims that it stifled the market by abusing its dominant position. In a surprise statement from the ad giant, the company appeared to be willing to go much further than it had originally suggested to …

Kelly Fiveash, 01 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7031_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2008/09/09/chrome_home_page_ad.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7031-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/09/16/feature_the_new_space_pioneers/</link><title>From launch to orbit: The new commercial space pioneers</title><description>From launch to orbit: The new commercial space pioneers

We all know that many 20th century prophecies of life in the new millennium never came to pass. Among them were flying cars, meals-in-a-pill and annihilation by Skynet, to name but a few. However, taking the crown of unfulfilled expectations has to be private spaceflight for business or pleasure. With all the rapid space tech …

Shaun Dormon, 16 Sep 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7031_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/08/28/space_21.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7031-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/09/09/almunia_says_google_has_submitted_revised_proposals_on_competition_concerns/</link><title>Google submits YET ANOTHER offer to fix 'search dominance' in EU</title><description>Google submits YET ANOTHER offer to fix 'search dominance' in EU

Google, in an effort to resolve the European Commission's competition concerns relating to the company's strong grip on the search market in the EU, has submitted yet another revised set of proposals to Brussels' officials. Antitrust commissioner Joaquin Almunia told Bloomberg that he had received the rejigged offer from Google …

Kelly Fiveash, 09 Sep 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7031_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2010/12/16/larry_page_and_sergey_brin3.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7031-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/30/jurors_internet_contempt_court/</link><title>Jurors start stretch in the cooler for Facebooking, Googling the accused</title><description>Jurors start stretch in the cooler for Facebooking, Googling the accused

Two men have been jailed for two months for breaking strict rules against using Facebook and Google while serving on a jury. The pair were found to be in contempt of court by senior judges in London yesterday. One of the jailed men posted a damning message on the social network about a child sex abuse defendant mid-trial; the …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 30 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7031_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7031-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/06/13/supreme_court_rules_that_human_genes_cant_be_patented/</link><title>US Supremes: Human genes can't be patented</title><description>US Supremes: Human genes can't be patented

In a welcome display of patent-law sanity, the US Supreme Court has unanimously ruled that human genes can't be patented. "We hold that a naturally occurring DNA segment is a product of nature and not patent eligible merely because it has been isolated," wrote Justice Clarence Thomas, who authored the court's decision. The …

Rik Myslewski, 13 Jun 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7031_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/06/13/dna_helix.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7031-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/05/15/isc_13/</link><title>Cluster kids, pick your weapons: It's the Battle of Leipzig 2.0</title><description>Cluster kids, pick your weapons: It's the Battle of Leipzig 2.0

Napoleon experienced his first defeat* there 200 years ago... Now nine teams of university undergrad students will travel to Leipzig in the hopes of winning the clash of big iron that is the International Supercomputing Conference 2013 (ISC’13) Student Cluster Challenge. Nine teams of university undergrad students will build …

Dan Olds, Gabriel Consulting, 15 May 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7031_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/05/14/isc_13.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>