<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7033">Porto</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:19:48" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7033-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/17/edward_snowden_brazil_asylum_bid/</link><title>Snowden: I'll swap you my anti-NSA knowhow for asylum ... Brazil says: Não</title><description>Snowden: I'll swap you my anti-NSA knowhow for asylum ... Brazil says: Não

NSA whistleblower Edward Snowden has apparently offered Brazil help in uncovering US surveillance of the South American nation – in a fresh plea for asylum. In an open letter published today by the Brazilian newspaper Folha de S. Paulo, it appears Snowden reckons he can assist in sniffing out NSA spying and protect peeps from …

Shaun Nichols, 17 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7033_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/07/11/nsa_sign.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7033-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/12/10/tall_vehicle_relay_experiment/</link><title>White Van Man could become a rolling radio relay</title><description>White Van Man could become a rolling radio relay

The idea that cars should share data among each other to automate some aspects of driving and make more efficient use of roads is not new. But researchers from the Universidade do Porto and Carnegie Mellon University have noted an important impediment to its adoption: cars are smaller than other vehicles – like lorries and vans …

Simon Sharwood, 10 Dec 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7033_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/12/10/tall_vehicle_relay_tests.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7033-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/10/31/argentina_stakes_online_claim_on_falklands/</link><title>Argentina stakes online claim on Falklands</title><description>Argentina stakes online claim on Falklands

Argentina has complained about the continued existence of the Falkland Islands' top-level internet address .fk, according to a local internet users society and other sources. The nation's foreign ministry has written to global domain name overseer ICANN to claim the Falklands belong to Argentina, according to Internauta. "The …

Kevin Murphy, 31 Oct 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7033_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7033-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/02/16/arruda_carnival/</link><title>Miniskirt outrage Brazilian becomes Carnival queen</title><description>Miniskirt outrage Brazilian becomes Carnival queen

The 20-year-old Brazilian lass who was expelled from São Paulo's Bandeirante University for wearing a miniskirt has strutted her stuff as a Rio Carnival queen. Geisy Arruda and her miniskirt Geisy Arruda provoked a near riot at the seat of learning last October by turning up to lectures in what fellow students considered …

Lester Haines, 16 Feb 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7033_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7033-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/06/22/air_crash_hoax/</link><title>Bolivian TV falls for Air France crash hoax</title><description>Bolivian TV falls for Air France crash hoax

Bolivian TV channel PAT has been left looking a bit daft after broadcasting extraordinary images of the last moments of Air France flight 447, lost over the Atlantic on 1 June: According to the report, the snaps were retrieved from a recovered Casio Z750, which was subsequently traced via the serial number to its owner - " …

Lester Haines, 22 Jun 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7033_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7033-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/09/21/phone_battery/</link><title>Yachting blogger plagued by wind, power issues</title><description>Yachting blogger plagued by wind, power issues

One of the things that makes it very easy to spot Americans who are cruising around the Med on sailing boats is the Iridium phones they seem to imagine they need. You only get two or three days to detect them, because they quickly discover that they can buy a Greek SIM card for less than the price of their next ten minutes, and …

Guy Kewney, 21 Sep 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7033_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7033-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/10/10/wsis_podcasts/</link><title>Governments make net grab - Podcast Exclusive</title><description>Governments make net grab - Podcast Exclusive

Who should have control of the Internet? Last month's United Nations meeting in Geneva saw the United States pitched against the EU as well as old foes China, Iran and Cuba in a fight for overall control of the Internet. Stalking the corridors in Geneva last month, Kieren McCarthy collared the great and good at the heart of the …

Team Register, 10 Oct 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7033_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7033-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/09/30/eu_deal_wsis/</link><title>EU deal threatens end to US dominance of internet</title><description>EU deal threatens end to US dominance of internet

Check out Kieren's radio report on Prepcom 3 A dramatic last-minute deal drawn up by the EU may mark the end of the US government's control of the internet. The UK, acting as European representative, stunned delegates from around the world during a late-night session on Wednesday when it produced a series of paragraphs that …

Kieren McCarthy, 30 Sep 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7033_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7033-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2004/07/14/infineon_ec/</link><title>EC green lights Infineon state aid</title><description>EC green lights Infineon state aid

The European Commission has allowed the Portuguese government to provide Infineon with a €71.96m ($88.71m) grant to fund the foundation of a memory chip fab. The grant amounts to 32 per cent of the cost of a project to expand production at its Vila do Conde (Grande Porto) facility. EC investigators had to examine the deal …

Tony Smith, 14 Jul 2004</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7033_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7033-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2003/06/03/weve_seen_the_future_indian/</link><title>We've seen the future, Indian Prez tells Gates – and you're not in it</title><description>We've seen the future, Indian Prez tells Gates – and you're not in it

Each year, while Bill Gates parties at the World Economic Forum at Davos, Richard M Stallman makes a trip to Porto Alegre. Stallman takes part in discussions on alternatives to globalization, US-style, at the World Social Forum. His travel choice appears to be paying off. Last week Indian President Dr Abdul Kalam called for a …

Andrew Orlowski, 03 Jun 2003</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7033_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>