<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7034">sony vaio laptop</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:47:21" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7034-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/11/sony_issues_battery_recall_as_vaio_goes_with_a_bang_not_a_whimper/</link><title>Sony battery recall as VAIO goes out with a bang, not a whimper</title><description>Sony battery recall as VAIO goes out with a bang, not a whimper

If you're one of the few people who bought a Sony VAIO Fit 11A laptop/tablet convertible unit in the last few months, you need to unplug it immediately and step away from the system, Sony has warned. "It has come to our attention that some of the internal, non-removable battery packs provided to us by a third party supplier and …

Iain Thomson, 11 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7034_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/07/18/fireball.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7034-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/07/bugger_my_jetpack_wheres_my_21stcentury_psion/</link><title>Bugger the jetpack, where's my 21st-century Psion?</title><description>Bugger the jetpack, where's my 21st-century Psion?

Way back in 2011 we covered a handy category of portable computer that has completely disappeared. The early A4 portables were a specialist item, much beloved of journalists but not a big hit with the wider world. It took a different design to win those hearts. Psion Organiser II Psion Organiser II Source: babbagecabbage …

Liam Proven, 07 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7034_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/10/09/hc20_17.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7034-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/22/sony_fdr_ax100e_4k_camera_due/</link><title>Sony brings 4K shooting to the masses in weeks</title><description>Sony brings 4K shooting to the masses in weeks

Las Vegas is about 5,200 miles (c. 8,400km) from Blighty’s capital, which makes CES a bit of schlep for all but the terminally keen. Knowing this, Sony UK showcased its finest for 2014 to the UK press this week, from 4K camcorders to er, 4K tellies... with some laptop goodness in between. Most of the laptops we'd all seen before …

Bob Dormon, 22 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7034_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/01/21/sony_fdr_ax100e_4.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7034-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/10/2014_chromebook_surge/</link><title>Why 2014 might just be the year of the Google Chromebook</title><description>Why 2014 might just be the year of the Google Chromebook

Can Google’s Chromebook become the laptop platform of choice during 2014? Probably not, but there’s certainly demand for it. According to US market-watcher NPD, during the 11 months from January through November 2013, the platform’s share of the computing device market had risen to 9.6 per cent from just 0.2 per cent in the same …

Tony Smith, 10 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7034_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/12/31/acer_c720_chromebook_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7034-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/28/review_roundup_lightweight_laptops/</link><title>Mass Effect: Ten lightweight laptops that won’t bust your back</title><description>Mass Effect: Ten lightweight laptops that won’t bust your back

The arrival of Intel’s Haswell processors this year promised a new generation of ultraportable laptops that would be slimmer, lighter and provide better battery life than ever before. With that in mind, El Reg decided to round up 10 of the lightest laptops that we could find and see if they really delivered the goods. Not every …

Cliff Joseph, 28 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7034_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/07/10/air_13_12.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7034-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/17/review_apple_macbook_air_11_inch_2013/</link><title>Apple MacBook Air 11-inch 2013: Netbook with next-gen tech</title><description>Apple MacBook Air 11-inch 2013: Netbook with next-gen tech

“Can’t innovate any more, my ass,” said Apple veep Phil Schiller as he unveiled the redesigned Mac Pro at the company’s Worldwide Developer Conference in June. The smooth, black cylindrical design of the Mac Pro and the visual revamp of the forthcoming iOS 7 were clearly intended as a riposte to the critics who had argued that …

Stephen Dean, 17 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7034_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/07/11/mba11_2.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7034-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/15/review_apple_macbook_air_13_inch_2013/</link><title>Apple MacBook Air 13-inch 2013: All’s well that Haswell</title><description>Apple MacBook Air 13-inch 2013: All’s well that Haswell

El Reg’s review of the latest 13-inch MacBook Air comes in two parts: here, I take a look at one of the build-to-order configurations offered by Apple, which upgrades the standard 1.3GHz Intel Core i5 processor, 4GB of 1066MHZ mobile DDR3 RAM, 128GB solid-state drive specification to a 1.7GHz Core i7 machine with 8GB of RAM and …

Tony Smith, 15 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7034_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/07/10/air_13_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7034-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/05/29/samsung_series_5_ultra_touch_ultrabook/</link><title>Review: Samsung Series 5 Ultra Touch Ultrabook</title><description>Review: Samsung Series 5 Ultra Touch Ultrabook

When it comes to handing out Windows 8 laptops to the UK reviewers, Samsung has been surprisingly glacial. Whether this is another Apple emulation strategy to become more elusive or a sign of hesitancy to have the brand tarnished by Windows 8’s underwhelming reception, is unclear. The hardware was paraded at CES 2013 five months …

Bob Dormon, 29 May 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7034_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/05/28/samsung_series_5_ultra_touch_ultrabook_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7034-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/04/16/feature_windows_rt_tablets_round_up/</link><title>Ten Windows tablets</title><description>Ten Windows tablets

Twelve months ago the idea of compiling a list of Windows tablets that you would actually want to buy would have been as impossible to do as it would have been farcical to suggest. But with the launch of Windows 8 and Windows RT all that has changed, and we are now faced with a bewildering array of fondleslabs all running …

Alun Taylor, 16 Apr 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7034_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/01/04/hp_envy_x2_windows_8_convertible_11.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7034-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/03/05/review_toshiba_satellite_u920t_ultrabook/</link><title>Review: Toshiba Satellite U920T Ultrabook</title><description>Review: Toshiba Satellite U920T Ultrabook

Whatever you might think about Windows 8, when it comes to taking the top down on the new ranges of convertible laptops, it’s certainly not boring. Every single one I’ve encountered so far has a different take on how to make the laptop-tablet duo dance work and Toshiba’s Satellite U920T Ultrabook offers yet another approach. …

Bob Dormon, 05 Mar 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7034_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/03/05/toshiba_satellite_u920t.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>