<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7037">how to write journalistic review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:13:28" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7037-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/08/16/shills/</link><title>Tech hacks should admit taking corporate coin, but don't start a witch hunt</title><description>Tech hacks should admit taking corporate coin, but don't start a witch hunt

Judge Alsup has required Google and Oracle to divulge a list of their paid shills - the bloggers and journos they've paid to comment on their copyright court showdown. This sets a major precedent, the consequences of which could echo throughout tech journalism. While there is a lot of blitting in the back buffers over this, I …

Trevor Pott, 16 Aug 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7037_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/06/13/cash_suitcase.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7037-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/02/19/yelp_pitch_revisited/</link><title>Yelp deflects 'Extortion 2.0' claim</title><description>Yelp deflects 'Extortion 2.0' claim

Yelp continues to face questions over the ethics of its new-age city guide, billed as a place where "real people" write "real reviews" of restaurants, bars, shops, and other local businesses. And it continues to evade those questions. As we reported in August, several San Francisco Bay Area businesses have told The Reg that …

Cade Metz, 19 Feb 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7037_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7037-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/10/24/wikipedia_letters/</link><title>Wikipedia: magic, monkeys and typewriters</title><description>Wikipedia: magic, monkeys and typewriters

Smart mobs? Wise crowds? An open access internet encyclopedia that heals itself? File it all under 'flying saucers', say Register readers. But something is changing since we last wrote about Wikipedia a year ago. Even project founder Jimmy Wales has been obliged to admit its entries are "a horrific embarrassment". Readability, …

Andrew Orlowski, 24 Oct 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7037_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7037-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/07/15/letters_1507/</link><title>From politics to porn, via Microsoft and the supernatural</title><description>From politics to porn, via Microsoft and the supernatural

Bernie Ebbers shed a tear or two as he was sentenced to 25 years in the nick for his part in the financial disaster that was WorldCom. We'd cry, too, in his shoes, and we suspect a lot of other people would too. But that doesn't necessarily mean there is an awful lot of love out there for him: As I was listening to the news …

Lucy Sherriff, 15 Jul 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7037_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7037-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2004/04/18/blogging_future/</link><title>The future of Weblogging</title><description>The future of Weblogging

The rise of Weblogging has been a cold shower for the complacent mass communication industries. Although the Weblogging pioneers are due much praise, their own rhetoric deserves examination, and they could also raise their sights higher. Nico Macdonald reports, and concludes with a radical proposal for the future of Weblogging …

Nico Macdonald, 18 Apr 2004</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7037_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>