<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7039">import .csv excel</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:23:49" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7039-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/12/20/outlook_2013_chops_legacy_word_excel/</link><title>Outlook 2013 spurns your old Word and Excel documents</title><description>Outlook 2013 spurns your old Word and Excel documents

Microsoft is cutting support for exporting and importing legacy Office documents in the latest version of its Outlook email client. Outlook 2013 won’t let you import or export data to or from .doc or .xls files for Word 1997 to 2003 and Excel versions 1997 to 2003, the company has revealed in a blog. Also getting canned are ACT …

Gavin Clarke, 20 Dec 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7039_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7039-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/03/21/how_to_get_paid_more/</link><title>You're crap and paid too much for the little work you actually do</title><description>You're crap and paid too much for the little work you actually do

You’re not getting paid as well as you should. I know this not only because you’re bothering to read this, but also because most techies are crap at extracting cash from their employers. It shouldn’t shock you too much to learn that I, as a City headhunter and former contractor, focus quite hard on money - so here's a few ideas …

Dominic Connor, 21 Mar 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7039_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7039-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/08/04/scottish_exam_results/</link><title>Rogue character space tripped Scottish exam results</title><description>Rogue character space tripped Scottish exam results

A rogue space in the date field caused almost 30,000 Scottish students to get their exam results a day early, as Excel versions clashed and human checking fell down. The texts telling students their Higher results (the Scottish equivalent of A-Levels) were supposed to go out Thursday morning, having been preloaded onto the …

Bill Ray, 04 Aug 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7039_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7039-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/06/02/google_docs_x_support/</link><title>Google Docs caves to MS Office 2007 file formats</title><description>Google Docs caves to MS Office 2007 file formats

Google has finally added support for Microsoft’s Word and Excel 2007 default file formats to its online Docs office suite. Mountain View confirmed the move yesterday. However, support for PowerPoint 2007’s file format remains out in the cold. The firm has added .docx and .xlsx to the list of file formats Google Docs accepts for …

Kelly Fiveash, 02 Jun 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7039_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/03/chandef3.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7039-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/11/13/groovy_mysql/</link><title>Get into data with Groovy</title><description>Get into data with Groovy

In the first part of this two-part series we looked at how Groovy provides a simple and intuitive approach to accessing MySQL. Compared to Java, Groovy is less verbose and more focused on what the developer wants to do with the database. Additionally, things like opening and closing database connections, writing boilerplate …

Dr Pan Pantziarka, 13 Nov 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7039_05_thumb.gif">http://regmedia.co.uk/2005/12/15/mysql_75.gif?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7039-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/10/24/jasperreports_tutorial/</link><title>Creating a Report with JasperReports</title><description>Creating a Report with JasperReports

Preparing presentation-quality reports is an everyday occurrence, so any tool that makes the job easier is worth a look. For developers working with Java, one such is JasperSoft’s JasperReports, which is capable of producing a range of outputs, including HTML, PDF, Excel XLS, CSV and XML file formats. The tool can build dynamic …

Deepak Vohra, 24 Oct 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7039_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>