<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7046">tuning fork</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:30:52" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7046-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/01/25_alternative_pc_operating_systems/</link><title>Fed up with Windows? Linux too easy? Get weird, go ALTERNATIVE</title><description>Fed up with Windows? Linux too easy? Get weird, go ALTERNATIVE

It's hard to believe, looking at the modern computing world, but there is still more to life than Windows or Unix… and today, most of the alternatives run on vanilla x86 hardware and are free. Most of them need considerably lower resources than the market-leaders, too, so an old PC is ideal for trying them out. VMs are fine, but …

Liam Proven, 01 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7046_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/01/steampunk.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7046-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/18/something_for_the_weekend/</link><title>Alarming tales: What goes on INSIDE Reg hack's hi-tech bedroom</title><description>Alarming tales: What goes on INSIDE Reg hack's hi-tech bedroom

Mrs Dabbsy is threatening to decamp to the spare room. It’s reminiscent of those radioactive weeks just over a year ago when she was a bearer of unstable atoms but the culprit this time is not an overactive thyroid but my choice of alarm clock. Sleeper Sleep sound, Dabbsy’s not around Source: Wiros Like many professional …

Alistair Dabbs, 18 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7046_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/03/18/pantless.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7046-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/22/cloudant_couchdb_code/</link><title>Sofa, so good ... BigCouch relaxes into comfy Apache CouchDB</title><description>Sofa, so good ... BigCouch relaxes into comfy Apache CouchDB

Database-as-a-service company Cloudant is pouring its own code into the Apache CouchDB project: the company wants to invigorate the open-source distributed database while halting development of its own fork of the tech. The code merge of Cloudant's tweaked BigCouch database into Apache CouchDB was announced on Monday, and brings …

Jack Clark, 22 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7046_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/07/17/forks_refork.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7046-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/02/26/intel_rolls_up_hadoop_distribution/</link><title>Intel takes on all Hadoop disties to rule big data munching</title><description>Intel takes on all Hadoop disties to rule big data munching

Look out Cloudera, MapR Technologies, EMC, Hortonworks, and IBM: Intel is the new elephant in the room. Intel has been dabbling for the past two years with its own distribution of the Hadoop stack, and starting in the second quarter it will begin selling services for its own variant of the Hadoop big data muncher. Intel is not …

Timothy Prickett Morgan, 26 Feb 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7046_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/07/15/intel_logo.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7046-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/10/03/java8_revolution_not_evolution_oracle/</link><title>Oracle: Java 8 will be revolution, not evolution</title><description>Oracle: Java 8 will be revolution, not evolution

Mark Reinhold, chief architect for Java at Oracle, gave details on developments in Java 8 and beyond, and announced the release of JavaFX 2.0 during his turn on the keynote stage at the JavaOne conference in San Francisco. Oracle cut back on its plans for Java 7 in order to get the new build released in July, adding three of the …

Iain Thomson, 03 Oct 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7046_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7046-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/12/03/gibson_roboguitar/</link><title>Gibson plugs in self-tuning roboguitar</title><description>Gibson plugs in self-tuning roboguitar

Legendary guitar manufacturer Gibson is reporting plenty of interest in its self-tuning Robot Guitar. Gibson's self-tuning roboguitar The technical details of how the axe keeps the strings nicely in tune - via pitch-monitoring bridge, CPU, and servo-motored machine heads - is available here. All the guitarists among you need …

Lester Haines, 03 Dec 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7046_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2007/12/03/gibson_sm.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7046-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/05/04/cloaking_device/</link><title>Scientists moot Romulan-style cloaking device</title><description>Scientists moot Romulan-style cloaking device

Two mathematicians have boldly gone where no boffin has gone before and described the theoretical possibility of a cloaking device, the BBC reports. However, before the Trekkies among you don your Romulan cozzies and rush for a copy of the Royal Society publication in which Nicolae Nicorovici and Graeme Milton expound their …

Lester Haines, 04 May 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7046_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7046-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2004/06/30/letters_3006/</link><title>Cyber appliances, deadly mobiles and free beer</title><description>Cyber appliances, deadly mobiles and free beer

We fear that some of you, our beloved readers, have misunderstood one or two of our stories this week. In particular, we refer to the news that Satan had been implicated in the latest cyber appliance attacks. At this point, we feel obliged to remind readers that it is supposed to be funny. It is slightly worrying that anyone …

Lucy Sherriff, 30 Jun 2004</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7046_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7046-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2002/05/03/hp_compaq_to_trade_under/</link><title>HP, Compaq to trade under “SRCAM” ticker</title><description>HP, Compaq to trade under “SRCAM” ticker

Hewlett Packard (HWP) and Compaq (CPQ) discarded sixty years of cumulative stock market history with a bold gesture that signifies their unity, the companies announced today. From now on, the merged entity will be known as "SRCAM", obsoleting the old ticker symbols. The change is effective from Monday - so please update your …

Andrew Orlowski, 03 May 2002</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7046_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>