<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7051">dinosaur names</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:58:11" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7051-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/07/new_tyrannosaur_species_lythronax_argestes/</link><title>BLOOD KING of the TYRANNOSAURS, grandad of T-Rex</title><description>BLOOD KING of the TYRANNOSAURS, grandad of T-Rex

A new kind of vicious tyrannosaur that pre-dates Tyrannosaurus rex has been unearthed in southern Utah and christened the "King of Gore". Artist's impression of the Lythronax argestes The Tyrannosauridae family already contains massive creatures whose names translate as "frightful" and "fierce" kings as well as "monstrous …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 07 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7051_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/07/lythronax_argestes_dinosaur.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7051-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/06/18/losing_your_job_after_50/</link><title>Fifty, fired and fretful: Three chaps stare down CAREER MORTALITY</title><description>Fifty, fired and fretful: Three chaps stare down CAREER MORTALITY

Donald* guessed what about to happen as soon as the meeting started, so he got in first with a question. “How much will my payout be?” And with that, a fifteen-year stint at a multinational vendor came to an end. Donald's on gardening leave. His employer was obliged to write him a handsome cheque, but his role had seen him …

Simon Sharwood, 18 Jun 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7051_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/02/23/thunder_thighs.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7051-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/06/14/steve_bong_guardiancoffee/</link><title>At #guardiancoffee, we can now TASTE THE FUTURE through a PRISM!</title><description>At #guardiancoffee, we can now TASTE THE FUTURE through a PRISM!

"Everything reactionary is the same; if you do not hit it, it will not fall. This is also like sweeping the floor; as a rule, where the broom does not reach, the dust will not vanish of itself. - Mao Tse Tung from "The Situation and Our Policy After the Victory in the War of Resistance Against Japan" (August 13, 1945), Selected …

Steve Bong, 14 Jun 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7051_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/06/14/hipster_coffee.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7051-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/08/31/postgresql_too_cool_for_school/</link><title>Hipsters hacking on PostgreSQL</title><description>Hipsters hacking on PostgreSQL

With the rise of NoSQL, it's easy to assume that old-school relational databases are simply living out their dinosaur dreams for legacy applications. But a funny thing happened on the way to the SQL cemetery: PostgreSQL became cool again. Yes, PostegreSQL. PostgreSQL was developed in 1986 by Michael Stonebraker. It was meant to …

Matt Asay, 31 Aug 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7051_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/08/31/postgresql.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7051-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/11/23/anne_mccaffrey/</link><title>Dragonriders of Pern author Anne McCaffrey dies</title><description>Dragonriders of Pern author Anne McCaffrey dies

Author of the Dragonrider series of books, Anne McCaffrey, died on Monday aged 85, having authored a huge number of books that straddled the border between science fiction and fantasy. The author suffered a stroke at her home in Ireland on Monday, and passed away shortly afterwards. Her publisher, Del Rey, posted a notification …

Bill Ray, 23 Nov 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7051_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7051-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/10/06/steve_jobs_bio_1/</link><title>The life and times of Steven Paul Jobs, Part One</title><description>The life and times of Steven Paul Jobs, Part One

When sober, F. Scott Fitzgerald may have been devastatingly intelligent, but he got it dead wrong when he wrote "there are no second acts in American lives". Think Elvis, for example. Or lefty sinkerballer Tommy John of the eponymous surgery. Or, for that matter, Grover Cleveland, whose two acts as US president were separated by …

Rik Myslewski, 06 Oct 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7051_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/gen_diskleds.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7051-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/01/21/computer_history_museum_revolution/</link><title>Gates, Woz, and the last 2,000 years of computing</title><description>Gates, Woz, and the last 2,000 years of computing

It's weird to see something from your childhood displayed as an ancient cultural artifact. Here at the newly refurbished Computer History Museum in Mountain View, California, I'm standing over a glass case that houses the Commodore 64, the same machine I begged my parents to buy me for Christmas in 1983. Compared to today's …

Gavin Clarke, 21 Jan 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7051_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7051-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/11/01/comp_sci_graduates_need_more_skills/</link><title>No wonder CompSci grads are unemployed</title><description>No wonder CompSci grads are unemployed

Recently a director at a huge bank asked me “Do British students learn algorithms?” At first I thought he was joking, but even though he was paying three times what the average new grad gets paid, he felt despair. Because of similar experiences I was surprised to read that only 17 per cent of CompSci grads from last year haven’ …

Dominic Connor, 01 Nov 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7051_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7051-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/07/09/mojoceratops/</link><title>New dinosaur dubbed 'Mojoceratops' - 'over a few beers'</title><description>New dinosaur dubbed 'Mojoceratops' - 'over a few beers'

A newly-discovered dinosaur has been officially named the "Mojoceratops". Apparently, beer was involved. The skull of Mojoceratops perifania. Credit: Yale Prehistoric head-frill mojo The discoverer of the new species is post-doctoral researcher Nicholas Longrich of Yale uni in the States, who found skulls and other evidence …

Lewis Page, 09 Jul 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7051_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7051-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/05/25/softky_robots_part_one/</link><title>Why do robot experts build such lousy robots?</title><description>Why do robot experts build such lousy robots?

In Silicon Valley, any conference calling itself the "Best of the Best" promises more fluff than stuff. But a recent Churchill Club event which promised the cream of the robotics industry confirmed the sceptics' worst fears. Consumer robotics is a business built mostly on play, hope and tinkering - rather than profit or …

Bill Softky, 25 May 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7051_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>