<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7057">web of science</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:05:12" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7057-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/15/hearbleed_triage_snafus/</link><title>Akamai scoffs humble pie: Heartbleed defence crumbles, new SSL keys for customers</title><description>Akamai scoffs humble pie: Heartbleed defence crumbles, new SSL keys for customers

Akamai has issued new SSL certificates to some of its customers after realising its customized OpenSSL was not immune to the Heartbleed bug as first thought. Some time ago, the web distribution giant modified the code to the open-source OpenSSL library and rolled the tweaked version out to just its servers: that adjustment …

John Leyden, 15 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7057_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2008/01/17/uncov_fail_ship.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7057-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/15/skygazers_prepare_for_blood_moon_caused_by_earth_eclipse/</link><title>Skygazers prepare for 'blood Moon' caused by Earth eclipse</title><description>Skygazers prepare for 'blood Moon' caused by Earth eclipse

North American night owls will be in prime position to catch their best view of a lunar eclipse at around 1am EDT Tuesday as our natural satellite is overshadowed by Earth. The Earth's shadow will start to cover the Moon's surface at 12:54am EDT and the cover the lunar surface completely between 3:07am and 4:25am, causing a …

Iain Thomson, 15 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7057_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/04/14/blood_moon.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7057-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/09/brit_ibm_researcher_wins_millennium_tech_prize/</link><title>Brit IBM prof gets life-changing 'Tech Nobel' for work in spintronics</title><description>Brit IBM prof gets life-changing 'Tech Nobel' for work in spintronics

A Brit boffin at IBM’s Almaden Research Centre has won a Finnish prize for spintronics research which led to a thousandfold increase in disk capacity. The €1m (£824,400) Millennium Technology prize has been awarded by the Technology Academy of Finland to Stuart Parkin, an IBM Fellow at Almaden where he manages the …

Chris Mellor, 09 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7057_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/04/09/stuart_parkin_teaser.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7057-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/29/hawkins_ai_feature/</link><title>Meet the man building an AI that mimics our neocortex – and could kill off neural networks</title><description>Meet the man building an AI that mimics our neocortex – and could kill off neural networks

Jeff Hawkins has bet his reputation, fortune, and entire intellectual life on one idea: that he understands the brain well enough to create machines with an intelligence we recognize as our own. If his bet is correct, the Palm Pilot inventor will father a new technology, one that becomes the crucible in which a general …

Jack Clark, 29 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7057_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/03/28/hawkins_419x278.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7057-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/25/aakash_tablet_india_project_comment/</link><title>Schoolkids given WORLD'S CHEAPEST TABLETS: Is it really that hard to swallow?</title><description>Schoolkids given WORLD'S CHEAPEST TABLETS: Is it really that hard to swallow?

For some time now The Register has been tracking an effort by the Indian government to provide their schoolchildren with low cost tablets. The subsidised cost of the devices for Indian families is slated to be 1,500 rupees (£14, $24), with the unsubsidised version available to the rest of the world for £30. The decision to …

Trevor Pott, 25 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7057_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/02/22/akash.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7057-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/24/google_withdraws_schaft_from_military_honeypot_spreads_the_wealth/</link><title>Google pulls SCHAFT out of military honeypot, sprays gold at bot team</title><description>Google pulls SCHAFT out of military honeypot, sprays gold at bot team

The team behind SCHAFT, the best-built bot so far in the DARPA Robotics Challenge, will stop dipping into the $1m prize pot it was awarded by the US military – and will instead rely on funds from its new owner, Google. "The decision by Team SCHAFT to self-fund allows DARPA to expand the competition and further develop disaster …

Iain Thomson, 24 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7057_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/01/17/terminatorgoogle.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7057-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/17/boffins_are_good_for_your_business_heres_why/</link><title>Proper boffins make your company succeed, even if you're not very technical</title><description>Proper boffins make your company succeed, even if you're not very technical

Good news for British techies. A wide-ranging innovation study recommends that firms should hire more staff who can solve complex technical problems, even if they’re not tech companies or the techies aren’t employed in a narrowly technical function. So says a report on Innovation and Growth prepared for the Department of …

Andrew Orlowski, 17 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7057_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/boffin.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7057-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/14/quote_of_the_week_ending_march_14/</link><title>Vine's 'educational nudity': 'So if I write 1+1=2 on my boobs we're grand?'</title><description>Vine's 'educational nudity': 'So if I write 1+1=2 on my boobs we're grand?'

This was the week when the internet World Wide Web turned 25 and websites were stuffed with listicles and infographics telling us all about it. But said sites also unfortunately found it difficult to differentiate between the Web and the internet. (For clarity, the internet is the one that's stored in a black box, see …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 14 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7057_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/07/09/chalkboard.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7057-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/11/bbc_pimps_up_iplayer/</link><title>Netflix needling you? BBC pimps up iPlayer ahead of BBC3 move</title><description>Netflix needling you? BBC pimps up iPlayer ahead of BBC3 move

The BBC unveiled a much-needed front-end makeover for its sprawling iPlayer service today – while dodging the inevitable questions about subscriptions. The corporation has updated iPlayer to take on commercial subscription rivals like Netflix, with shows available for longer – 30 days, subject to Trust approval. The details of …

Andrew Orlowski, 11 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7057_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2010/06/28/iplayer_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7057-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/09/googles_tech_training_for_australian_teachers_revealed/</link><title>Google's tech training for Australian teachers revealed</title><description>Google's tech training for Australian teachers revealed

The University of Adelaide's Computer Science Research Group, which was engaged by Google to develop a course to teach digital technologies to Primary School teachers, has released an outline of the course. Google's interest in the matter arises from its support of Australia's Digital Technologies curriculum, the nation's first …

Simon Sharwood, 09 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7057_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/11/flappy_birds_bird.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>