<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7064">Korea weather</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:37:11" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7064-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/18/twitter_alert_system_uk_ireland/</link><title>#ALERT! There'll be EMERGENCIES on TWITTER for UK, Ireland</title><description>#ALERT! There'll be EMERGENCIES on TWITTER for UK, Ireland

Twitter has brought its emergency alert system to the UK and Ireland after it kicked off in the US, Japan and South Korea in September. The microblogging site has signed up Blighty's coppers, firefighters and other government agencies so they can tweet urgent messages at the country in times of crisis, or at least the small …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 18 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7064_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/01/19/twicon_2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7064-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/29/weather_forecast_model_is_imperfect_qed_climate_science_is_rubbish/</link><title>Bugs in beta weather model used to trash climate science</title><description>Bugs in beta weather model used to trash climate science

Development work on a not-yet-prime-time weather forecasting model has been seized on as proof that climate models can't be trusted. The reason? Folks who aren't keen on climate change discovered this paper in the journal of the American Meteorological Society, in which Song-You Hong of South Korea's Yonsei University Department …

Richard Chirgwin, 29 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7064_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/06/06/tianhe_2_render.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7064-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/05/22/big_data_in_japan_manga_anime_map/</link><title>Japan uses big data to map cultural climate change</title><description>Japan uses big data to map cultural climate change

Big data boffins at Tokyo University have found a novel way to help Japan’s faltering economy: by producing an interactive trending map for manga, gaming and other content producers to see where in Asia their products are most popular. The Asia Trend Map was developed by Tokyo University associate professor Matsuo Yutaka with …

Phil Muncaster, 22 May 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7064_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/05/22/doraemon_screen_grab_weather_map.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7064-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/04/30/china_cluster_combat_concluded/</link><title>Red-hot students, an all-day romp and an £11,000 bonanza</title><description>Red-hot students, an all-day romp and an £11,000 bonanza

Red-hot cluster-building students from Tsinghua University in Beijing stepped up their already high-level game - and took two of the three awards up for grabs at the inaugural Asia Student Cluster Challenge (ASC’13) finals last week in Shanghai. ASC’13 is the first leg in 2013’s Student Cluster Competition Triple Crown - a long- …

Dan Olds, Gabriel Consulting, 30 Apr 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7064_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/04/29/student_cluster_performance.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7064-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/03/22/china_makes_linux_os_with_canonical_help/</link><title>Ubuntu tapped by China for national operating system</title><description>Ubuntu tapped by China for national operating system

Ubuntu is going to become the reference architecture for a Linux distribution, backed and developed by the Chinese government. The news means Ubuntu-stewards Canonical will work with China's National University of Defense Technology, and The China Software and Integrated Chip Promotions Center, to develop a Chinese-flavored …

Jack Clark, 22 Mar 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7064_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7064-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/03/21/google_changes_adwords_trademark_policy/</link><title>Google extends trademarks-in-ads policy to whole world</title><description>Google extends trademarks-in-ads policy to whole world

Google has altered its policy on the use of trademarks on AdWords, extending permission for advertisers to use rivals' trademarks in their ads to every nation on earth. The text ads giant has posted a trademark policy update in which it offers the following explanation for the change: Google's goal is to provide our users with …

Simon Sharwood, 21 Mar 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7064_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2008/03/18/google_adwords_machine.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7064-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/12/18/search_engines_we_have_known/</link><title>Search engines we have known ... before Google crushed them</title><description>Search engines we have known ... before Google crushed them

Remember when the internet was young, moving your bulky monitor was a two-person job and 1.4MB disks didn't look like a typo? Back then (most) people didn't have to choose which web search engine they were going to use: it came prepared by the operating system maker, such as Microsoft and MSN Search, or the folks you got your …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 18 Dec 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7064_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/12/17/altavvista2.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7064-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/10/23/vmware_q3_2012_numbers/</link><title>VMware profits pinched in Q3, but not as pinchy as expected</title><description>VMware profits pinched in Q3, but not as pinchy as expected

Despite the fact that the economic conditions in Europe and Australia weakened in the third quarter and that the company didn't launch its updated virtualization and cloud software until late August, VMware turned in numbers that more or less met expectations. Just the same, profits were down 11.7 per cent to $156.8m against a …

Timothy Prickett Morgan, 23 Oct 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7064_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/08/27/vmware_monster_vm.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7064-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/08/15/resource_boom_bolsters_telco/</link><title>Mining boom sparks IT jobs rush</title><description>Mining boom sparks IT jobs rush

Australia’s mining and resources boom is driving demand for IT workers, as new, lucrative tenders see vendors and miners alike start work on new projects. Kordia Solutions Australia snared a flagship coal seam gas tender this week with the AUD$90 million communications services contract from Australia Pacific LNG (APLNG), after …

Natalie Apostolou, 15 Aug 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7064_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/08/15/prelude_natural_gas_plant.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7064-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/03/31/sgi_awe_korea_af_japan_cyclone/</link><title>UK nuke lab, Korean Air Force buy SGI supers</title><description>UK nuke lab, Korean Air Force buy SGI supers

Supercomputer maker Silicon Graphics Inc (SGI) has sold two of its shared memory Altix UV systems to the UK's Atomic Weapons Establishment (AWE) nuke lab and an Altix ICE 8400 cluster to the Korean Air Force. The company is also making processing capacity on its Cyclone HPC cloud service available to customers in Japan who have …

Timothy Prickett Morgan, 31 Mar 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7064_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>