<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7067">used kindle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:05:33" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7067-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/15/amazon_3d_phone_rumours_and_technology/</link><title>Rounded corners? Pah! Amazon's '3D phone has eye-tracking tech'</title><description>Rounded corners? Pah! Amazon's '3D phone has eye-tracking tech'

Amazon is reportedly planning to launch a smartphone with an active 3D display. It is claimed the device has been shown to developers in California ahead of an official unveiling in June, and that the tech will go on sale in September. The Wall Street Journal reports that the glasses-free 3D technology uses "retina" tracking, …

Simon Rockman, 15 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7067_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/05/06/fantasy_tech_3.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7067-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/09/review_dell_wyse_cloud_connect_android_ultrathin_client/</link><title>Dell Wyse Cloud Connect: Pocket Android desktop</title><description>Dell Wyse Cloud Connect: Pocket Android desktop

When somebody hands you a dongle-sized computer, you might, for a moment, be impressed. But when they then put it in a bag with a Bluetooth keyboard and mouse and suggest you find a monitor somewhere, you might wonder what exactly it is they are trying to sell you. Dell Wyse Cloud Connect Android dongle Mini USB – fancy seeing …

Bob Dormon, 09 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7067_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/03/12/dell_wyse_cloud_connect.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7067-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/24/mwc_2014_new_nokia_android_phones_coming_europe_toikkanen/</link><title>Nokia launches Euro ANDROID invasion, quips: 'Microsoft knew what they were buying'</title><description>Nokia launches Euro ANDROID invasion, quips: 'Microsoft knew what they were buying'

Microsoft was aware of Nokia's plans to release a range of Android phones, the man in charge of the new range told us today. And the new Nokiadroids - of which there are more than anyone predicted - will be coming to the UK - possibly sooner than anyone realises. Timo Toikkanen, Executive Vice President of Nokia Mobile Phones …

Andrew Orlowski, 24 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7067_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/03/microsoft_nokia.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7067-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/23/feature_christmas_gift_giving_gotchas/</link><title>Gift-giving gotchas: How to avoid Xmas morning EMBARRASSMENT</title><description>Gift-giving gotchas: How to avoid Xmas morning EMBARRASSMENT

You might think, what with gift buying out of the way, the hard work of the holiday season is largely done. Not so. Before you reach for the wrapping paper and sticky tape, there’s a fair bit more you can do to ensure a trouble- and tantrum-free Christmas Day. Batteries not included If you’ve been buying gadgets, don’t forget …

Nigel Whitfield, 23 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7067_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/08/16/gift.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7067-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/16/end_xmas_prezzie_indecision_misery_with_el_regs_lastminute_gift_guide/</link><title>Excise Xmas prezzie indecision MISERY with El Reg’s gift guide²</title><description>Excise Xmas prezzie indecision MISERY with El Reg’s gift guide²

Christmas is special. When else will you spending lots of money you don’t have buying things they don’t deserve for people you don’t like? That said, we all grudgingly accept that you may want to buy some presents for people this year – bah humbug – even if you haven’t an earthly what to buy them. To help you out, we’ve come up …

Nigel Whitfield, 16 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7067_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/08/16/red_gift.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7067-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/06/palantir_mega_funding/</link><title>Big Brother's software firm Palantir valued at $9 BEEELION</title><description>Big Brother's software firm Palantir valued at $9 BEEELION

How much does it cost to buy out one of big brother's favored toolmakers? Around $9bn, according to a recent valuation of Silicon Valley darling Palantir. The "Big Data" analysis company made a Form D filing with the SEC on Thursday disclosing a $58m cash infusion, and other reports by The Wall Street Journal, The New York Times …

Jack Clark, 06 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7067_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/04/19/kindle_bb.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7067-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/21/review_apple_ipad_mini_retina_display/</link><title>Dear-ly beloved: Apple’s costly iPad Mini with Retina Display</title><description>Dear-ly beloved: Apple’s costly iPad Mini with Retina Display

Last year’s iPad Mini really was playing second fiddle to the regular iPad. Not merely smaller than its sibling, the Mini had a much lower resolution display. It had a less powerful processor too. It felt like a product Apple was obliged to make rather than one it actually wanted to. Twelve months on, and the Mini’s first update …

Tony Smith, 21 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7067_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/19/ipm_8.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7067-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/31/nook_glowlight/</link><title>B&amp;N's spooky glowing Nook unzips wand, turns 4GB into 2.5GB of space</title><description>B&amp;N's spooky glowing Nook unzips wand, turns 4GB into 2.5GB of space

Just in time for the holiday shopping season, US bookseller Barnes &amp; Noble has refreshed its Nook line of e-readers with an upgraded glowing E Ink model. The new Android-powered device is essentially a refresh of the earlier Nook Simple Touch with GlowLight version, although this one drops the Simple Touch branding in favor of …

Neil McAllister, 31 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7067_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/10/31/nook_glowlight.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7067-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/25/on_saying_goodbye/</link><title>Reg mobile correspondent Bill Ray hangs up his Vulture hat</title><description>Reg mobile correspondent Bill Ray hangs up his Vulture hat

It's Friday afternoon and my last day as a reporter for The Register. After well over 4,000 articles, and seven years, I'm hanging up my hack's mac and filing away my Press card. I'm not jumping ship to The Telegraph or taking a seat at the New York Times as some of my colleagues have, partly because they never offered me the …

Bill Ray, 25 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7067_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/26/bill-ray.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7067-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/17/windows_8_point_1_surface_two/</link><title>Here comes Windows 8.1! Microsoft grits teeth, pushes upgrade to world</title><description>Here comes Windows 8.1! Microsoft grits teeth, pushes upgrade to world

Microsoft today unleashed Windows 8.1, the version to soothe folks ruffled by the touchscreen-friendly user interface. Crucially, the software giant really didn’t want to make this particular upgrade: it's effectively stepped back from the original Windows 8 blueprint. At 4am Pacific time (7am Eastern, 12 noon UK time), …

Gavin Clarke, 17 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7067_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/11/win_1_8_pin_to_start.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>