<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7070">compact flash memory card</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:38:26" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7070-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/28/sony_xperia_z1_compact/</link><title>Little pink handjob: Sony's Xperia Z1 Compact</title><description>Little pink handjob: Sony's Xperia Z1 Compact

For the last 18 or so months, if you'd wanted a high-end Android smartphone you’ve had to make do with something a bit on the large size. The HTC One, Samsung Galaxy S4, LG G Flex, Nokia 925, Sony Xperia Z1 all have one thing in common: they are big old Hectors compared to Apple’s iPhone 5S. Sony Xperia Z1 Compact Sony Xperia …

Alun Taylor, 28 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7070_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/03/10/sony_xperia_z1_compact.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7070-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/01/acer_c720_chromebook/</link><title>Acer C720 Chromebook with Haswell battery boosting goodness</title><description>Acer C720 Chromebook with Haswell battery boosting goodness

You know, sometimes you’ve got to wonder what enables a design to go into production. I’m looking at the Acer C720 Chromebook and appreciating its dinkiness, the non-reflective 11.6in TFT screen and the fact that it was more than happy to take a bog-standard USB Ethernet adapter and run with it. Acer C720 Chromebook Acer's C720 …

Bob Dormon, 01 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7070_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/12/31/acer_c720_chromebook_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7070-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/10/samsung_uncloaks_industrys_first_oneterabyte_msata_ssd/</link><title>Samsung uncloaks 'industry's first' one-terabyte mSATA SSD</title><description>Samsung uncloaks 'industry's first' one-terabyte mSATA SSD

Samsung has revealed what it dubs the "industry's first" one-terabyte solid-state drive in the compact mSATA form factor. From what we know of the SSD landscape, their claim is an honest one – by over a factor of two, seeing as how 480GB mSATA SSDs from Crucial and a few others are the most capacious such drives available in the …

Rik Myslewski, 10 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7070_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/12/09/samsung_ssd_419x278.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7070-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/25/review_electric_imp_internet_of_things_card/</link><title>Little devil: Electric Imp is an Internet of Things Wi-Fi PC-ON-AN-SD-CARD</title><description>Little devil: Electric Imp is an Internet of Things Wi-Fi PC-ON-AN-SD-CARD

Most products’ origins are prosaic: an inventor or a suit spots a gap in the market and attempts to fill it. Other products, however, have rather more bizarre beginnings. A case in point: Electric Imp came about because co-founder Hugo Fiennes wanted to connect the lights in his new bathroom to the internet. That’s just the kind …

Tony Smith, 25 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7070_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/20/imp_8.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7070-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/09/17/20_years_of_the_apple_newton/</link><title>Stylus counsel: The rise and fall of the Apple Newton MessagePad</title><description>Stylus counsel: The rise and fall of the Apple Newton MessagePad

It will forever be remembered as the butt of a-thousand-and-one jokes about its poor handwriting recognition, but Apple’s MessagePad was bold in its conception. Its legacy is ARM’s conquest of the mobile microprocessor world. The company said on 8 August 1993: The Newton MessagePad is the first in a family of communications …

Tony Smith, 17 Sep 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7070_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/16/mp_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7070-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/09/09/review_google_asus_nexus_7_2013/</link><title>Google Nexus 7 2013: Fondledroids, THE 7-inch slab has arrived</title><description>Google Nexus 7 2013: Fondledroids, THE 7-inch slab has arrived

When Google launched the Asus-built Nexus 7 Android tablet back in August 2012, it dropped a big mean city-raised alleycat among the budget tablet pigeons. Starting at only £160 for the 8GB version, the Nexus 7 offered performance, style and build quality (kind of) at a price that previously had only bought you shoddy no-name …

Alun Taylor, 09 Sep 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7070_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/09/nexus7_6.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7070-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/18/data_storage_technology/</link><title>Why data storage technology is pretty much PERFECT</title><description>Why data storage technology is pretty much PERFECT

Reliable data storage is central to IT and therefore to modern life. We take it for granted, but what lies beneath? Digital video guru and IT author John Watkinson gets into the details of how it works together and serves us today, as well as what might happen in the future. Brain cells at the ready? This is gonna hurt. Digital …

John Watkinson, 18 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7070_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/07/19/flash_storage_chip.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7070-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/06/11/review_beagleboard_beaglebone_black/</link><title>Review: Beagleboard Beaglebone Black</title><description>Review: Beagleboard Beaglebone Black

It's nice to see that the broader community of Arduino, Raspberry Pi and Beagleboard Beaglebone users is a friendly and seemingly mature one. Each of these board computers has its own adherents, but few of them seem to feel the need to engage in the kind of hair-pulling and name-calling that defined the Windows versus Mac spat …

Tony Smith, 11 Jun 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7070_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/06/03/bbb_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7070-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/04/29/feature_ten_netbook_ancestors/</link><title>Ten ancestors of the netbook</title><description>Ten ancestors of the netbook

Come 2015, we’re told, the netbook will be dead and gone, out-evolved by the more fleet of foot, more desirable media tablet. We shouldn’t mourn the netbook’s passing, though. It has had, in one form or another, a good innings. While some folk may look back to the category’s debut in 2007 with the launch of Asus’ Eee PC 701 - …

Tony Smith, 29 Apr 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7070_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/04/22/portfolio.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7070-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/04/04/review_intel_next_unit_of_computing/</link><title>Review: Intel Next Unit of Computing barebones desktop PC</title><description>Review: Intel Next Unit of Computing barebones desktop PC

Intel must really like the sound of its own ‘voice’. How else can you explain the fact that sliding open the box containing the chip giant’s latest desktop package plays the ding-da-ding-ding-ding jingle as soon as you open it. Amaze your friends! Irritate your colleagues! Keep opening and closing the box to replay the ditty …

Tony Smith, 04 Apr 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7070_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/03/22/nuc_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>