<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7077">django django</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:10:53" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7077-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/03/italy_copyright_law_google_demote_carly_rae_jepsen/</link><title>Italy has a clumsy new pirate-choker law. But can anyone do better?</title><description>Italy has a clumsy new pirate-choker law. But can anyone do better?

New technology means anyone can now create and distribute their creative works, like photos or music, like never before – but, in turn, it also means that anyone can now rip off creators. And yesterday, a range of speakers – from Google to legal experts to enforcement teams – met at the London HQ of law firm Bristows for an …

Andrew Orlowski, 03 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7077_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2009/06/30/destroy_capitalism_support_piracy_nesson.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7077-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/23/fedora_20_final_review/</link><title>DJANGO UNCHAINED: Don't let 'preview' apps put you off Fedora 20</title><description>DJANGO UNCHAINED: Don't let 'preview' apps put you off Fedora 20

If you're a fan of GNOME 3 and the GNOME Shell, Fedora 20 will be a welcome update. This release sees an upgrade for Fedora's default GNOME spin, bringing the desktop to GNOME 3.10. Fedora's live desktop CD has used GNOME by default for many years now. Once upon a time that was completely unremarkable. However, since Ubuntu now …

Scott Gilbertson, 23 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7077_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/05/31/fedora_schrodinger_s_cat_linux.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7077-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/05/fedora_19_final_review/</link><title>Fedora back on track with Schrödinger's cat</title><description>Fedora back on track with Schrödinger's cat

Fedora 19, codenamed Schrödinger's Cat, follows the much-delayed Fedora 18 and the good news is things looks to be back on track. Not only is the release just a week away but it also sees Fedora returning to its core focus: building useful software for developers. The Ubuntu Linux distro may be busy tricking out its new touch- …

Scott Gilbertson, 05 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7077_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/05/31/fedora_schrodinger_s_cat_linux.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7077-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/05/31/fedora_19_beta_review/</link><title>Fedora's Schrödinger's Cat Linux gives coders claws for thought</title><description>Fedora's Schrödinger's Cat Linux gives coders claws for thought

The Schrödinger's cat thought experiment, devised by Erwin Schrödinger in 1935, pits the theory of quantum superposition against what we observe to be true. In the world of Linux distros, in theory the beta version of Fedora 18 was slated for release in early October 2012 with the aim of producing a final build in November that …

Scott Gilbertson, 31 May 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7077_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/05/31/fedora_schrodinger_s_cat_linux.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7077-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/02/25/razzie_results/</link><title>Razzie voters drive stake through Twilight</title><description>Razzie voters drive stake through Twilight

The 33rd Razzie Awards honoured Twilight: Breaking Dawn Part 2 over the weekend with no less than seven statuettes for outrages against the cinematic art, with the final installment of the teen vampire franchise picking up Worst Picture, Worst Actress (Kristen Stewart) Worst Supporting Actor (Taylor Lautner), Worst Screen Couple …

Lester Haines, 25 Feb 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7077_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7077-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/02/08/game_column_feb/</link><title>Bioshock Infinite, Devil May Cry, SimCity</title><description>Bioshock Infinite, Devil May Cry, SimCity

The first few months of the year are, as ever, a time for the public and publishers alike to draw breath after the Christmas frenzy. Only a handful of full-price games launch, giving gamers time to catch a breath and ponder what they’ll spend their money on in the year to come. That said, this period is already clocking up …

Mike Plant, 08 Feb 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7077_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/games_6.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7077-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/08/20/python_amazon_beanstalk/</link><title>Python slithers up Amazon's Beanstalk</title><description>Python slithers up Amazon's Beanstalk

Python has become the newest language welcomed into the Amazon’s cloud fold, through the Amazon Web Services' Elastic Beanstalk. The cloud giant today announced that Python applications are now supported on Elastic Beanstalk – along with PHP, Java and Microsoft’s family .NET. The news smooths the way for the DJango and Flask …

Gavin Clarke, 20 Aug 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7077_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7077-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/06/18/scripting_languages_in_the_enterprise/</link><title>Python wraps its coils around the enterprise</title><description>Python wraps its coils around the enterprise

The enterprise, long the stodgy bastion of mainframes, Oracle databases, and Windows servers, is starting to look a lot more like the consumer technology companies that eschew it. As enterprises embrace the web as a way to conduct business and manage employees, they're embracing the very technology stacks originally made popular …

Matt Asay, 18 Jun 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7077_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7077-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/04/30/inside_pinterest_virtual_data_center/</link><title>Revealed: Inside super-soaraway Pinterest's virtual data centre</title><description>Revealed: Inside super-soaraway Pinterest's virtual data centre

It's every startup's dream: to be growing faster than Facebook without having to build a Facebook-sized server farm. Pinterest is an online picture pinboard for organising your favourite snaps and sharing them. It was founded by Ben Silbermann, Paul Sciarra, and Evan Sharp in March 2010, and it's growing like crazy with just 12 …

Timothy Prickett Morgan, 30 Apr 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7077_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/gen_glare.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7077-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/09/29/heroku_python_engine_yard_jruby/</link><title>Heroku floats heavenly Python into platform cloud</title><description>Heroku floats heavenly Python into platform cloud

The polyglotting of platform clouds continues apace, with the Heroku platform-as-a-service cloud, owned by Salesforce.com, announcing support for PHP, and with PaaS competitor Engine Yard adding support for JRuby. Heroku, which deploys its PaaS layer on top of Amazon's EC2 compute cloud, already supports Ruby, Node.js, Clojure, …

Timothy Prickett Morgan, 29 Sep 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7077_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>