<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7078">count in korean</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:35:47" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7078-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/08/next_television_curved_screen/</link><title>Bendy or barmy: Why your next TV will be curved</title><description>Bendy or barmy: Why your next TV will be curved

For a while it looked like the future of television was fairly clear-cut. Full HD would beget 4K Ultra HD and at some point in the future, presumably when we all owned flying cars and had relatives commuting to Mars, that would evolve into 8K Super Hi-Vision. Apart from trifling things like resolution, colour gamut and frame …

Steve May, 08 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7078_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/09/lg_ultra_hd_curved_oled_tv.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7078-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/14/something_for_the_weekend/</link><title>Spam, a lot of it: Bubble tea is the Seoul of wit</title><description>Spam, a lot of it: Bubble tea is the Seoul of wit

Your Spam Manager is holding 4 messages. Oh here we go... Subject: Customer Invoice Payment From an email address beginning "realestatetips"? I think not. Subject: PLEASE Update BANK DetaiLS Gosh yes that looks genuine, must open that later and run the attachment. Subject: Carreer oppurtunity As a literary agent, I suppose …

Alistair Dabbs, 14 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7078_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/14/spam_11.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7078-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/11/kaesong_internet_connectivity_norks/</link><title>North Korea to switch on the interwebs</title><description>North Korea to switch on the interwebs

North Korea has agreed to allow internet access within its borders, or at least within the bounds of an industrial park run jointly with firms from the South. Pyongyang officials have agreed to open a business centre in the Kaesong Industrial Complex in the first half of the year, which will initially house 20 internet-connected …

Phil Muncaster, 11 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7078_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/04/kim_jong_un_computer.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7078-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/31/canalys_fourth_quarter_pcs_tablets/</link><title>Apple and Android split Santa's stash, go on Xmas PC and tab high</title><description>Apple and Android split Santa's stash, go on Xmas PC and tab high

Apple sold more tablets and PCs than anybody over the Christmas trading period but – just like everybody else – it felt growing pressure from Google’s Android. That is the story of PC and tablet makers for the fourth quarter of 2013, according to the first numbers for the period from analyst outfit Canalys, given to The Register …

Gavin Clarke, 31 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7078_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/28/christmas_child_tablet_shutterstock.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7078-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/09/stars_of_ces_2014/</link><title>Spock-style gadget can SMELL my PEE! Weird gizmos of CES 2014</title><description>Spock-style gadget can SMELL my PEE! Weird gizmos of CES 2014

The Las Vegas-hosted 2014 Consumer Electronics Show (CES) is still running, of course, but the majority of the announcements have been made: a fair few before the show even started, in a bid to get ahead of the rest. Like early morning shoppers, though, everyone figures out the pre-show press release trick soon enough and now …

Tony Smith, 09 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7078_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/01/08/ces_17.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7078-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/08/29/apples_tops_the_target_list_for_litigious_patent_trolls/</link><title>Apple tops target list for litigious patent trolls</title><description>Apple tops target list for litigious patent trolls

Apple has gained the dubious honor of being the top target for patent trolls, or to give them their polite title, Non-Practicing Entities (NPE). Patent Freedom, a collection of companies that monitor the booming NPE industry, reports that in 2012 Cupertino topped the list for patent litigation with 44 cases brought and another …

Iain Thomson, 29 Aug 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7078_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/06/20/troll.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7078-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/26/solidfire_shoots_out_big_muvver/</link><title>SolidFire snaps up $31m in funding, brandishes 3.4PB monster</title><description>SolidFire snaps up $31m in funding, brandishes 3.4PB monster

Cloud flash array startup SolidFire has snagged $31 million in C-round funding and revealed a bad-ass flash array delivering up to 7.5 million IOPS - and a claimed 3.4PB capacity. That capacity in SolidFire's SF9010 is after dedupe, compression and thin provisioning have been applied, and with the maximum of 100 nodes ganged …

Chris Mellor, 26 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7078_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2008/11/12/godzillaattack.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7078-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/05/31/samsung_plays_intel_against_arm/</link><title>Galaxy Tab 3 10.1: Samsung plays Intel against ARM</title><description>Galaxy Tab 3 10.1: Samsung plays Intel against ARM

Samsung are about to announce a Galaxy tablet running Android but with Intel inside. And while it is a victory for the US chip goliath, it's also one which could prove pyrrhic given the large amount of cash Intel will have to cough. Samsung has booked a London launch for 20 June, with new Windows tablets expected but not …

Bill Ray, 31 May 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7078_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7078-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/01/02/arm_server_future/</link><title>ARM server hype ramps faster than ARM server chips</title><description>ARM server hype ramps faster than ARM server chips

If I didn't have to man El Reg's systems desk for a paycheck and had a little venture capital to blow, I might start a company called Leg Systems, headquartered on the Isle of Man – not because of its tax haven status (which is eroding), but because my company would sell ARM-based systems and say that we wouldn't charge an arm …

Timothy Prickett Morgan, 02 Jan 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7078_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/01/02/isle_of_man_flag.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7078-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/12/31/2012_review/</link><title>2012 in tech: Apple up the Cook without a paddle, ARM, slab wars... and MORE</title><description>2012 in tech: Apple up the Cook without a paddle, ARM, slab wars... and MORE

Great Britain reminded the world who invented the web at London 2012 Olympics, Apple cocked up its maps, Microsoft returned to hardware with Surface, we saw a rise of the machines on Wall Street and many of us rubbed our hands with glee as Facebook IPO's deflated. This was the last 12 months in technology. So put the in-laws on …

Gavin Clarke, 31 Dec 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7078_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/12/27/berner_lee_olympics_opening_ceremony.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>