<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7079">a-team theme music</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:03:13" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7079-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/27/review_opensuse_13_1/</link><title>OpenSUSE 13.1: Oh look, a Linux with YOU in mind (and 64-bit ARMs)</title><description>OpenSUSE 13.1: Oh look, a Linux with YOU in mind (and 64-bit ARMs)

Linux distro OpenSUSE 13.1 is a modest but important update that concentrates on stability and overall polish. There are quite a few new features - like the rewritten system configuration utility YaST, new developer tools even a new version of OpenSUSE for Raspberry Pi - but 13.1 is really focused on building a rock-solid Linux …

Scott Gilbertson, 27 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7079_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/18/opensuse_13_beta_1_screen_shot2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7079-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/09/09/history_of_magnetic_tape_part_one/</link><title>Reelin' in the years: Tracking the history of magnetic tape</title><description>Reelin' in the years: Tracking the history of magnetic tape

Today marks the 80th anniversary of the first patent filing for a magnetic tape recording medium, though the tech I worked with was a bit more recent than that. Still, it has been quite some time since I last went shopping for tape. I recall the last time as being a deal on a load of JVC miniDV cassettes that I still haven't …

Bob Dormon, 09 Sep 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7079_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/04/12/fritz_pfleumer_with_tape_recorder.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7079-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/08/24/top_10_steve_ballmer_quotes_from_microsoft_history/</link><title>Top 10 Steve Ballmer quotes: '%#&amp;@!!' and so much more</title><description>Top 10 Steve Ballmer quotes: '%#&amp;@!!' and so much more

When it comes to quotable CEOs, Steve Ballmer may not be the best in the business, but he has managed come up with some zingers. As he prepares to make his transition from top dog at Microsoft, we thought it would be a good time to survey some of the most memorable Ballmerisms of past years, and see how they worked out in …

Iain Thomson, 24 Aug 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7079_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2010/02/19/ballmerfallout.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7079-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/08/19/midi_spec_1_is_30_happy_birthday_musical_instrument_digital_interface/</link><title>Happy birthday MIDI 1.0: Getting pop stars wired for 30 years</title><description>Happy birthday MIDI 1.0: Getting pop stars wired for 30 years

Back in the early days of computer music, Reg man Bob Dormon was a professional recording engineer and music programmer. With a little help from some of his old music gear, he documents the rise of MIDI from a creative concept to its practical applications – which have ultimately led to its recognition as a Grammy Award-winning …

Bob Dormon, 19 Aug 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7079_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/08/14/dennis_irwin_illustration_midi_birthday_party.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7079-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/12/31/2012_review/</link><title>2012 in tech: Apple up the Cook without a paddle, ARM, slab wars... and MORE</title><description>2012 in tech: Apple up the Cook without a paddle, ARM, slab wars... and MORE

Great Britain reminded the world who invented the web at London 2012 Olympics, Apple cocked up its maps, Microsoft returned to hardware with Surface, we saw a rise of the machines on Wall Street and many of us rubbed our hands with glee as Facebook IPO's deflated. This was the last 12 months in technology. So put the in-laws on …

Gavin Clarke, 31 Dec 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7079_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/12/27/berner_lee_olympics_opening_ceremony.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7079-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/10/10/ms_security_intel_report_v13/</link><title>Microsoft: Pirates at high risk of malware infection</title><description>Microsoft: Pirates at high risk of malware infection

Web-based attacks are on the rise, but according to Microsoft security researchers, the risks involved with casual browsing are nothing compared to the dangers of downloading and sharing illicit software, videos, music, and other media. In the latest edition of the Microsoft Security Intelligence Report, published on Monday, …

Neil McAllister, 10 Oct 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7079_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7079-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/09/27/talktalk_youview_iptv_launch/</link><title>TalkTalk's YouView box gets Ab Fab reception</title><description>TalkTalk's YouView box gets Ab Fab reception

UK telecoms provider TalkTalk added YouView IPTV to its product portfolio in London today with the release of its own set top box. Although made by Huawei, the telco had a hand in its interface design and offers it free to all its Plus package customers. TalkTalk YouView set top box launch TalkTalk's STB is Huawei built but the …

Bob Dormon, 27 Sep 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7079_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/27/talktalk_youview_stb_launch_75.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7079-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/11/01/scc_texas/</link><title>University of Texas</title><description>University of Texas

This is the second year the University of Texas Longhorns will compete in the Student Cluster Challenge at the annual Supercomputing Conference. They brought a lot of personality to the competition last year with a “TACC to the Future” theme combining one of their sponsors (University of Texas Advanced Computing Center) with the …

Dan Olds, Gabriel Consulting, 01 Nov 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7079_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/gen_hd.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7079-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/10/10/steve_jobs_bio_2/</link><title>The life and times of Steven Paul Jobs, Part Two</title><description>The life and times of Steven Paul Jobs, Part Two

Before Steve Jobs introduced the iMac on May 6, 1998, his life – as we detailed earlier – had been a roller-coaster of ups and downs. After the iMac shipped on August 15 of that same year, however, he and the company he led traded that carnival ride for a rocket. The iMac was an immediate success. "We have had a phenomenal …

Rik Myslewski, 10 Oct 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7079_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/gen_glare.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7079-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/06/30/ten_years_on_g4_cube_rip/</link><title>The Cube: Apple's daftest, strangest romance</title><description>The Cube: Apple's daftest, strangest romance

Ten years ago on Sunday, Apple called it quits on one of its oddest products ever, the G4 Cube. The Cube was a strange and wonderful machine that continues to fascinate today - but it was widely perceived to have failed. Some people thoroughly enjoyed the failure, thinking it served Apple right. Dull people will always cheer a …

Andrew Orlowski, 30 Jun 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7079_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/06/30/cube_sm.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>