<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7082">The raven</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:29:56" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7082-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/24/game_theory_pikmin_3_the_raven_dota_2/</link><title>Pikmin to the rescue: Can Nintendo revamp revive Wii U fortunes?</title><description>Pikmin to the rescue: Can Nintendo revamp revive Wii U fortunes?

With the heatwave apparently set to give way to stormy weather, it might be about time to batten down the hatches and get comfy with a new game. This week we’re off for a walk in the forest with Pikmin 3, tracking down a master thief in The Raven and getting overwhelmed by choice in Valve’s Dota 2. Pikmin 3 The Wii U’s version …

Mike Plant, 24 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7082_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/07/24/pikmin3_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7082-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/11/30/raven_beak_gesture/</link><title>Ravens' secret sign code probed</title><description>Ravens' secret sign code probed

A conspiracy of ravens may be conspiring more than we ever thought, as researchers have discovered that the carrion-scoffing birds use their beaks to gesture and communicate. Raven croaking Raven croaking. Credit: Franco Atirador Previously, so-called deictic gestures – such as pointing to signify "look" and holding something …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 30 Nov 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7082_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7082-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/06/29/games_review_singularity/</link><title>Singularity</title><description>Singularity

I'm not sure why I'm writing this review when you've already played Singularity countless times before. Don't worry, though. Your memory isn't failing you. Quite the contrary, it's working far too well. Singularity Now now, you've gone and got a head of yourself You see, you fought Singularity's amorphous mutants in Dead …

Andrew Bailey, 29 Jun 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7082_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2010/06/28/games_review_singularity_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7082-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/12/04/3d_football_broadcast/</link><title>American 'football' goes 3D</title><description>American 'football' goes 3D

Three select - and well-connected - audiences in Los Angeles, New York, and Boston were scheduled Thursday night to watch the first 3D broadcast of an American "football" game, according to Dvice. The technology behind this demonstration event will be provided by 3ality Digital, a California company whose chairman, David Modell …

Rik Myslewski, 04 Dec 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7082_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7082-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/07/08/aerovironment_puma_deal_socom/</link><title>Aerovironment sells hurl 'n' splash roboplane to US spec-ops</title><description>Aerovironment sells hurl 'n' splash roboplane to US spec-ops

The US Special Operations Command, SOCOM - aka the "snake eater community"* - has just placed a new order for hand-launched aerial surveillance robots which could be worth up to $200m and see hundreds of portable drones delivered. The potentially very lucky company is Aerovironment, already well known for such projects as the …

Lewis Page, 08 Jul 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7082_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7082-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/10/19/vrs_value_gap_report/</link><title>Apple, Tesco 'most to blame' for music biz crisis</title><description>Apple, Tesco 'most to blame' for music biz crisis

A new report suggests that Apple and Tesco, not P2P file sharers, should take the most blame for the woes of the British music industry. The report, prepared privately by consultants Capgemini for the Value Recognition Strategy working group, set out to examine the "value gap", the amount sound recordings revenue has fallen in …

Andrew Orlowski, 19 Oct 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7082_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2006/05/03/itunes_sm.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7082-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/04/20/no_no_not_the_robodoc_aieee/</link><title>NASA, DoD in underwater astronaut doc-bot trial</title><description>NASA, DoD in underwater astronaut doc-bot trial

American surgeons will carry out a realistic simulation of zero-gee robotic surgery next month, the Associated Press reports. The US Department of Defense (DoD) "Raven" robo-surgeon is being developed with the intention of treating injured soldiers on far-flung battlefields where no human doc may be available. It reportedly …

Lewis Page, 20 Apr 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7082_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7082-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/02/21/ravens_hide_in_tower/</link><title>Bird flu menaces British monarchy</title><description>Bird flu menaces British monarchy

The Tower of London's famous ravens have been locked up in a bid to isolate them from the deadly H5N1 strain of avian influenza that is sweeping the world. Rest assured though, the ravens enjoy an immune boosting diet of blood-soaked biscuits, boiled eggs and cod liver oil. Legend has it that when none of the birds are left, …

Christopher Williams, 21 Feb 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7082_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7082-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/10/13/video_ipod_analysis/</link><title>Video iPod plus Front Row: Media Center killer, or shoulder-shrug?</title><description>Video iPod plus Front Row: Media Center killer, or shoulder-shrug?

OK, we've got a lot of things to get through today, so let's get started. As Steve Jobs usually says, introducing another load of, um, stuff. So on Wednesday he unveiled a desktop computer with a remote control; iPods that can play video; and an updated iTunes Music Store that will sell you videos, and if you live in the US, TV …

Charles Arthur, 13 Oct 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7082_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/03/chandef15.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7082-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/08/02/cisco_exploits/</link><title>Exploit writers team up to target Cisco routers</title><description>Exploit writers team up to target Cisco routers

LAS VEGAS In a room at the Alexis Park Hotel, a nightmare scenario for Cisco has begun to unfold. It's Saturday night, a time for blowout parties at the annual DEF CON hacker convention, including the Goth-flavored Black and White Ball. But a half dozen researchers in the nondescript room quietly drink, stare at the screens of …

Robert Lemos, 02 Aug 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7082_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>