<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7083">I'm on the road again</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:57:58" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7083-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/14/high_fidelity_pure_audio_launch_event_elton_john_goodbye_yellow_brick_road/</link><title>Audio fans, prepare yourself for the Second Coming ... of Blu-ray</title><description>Audio fans, prepare yourself for the Second Coming ... of Blu-ray

Apparently, 60 per cent of the population has access to Blu-ray players. Who’d have thunk it? Really, if you include the Sony PlayStation consoles and now the Xbox One, it all adds up... possibly. The statistic came from Olivier Robert-Murphy, global head of new business at Universal Music Group, during an event held at …

Bob Dormon, 14 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7083_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/04/10/hfpa_discs.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7083-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/10/geeks_guide_visits_ibm_hursley/</link><title>IBM Hursley Park: Where Big Blue buries the past, polishes family jewels</title><description>IBM Hursley Park: Where Big Blue buries the past, polishes family jewels

Would you like to work in a cross between Downton Abbey and Silicon Valley? For a small selection of IBMers, that’s the only way to describe their working environment, although the place we’re talking about is officially called Hursley Park. You can get there by turning off the M3 and rattling through some pretty English village …

Joe Fay, 10 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7083_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/04/07/ibm_mainframe_portable_toolkit.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7083-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/10/microsoft_builds_teleporter_weapon_to_send_vmware_into_azure/</link><title>Microsoft builds teleporter weapon to send VMware into Azure</title><description>Microsoft builds teleporter weapon to send VMware into Azure

Microsoft has fired another shot in its campaign to win over VMware users, in the form of an updated Virtual Machine Converter that can move virtual machines from ESXi to Hyper-V. It's no secret Microsoft covets VMware users: in recent times it has created a certification helping VMware users to grok Hyper-V. Redmond also uses …

Simon Sharwood, 10 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7083_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2009/12/10/azure.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7083-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/04/willowra_xp_migration_conclusion/</link><title>Deep desert XP-ocalypse averted as Reg man returns</title><description>Deep desert XP-ocalypse averted as Reg man returns

Yesterday was day three of my XP-ocalypse aversion mission to upgrade the PCs at the remote Wirliyatjarrayi Learning Centre. The day started with the dew on the ground and the desert sun struggling to penetrate a low, hazy, layer of cloud. The air was just a tad sticky and I wondered if it might rain. I hoped not: the road to …

Simon Sharwood, 04 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7083_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/04/03/willowra_store.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7083-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/03/italy_copyright_law_google_demote_carly_rae_jepsen/</link><title>Italy has a clumsy new pirate-choker law. But can anyone do better?</title><description>Italy has a clumsy new pirate-choker law. But can anyone do better?

New technology means anyone can now create and distribute their creative works, like photos or music, like never before – but, in turn, it also means that anyone can now rip off creators. And yesterday, a range of speakers – from Google to legal experts to enforcement teams – met at the London HQ of law firm Bristows for an …

Andrew Orlowski, 03 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7083_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2009/06/30/destroy_capitalism_support_piracy_nesson.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7083-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/29/hawkins_ai_feature/</link><title>Meet the man building an AI that mimics our neocortex – and could kill off neural networks</title><description>Meet the man building an AI that mimics our neocortex – and could kill off neural networks

Jeff Hawkins has bet his reputation, fortune, and entire intellectual life on one idea: that he understands the brain well enough to create machines with an intelligence we recognize as our own. If his bet is correct, the Palm Pilot inventor will father a new technology, one that becomes the crucible in which a general …

Jack Clark, 29 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7083_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/03/28/hawkins_419x278.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7083-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/21/city_lifeline_london_colocation_data_centre/</link><title>Hot racks and cool customers: Colocating in the capital</title><description>Hot racks and cool customers: Colocating in the capital

In a world where data centre duties are increasingly relocated to lower cost territories in the East and beyond, why would anyone want to set up shop in the heart of London? Even if there was a requirement for your data to be UK-based, surely a location in the shires where rents are lower would make sense. City Lifeline …

Bob Dormon, 21 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7083_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/20/generator_output_meters.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7083-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/20/big_data_teenage_fumblings/</link><title>Big Data is like TEENAGE SEX</title><description>Big Data is like TEENAGE SEX

The joke doing the rounds on social media compares big data to teenage sex: everyone's talking about it, only a few know how to do it, they all think everyone else is at it and so pretend they are too. And humans fumbling about in the dark, so to speak, are the weakest link in the world of analytics and data, said Steve Brazier …

Paul Kunert, 20 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7083_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/05/03/ttens.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7083-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/12/archaeologic_amstrad_cpc_464/</link><title>You’re NOT fired: The story of Amstrad’s amazing CPC 464</title><description>You’re NOT fired: The story of Amstrad’s amazing CPC 464

It was a home computer that embodied so many contradictions. It was launched months after the British microcomputer boom of the early 1980s had peaked. It was a rush job: the machine that was revealed to the press in the Spring of 1984 hadn’t even existed nine months previously. It was one of the best-produced British micros of …

Tony Smith, 12 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7083_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/01/13/464_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7083-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/24/thirty_years_of_the_apple_macintosh_p1/</link><title>Apple’s Mac turns 30: How Steve Jobs’ baby took its first steps</title><description>Apple’s Mac turns 30: How Steve Jobs’ baby took its first steps

Thirty years ago this Friday, at approximately 9:45am on Tuesday, 24 January, 1984, the Macintosh introduced itself after Steve Jobs unveiled it at an Apple shareholders' meeting in Cupertino's Flint Center for the Performing Arts. "Hello. I'm Macintosh. It sure is great to get out of that bag," the odd-looking 16.5-pound box …

Rik Myslewski, 24 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7083_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/01/23/think_different.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>