<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7084">Burn after reading review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:23:06" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7084-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/13/archaeologic_the_research_machines_380z_story/</link><title>The micro YOU used in school: The story of the Research Machines 380Z</title><description>The micro YOU used in school: The story of the Research Machines 380Z

If you’re a British techie of a certain age, there’s only one microcomputer that defines your first memories of computing at school. No, not Acorn’s BBC Micro – the Research Machines 380Z. While Acorn was still knocking up the Proton, the machine being designed as the successor to the Atom, and while the BBC was pondering how it …

Tony Smith, 13 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7084_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/10/29/380z_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7084-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/02/02/windows_phone_get_going/</link><title>Five ways Microsoft can rescue Windows Phone</title><description>Five ways Microsoft can rescue Windows Phone

Windows Phone might be the most impressive bit of software Microsoft has produced - but it isn't setting the world on fire. The iPhone and Android go from strength to strength - the latter proliferating so widely even Google doesn't know how many Android systems are out there. (It can't count the Chinese forks which don't use …

Andrew Orlowski, 02 Feb 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7084_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/09/02/htc_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7084-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/04/22/seti_goes_cloud_and_open_source/</link><title>ET, phone back: Alien quest seeks earthling coders</title><description>ET, phone back: Alien quest seeks earthling coders

It was the year of Star Wars and Close Encounters, and in the flatlands of Ohio, a man stumbled upon something possibly alien in origin. On August 17, 1977, Ohio State University astronomer Jerry Ehman was sitting at his kitchen table, pouring over pages of printouts from the SETI Project's Big Ear radio telescope's computers. …

Gavin Clarke, 22 Apr 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7084_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7084-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/07/26/review_optical_drive_lite_on_ihbs112/</link><title>Lite-on iHBS112 internal Blu-ray writer</title><description>Lite-on iHBS112 internal Blu-ray writer

Lite-On is certainly pushing the boundaries of optical disc burning at aggressive prices. The iHBS112 is an internal drive that goes beyond the combo by letting you read and write Blu-ray, DVD and CD media in one unit. Its Blu-ray writing speed, 12x, matches the current fastest on the market. That's not bad for £123. As a …

Alistair Dabbs, 26 Jul 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7084_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2010/07/21/lite_on_ihbs112_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7084-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/10/15/review_storage_blu_ray_combo_drive_plds_ihes208/</link><title>PLDS iHES208 Blu-ray drive</title><description>PLDS iHES208 Blu-ray drive

PLDS is a joint venture between Philips and Lite-On that develops optical disc drive technologies and markets related products. The PLDS iHES208 internal drive is new take on the 'combo' drive concept, providing complete CD and DVD reading and writing functions, plus the ability to play Blu-ray titles at full 1080p quality. …

Alistair Dabbs, 15 Oct 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7084_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2009/10/14/plds_ihes208_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7084-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/05/29/review_phone_doro_phoneeasy_345_gsm/</link><title>Doro PhoneEasy 345gsm</title><description>Doro PhoneEasy 345gsm

Swedish firm Doro's basic handsets for elderly or disabled users have been around since 2007. With the latest range of PhoneEasy handsets, the company raises the bar from its original sackcloth and ashes models in terms of build, style and functionality. Doro 345gsm Doro's PhoneEasy 345gsm Unlike its super-basic cousin, the …

Dave Oliver, 29 May 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7084_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2009/05/28/doro_345_gsm_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7084-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/05/05/review_blu_ray_drive_pioneer_bdr_203bk/</link><title>Pioneer BDR-203BK</title><description>Pioneer BDR-203BK

Installing a Blu-ray Disc recorder is the latest must-have upgrade for desktops, but because they remain thin on the ground, they maintain a price premium. Given the high storage capacity of the Blu-ray format, write speed is particularly important and we’re starting to see drives capable of 8x writing on 25GB and 50GB …

Simon Williams, 05 May 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7084_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2009/05/01/pioneer_bdr203bk_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7084-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/08/02/nokia_new_coke/</link><title>Nokia's New Coke moment?</title><description>Nokia's New Coke moment?

Some products bewitch because of their style or inventiveness - such as the iPhone. But others earn their keep through sheer usefulness, and for a decade Nokia's Communicator has proved itself to be one of the latter. Until now, that is. While it may be too early to call this Nokia's "New Coke" moment, MBA students may be …

Andrew Orlowski, 02 Aug 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7084_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2007/02/12/nokia_e90_2.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7084-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/07/21/comments/</link><title>Keeping abreast of disappointing Apple products</title><description>Keeping abreast of disappointing Apple products

The iPhone continues to dominate this week, with many comments telling us or fellow readers to shut up. Nobody seems to have any intention of doing so, which is as it should be. Reg reviewer Cade Metz decided to return his iPhone and moaned about the restocking fee. This led to a great many comments. As usual, there was a …

Robin Lettice, 21 Jul 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7084_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7084-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/09/12/letters_1209/</link><title>Chickens and guinea pigs menace civil liberties</title><description>Chickens and guinea pigs menace civil liberties

We'll start with the paranoid and then roll out the black helicopters. How does that sound? First, the EU opened a consultation on whether or not surveillance technology is intruding on our lives, or infringing our civil liberties. The balance of your responses can be summed up with this letter: 'The EC, however, said its …

Lucy Sherriff, 12 Sep 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7084_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>