<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7091">don't listen to a word i say</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:59:13" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7091-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/18/that_obama_nsa_reform_speech_with_el_reg_annotations/</link><title>Those NSA 'reforms' in full: El Reg translates US Prez Obama's pledges</title><description>Those NSA 'reforms' in full: El Reg translates US Prez Obama's pledges

On Friday, President Obama gave his long-awaited speech on plans to reform the activities of the US intelligence services and how they monitor the rest of the world. You can watch the entire speech here, but words are tricky things – never more so than when national security is involved. As such we've taken a transcript of the …

Iain Thomson, 18 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7091_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2008/10/09/nsaseal.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7091-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/13/sorry_the_tories_didnt_make_the_internet_disappear/</link><title>Oh My GOD! Have the TORIES ERASED THE INTERNET?*</title><description>Oh My GOD! Have the TORIES ERASED THE INTERNET?*

A story that the Conservatives “made the internet disappear” has ignited news channels today. In fact, the story demonstrates yet again how ignorant most journalists are of the basic workings of the internet - and it demonstrates how the thirst for conspiratorial thinking dominates political news. Perhaps not surprisingly, this …

Andrew Orlowski, Kelly Fiveash, Lewis Page, 13 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7091_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/11/08/phoner_with_obama.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7091-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/09/13/ir35_staying_on_the_right_side_of_hrmc/</link><title>Moving from permie to mercenary? Avoid a fine - listen to Ben Franklin</title><description>Moving from permie to mercenary? Avoid a fine - listen to Ben Franklin

Benjamin Franklin said that nothing in this world is certain except death and taxes. He also coined the idea that “time is money”, and once wrote that “wine is constant proof that God loves us and loves to see us happy”, so we can assume that he would have understood contractors pretty well. Taxes may be certain, but the amount …

Tim Phillips, 13 Sep 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7091_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/07/20/benjamin_franklin_dollar_money.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7091-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/01/german_rage_at_us_surveillance_project/</link><title>PRISM leaks: WTF, you don't spy on your friends, splutters EU</title><description>PRISM leaks: WTF, you don't spy on your friends, splutters EU

Berlin has accused Washington of treating it "like a Cold War enemy" after it emerged that US spooks spied on targets from friendly European countries. Vice-president of the European Commission, Neelie Kroes, told BBC: Of course it is a shock and it's not acceptable at all. It's not acceptable because it is a friendly …

Jasper Hamill, 01 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7091_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7091-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/01/11/bt_broadband_ip_profile_throttled/</link><title>Is this possibly the worst broadband in the world?</title><description>Is this possibly the worst broadband in the world?

Four kilometres to the north of here, in semi-rural Kent, the pavements are stuffed with fibre-optic cable and the streets are lined with drab green cabinets, all nicely tooled up for superfast broadband. But here, we rely on plain old ADSL piped in from a small BT exchange, 1.7km to our south (as the crow flies). You can see it …

Drew Cullen, 11 Jan 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7091_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/01/10/wormshill_exchange.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7091-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/02/17/bofh_2012_episode_2/</link><title>BOFH: Moon landings, Pong and the case of the smoking server

*[BOFH]: Bastard Operator from Hell</title><description>BOFH: Moon landings, Pong and the case of the smoking server

"It's about your assistant," the Boss says, looking around carefully as he nods me into his office. "Yes?" "He told me something yesterday. Something disturbing." "Oh, I wouldn't believe everything he says, he's prone to making outrageous statements. I mean the goat lived and the charges against him were dropped." "What …

Simon Travaglia, 17 Feb 2012

*[BOFH]: Bastard Operator from Hell</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7091_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2004/06/16/bofh_logo.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7091-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/10/15/ten_in_ear_headphones_with_microphones/</link><title>Ten... earphones for mobiles</title><description>Ten... earphones for mobiles

Here we go again with some more headphones, but this time I'm looking at those faithful friends you'd use on a daily basis with your smartphone. While still likely to be churning through MP3s, their function is also to act as hands-free kit, so conversational ability is key. While you can spend silly money on smartphone earbuds …

Caleb Cox, 15 Oct 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7091_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/10/17/phones_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7091-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/07/28/ten_in_ear_headphones/</link><title>Ten... in-ear headphones</title><description>Ten... in-ear headphones

It's time for another headphone roundup and considering we've already covered the bulkier over-ear and on-ear models, it was inevitable that in-ears would follow. After all, not everyone likes walking the streets, turning heads with a pair of oversized Mickey Mousers on. The market is inundated with hundreds of in-ear monitors …

Caleb Cox, 28 Jul 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7091_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/07/28/headphones_9.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7091-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/05/13/bofh_2011_episode_5/</link><title>BOFH:﻿﻿ Every silver lining has a cloud

*[BOFH]: Bastard Operator from Hell</title><description>BOFH:﻿﻿ Every silver lining has a cloud

"Code Magenta," the PFY mumbles quietly as he wanders past me on the way to Mission Control. "Code Magenta!" the Director's PA repeats in hushed tones, unable to keep her nose out of things that don’t concern her – "What does that mean?" "It's a systems code about operational availability," I lie. "We have various codes …

Simon Travaglia, 13 May 2011

*[BOFH]: Bastard Operator from Hell</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7091_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2004/06/16/bofh_logo.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7091-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/04/08/bbc_newsnight_unicorns_and_the_web/</link><title>The BBC struggles with concept of 'tech bubble'</title><description>The BBC struggles with concept of 'tech bubble'

The BBC has a real problem with social media. It's delighted when something new appears. It slips into the patrician role that comes naturally to broadcasters – and especially the BBC. It can express childlike wonderment – Wow! – at something new and amazing. Getting beyond that though, is where the trouble starts. Perhaps the …

Andrew Orlowski, 08 Apr 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7091_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>