<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7095">iron in water supply</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:32:28" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7095-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/21/city_lifeline_london_colocation_data_centre/</link><title>Hot racks and cool customers: Colocating in the capital</title><description>Hot racks and cool customers: Colocating in the capital

In a world where data centre duties are increasingly relocated to lower cost territories in the East and beyond, why would anyone want to set up shop in the heart of London? Even if there was a requirement for your data to be UK-based, surely a location in the shires where rents are lower would make sense. City Lifeline …

Bob Dormon, 21 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7095_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/20/generator_output_meters.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7095-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/24/thirty_years_of_the_apple_macintosh_p1/</link><title>Apple’s Mac turns 30: How Steve Jobs’ baby took its first steps</title><description>Apple’s Mac turns 30: How Steve Jobs’ baby took its first steps

Thirty years ago this Friday, at approximately 9:45am on Tuesday, 24 January, 1984, the Macintosh introduced itself after Steve Jobs unveiled it at an Apple shareholders' meeting in Cupertino's Flint Center for the Performing Arts. "Hello. I'm Macintosh. It sure is great to get out of that bag," the odd-looking 16.5-pound box …

Rik Myslewski, 24 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7095_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/01/23/think_different.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7095-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/09/stars_of_ces_2014/</link><title>Spock-style gadget can SMELL my PEE! Weird gizmos of CES 2014</title><description>Spock-style gadget can SMELL my PEE! Weird gizmos of CES 2014

The Las Vegas-hosted 2014 Consumer Electronics Show (CES) is still running, of course, but the majority of the announcements have been made: a fair few before the show even started, in a bid to get ahead of the rest. Like early morning shoppers, though, everyone figures out the pre-show press release trick soon enough and now …

Tony Smith, 09 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7095_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/01/08/ces_17.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7095-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/06/10/inside_chinas_tianhe2_massive_hybrid_supercomputer/</link><title>Enter the Dragon: The Chinese superputer set to win the Top500 crown</title><description>Enter the Dragon: The Chinese superputer set to win the Top500 crown

The Chinese government can keep a secret probably as well as any organisation on the planet, but pride will get the best of anyone - at least some of the time. And so it is that Xiangke Liao, the professor from the National University of Defense Technology has outed the details of the "Tianhe-2" massively parallel supercomputer …

Timothy Prickett Morgan, 10 Jun 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7095_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/06/06/tianhe_2_render.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7095-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/05/24/geeks_guide_gchq/</link><title>INSIDE GCHQ: Welcome to Cheltenham's cottage industry</title><description>INSIDE GCHQ: Welcome to Cheltenham's cottage industry

For staff at the Government Communications Headquarters (GCHQ) in Cheltenham, there’s an air of Fight Club about the place. The first rule about GCHQ is you don’t talk about GCHQ. It’s a well observed tradition, even though there are road signs and a bus route directing you to this highly secret establishment, the nerve centre …

Bob Dormon, 24 May 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7095_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/05/20/gchq_benhall_doughnut_aerial_view_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7095-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/03/27/geeks_guide_leo/</link><title>Blighty's revolutionary Cold War teashop computer - and Nigella Lawson</title><description>Blighty's revolutionary Cold War teashop computer - and Nigella Lawson

The Victorian offices were bulldozed long ago for a stack of flats and mirrored offices, and there's not a single indication to the significance of this site - or what happened here. This isn't the scene of a lost battle, and the bones of a missing Plantagenet king do not slumber beneath the car park serving the offices. Sixty- …

Gavin Clarke, 27 Mar 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7095_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/03/25/reading_tape_leo_ii_computer.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7095-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/03/18/rackspace_server_fleet_open_compute/</link><title>Rackspace: Why we're designing our own cloud servers</title><description>Rackspace: Why we're designing our own cloud servers

Any cloud computing provider that wants to operate at scale and compete against its peers is under pressure to build some kind of custom hardware. It may, in fact, be necessary to compete at all. That is what Rackspace, which is making the transition from website hosting to cloud systems, believes. And that's why the San Antonio …

Timothy Prickett Morgan, 18 Mar 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7095_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/rackspace.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7095-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/03/08/ibm_power_systems_manufacturing_mexico/</link><title>IBM moves Power Systems manufacturing from Minnesota to Mexico</title><description>IBM moves Power Systems manufacturing from Minnesota to Mexico

It is the end of an era – the minicomputer era to be precise – for the IBMers who work in the company's sprawling Rochester, Minnesota facility. Their jobs are moving to Mexico. Big Blue had a meeting with the approximately 2,800 employees in the facility on Tuesday afternoon and told them it would cease manufacturing operations …

Timothy Prickett Morgan, 08 Mar 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7095_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/03/07/ibm_rochester_logo.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7095-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/11/24/planetary_resources/</link><title>Asteroid miners hunt for platinum, leave all common sense in glovebox</title><description>Asteroid miners hunt for platinum, leave all common sense in glovebox

Isn't it exciting that Planetary Resources is going to jet off and mine the asteroids? This is every teenage sci-fi geek's dream, that everything we imbibed from Verne through Heinlein to Pournelle is going to come true! But there's always someone, isn't there, someone like me, ready to spoil the party. The bit that I cannot …

Tim Worstall, 24 Nov 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7095_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/27/earth_nasa.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7095-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/10/08/view_to_a_kill/</link><title>Target Silicon Valley: Why A View to a Kill actually made sense</title><description>Target Silicon Valley: Why A View to a Kill actually made sense

A View to a Kill is generally regarded as one of the least successful Bond movies. Yet it stands out for two things: a suave villain who is deranged in an entirely believable way, and a villainous plot that appeared both logical and plausible. While its box office performance was passable at $152m, on a budget of $30m, even …

Joe Fay, 08 Oct 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7095_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/10/roger_moore_3_bond_feat.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>