<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7096">touchpad scroll dell latitude</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:56:47" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7096-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/04/08/review_laptop_dell_latitude_z/</link><title>Dell Latitude Z</title><description>Dell Latitude Z

If you want a laptop to impress, then a likely choice is a high-end MacBook rather than an amorphous black box Windows notebook, that looks about as cool as a fridge-freezer. With admiring glances in mind, is Dell's Inspiron Latitude Z, a machine the company is heralding as the thinnest and most stylish 16in laptop around. Dell …

Alun Taylor, 08 Apr 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7096_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2010/04/08/dell_latitude_z_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7096-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/11/14/review_netbook_acer_aspire_one_d250_android/</link><title>Acer Aspire One D250 with Android</title><description>Acer Aspire One D250 with Android

Installing a second operating system on a PC is nothing new. Plenty of manufacturers have done so before, building a slimline Linux distro into their machines to provide a much more rapid start-up than Windows can manage: full access to the internet within seconds of pressing on power key. Acer Aspire One D250 with Android Acer …

Tony Smith, 14 Nov 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7096_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2009/11/11/d250_and_6.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7096-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/11/28/review_laptop_sony_vaio_z11/</link><title>Sony Vaio Z11 13in laptop</title><description>Sony Vaio Z11 13in laptop

Apple may have grabbed headlines for releasing its new MacBook Pro with two GPUs on board - one for casual, one for best - but Sony had already done so, with its Vaio Z11, launched in the summer and now available for review. Sony Vaio Z11 Sony's Vaio Z11: As a recently launched laptop, it's no surprise that the Z11 is based …

Tony Smith, 28 Nov 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7096_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2008/12/24/z11_sm.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7096-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/11/21/review_laptop_sony_vaio_tt/</link><title>Sony Vaio TT slim'n'light laptop</title><description>Sony Vaio TT slim'n'light laptop

Sony has been pitching small, slim laptops at executives for years now, packing in as much functionality into as compact a chassis as it can and charging a premium for it. Why mess with a successful formula? So the new Vaio TT doesn't. There's clearly a market for this kind of machine, as the success of previous Sony thin'n' …

Tony Smith, 21 Nov 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7096_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2008/12/24/tt_sm.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7096-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/04/14/review_acer_8104/</link><title>Acer TravelMate 8100 'Sonoma' notebook</title><description>Acer TravelMate 8100 'Sonoma' notebook

Acer must be making life very difficult for other notebook manufacturers. The company has built a solid reputation for manufacturing high-quality portables at very attractive prices, and the TravelMate 8104WLMi is no exception, writes Riyad Emeran. Acer TravelMate 8104WLMi The 8104WLMi is Acer's first 'Sonoma' notebook, and it …

Trusted Reviews, 14 Apr 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7096_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>