<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7098">tour moscow</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:09:02" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7098-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/29/how_russian_megahack_suspects_got_tracked/</link><title>'World's BIGGEST online fraud': Suspect's phone had 'location' switched on</title><description>'World's BIGGEST online fraud': Suspect's phone had 'location' switched on

Two Russians arrested over their suspected involvement in the largest online fraud in US history were tracked down by analysing photos they posted to social media sites and tracking the location of one suspect's mobile phone, Reuters reports. Four Russians and a Ukrainian national were named as suspects in a credit card hacking …

John Leyden, 29 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7098_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7098-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/18/carter_warns_america_no_democracy_prism/</link><title>Ex-prez Carter: 'America has no functioning democracy' with PRISM</title><description>Ex-prez Carter: 'America has no functioning democracy' with PRISM

Former US President Jimmy Carter has applauded the whistle-blowing of Edward Snowden and says the current surveillance state means the US is in dire political straits. "America has no functioning democracy," Carter told a meeting of The Atlantic Bridge in Atlanta on Tuesday, Der Speigel reports. Carter said that Snowden's …

Iain Thomson, 18 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7098_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/07/18/jimmy_carter.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7098-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/05/09/inside_nsa/</link><title>Museum unscrambles secret agency's past</title><description>Museum unscrambles secret agency's past

A few of us got through the metal detectors before the National Security Agency (NSA) realised we were in the wrong place. We had arrived, expunged of all electronic devices from mobile phones to cameras, at the Visitors' Centre, a security outpost for visiting security personnel, instead of the National Cryptologic Museum 370 …

Wendy M. Grossman, 09 May 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7098_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/03/chandef6.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7098-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/1999/10/21/robot_cat_barred_from_flight/</link><title>Robot cat barred from flight to Moscow</title><description>Robot cat barred from flight to Moscow

A bizarre story in This is London tells of Reading University head of cybernetics Kevin Warwick's skirmish with British Airways. Warwick (is there a Kevin Reading at Warwick University?) allegedly tried to book his robotic cat a seat on a BA flight to Moscow. BA staff were adamant that the "cat" should go in the hold, as animals …

Kieran Skittles, 21 Oct 1999</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7098_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>