<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7102">vlc mac</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:26:56" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7102-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/16/review_kingston_datatraveler_microduo_64gb/</link><title>Kingston DataTraveler MicroDuo: Turn your phone into a 72GB beast</title><description>Kingston DataTraveler MicroDuo: Turn your phone into a 72GB beast

The Kingston DataTraveler microDuo is a convenient flash storage device that features a full-size USB interface at one end and micro USB at the other. The thinking here is that you can upload data to it from your computer or NAS box, and then stuff it into your phone or tablet for easy file sharing and to supplement any fixed …

Bob Dormon, 16 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7102_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/04/07/motorola_moto_g_with_kingston_dt_microduo.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7102-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/28/five_oses_to_save_your_xp_netbook/</link><title>DEATH-PROOF your old XP netbook: 5 OSes to bring it back to life</title><description>DEATH-PROOF your old XP netbook: 5 OSes to bring it back to life

My son's school has decreed that next year he'll need a computer of some sort. Mr 12 wants an iPad. I want him to use the 2009-vintage Lenovo S10e Netbook gathering dust in the study, because it's already been paid for. The netbook is also fit for purpose: it was the very model handed out in Australian schools circa 2009. It's …

Simon Sharwood, 28 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7102_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/27/macpup_screenshot.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7102-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/05/31/review_pure_jongo_s3_multiroom_speakers/</link><title>Review: Pure Jongo S3 multiroom speakers</title><description>Review: Pure Jongo S3 multiroom speakers

I’ll admit, I didn’t think I was going to have much to say about Pure’s Jongo S3 speakers, the latest addition to its growing wireless audio gear range. It connects to mobile devices, but what else is new? Well, there are a few nice touches to this boombox, the most significant being its integration with the online streaming …

Bob Dormon, 31 May 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7102_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/05/30/pure_jongo_s3_multiroom_speaker.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7102-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/03/28/review_lenovo_thinkpad_2_windows_8_tablet/</link><title>Review: Lenovo ThinkPad Tablet 2</title><description>Review: Lenovo ThinkPad Tablet 2

I’ve tried out quite a few variations on the Windows 8 theme just lately – touchscreen notebooks mainly – but I’ve been dabbling with Boot Camp and virtual machine incarnations on the desktop too but without the finger friendliness. So trying out Lenovo’s business-centric ThinkPad Tablet 2 seemed like it would be an easy …

Bob Dormon, 28 Mar 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7102_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/03/27/lenovo_thinkpad_tablet2_modern.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7102-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/11/20/ten_linux_apps_you_must_instal/</link><title>Ten Linux apps you must install</title><description>Ten Linux apps you must install

Unless you are operating in the enterprise class, most Linux software is free, which is both a blessing and a hindrance. Sure, there are some truly fantastic apps out there, but all to often you have to wade through a mess of buggy unfinished projects with dependencies on other defunct code to get to what you want. To help with …

Shaun Dormon, 20 Nov 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7102_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/10/25/synaptic_package_manager.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7102-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/08/09/nokia_qt/</link><title>Nokia straps Qt into ejector seat and hits the shiny red button</title><description>Nokia straps Qt into ejector seat and hits the shiny red button

Nokia's back-room clear out continues with the Qt platform being sold to Finnish firm Digia Oyj for an undisclosed sum. As part of the deal 125 engineers will swap employers. Digia was a licensee of Qt, distributing commercial and freeware versions of the platform and development tools, but now it owns the whole shebang. Qt was …

Bill Ray, 09 Aug 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7102_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7102-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/08/04/ten_freeware_apps_for_macs/</link><title>Ten freeware gems for new Macs</title><description>Ten freeware gems for new Macs

It seems that Mac OS is forever moving further towards a closed computing model, especially with the introduction of Gatekeeper in Mountain Lion. Don’t despair just yet though, Mac users can still take advantage of an abundance of free and open-source applications available in the traditional way. We've put found ten top notch …

Shaun Dormon, 04 Aug 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7102_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/07/27/sketchbook_express.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7102-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/10/28/apple_lossless_audio_codec_open_source/</link><title>Apple shifts Lossless Audio Codec to open source</title><description>Apple shifts Lossless Audio Codec to open source

Cupertino has open sourced its Apple Lossless Audio Codec (ALAC), seven years after first introducing it. The ALAC can reduce the amount of storage needed for audio files by as much as 50 per cent, but without losing any of the fidelity of the original recording. This is unlike lossy formats like MP3 and AAC, which strip out …

Iain Thomson, 28 Oct 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7102_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7102-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/07/01/ten_compact_cameras/</link><title>Ten... pocket compact cameras</title><description>Ten... pocket compact cameras

When it comes to quick pics, the expedience of a phonecam can't be overestimated, yet the image quality expectations frequently are. With this in mind Reg Hardware has rounded up the smallest and cheapest compacts produced by all the usual suspects from the photography world. Here are ten cameras that will not only take decent …

Bob Dormon, 01 Jul 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7102_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/06/30/ten_compact_cameras.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7102-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/02/05/review_equinux_tizi_ios4_tv_tuner/</link><title>Equinux Tizi iPhone TV tuner</title><description>Equinux Tizi iPhone TV tuner

There’s no shortage of TV tuners available these days, ranging from cheap and cheerful USB gadgets to more expensive network-enabled devices such as the Slingbox range or Elgato’s Netstream. However, the Tizi is the first TV tuner I’ve seen that is exclusively designed for the iOS platform. Equinux Tizi Portable TV: Equinux's …

Cliff Joseph, 05 Feb 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7102_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/02/04/equinux_tizi_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>