<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7106">active learning survey</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:10:35" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7106-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/29/hacked_assaulted_by_a_ddoser_dont_call_the_cops/</link><title>Been hacked? Don't dial 999: The plods are too dense, sniffs sec bigwig</title><description>Been hacked? Don't dial 999: The plods are too dense, sniffs sec bigwig

Police are powerless to stop super-smart criminals from hacking the world's biggest companies, a top-ranking security bod has warned. Juniper Networks' security chief said there was simply no longer any point in calling the police when hackers and DDoSers came to call, because the cops can't do anything. He wants to see a world …

Jasper Hamill, 29 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7106_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/07/26/schmoke_pancake.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7106-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/08/09/bcs_computer_security_survey/</link><title>Brits adopt 'safe surfing' habits</title><description>Brits adopt 'safe surfing' habits

Nine in 10 Britons take security precautions when surfing online, according to a new survey which goes against previous research that suggested Britain was a nation of cyber-security slackers. The upbeat poll of 2,000 Brits, commissioned by the British Computer Society (BCS), also found that 92 per cent of online shoppers take …

John Leyden, 09 Aug 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7106_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/03/chandef3.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7106-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/07/01/letters_0107/</link><title>Crispy vulture beats bald eagle</title><description>Crispy vulture beats bald eagle

The US government has decided to hang on to control of the net's root servers. Not an entirely unanticipated move, but one that will, as they say, have repercussions. Lots of cross Americans immediately wrote to us to explain why we should be pleased that Uncle Sam is still in charge: The US created the internet. Next thing …

Lucy Sherriff, 01 Jul 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7106_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>