<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7112">facebook icons</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:26:03" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7112-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/27/gnome_3_12_review/</link><title>GNOME 3.12: Pixel perfect ... but homeless</title><description>GNOME 3.12: Pixel perfect ... but homeless

When the GNOME 3.x desktop arrived it was, frankly, unusable. It wasn't so much the radical departure from past desktop environments, as the fact that essential things did not work properly or, more frustratingly, had been deemed unnecessary. Fast-forward three years and while GNOME 3.12 – released Wednesday – still isn't the …

Scott Gilbertson, 27 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7112_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/03/27/gnome.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7112-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/21/gnome_3_12_beta_review/</link><title>Sanity now: Gnome 3.12 looking sensible - at least in beta</title><description>Sanity now: Gnome 3.12 looking sensible - at least in beta

The GNOME team has released the first beta of GNOME 3.12, the next major release for the popular desktop and UI environment. Unlike the past few releases, there's a ton of new stuff in GNOME 3.12. The highlights include a slew of new apps, a major makeover for the long-standing video player, better privacy controls, support for …

Scott Gilbertson, 21 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7112_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/04/11/gnome_shell_apps.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7112-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/15/salesforce_massive_outage/</link><title>'Planned maintenance' CRIPPLES nearly HALF of all Salesforce instances in Europe, US</title><description>'Planned maintenance' CRIPPLES nearly HALF of all Salesforce instances in Europe, US

Botched network maintenance has been blamed for a huge crash at Saleforce’s data centres, taking out customers’ CRM and data services across the US and Europe. Seven of Salesforce’s 17 North American instances and two out of four in EMEA went down. Servers started dropping out just before 2am UTC on 15 November, with outages …

Gavin Clarke, 15 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7112_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/06/12/closed_sign.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7112-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/08/microsoft_bizarre_inori_ie_campaign/</link><title>Oooh! My NAUGHTY SKIRT keeps riding up! Hello, INTERNET EXPLORER</title><description>Oooh! My NAUGHTY SKIRT keeps riding up! Hello, INTERNET EXPLORER

Microsoft has come up with a new way to market Internet Explorer to Asian customers, and it's a major departure from the kinds of ad campaigns we're used to seeing from Redmond here in the West. Inori Aizawa, the 'personification of IE' Here she is, Miss Internet Explorer Meet Inori Aizawa, Microsoft's latest spokeswoman. Or …

Neil McAllister, 08 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7112_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/08/inori2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7112-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/09/30/google_preps_mobile_gmail_for_ad_push/</link><title>OUCH: Google preps ad goo injection for Android mobile Gmail app</title><description>OUCH: Google preps ad goo injection for Android mobile Gmail app

The world's biggest advertising company is preparing to push adverts into its Android mobile Gmail client, no doubt to the surprise and alarm of fandroids who thought their private data was recompense enough. The news comes from Android Police, which has been busily dismantling the latest version of the Gmail app for Android ( …

Bill Ray, 30 Sep 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7112_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/10/30/android_threat.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7112-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/09/20/nokia_lumia_1020_review/</link><title>Nokia Lumia 1020: It's an imaging BEAST... and it makes calls too</title><description>Nokia Lumia 1020: It's an imaging BEAST... and it makes calls too

Nokia's marketing department is comparing its new imaging champ, the Lumia 1020 smartphone, to digital SLR cameras. That's just silly. But what the Lumia 1020 can lay claim to is that it takes the best photos of any current modern smartphone – by a clear head and shoulders. And Nokia has packaged it into a modern phone, rather …

Andrew Orlowski, 20 Sep 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7112_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/19/nokia_procam_w540px.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7112-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/09/13/review_zte_open_firefox_os_phone/</link><title>ZTE Open: This dirt-cheap smartphone is a swing and a miss</title><description>ZTE Open: This dirt-cheap smartphone is a swing and a miss

Of the various open source Android challengers currently under development, the Mozilla Foundation's Firefox OS was the first to reach the market with actual, commercially available products. The ZTE Open smartphone is one such product. Unfortunately, that's about all it's got going for it. When ZTE started selling the Open via …

Neil McAllister, 13 Sep 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7112_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/12/zte_open_firefox.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7112-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/06/26/microsoft_build_wednesday_keynote/</link><title>Microsoft talks up devices, Windows 8.1 at developer shindig</title><description>Microsoft talks up devices, Windows 8.1 at developer shindig

Everything is beautiful at Microsoft's Build developer conference this year. Beautiful, gorgeous, delightful, beautiful, absolutely beautiful. These days, Redmond's mouthpieces seem to stammer out the word "beautiful" about as often as most speakers say "uh." But beyond all the disingenuous awe and self-congratulation, Wednesday …

Neil McAllister, 26 Jun 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7112_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/05/30/win81_new_start_screen.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7112-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/06/24/ftc_to_cast_an_eye_over_googles_waze_buy/</link><title>FTC to cast an eye over Google's Waze buy</title><description>FTC to cast an eye over Google's Waze buy

Google's acquisition of Israeli mobile navigation app vendor Waze is going to get an anti-trust examination by the FTC. Earlier this month, Mountain View's acquisition team flipped open the wallet to the tune of $US1.3 billion for the social map app, its sub-$US70 million revenue, and its claimed fifty million users. When the …

Richard Chirgwin, 24 Jun 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7112_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7112-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/06/14/quotw_ending_14_june/</link><title>'Sometimes life doesn’t afford proper goodbyes'</title><description>'Sometimes life doesn’t afford proper goodbyes'

American spooks are watching everything you do - but don't worry about that too much, here comes a nice new iOS design. That was pretty much the message of the week in tech, when the world woke up to an online surveillance programme that made Big Brother look like a little sissy, while fanbois mulled the end of iPhones as they …

Jasper Hamill, 14 Jun 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7112_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>