<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7118">part time jobs texas city</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:20:03" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7118-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/03/08/ibm_power_systems_manufacturing_mexico/</link><title>IBM moves Power Systems manufacturing from Minnesota to Mexico</title><description>IBM moves Power Systems manufacturing from Minnesota to Mexico

It is the end of an era – the minicomputer era to be precise – for the IBMers who work in the company's sprawling Rochester, Minnesota facility. Their jobs are moving to Mexico. Big Blue had a meeting with the approximately 2,800 employees in the facility on Tuesday afternoon and told them it would cease manufacturing operations …

Timothy Prickett Morgan, 08 Mar 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7118_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/03/07/ibm_rochester_logo.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7118-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/12/24/2011_review/</link><title>Reg review of 2011: Jobs, floaters and 90,000 tons of radioactive water</title><description>Reg review of 2011: Jobs, floaters and 90,000 tons of radioactive water

Time-travelling neutrinos, lost Russian space probes, and a nuclear meltdown in Japan proved the worlds of physics, space and nature remain untamed for our brave boffins. In tech, meanwhile, Hewlett-Packard melted down, Steve Jobs died and his company's iPad proved untouchable in leaving PC makers lumbered with millions of …

Gavin Clarke, 24 Dec 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7118_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7118-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/01/03/sirius_msi_systems_acquisition/</link><title>Sirius to top $1bn in sales with MSI Systems acquisition</title><description>Sirius to top $1bn in sales with MSI Systems acquisition

The rate at which private equity firms are gathering cheap money to make acquisitions combined with an IT industry consolidating on many fronts can make you dizzy. That's why it's not much of a surprise that Sirius Computer Solutions has acquired MSI Systems Integrators for an undisclosed sum. Both are among the largest players …

Timothy Prickett Morgan, 03 Jan 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7118_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/03/chandef8.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7118-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/06/26/psion_special/</link><title>Psion: the last computer</title><description>Psion: the last computer

The Series 5 pocket computer from Psion was launched 10 years ago this week. It was a remarkable achievement: entirely new silicon, a new operating system, middleware stack and applications were developed from scratch in just over two years. This was the last time anyone undertook such a daunting task: it may be the last time …

Andrew Orlowski, 26 Jun 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7118_04_thumb.gif">http://regmedia.co.uk/_teaser/75x75/flag_united_kingdom.gif?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7118-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/04/28/letters/</link><title>Comment on this story and we'll sue you</title><description>Comment on this story and we'll sue you

The word on the street this week is: be careful what you say, especially on the internet. It all kicked off with a Hamburg court ruling that forum moderators were legally responsible for posts. Cue general outrage: Great, thanks to lawyers another thing that we cannot be held responsible for and quite possibly the end of most …

Lester Haines, 28 Apr 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7118_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7118-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2004/09/23/orlowski_interactive_keynote/</link><title>How the music biz can live forever, get even richer, and be loved</title><description>How the music biz can live forever, get even richer, and be loved

[Earlier this week Register San Francisco bureau chief Andrew Orlowski spoke at the In the City convention in the UK, telling the cream of the music industry it's never had it so good, that it's been swindled by the technologists, and that it should dump DRM and embrace freedom. As, to our knowledge, he got out alive, we think …

Andrew Orlowski, 23 Sep 2004</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7118_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>