<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7119">chocolate photo</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:32:02" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7119-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/18/google_glass_at_home_trial/</link><title>Google lets wannabe Glass Explorers ADMIRE THEMSELVES in their own mirrors</title><description>Google lets wannabe Glass Explorers ADMIRE THEMSELVES in their own mirrors

Interested in Google Glass but worried that you'll look like a dork wearing it? The Chocolate Factory is testing out a new pilot program to help ease your mind. Reddit user "clide" says he was recently selected to participate in an at-home trial in which he was allowed to try on a few different styles of the high-tech specs …

Neil McAllister, 18 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7119_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/10/31/glass_earbud1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7119-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/01/google_adds_page_view_counters_to_profile_pages/</link><title>Page through Page's page page-views: Google+ shows how many saw your profile</title><description>Page through Page's page page-views: Google+ shows how many saw your profile

Google has added a new feature to its Google+ kinda-social network that identifies how many people have looked at your profile page, blog and photos on Google+. "Starting today you’ll see a new number on your Google+ profile or page: total content views," said Eddie Kessler, a Google engineering manager. "This number is the sum …

Iain Thomson, 01 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7119_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/01/20/yawn.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7119-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/21/review_google_chromecast/</link><title>Reg tries out Google's Chromecast: Yep, we even tested smut sites</title><description>Reg tries out Google's Chromecast: Yep, we even tested smut sites

Google’s Chromecast has finally gone on sale in the UK after an age of waiting following its initial US release in July last year. This digital media player in the form of an HDMI dongle delivers streaming content to a telly including support for the BBC’s iPlayer. It’s only 30 quid too – so you might as well buy one even if it …

Bob Dormon, 21 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7119_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/03/21/google_chromecast.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7119-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/27/project_ara_developer_conferences/</link><title>Mix-and-match mobiles: Google unveils Project Ara dev conference</title><description>Mix-and-match mobiles: Google unveils Project Ara dev conference

Google says it is planning a series of three online developer conferences this year in support of Project Ara, the modular mobile phone design being developed by its Motorola Mobility division. Announced last year, Ara is a unique concept that will allow users to build their own devices from a collection of snap-together parts. …

Neil McAllister, 27 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7119_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/27/project_ara.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7119-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/31/end_of_year_review_2013/</link><title>Glassholes, snapt**ts, #blabbergasms, selfies and PRISM: The Reg's review of 2013</title><description>Glassholes, snapt**ts, #blabbergasms, selfies and PRISM: The Reg's review of 2013

"Selfie" is the Oxford English Dictionary's word of the year. There's nothing new about a "selfie" - it's a self-portrait - but a perfect storm of social networks and smartphones has given popularity to a word and an act even world leaders feel it's OK to do on really serious occasions. In keeping with a long tradition here at …

Gavin Clarke, 31 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7119_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/03/09/google_glass.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7119-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/13/eff_google_for_pulling_android_app_permissions_filter/</link><title>Google tells EFF: Android 4.3's privacy tool was a MISTAKE, we've yanked it</title><description>Google tells EFF: Android 4.3's privacy tool was a MISTAKE, we've yanked it

Privacy campaign group the Electronic Frontier Foundation is more than a little miffed with Google – after the Chocolate Factory pulled an Android tool that lets users control the information apps can harvest. The software, dubbed App Ops, was bundled into Android 4.3 as a hidden application. For each installed program, it …

Iain Thomson, 13 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7119_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/03/android_kitkat_535.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7119-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/12/snowden_latest_nsa_using_google_cookies_to_id_internet_users/</link><title>Snowden latest: NSA stalks the human race using Google, ad cookies</title><description>Snowden latest: NSA stalks the human race using Google, ad cookies

The already strained relationship between Google and the NSA has got a little bit worse, after claims in the latest Snowden leak that intelligence agencies are using the Chocolate Factory's cookies to track targets. Documents seen by the Washington Post show that the NSA and the British snoops at GCHQ have found a way to …

Iain Thomson, 12 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7119_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2009/06/22/big_brother.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7119-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/12/surface_pro_2_review/</link><title>'Daddy, can I use the BLACK iPAD?': Life with the Surface Pro 2</title><description>'Daddy, can I use the BLACK iPAD?': Life with the Surface Pro 2

“Daddy, can I use the black iPad?” my four-year-old daughter asks as she spots the Surface Pro 2 I'm reviewing for The Reg. She has, without knowing it, encapsulated Microsoft's problem on Surface in a nutshell. I’d been passing the Surface Pro 2 around to friends and family at a weekend gathering to garner their feedback. …

Gavin Clarke, 12 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7119_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/08/surface_pro_keyboard_photo_gavin_clarke.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7119-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/31/google_unwraps_android_kitkat_and_nexus_5_mobe/</link><title>Google RIPS aside curtain, exposes Nexus 5 phone, KitKat Android 4.4 coupling</title><description>Google RIPS aside curtain, exposes Nexus 5 phone, KitKat Android 4.4 coupling

Google has released its latest major Android build, version 4.4 codenamed KitKat, and has started selling its new Nexus 5 smartphone as the first device to run the new OS. Nexus 5 Behold, Google's shiny new mobe ... the Nexus 5 KitKat, aka Android 4.4, has faster multitasking and full voice control, according to Google, and a …

Iain Thomson, 31 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7119_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/10/31/nexus_5.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7119-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/31/google_glass_v2_photos/</link><title>Google's new Glass: Now with audio connection INSIDE the SKULL</title><description>Google's new Glass: Now with audio connection INSIDE the SKULL

Google has posted two images of the next generation of its much-mocked Glass wearable tech, revealing for the first time the direction it plans to go for future versions of the product. Photo of Google Glass version 2 Meet the new Glass ... mostly very similar to the old Glass The photos appeared on the Glass team's Google+ …

Neil McAllister, 31 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7119_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/10/31/glass_earbud1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>