<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7121">who is the man in the m&amp;m commercial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:07:24" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7121-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/08/cobol_s_360_anniversary/</link><title>The gift of Grace: COBOL's odyssey from Vietnam to the Square Mile</title><description>The gift of Grace: COBOL's odyssey from Vietnam to the Square Mile

Cobol is the language most associated with mainframes, especially the IBM System 360 whose 50th anniversary is being celebrated or at least commemorated this week. But when COBOL was first spawned in the mid-1950s, it wasn’t intended for programmers. It was aimed instead at “accountants and business managers” – basically a Stone …

Dominic Connor, 08 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7121_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/03/09/grace_hopper_419x278.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7121-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/07/ibm_s_360_50_anniversary/</link><title>Why won't you DIE? IBM's S/360 and its legacy at 50</title><description>Why won't you DIE? IBM's S/360 and its legacy at 50

IBM's System 360 mainframe, celebrating its 50th anniversary on Monday, was more than a just another computer. The S/360 changed IBM just as it changed computing and the technology industry. The digital computers that were to become known as mainframes were already being sold by companies during the 1950s and 1960s - so the S/ …

Gavin Clarke, 07 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7121_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/07/01/ibm_system_360_model_50.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7121-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/29/hawkins_ai_feature/</link><title>Meet the man building an AI that mimics our neocortex – and could kill off neural networks</title><description>Meet the man building an AI that mimics our neocortex – and could kill off neural networks

Jeff Hawkins has bet his reputation, fortune, and entire intellectual life on one idea: that he understands the brain well enough to create machines with an intelligence we recognize as our own. If his bet is correct, the Palm Pilot inventor will father a new technology, one that becomes the crucible in which a general …

Jack Clark, 29 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7121_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/03/28/hawkins_419x278.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7121-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/14/monitor_micro_men/</link><title>Micro Men: The story of the syntax era</title><description>Micro Men: The story of the syntax era

is an occasional column written at the crossroads where the arts, popular culture and technology intersect. Here we look back at the BBC TV movie Micro Men, a retro-tech fan favourite which tells the story of the rivalry between former colleagues Sir Clive Sinclair and Chris Curry, and how the two men kickstarted the British …

Tony Smith, 14 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7121_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/10/mm_12.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7121-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/12/archaeologic_amstrad_cpc_464/</link><title>You’re NOT fired: The story of Amstrad’s amazing CPC 464</title><description>You’re NOT fired: The story of Amstrad’s amazing CPC 464

It was a home computer that embodied so many contradictions. It was launched months after the British microcomputer boom of the early 1980s had peaked. It was a rush job: the machine that was revealed to the press in the Spring of 1984 hadn’t even existed nine months previously. It was one of the best-produced British micros of …

Tony Smith, 12 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7121_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/01/13/464_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7121-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/12/archaeologic_sinclair_ql/</link><title>Sinclair’s 1984 big shot at business: The QL is 30 years old</title><description>Sinclair’s 1984 big shot at business: The QL is 30 years old

In May 1983, Sinclair Research Managing Director Nigel Searle began briefing the press about the successful British micro maker’s next big release. It was 13 months after the company had launched the Spectrum and although that machine had become a huge success, punters and market-watchers were keen to hear about what Sinclair …

Tony Smith, 12 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7121_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/12/13/ql_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7121-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/10/phil_houghton_interview/</link><title>Teary-eyed snappers recall the golden age of film</title><description>Teary-eyed snappers recall the golden age of film

For those readers with a tendency to get teary-eyed over the golden age of film, and the days before digital swept physical photographic media into the cutting room bin of history, we're delighted to take a trip down memory lane today with professional photographer Phil Houghton. Portrait of Phil Houghton holding mighty Nikon …

Lester Haines, 10 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7121_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/12/05/phil_houghton_teaser.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7121-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/28/vmware_community_deep_dive/</link><title>I dived deep into the VMware community. Here's what I found...</title><description>I dived deep into the VMware community. Here's what I found...

The VMware community is more complex than any other IT community I've studied. El Reg sysadmin blogger Phoummala Schmitt has given a fantastic look at the stark contrast between the VMware and Microsoft communities. I am going to delve into the details of the VMware community a little more thoroughly. The tweets must flow If …

Trevor Pott, 28 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7121_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/28/vmworld_small_index.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7121-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/07/alfresco_ipo_analysis/</link><title>Alfresco's IPO is bad news for tech stock junkies</title><description>Alfresco's IPO is bad news for tech stock junkies

UK open-source software biz Alfresco took a big decision in January when it named its first new chief executive in eight years, replacing the British John Powell with the American Doug Dennerline. Powell, who had been CEO since the founding of Alfresco, captained the British company from small fish to 1,300-customer whale, …

Gavin Clarke, 07 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7121_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/10/01/john_newton2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7121-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/08/27/data_mining_for_the_ppi_scandal/</link><title>Loads of mis-sold PPI, but WHO will claim? This man's paid to find out</title><description>Loads of mis-sold PPI, but WHO will claim? This man's paid to find out

When the opening line of a conversation starts, “I read an interesting number the other day”, it’s fairly safe to assume that you’re talking to someone whose business it is to know about "interesting numbers". Perhaps unsurprisingly, these words were uttered by an economist whose ability to find god gold in the numbers is the …

Bob Dormon, 27 Aug 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7121_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/08/29/canary_wharf_at_night_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>