<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7129">avg home edition</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:37:28" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7129-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/05/11/ten_freeware_apps_for_pcs/</link><title>Ten... freeware gems for new PCs</title><description>Ten... freeware gems for new PCs

Reg Hardware PC Week If you’ve just purchased a spanking new Windows PC, what to slap on there often leaves pause for thought. The trial bloatware that inevitably came with your machine might keep you busy for a while until the payment nag screens start. Yet those costs and curses aside, there are plenty of free apps out …

Shaun Dormon, 11 May 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7129_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/08/ten_free_apps_to_instal_on_new_pcs.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7129-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/11/02/sophos_mac_anti_virus/</link><title>Sophos debuts freebie anti-virus scanner for Macs</title><description>Sophos debuts freebie anti-virus scanner for Macs

Sophos released a free of charge Mac anti-virus product for consumers on Tuesday in a bid to highlight the growing security risk against the platform and to shake fanbois out of their complacency. The business-focused internet security firm is making Sophos Anti-Virus Home Edition for Mac available for download at no charge - …

John Leyden, 02 Nov 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7129_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/03/chandef2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7129-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/01/20/avast5/</link><title>New avast freebie security scanner aims to keel-haul MS</title><description>New avast freebie security scanner aims to keel-haul MS

A new version of avast aims to offer users of free anti-malware technology faster running protection against the latest hacking attacks, while offering alternatives to AVG and Microsoft Security Essentials. avast Free 5.0 comes with the same engine under its bonnet as its premium sibling, avast Pro Antivirus 5.0. Both versions …

John Leyden, 20 Jan 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7129_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7129-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/05/21/bitdefender_free_av/</link><title>BitDefender launches 'suck it and see' free anti-virus scanner</title><description>BitDefender launches 'suck it and see' free anti-virus scanner

Romanian anti-virus firm BitDefender has begun offering a free version of its anti-virus scanner software to consumers. Similarly cut-down versions of BitDefender's anti-phishing and chat encryption software are also being offered at no charge to home users. The launch of free editions of its security suites is designed to …

John Leyden, 21 May 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7129_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/03/chandef4.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7129-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/12/02/apple_mac_av_advice/</link><title>Apple tells Mac users: Get anti-virus</title><description>Apple tells Mac users: Get anti-virus

For the first time, Apple is recommending the use of anti-virus tools to protect Mac systems. Long something of a phantom menace, strains of malware capable of infecting Mac machines have gradually been increasing in prevalence over recent months. In addition, VXers are making more use of web-based attack and applications …

John Leyden, 02 Dec 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7129_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2007/09/18/apple_logo_sm.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7129-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/03/14/grisoft_sme_launch/</link><title>GRISoft targets SMEs' security sweet spot</title><description>GRISoft targets SMEs' security sweet spot

Czech anti-virus firm GRISoft is targeting the small and medium sized business market with revamped versions of its network security products. Versions of its AVG Small Business Server for Internet Security and Anti-Malware are designed to protect the file access and email servers of smaller firms from virus infestation and …

Team Register, 14 Mar 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7129_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7129-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2003/11/18/ca_revives_free_av_software/</link><title>CA revives free AV software offer</title><description>CA revives free AV software offer

Computer Associates today revived a free AV software offer to consumers months 18 months after canning a similar service as no longer viable. In conjunction with Microsoft, CA is offering "qualified Windows home computer users" with a no-charge, one-year subscription to CA's eTrust EZ Armor antivirus and firewall desktop …

John Leyden, 18 Nov 2003</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7129_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7129-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2002/02/22/ca_cans_updates_for_free/</link><title>CA cans updates for free personal AV package</title><description>CA cans updates for free personal AV package

Computer Associates (CA) is to cease providing updates for its free InoculateIT Personal Edition (IPE) anti-virus software on May 15. CA stopped taking on new users for IPE in June last year and replaced it with the eTrust EZ Antivirus subscription service; at the time it advised users that support was to be continued at no …

John Leyden, 22 Feb 2002</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7129_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>