<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7131">golf games</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:56:53" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7131-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/23/club_wembley_reg_reader_offer/</link><title>Treat yourself to some FA, NFL or 1D action at Wembley Stadium</title><description>Treat yourself to some FA, NFL or 1D action at Wembley Stadium

Clients are a fickle lot, but most would leap at the chance to see the FA Cup final at Wembley Stadium. Or a big pop concert. No? Maybe a NFL game could tickle their fancy. The Register is a media partner of Wembley Stadium and this is our promo. Here is a great chance to reward your valued customers – or indeed yourself. …

David Gordon, 23 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7131_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/05/16/wembley_image_01.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7131-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/21/doctor_who_the_right_stuff/</link><title>Dry, cold and volatile: How to survive Mars, and your fellow crew</title><description>Dry, cold and volatile: How to survive Mars, and your fellow crew

What did you want to be when you grew up? Chances are as a follower of Dr Who, you wanted to be a Time lord. While travel in time sadly isn’t on the cards, space travel is becoming a reality with Virgin Galactic’s SpaceShipTwo working through 50-plus rocket-powered test flights to qualify for passenger flights and with the Space …

Dave Wilby, 21 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7131_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/10/09/thomas_presquet_eva_training_with_nasa_photo_esa.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7131-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/03/15/samsung_galaxy_s_4_rollout/</link><title>Samsung's new Galaxy S 4: iPhone assassin or Android also-ran?</title><description>Samsung's new Galaxy S 4: iPhone assassin or Android also-ran?

After weeks of hypegasmic drum-beating at a level unusual for the South Korean consumer-electronics giant, Samsung unveiled its Galaxy S 4 at an embarassingly over-the-top, show-biz–infused gala on Thursday evening. Held in New York City, the extravaganza overshadowed the fact that the Galaxy S 4 appears to be a fine Android …

Rik Myslewski, 15 Mar 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7131_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/03/15/samsung_s_4.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7131-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/11/24/ten_playstation_3_games_you_may_have_missed/</link><title>Ten PlayStation 3 games you may have missed</title><description>Ten PlayStation 3 games you may have missed

While summer was a fairly dry time for games releases, this autumn has gone haywire in the build up to Christmas and as a result, it feels like more titles are being handed out than knighthoods. As usual, we've sifted through the good and the bad to compile a list of any worthy ones you may have missed. While the following ten …

Caleb Cox, 24 Nov 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7131_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/11/16/games_9.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7131-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/07/23/olympics_cio/</link><title>Is running IT for the Olympics the worst job in the world?</title><description>Is running IT for the Olympics the worst job in the world?

It's going to be the Worst Tech Job in the world ... or the best. It all depends on how the Olympics IT works this summer. Michele Hyron will be either in front of a Parliamentary committee explaining why the tech at the Olympics was a fiasco, or enjoying a well-earned rest - because she is ATOS's chief integrator for the Games …

Dominic Connor, 23 Jul 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7131_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/olympics2012.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7131-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/02/27/review_game_ten_playstation_vita_launch_games/</link><title>Ten... PlayStation Vita launch games</title><description>Ten... PlayStation Vita launch games

Reg Hardware Mobile Week Sony has made sure the Vita doesn't suffer from the same lack of games the Nintendo 3DS did upon release, so there's a broad set of launch titles to keep fans happy. Combine that with dozens of third-party offerings and you have a quality bunch to pick from. I had to narrow down ten from a collection …

Caleb Cox, 27 Feb 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7131_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/02/24/vitagames_9.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7131-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/01/27/playstation_vita_games_to_cost_as_much_as_ps3_titles/</link><title>Playstation Vita games match PS3 software prices</title><description>Playstation Vita games match PS3 software prices

As next month's PlayStation Vita launch edges near, publishers have revealed prices for the games that'll be available, with some titles even stretching to a big-ticket £45. The news that games could cost the same as PS3 titles won't to win favour from gamers, especially when smartphone games can be had for extremely low prices …

Caleb Cox, 27 Jan 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7131_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/10/19/vita_2.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7131-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/11/23/sony_demoes_augmented_reality_on_ps_vita/</link><title>Sony demos Augmented Reality on PS Vita</title><description>Sony demos Augmented Reality on PS Vita

Sony showed off the PlayStation Vita's Augmented Reality features last night, and announced the full line-up of launch titles. The company put the spotlight on AR, revealing the device will handle six Augmented Reality markers at launch, with three games available to download free from the PlayStation Store. You can see the tech …

Caleb Cox, 23 Nov 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7131_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/10/19/vita_2.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7131-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/11/11/first_look_sony_ps_vita_handheld_gaming_console/</link><title>Hands on with the Sony PlayStation Vita</title><description>Hands on with the Sony PlayStation Vita

It seems fair to state that for a while now Sony's PSP handheld games console has been experiencing something of long and undignified death. Even the Japanese technology giant itself saw fit to limit PSP software releases to largely redundant updates of its EyePet and Invizimals franchises – a move hardly likely to cause a …

Mike Plant, 11 Nov 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7131_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/10/19/vita_2.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7131-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/09/07/igamer_review_apptoyz_appblaster/</link><title>appToyz appBlaster</title><description>appToyz appBlaster

Gaming peripherals have a bad reputation, and not without good reason. From the sublime Steel Battalion controller to every ridiculous Wii peripheral, these plastic appendages have one thing in common: they make gamers look sublimely ridiculous. appToyz appBlaster Point and shoot: appToyz appBlaster Even those which actually …

Andrew Bailey, 07 Sep 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7131_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/09/07/apptoyz_appblaster.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>