<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7133">museum of natural history</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:26:11" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7133-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/28/diplodocus_sells_at_auction/</link><title>COMPLETE, FIFTY-FOOT DINOSAUR sold to MYSTERIOUS, reclusive bidder for £480k</title><description>COMPLETE, FIFTY-FOOT DINOSAUR sold to MYSTERIOUS, reclusive bidder for £480k

A rare skeleton of one of the largest creatures ever to walk the Earth has been sold at auction for nearly half a million quid to a mystery buyer. A near complete 17-metre-long Diplodocus longus skeleton, aged 150 million years and widely thought to be a female, was sold for £480,000 ($779,856) on Thursday by Summers Place …

Gavin Clarke, 28 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7133_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/02/23/thunder_thighs.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7133-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/07/new_tyrannosaur_species_lythronax_argestes/</link><title>BLOOD KING of the TYRANNOSAURS, grandad of T-Rex</title><description>BLOOD KING of the TYRANNOSAURS, grandad of T-Rex

A new kind of vicious tyrannosaur that pre-dates Tyrannosaurus rex has been unearthed in southern Utah and christened the "King of Gore". Artist's impression of the Lythronax argestes The Tyrannosauridae family already contains massive creatures whose names translate as "frightful" and "fierce" kings as well as "monstrous …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 07 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7133_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/07/lythronax_argestes_dinosaur.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7133-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/30/new_species_humpback_dolphin/</link><title>Shy, bashful HUMPBACK DOLPHINS expose themselves to boffins</title><description>Shy, bashful HUMPBACK DOLPHINS expose themselves to boffins

A previously unknown species of humpback dolphin has been blithely swimming the waters off northern Australia, according to scientists. A research team made up of scientists from the Wildlife Conservation Society (WCS), the American Museum of Natural History and other groups set out to figure out the number of distinct types of …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 30 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7133_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/10/30/new_humpback_dolphin_species.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7133-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/17/water_spider_brain/</link><title>Behold, the MONSTER-CLAWED critter and its terrifying SPIDER BRAIN</title><description>Behold, the MONSTER-CLAWED critter and its terrifying SPIDER BRAIN

Boffins have uncovered the earliest known complete central nervous system in a never-before-described water-spider-like creature that prowled the ocean 520 MILLION years ago. A fossil of the megacheiran Leanchoilia illecebrosa, showing its characteristic forceps-like great appendages The massively clawed beast is an example …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 17 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7133_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/10/17/water_spider_fossil.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7133-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/16/rare_oarfish_find/</link><title>OAR-some! 18ft SEA SERPENT discovered off US coast</title><description>OAR-some! 18ft SEA SERPENT discovered off US coast

A marine boffin has come across a terrifying 18-foot "sea serpent" off the coast of California. Youtube Video Marine science instructor Jasmine Santana was swimming along the coast of Catalina Island when she came across the huge beast, which was actually a rare oarfish, but nonetheless the "discovery of a lifetime", according …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 16 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7133_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/10/16/oarfish_girl.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7133-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/10/history_of_magnetic_tape_part_three/</link><title>Video thrilled the radio star: Tracking the history of magnetic tape</title><description>Video thrilled the radio star: Tracking the history of magnetic tape

El Reg's magnetic tape odyssey has covered tape's early beginnings in sound recording in part one and its revolution in computing in part two. In this final part, we look at how film and TV became some of magnetic tape's best customers. The music and computer industries weren’t the only early adopters of magnetic tape. The …

Bob Dormon, 10 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7133_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/10/10/rca_video_recorder_ad2_480.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7133-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/09/19/history_of_magnetic_tape_part_two/</link><title>Tracking the history of magnetic tape: A game of noughts and crosses</title><description>Tracking the history of magnetic tape: A game of noughts and crosses

America began its love affair with tape following WWII, when Jack Mullin, serving in the US Army Signal Corps, dropped in on German radio broadcaster Bad Nauheim and returned home with two portable Magnetophons and 50 reels of tape. News of his 1947 Hollywood equipment demos reached entertainer Bing Crosby who recognised the …

Bob Dormon, 19 Sep 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7133_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/17/ibm_3410_open_reel_tape_subsystem.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7133-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/09/11/wooly_mammoths_killed_by_climate_change/</link><title>Cavemen innocent in MAMMOTH MURDER case: DNA evidence</title><description>Cavemen innocent in MAMMOTH MURDER case: DNA evidence

Boffins have claimed that the demise of the woolly mammoth was caused by climate change, offering up an alternate theory to the premise that its spot on the human menu was to blame for the species' extinction. British and Swedish researchers examined 300 mammoth carcasses from around the world and found that populations tumbled …

Jasper Hamill, 11 Sep 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7133_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/05/30/mammoth_carcass.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7133-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/09/09/history_of_magnetic_tape_part_one/</link><title>Reelin' in the years: Tracking the history of magnetic tape</title><description>Reelin' in the years: Tracking the history of magnetic tape

Today marks the 80th anniversary of the first patent filing for a magnetic tape recording medium, though the tech I worked with was a bit more recent than that. Still, it has been quite some time since I last went shopping for tape. I recall the last time as being a deal on a load of JVC miniDV cassettes that I still haven't …

Bob Dormon, 09 Sep 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7133_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/04/12/fritz_pfleumer_with_tape_recorder.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7133-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/08/16/sss/</link><title>'Abel, put that camera down right now! Abel, you're fired. Out!'</title><description>'Abel, put that camera down right now! Abel, you're fired. Out!'

This was the week where we all heard AOL boss Tim Armstrong publicly fire a hapless camera-toting creative in the middle of a tense conference call about the fate of local news platform Patch. The meeting took place last week, but the audio was leaked just a few days ago, when we were all treated to a recording of the moment the …

Jasper Hamill, 16 Aug 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7133_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2007/12/18/zuck_arrow.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>