<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7134">history of yoga</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:49:39" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7134-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/11/feature_geeks_guide_uk_national_archive/</link><title>How the UK's national memory lives in a ROBOT in Kew</title><description>How the UK's national memory lives in a ROBOT in Kew

The UK’s National Archives in Kew have enough gems and hidden secrets to keep Indiana Jones or Robert Langdon in sequels for the next couple of centuries, with everything from the Domesday book to the UK’s official UFO records socked away safely in its sanctum. But for the swashbuckling archaeological hero of the future, whips, …

Joe Fay, 11 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7134_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/12/09/national_archive_robot_room.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7134-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/01/18/7_reasons_windows_rt_was_doa/</link><title>Microsoft's ARM blunder: 7 reasons why Windows RT was DOA</title><description>Microsoft's ARM blunder: 7 reasons why Windows RT was DOA

Industry doomsayers were circling Windows 8 like buzzards before it even launched, but they picked the wrong carcass. Microsoft's real 2012 roadkill was Win8's ARM-powered cousin, Windows RT. The chattering class's comparisons of Windows 8 and Windows Vista are premature – it will take several more quarters before we can gauge …

Neil McAllister, 18 Jan 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7134_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/06/21/microsoft_surface_tablets.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7134-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/01/08/intel_ultrabook_plans/</link><title>Intel bets the farm on touch-enabled 'convertible and detachable' Ultrabooks</title><description>Intel bets the farm on touch-enabled 'convertible and detachable' Ultrabooks

To hear Intel tell it, the days of the good ol' laptop are numbered, and the future belongs to touch-enabled convertibles – laptops that lead a double life as both clamshells and tablets. "We fundamentally believe that there's a convergence happening between what traditionally have been notebook computing and tablet computing, …

Rik Myslewski, 08 Jan 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7134_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7134-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/11/12/mcafee_murder_report/</link><title>Report: McAfee founder wanted for murder in Belize</title><description>Report: McAfee founder wanted for murder in Belize

John McAfee, the founder of the antivirus software firm that still bears his name, is wanted in Belize in connection with the murder of American expatriate Gregory Faull, who was found dead on Sunday. Marco Vidal, head of the country's Gang Suppression Unit, told Gizmodo that McAfee was a prime suspect in the case. Faull, who …

Iain Thomson, 12 Nov 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7134_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/07/17/police_tape.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7134-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/05/16/nokia_kills_ovi_brand/</link><title>Nokia finally gives Ovi brand a mercy bullet</title><description>Nokia finally gives Ovi brand a mercy bullet

"People often ask, 'What's a "Nokia"? – is it some new kind of yoga or a fashionable new diet?' Then you remind them – it's the platform for the Ovi mobile services experience – and the fog of confusion quickly clears." – The Register, August 2010 Tears will be shed in Shoreditch and Soho tonight as Nokia has confirmed it is …

Andrew Orlowski, 16 May 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7134_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7134-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/06/23/letters/</link><title>Planet X a bigger threat than malware</title><description>Planet X a bigger threat than malware

Right, let's get down to it cos there's some top-notch footie to be watched and much beer to be simultaneously drunk this fine Friday afternoon. First up: the UK's Court of Appeal says that PlayStation 2 is not a PC. It's all to do with the electronics monolith wanting to have it declassified as a games console and thereby get …

Lester Haines, 23 Jun 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7134_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7134-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2004/08/19/infected_in20_minutes/</link><title>Infected in 20 minutes</title><description>Infected in 20 minutes

What normally happens within twenty minutes? That's how long your average unprotected PC running Windows XP, fresh out of the box, will last once it's connected to the Internet. It's interesting to ponder just how much time - in hours, in minutes, sometimes in mere seconds - it takes for a disaster to occur. The space shuttle …

Scott Granneman, 19 Aug 2004</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7134_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>