<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7136">Soccer trick</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:04:25" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7136-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/10/15/games_reviews_fifa_vs_pro_evo_2011/</link><title>Fifa 11 vs Pro Evolution Soccer 2011</title><description>Fifa 11 vs Pro Evolution Soccer 2011

Loyalty in football is a strange thing. Through thick and thin, we stay behind our fave football teams. We remain very opinionated about which broadcaster is better. But we're all glory hunters when it comes to football games - we want the best. Loyalty only lasts so long. There's only ever been two footie games that bring such …

Caleb Cox, 15 Oct 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7136_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2010/10/14/fifa_2011_vs_pro_evo_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7136-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/03/26/house_of_cards_alberta_gambling_china/</link><title>Canada puts its mounted booties down</title><description>Canada puts its mounted booties down

Canuckia gets tough The controversy in Canada surrounding the expansion of online gambling took another turn this week as the attorney general of Alberta weighed in on the recent attempt by the Alexander First Nation to begin offering the same online gambling services as the Kahnawake tribe in Quebec. The Kahnawake of Quebec …

Burke Hansen, 26 Mar 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7136_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7136-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/11/29/otto_sadville/</link><title>Bloggers turn to Sadville to fabricate child traumas</title><description>Bloggers turn to Sadville to fabricate child traumas

Was Daniel Sadville a knight with a moral compass wound tight or one of those pagan spiritualists out to make a huckster from anything that moved? That's what the audience wanted to know - just before they pulled out the tomatoes and the jackhammers - Julio Stantore, Large Gland Weeping My recent "How to help bloggers restore …

Otto Z. Stern, 29 Nov 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7136_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>