<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7137">Cat movies</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:08:55" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7137-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/11/ten_tech_toys_for_xmas/</link><title>Ten top tech toys to interface with a techie’s Christmas stocking</title><description>Ten top tech toys to interface with a techie’s Christmas stocking

‘Tis the season for dropping unsubtle hints about gifts that YOU’D like to receive, or – if you prefer – for making a list of things that you would buy for nephews and nieces but, because you’re an evil misanthropic Uncle or Auntie, you’ll buy for yourself instead. At least that way there’ll be no tantrums round the tree and …

Nigel Whitfield, 11 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7137_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/07/05/pilite_2.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7137-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/18/review_sony_xperia_z1/</link><title>Getting it right on the second attempt: Sony Xperia Z1</title><description>Getting it right on the second attempt: Sony Xperia Z1

The Xperia Z has had a surprisingly short stint as the top dog of Sony’s smartphone range and has now been unceremoniously ousted by the Xperia Z1. Sony Xperia Z1 Sony’s Xperia Z1: getting it right, second time around? But the new Z1 isn’t just a cosmetic warm-over. It has a more powerful processor, a much improved screen, a …

Alun Taylor, 18 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7137_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/18/z1_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7137-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/03/review_sony_xperia_ultra_z/</link><title>Sony Xperia Z Ultra: The quad-core 2.2GHz MEGA SCREEN PHONDLESLAB</title><description>Sony Xperia Z Ultra: The quad-core 2.2GHz MEGA SCREEN PHONDLESLAB

Two years after Samsung opened the Very Large Phone (VLP™) Pandora’s Box with the original Galaxy Note, Sony has thrown its hat into the ring with the Xperia Z Ultra: a device boasting a 6.4-inch screen and a 2.2GHz quad-core processor. Now I have a pretty wild imagination, especially after a few pints and an injudicious late- …

Alun Taylor, 03 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7137_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/30/uz_11.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7137-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/08/07/making_world_war_z_3d/</link><title>The terrifying tech behind this summer's zombie assault</title><description>The terrifying tech behind this summer's zombie assault

So there you are in the cinema. Watching Titanic again for some reason. Kate Winslet has just saucily suggested to Leonardo Di Caprio that he paints her like one of his French girls. Then she leans over and pokes you in the eye. What happened there? You’ve got a fair idea how 3D films are made, and you’re pretty confident that …

Michael Moran, 07 Aug 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7137_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/13/zombie.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7137-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/04/19/youtube_wins_copyright_case_again/</link><title>YouTube beats off $1bn Viacom copyright case once AGAIN</title><description>YouTube beats off $1bn Viacom copyright case once AGAIN

The courts have once more sided with YouTube in the copyright case brought against it by Viacom and others. The billion-dollar lawsuit was first filed way back in 2007, not long after Google snapped up the video streaming service. Viacom alleged that YouTube was knowingly allowing copyright-infringing material to be posted onto …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 19 Apr 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7137_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7137-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/03/08/hug_a_pirate/</link><title>Congratulations, freetards: You are THE FIVE PER CENT</title><description>Congratulations, freetards: You are THE FIVE PER CENT

Meet the most pampered group in the UK. Bankers? Farmers? Wind-farm operators? The depressed river mussel? Actually, none of the above. It's copyright infringers. New research from UK communications regulator Ofcom shows that filling your boots with pirate downloads remains risk free and a money saver, particularly if you like …

Andrew Orlowski, 08 Mar 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7137_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7137-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/11/02/bond_quiz/</link><title>Bond fans: Test your 007 trivia, now!</title><description>Bond fans: Test your 007 trivia, now!

As the dust settles on on our recent round of Bond polls - in which readers voted Ernst Stavro Blofeld, Sean Connery and Casino Royale the vilest Bond villain, the ultimate movie Bond and the best Bond film, respectively - we're offering fans the chance to see if they've really got what it takes to hold the coveted 00 number. …

Lester Haines, 02 Nov 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7137_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7137-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/10/27/copyright_office_dcma_exemptions/</link><title>US Copyright Office approves phone jailbreaking and video remixes</title><description>US Copyright Office approves phone jailbreaking and video remixes

The US Copyright Office has published the latest exceptions to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA) and it's good news for phone jailbreakers and video remixers, who are now legal – well, until 2015, at least. The terms of DMCA lockdowns are reviewed every three years, and the Electronic Frontier Foundation (EFF) is …

Iain Thomson, 27 Oct 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7137_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7137-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/04/13/movie_compo/</link><title>So what's the worst movie NEVER made?</title><description>So what's the worst movie NEVER made?

Our hunt for the worst movie ever proved highly popular with you, our beloved cinema-going readers, and the list of nominees makes such chilling reading that we began to wonder if it would be possible to shoot a film so atrocious that it would prompt audiences to run screaming from the cinema vowing never again to badmouth …

Lester Haines, 13 Apr 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7137_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7137-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/11/22/product_round_up_ten_monster_tellies/</link><title>Ten... Monster tellies</title><description>Ten... Monster tellies

Back in the day you had to resort to a cabinet-sized rear projection TV if you wanted to watch Dallas on anything larger than a 37in CRT. Thankfully times have changed. Technically advanced, visually stunning super-screens are now the order of the day from every major brand. You need only oust some living room essentials – sofa …

Steve May, 22 Nov 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7137_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/11/15/sony_bravia_kdl-55hx923.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>