<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7138">lance armstrong oprah</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:34:54" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7138-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/01/21/armstrong_reclassified/</link><title>Oz library finds Lance Armstrong books a new home: The fiction section</title><description>Oz library finds Lance Armstrong books a new home: The fiction section

An Australian library has announced it will reclassify books by Lance Armstrong as fiction, the Sydney Morning Herald reports. The announcement at Manly Library moving Lance Armstrong books to fiction Book browsers at Manly Library in Sydney wishing to draw inspiration from Lance Armstrong: World's Greatest Champion and other …

Lester Haines, 21 Jan 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7138_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7138-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/10/28/twitterpeek_mobile/</link><title>TwitterPeek - the handset that spews Web2.0rhea...</title><description>TwitterPeek - the handset that spews Web2.0rhea...

Are you into Twitter? Are you insanely, over-the-top, Tweeting-at-your-mother's-funeral into Twitter? Well, now there's a device made just for your crippling character flaw, you lucky duck. Peek, the folks who make always-on handsets just for email, bring you TwitterPeek: a $200 mobile that does nothing but send, receive, and …

Austin Modine, 28 Oct 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7138_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7138-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/01/23/brandchannel_2005_brand_survey/</link><title>Google crushes Apple in battle of the brands</title><description>Google crushes Apple in battle of the brands

Google has knocked Apple off the top of a list of the world's most influential brands in 2005, doing unto the iPod maker what it did to the Internet advertising company in 2004. The list was compiled by brandchannel.com and was based on a survey of 2,528 branding professionals and members of the public. The poll was conducted …

Tony Smith, 23 Jan 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7138_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>