<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7141">Cambridge must do</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:28:53" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7141-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/19/ee_phone_network_uk_outage/</link><title>It's not you, it's EE: UK mobile network goes titsup, blames gremlins</title><description>It's not you, it's EE: UK mobile network goes titsup, blames gremlins

Brits on the UK cell network EE are reporting dodgy connections, delayed text messages and other problems tonight. Some users are unable to make calls even though they have a full signal strength showing on their mobiles. According to handy uptime monitoring website downdetector.co.uk, most of the complaints are coming in from …

Chris Williams, 19 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7141_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/15/angry_woman_mobile_shutterstock_small.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7141-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/19/future_of_wireless_2014/</link><title>What have Cherie Blair, Jonathan Porritt and El Reg's mobile desk got in common?</title><description>What have Cherie Blair, Jonathan Porritt and El Reg's mobile desk got in common?

For all the trumpeting of Silicon Roundabout with its app companies and ecosystem start-ups, or northern California with improved user experiences and social media, the real work in mobile gets done here in old Blighty: specifically, on the silicon fens of Cambridge. Cambridge, as all the world knows, is the home of ARM and CSR …

Simon Rockman, 19 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7141_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/02/03/original_blue_marble.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7141-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/06/global_warming_real_just_not_as_scary_as/</link><title>Global Warming IS REAL, argues sceptic mathematician - it just isn't THERMAGEDDON</title><description>Global Warming IS REAL, argues sceptic mathematician - it just isn't THERMAGEDDON

The "certainty" that underpins European and UK climate policy may be wildly misplaced, as the models that the climate science establishment presents to politicians as evidence run far too hot. That's according to a report released yesterday by UK think-tank the Global Warming Policy Foundation. And this is very good news, says …

Andrew Orlowski, 06 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7141_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/11/27/globe.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7141-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/12/archaeologic_amstrad_cpc_464/</link><title>You’re NOT fired: The story of Amstrad’s amazing CPC 464</title><description>You’re NOT fired: The story of Amstrad’s amazing CPC 464

It was a home computer that embodied so many contradictions. It was launched months after the British microcomputer boom of the early 1980s had peaked. It was a rush job: the machine that was revealed to the press in the Spring of 1984 hadn’t even existed nine months previously. It was one of the best-produced British micros of …

Tony Smith, 12 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7141_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/01/13/464_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7141-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/06/feature_killing_patent_trolls/</link><title>How to kill trolls and influence Apple people: A patent solution</title><description>How to kill trolls and influence Apple people: A patent solution

Having decided that the patent problem is an attempt to solve a public goods problem, as we did in part 1, let's have a look at the specific ways that we put our oar into those perfect and competitive free markets. It's worth just noting that patents and copyright are not, absolutely not, the product of some fevered free market …

Tim Worstall, 06 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7141_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2009/02/11/rubdogagainsttable.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7141-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/20/andrew_fentem_interview/</link><title>Andrew Fentem: Why I went to an arts quango to fund pre-iPhone multitouch</title><description>Andrew Fentem: Why I went to an arts quango to fund pre-iPhone multitouch

In the late '90s British inventor Andrew Fentem pioneered multitouch techniques, years before Apple brought them to market in the iPhone and later the iPad. He won backing for his technology from Britain's new innovation quango: but its incompetence meant that Apple ultimately looked elsewhere. We told the story of how the UK …

Andrew Orlowski, 20 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7141_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/04/27/toshiba_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7141-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/13/uk_innovation_nesta_fentem/</link><title>How Britain could have invented the iPhone: And how the Quangocracy cocked it up</title><description>How Britain could have invented the iPhone: And how the Quangocracy cocked it up

This is a disturbing, cautionary tale of quasi-government and its bungling. It describes how Britain could have led the recent advances in touchscreen technology, developing kit capable detecting more than one fingertip at once, years before Apple did – if it weren't for the nation's treacle-footed, self-serving quangocracy. …

Andrew Orlowski, 13 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7141_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/11/krusty.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7141-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/29/unsung_heroes_john_miller_kirkpatrick/</link><title>Britain’s forgotten first home computer pioneer: John Miller-Kirkpatrick</title><description>Britain’s forgotten first home computer pioneer: John Miller-Kirkpatrick

Too few people today remember John Miller-Kirkpatrick, the enthusiastic founder, owner, manager and technical director of Bywood Electronics. He died in December 1978 at the monstrously young age of 32, less than two years before the début of the Sinclair ZX80 and the start of the UK home computing boom – for which he had helped …

Tony Smith, 29 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7141_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/14/jmk_14.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7141-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/19/doctor_who_theme_elements_examined/</link><title>Delia and the Doctor: How to cook up a tune for a Time Lord</title><description>Delia and the Doctor: How to cook up a tune for a Time Lord

As a theme tune, Ron Grainer’s music for Doctor Who needs no introduction. But to describe this unique piece of electronic music as solely Ron Grainer’s composition would be a disservice to the considerable musical contribution made by Delia Derbyshire, who in 1963 set about realising the original score at the BBC’s Radiophonic …

Bob Dormon, 19 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7141_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/07/delia_derbyshire_editing_3.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7141-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/15/world_solar_challenge_following_a_top_gun/</link><title>So you want to be a solar racer? You'll need a laptop and some string</title><description>So you want to be a solar racer? You'll need a laptop and some string

On Sunday, Mark Winterbottom, Jamie Whincupp and Craig Lowndes stood on the podium after Australia's epic Bathurst 1000 race and waxed lyrical about the importance of their teams, and well they might: nobody driving against any kind of competition, whether race or challenge, goes far without their team. Out on the road, at the …

Richard Chirgwin, 15 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7141_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/10/14/twente_unlidded_600.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>