<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7144">can headphones cause hearing loss</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:56:33" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7144-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/01/06/letters/</link><title>Cheerleading not fatal: official</title><description>Cheerleading not fatal: official

Our piece earlier this week about the possible health risks of cheerleading (death being the most noteworthy, hence the shamelessly sensationalist headline), provoked the following immediate response: I just finished reading your article 'Cheerleading can kill: official'. It is growing leaps and bounds in your country and does …

Lester Haines, 06 Jan 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7144_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7144-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/01/04/ipod_cans/</link><title>iPods can damage hearing, says deaf rock star</title><description>iPods can damage hearing, says deaf rock star

Who guitarist Pete Townshend has sort-of backed recent sensational claims that iPod headphones can permanently damage your hearing, the BBC notes. Giving forth on his website, the sexagenarian guitar worrier declares: "I have unwittingly helped to invent and refine a type of music that makes its principal proponents deaf," …

Lester Haines, 04 Jan 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7144_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7144-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/12/20/electric_earbuds/</link><title>iPod headphones may damage hearing</title><description>iPod headphones may damage hearing

Music lovers are being warned that the popular 'earbud' headphones worn by users of iPods and MP3 players could lead to hearing loss. The warning comes from Dean Garstecki, a Northwestern University audiologist and professor, who said that because earbuds are placed directly into the ear, they can boost the sound signal by as …

ElectricNews.net, 20 Dec 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7144_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>