<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7146">why do leaves fall</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:03:20" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7146-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/09/turnbull_leaves_australias_broadband_blackspots_in_the_dark/</link><title>Turnbull leaves Australia's broadband blackspots in the dark</title><description>Turnbull leaves Australia's broadband blackspots in the dark

Australians without broadband are no closer to being able to understand when, or if, the nation's National Broadband Network (NBN) will make fast data connections available, after Australia's Communications Minister Malcolm Turnbull issued a new Statement of Expectations document to NBN Co, the entity charged with building the …

Simon Sharwood, 09 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7146_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/04/09/malcolm_turnbull_shaking_hands_with_oldies.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7146-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/09/not_the_stockopolis/</link><title>No, we're not in an IT 'stockapoclyse' – boom (and bust) is exactly what tech world needs</title><description>No, we're not in an IT 'stockapoclyse' – boom (and bust) is exactly what tech world needs

Is this the stockapoclyse, as tech shares crater into the ground and no more money gets invested into the sector? Or is that 20 per cent fall in the largest internet-based companies – Netflix, Flicker and Twitter – that $275bn drop in collective value over the last month, just an overdue correction to recent price run ups? Well …

Tim Worstall, 09 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7146_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/12/stock_ticker_board.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7146-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/10/pm_cameron_jumps_aboard_internet_of_thingies/</link><title>PM Cameron leaps aboard Internet of Thingies</title><description>PM Cameron leaps aboard Internet of Thingies

Prime Minister David Cameron thinks he has spotted the "Second Industrial Revolution" – and it’s the Internet of Things. Speaking at the start of the CeBIT show in Hannover, Cameron foresaw British software and services companies working up with German engineering and manufacturing companies to turn IoT from a “slogan to a fact …

Andrew Orlowski, 10 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7146_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/11/08/phoner_with_obama.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7146-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/21/city_lifeline_london_colocation_data_centre/</link><title>Hot racks and cool customers: Colocating in the capital</title><description>Hot racks and cool customers: Colocating in the capital

In a world where data centre duties are increasingly relocated to lower cost territories in the East and beyond, why would anyone want to set up shop in the heart of London? Even if there was a requirement for your data to be UK-based, surely a location in the shires where rents are lower would make sense. City Lifeline …

Bob Dormon, 21 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7146_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/20/generator_output_meters.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7146-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/21/what_does_nhs_it_want_to_extract/</link><title>What does the NHS’s new IT plan really want to extract from us?</title><description>What does the NHS’s new IT plan really want to extract from us?

Following last month’s announcement of a £1m nationwide spam drop, what now for care.data, the NHS's latest multi-million pound big data project? Is it, as the carefully managed news release implied, merely taking its time – in fact, delaying a key project by almost a year - so as to nail issues of patient confidentiality? Or is …

Jane Fae Ozimek, 21 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7146_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/10/dentistry.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7146-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/07/blackberry_under_chen/</link><title>Heins didn't have the beans. Can comeback king Chen fish BlackBerry out of jam?</title><description>Heins didn't have the beans. Can comeback king Chen fish BlackBerry out of jam?

BlackBerry’s plan for rebirth using the dream team of Alicia Keys and chief executive Thorsten Heins has failed. Sybase turnaround king and CEO-of-the-moment John Chen is now its new great hope. Heins lasted less than two years in the hotseat at BlackBerry. He was named CEO in January 2012, taking over from co-CEOs Mike …

Gavin Clarke, 07 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7146_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/06/4128833646_ba47dc91be_z.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7146-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/06/feature_when_you_can_be_id_checked_in_uk/</link><title>Thought you didn't need to show ID in the UK? Wrong</title><description>Thought you didn't need to show ID in the UK? Wrong

One of the first things Britain's home secretary Theresa May did on taking office was to abolish the previous government’s identity cards scheme. But while she made ID cards history, she is in the process of extending Britain’s range of identity document checks. The "sample" UK ID card from the previous government's 2008 effort …

SA Mathieson, 06 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7146_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/05/18/tatoo2.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7146-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/08/06/ibm_flex_system_x86_power_update/</link><title>IBM gooses Flex modular systems with Power7+, double-stuffed Xeon E5</title><description>IBM gooses Flex modular systems with Power7+, double-stuffed Xeon E5

Big Blue is hoping to compete better with the very dense blade and modular server designs available from HP, Dell, Silicon Graphics, Super Micro, and a few others with a new twin Flex System node that sandwiches two servers into a single slot. In addition, IBM is rolling out new Power7+ nodes for the Flex System, addressing the …

Timothy Prickett Morgan, 06 Aug 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7146_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/04/16/ibm_flex_chassis_front.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7146-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/29/microsoft_might_yet_win/</link><title>Microsoft haters: You gotta lop off a lot of legs to slay Ballmer's monster</title><description>Microsoft haters: You gotta lop off a lot of legs to slay Ballmer's monster

Contrary to increasingly popular belief, Microsoft is not a “dead” company, nor at immediate risk of collapse. I do, however, believe that Microsoft’s “Windows on the endpoint” monopoly days have passed, that Microsoft’s senior management are aware of this and are actively taking steps to compensate. Similarly, I believe that …

Trevor Pott, 29 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7146_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/07/29/warrior.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7146-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/04/30/cray_q1_2012_numbers/</link><title>Cray peddles more iron than expected in Q1</title><description>Cray peddles more iron than expected in Q1

It is tough to find a choppier business than the supercomputer market, and Cray CEO Peter Ungaro had to remind Wall Street once again to not judge the company on a single quarter, and particularly on the first quarter that it has just turned in. While the company's top line was a little better than expected, issues with the …

Timothy Prickett Morgan, 30 Apr 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7146_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/04/30/cray_xc30.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>