<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7150">senior java developer</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:16:37" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7150-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/10/geeks_guide_visits_ibm_hursley/</link><title>IBM Hursley Park: Where Big Blue buries the past, polishes family jewels</title><description>IBM Hursley Park: Where Big Blue buries the past, polishes family jewels

Would you like to work in a cross between Downton Abbey and Silicon Valley? For a small selection of IBMers, that’s the only way to describe their working environment, although the place we’re talking about is officially called Hursley Park. You can get there by turning off the M3 and rattling through some pretty English village …

Joe Fay, 10 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7150_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/04/07/ibm_mainframe_portable_toolkit.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7150-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/25/from_corporate_to_startup_lessons_learned/</link><title>From corporate bod to startup star: The 10-month gig that changed everything</title><description>From corporate bod to startup star: The 10-month gig that changed everything

For pretty much my entire career as a techie (variously a developer, manager, and consultant) I’ve worked for very large, usually global, companies, most of them in the financial industry. A couple of years ago I decided I needed a break from that world. After taking some time off to de-stress and pursue a few personal projects …

Dave Mandl, 25 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7150_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2008/04/10/arrington_cigar.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7150-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/08/ibm_steve_smith_importance_of_partners/</link><title>Indirect proposition: Inside IBM UK software supremo's profit plan</title><description>Indirect proposition: Inside IBM UK software supremo's profit plan

IBM’s Stephen Smith shrugs off our suggestion there’s more pressure on him now than ever before. And no wonder: he is a man with a profit-generating plan. Smith is the UK and Ireland head of IBM’s Software Group – a unit that’s home to some of the biggest names in software, never mind the Big Blue brand itself. As a whole, the …

Gavin Clarke, 08 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7150_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/16/box_in_cloud.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7150-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/07/third_android_master_key_vuln_squashed/</link><title>KitKat swats yet another Android 'MasterKey' bug</title><description>KitKat swats yet another Android 'MasterKey' bug

Android 4.4 contains a fix for yet another – albeit weaker variant – of the so-called MasterKey bug that first surfaced in July. The vulnerability first shook the security world when mobile security startup Bluebox Security warned about a class of flaw that potentially affected 99 per cent of Android devices. The problem …

John Leyden, 07 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7150_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/03/android_kitkat_535.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7150-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/04/google_living_omega_cloud/</link><title>IT'S ALIVE! IT'S ALIVE! Google's secretive Omega tech just like LIVING thing</title><description>IT'S ALIVE! IT'S ALIVE! Google's secretive Omega tech just like LIVING thing

One of Google's most advanced data center systems behaves more like a living thing than a tightly controlled provisioning system. This has huge implications for how large clusters of IT resources are going to be managed in the future. "Emergent" behaviors have been appearing in prototypes of Google's Omega cluster management and …

Jack Clark, 04 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7150_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/11/25/2001_hal_poster.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7150-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/18/feature_mobile_security_malware/</link><title>Got a mobile phone? Then you've got a Trojan problem too</title><description>Got a mobile phone? Then you've got a Trojan problem too

Something wonderful has happened: phones have got smart, but the bad news is they may open the door to those you don’t want to let in. Time was when getting software to run properly on your mobile phone was such a challenge that it was nigh on impossible for bad guys to write malware that worked. Most phones used proprietary …

Simon Rockman, 18 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7150_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/26/mobile_phone_bacteria.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7150-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/08/20/nt_at_20/</link><title>Windows NT: Remember Microsoft's almost perfect 20-year-old?</title><description>Windows NT: Remember Microsoft's almost perfect 20-year-old?

If you want to be reminded that you're getting old, ask a youngster what Windows NT is. Chances are, there'll be blank looks all round. Windows What? Is it, like, a codename for a new version? You can't blame them. There hasn't actually been a proper "Windows NT" release since the late 1990s, so for almost anyone under 30 it's …

Andrew Orlowski, 20 Aug 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7150_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/08/20/windows_nt_boot.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7150-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/24/windows_azure_java_openjdk/</link><title>Azure inhales open source Java implementation</title><description>Azure inhales open source Java implementation

Microsoft and Azul Systems have hoisted the open source Java implementation OpenJDK onto the Redmond's Azure cloud, giving developers access to the language on Azure's Windows-based cloud services. The news was announced by Azul Systems at the O'Reilly Open Source Convention in Portland, Oregon, on Wednesday. The OpenJDK for …

Jack Clark, 24 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7150_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/30/openjdk_logo.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7150-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/02/making_it_in_city_tech/</link><title>A short, sharp tool kit to get you to the top in financial IT</title><description>A short, sharp tool kit to get you to the top in financial IT

Congratulations, you’ve started moving up the food chain. But there is still a long way to go. Having been an occasionally competent head of IT at a midsize City firm after working my way up, I’d like to share with you things I should have known then. These are the lessons I’ve learned at some cost to both my employers and …

Dominic Connor, 02 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7150_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/03/28/tkg_10.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7150-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/06/27/ex_vmware_coo_joins_salesforce_rival/</link><title>Ex-VMware ops chief floats over to Salesforce rival</title><description>Ex-VMware ops chief floats over to Salesforce rival

VMware’s former chief operating officer Tod Nielsen has jumped ship to join Heroku, Salesforce.com’s Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS) cloud operation. Nielsen has been named chief executive of Heroku, assuming the role vacated by Byron Sebastian who left the company in September 2012. Sebastian had been both CEO and executive vice …

Gavin Clarke, 27 Jun 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7150_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/04/19/welcome_matt.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>