<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7153">pig latin help</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:02:28" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7153-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/02/24/otto_mexico/</link><title>America can lick the Asian peril by training Mexican smarties</title><description>America can lick the Asian peril by training Mexican smarties

We will add that the working class in the United States, because of its high standard of living, does not clearly see the contradictions existing in US society. To the US working class, these contradictions, which are blunted, appear incomprehensible and they cannot gain clear consciousness of their own exploitation as long as …

Otto Z. Stern, 24 Feb 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7153_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7153-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/02/18/l33tsp34k_for_parents/</link><title>L33tsp34k for the luddite classes</title><description>L33tsp34k for the luddite classes

Microsoft has published a parent's guide to online slang, and we were unable to resist it. It aims to educate confused parents about the wacky online world their kids inhabit, so that mums and dads across America don't freak out when they spy on their offsprings' email, and can't understand a word of it. The idea behind it is …

Lucy Sherriff, 18 Feb 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7153_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7153-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2001/05/09/music_biz_backs_antinapster_mp3/</link><title>Music biz backs anti-Napster MP3 sniffer-outer</title><description>Music biz backs anti-Napster MP3 sniffer-outer

The music industry today gave its backing to software that allows punters to do its dirty work for it. The software, called Songbird, allows users to search for songs on the Napster network (you have to be a registered Napster user to perform the search). It is aimed at copyright owners who want to see which of their songs are …

Tony Smith, 09 May 2001</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7153_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>