<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7154">stones satisfaction</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:07:52" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7154-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/01/09/electricity_starvation_rations/</link><title>'Leccy-starved Reg hack: 'How I survive on 1.5kW'</title><description>'Leccy-starved Reg hack: 'How I survive on 1.5kW'

Here's a provocative question for readers in these power-hungry times: could you survive in a house where the total power draw of all your electrical appliances and fittings at any one time can't exceed 1.5kW? An overloaded kilowatt meter Preposterous, we hear you cry. Stick a load in the washing machine and put the kettle on …

Lester Haines, 09 Jan 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7154_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/01/08/kilowatt_meter.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7154-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/07/04/data_centre_orchestration/</link><title>What's the point of data centre orchestration?</title><description>What's the point of data centre orchestration?

Flipping the script on the 80/20 rule is the idea of data centre orchestration. It promises to take 80 per cent of the time IT departments spend fire-fighting and reallocate it to service delivery – putting big smiles on board members' faces and increasing job satisfaction in the IT department. Good luck with that, you might …

Phil Mitchell, 04 Jul 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7154_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/gen_usb.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7154-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/09/29/apple_app_store_satisfaction/</link><title>iPhone devs' riches exceed expectations</title><description>iPhone devs' riches exceed expectations

Money can ease the pain of many things: a messy divorce, holding down a US contractor's job in the City of Fallujah, tripping over the paving stones on some lost and neglected city street. It can also make up for shortcomings in Apple's App Store, it seems. A significant number of iPhone developers are making more money than …

Gavin Clarke, 29 Sep 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7154_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7154-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2002/08/14/compaq_com_surfers_in_random/</link><title>Compaq.com surfers in random redirection mystery</title><description>Compaq.com surfers in random redirection mystery

Compaq and HP staff visiting the Compaq.com Web site this morning were thrown a wild card. Instead of getting redirected to the new.hp.com they found themselves surfing either a Rolling Stones Fan Club site or thrown onto a site flogging software for adult entertainment sites. Surfers outside the company were redirected to the …

John Leyden, 14 Aug 2002</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7154_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/gen_cd.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>