<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7165">vice president residence</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:57:11" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7165-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/21/rob_bearden_hortonworks_playbook/</link><title>Rob 'Flipper' Bearden plans to FLOAT his Hadoop heffalump</title><description>Rob 'Flipper' Bearden plans to FLOAT his Hadoop heffalump

To some, Rob Bearden is a hero. In just a few years, the venture capitalist flipped two open-source startups, turning diamonds in the rough into gems in the corporate M&amp;A crown. In 2006, he sold app server disrupter JBoss to Red Hat within a few years of joining for an estimated $350m, and just a year after joining SpringSource …

Gavin Clarke, 21 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7165_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/01/14/hortonworks_logo.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7165-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/04/sinofsky_retirement_deal/</link><title>Win 8 man Sinofsky's 'retirement' deal: $14m shares, oath of silence</title><description>Win 8 man Sinofsky's 'retirement' deal: $14m shares, oath of silence

Windows 8 architect Steven Sinofsky has officially “retired” from Microsoft having inked a deal in which he cops a share payout worth $14m in exchange for not joining the competition. The agreement comes six months after he unexpectedly left the company. The deal was revealed as Microsoft closed its fiscal year. The company …

Gavin Clarke, 04 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7165_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/10/25/sinofsky_skateboard_surface.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7165-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/03/12/celeb_doxing/</link><title>Oops, they did it again? Britney Spears, Paris Hilton 'LAID BARE ALL OVER THE WEB'</title><description>Oops, they did it again? Britney Spears, Paris Hilton 'LAID BARE ALL OVER THE WEB'

A rogue website has leaked what's claimed to be the detailed financial records of US celebs, politicians and other public figures. The site has published the alleged financial lowdown on US first lady Michelle Obama, blowhard Donald Trump, Arnold Schwarzenegger and both Paris Hilton and Britney Spears, among many others. Vice …

John Leyden, 12 Mar 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7165_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7165-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/12/06/john_mcafee_heart_attack/</link><title>John McAfee rushed to hospital over heart attack fears</title><description>John McAfee rushed to hospital over heart attack fears

Eccentric tech millionaire and fugitive John McAfee was rushed to a hospital in Guatemala on Thursday after suffering what his lawyer says were two mild heart attacks. At the time, McAfee was in the custody of Guatemala's Special Police Task Force, which had detained him for questioning after he entered the country illegally …

Neil McAllister, 06 Dec 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7165_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/11/13/john_mcafee.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7165-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/03/16/cloudera_hadoop_launch/</link><title>Cloudera floats commercial Hadoop distro</title><description>Cloudera floats commercial Hadoop distro

Face it: You want to launch your own Google and get your hands on some of that (easy?) internet money. Well, now's your chance to take a stab at it. Today, a startup called Cloudera is launching a commercial distribution of the Google-inspired open source Hadoop software underpinning Yahoo, Facebook, and a number of other hot- …

Timothy Prickett Morgan, 16 Mar 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7165_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/03/chandef9.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7165-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/09/26/springsource_president_coo/</link><title>SpringSource VC investor takes COO role</title><description>SpringSource VC investor takes COO role

SpringSource, steward of the ever-popular Spring open source Java framework, is getting an operations specialist from the investment community with an application-server background. The position of president and chief operations officer has apparently been created and awarded to Rob Bearden, an entrepreneur in residence with …

Gavin Clarke, 26 Sep 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7165_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7165-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/08/01/second_life_to_dwarf_web_in_ten_years/</link><title>Second Life will dwarf the web in ten years</title><description>Second Life will dwarf the web in ten years

Within ten years, virtual worlds will be bigger than the Web itself. So says Philip Rosedale, the man who invented Second Life. Speaking at the Stanford Summit, an annual tech industry conference, the Linden Lab CEO predicted that a completely-open virtual world architecture – much like the one he’s touting for Second Life - …

Cade Metz, 01 Aug 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7165_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7165-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/11/24/secondlife_greygoo_attack/</link><title>Second life plagued by 'grey goo' attack</title><description>Second life plagued by 'grey goo' attack

For about two hours, the virtual landscape of Second Life filled with golden rings and the distinctive two-tone ding of Sega's popular Sonic the Hedgehog games. The rings' listed creator was the fictional "Dr Robotnik," a character from the Sonic games. However, the deluge of rings was not some form of cross promotion, but a …

Robert Lemos, 24 Nov 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7165_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7165-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/11/28/anti_terror_databases/</link><title>EC outlines anti-terror database measures</title><description>EC outlines anti-terror database measures

The European Commission last week adopted two measures designed to assist in the fight against terrorism and serious crime by improving the development of and access to common European databases. Of particular interest to the Commission in this context are the databases for the planned Visa Information System (VIS), the …

OUT-LAW.COM, 28 Nov 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7165_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7165-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2003/12/18/us_secret_service_airbrushes_aerial/</link><title>US Secret Service airbrushes aerial photos</title><description>US Secret Service airbrushes aerial photos

Call it the case of the missing White House. Users of Mapquest's free aerial photo database recently noticed that details of several Washington D.C. government buildings were no longer discernable in overhead images of the U.S. capital. A comparison of old and new images posted on the government secrecy watchdog site Cryptome …

Kevin Poulsen, 18 Dec 2003</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7165_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>