<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7166">pita recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:18:03" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7166-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/28/beer_bacon_study/</link><title>Booze and bacon sarnies: A recipe for immortality?</title><description>Booze and bacon sarnies: A recipe for immortality?

Earlier this week, a chilling and extremely newsworthy report established a link between fried meat and Alzheimer's disease. "Bacon is particularly problematic," doomwatched the Daily Mail, a noted proponent of the "if it's tasty it'll kill you" school of scientific killjoyery. Neil Cardy's massive bacon sarnie from a cafe on …

Lester Haines, 28 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7166_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/27/beer_bacon_teaser.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7166-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/08/03/bauernfruhstuck_bacon_sarnie/</link><title>Post-pub nosh deathmatch: Bauernfrühstück v bacon sarnie</title><description>Post-pub nosh deathmatch: Bauernfrühstück v bacon sarnie

As long-term Reg readers are aware, it's been scientifically proven that bacon has almost miraculous powers to cure the effects of a night on the sauce. Accordingly, we at the Special Projects Bureau went in search of two world-class sliced pork recipes designed to ameliorate the pain of a severe liver-kicking. Prepare your …

Lester Haines, 03 Aug 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7166_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/07/30/bauernfruhstuck_ingredients.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7166-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/07/06/haggis_huevos/</link><title>Post-pub nosh deathmatch: Haggis pakora v huevos rancheros</title><description>Post-pub nosh deathmatch: Haggis pakora v huevos rancheros

It's been more than a month on the salads and with our necks in the fruit bowl for the Special Projects Bureau's elite post-pub nosh deathmatch team, following the mealy pudding v migas clash of titans. We reckon our arteries have recovered sufficiently to make another foray into the calorie-packed world of nourishment designed …

Lester Haines, 06 Jul 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7166_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7166-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/05/18/mealy_migas/</link><title>Post-pub nosh deathmatch: Mealy pudding v migas</title><description>Post-pub nosh deathmatch: Mealy pudding v migas

Following a long winter hibernation burning the fat reserves gained from a generous serving of Dutch delicacy kapsalon, our Special Projects Bureau post-pub nosh team has emerged blinking into the spring sunshine to bring you a further selection of quality international cuisine designed to soak up the excesses of a night on the …

Lester Haines, 18 May 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7166_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>