<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7174">seal team 6</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:59:34" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7174-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/21/google_glass_myths/</link><title>TEN THINGS Google believes you believe about Glassholes and wishes you didn't</title><description>TEN THINGS Google believes you believe about Glassholes and wishes you didn't

Google Glass wearers, or Explorers as Google likes to call them, have been getting some bad press of late, and the company has been moved to defend the headsets against the rise of rumor and speculation. "Mr. Rogers was a Navy SEAL. A tooth placed in soda will dissolve in 24 hours. Gators roam the sewers of big cities and Walt …

Iain Thomson, 21 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7174_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/18/homer_glasshole.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7174-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/11/mariadb_version_10_beta/</link><title>Oracle's nemesis MariaDB releases sleekest seal yet to beta</title><description>Oracle's nemesis MariaDB releases sleekest seal yet to beta

MariaDB has capped off a dazzling year with the release of a beta of Version 10 of the free MySQL replacement. The beta of the database was announced on Thursday and sees the technology gain some features that can't be found in the MySQL database upon which it is based, further driving a wedge between it and the Oracle-backed …

Jack Clark, 11 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7174_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/12/google_moves.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7174-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/04/02/race_for_space_1/</link><title>Rocket boffinry in pictures: Gulp the Devil's venom and light a match</title><description>Rocket boffinry in pictures: Gulp the Devil's venom and light a match

It's been more than 70 years since the first successful test flight of the German Vergeltungswaffe 2 (V2) - the weapon that paved the way for subsequent rocket-based efforts to escape Earth's surly bonds. On 3 October 1942, a team headed by Wernher von Braun watched its creation rise from the launchpad at Peenemünde, little …

Lester Haines, 02 Apr 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7174_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7174-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/12/20/apple_televisions_being_tested_by_hon_hai/</link><title>Apple said to be testing 46, 55-inch big-screen TVs</title><description>Apple said to be testing 46, 55-inch big-screen TVs

Apple's much-rumored big-screen TV effort – the one that CEO Tim Cook recently called "an area of intense interest" – is merrily cranking along in a Foxconn factory. So says a source at Hon Hai Precision Industry, Foxconn's parent company, according to Focus Taiwan. The scuttlebutt is that tests of "several designs" of the …

Rik Myslewski, 20 Dec 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7174_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7174-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/11/09/seven_seals_spanked_for_spilling_beans/</link><title>Navy SEALs from Bin Laden kill unit spanked for video game work</title><description>Navy SEALs from Bin Laden kill unit spanked for video game work

Seven members of US special forces have been slapped on the wrist and had their pay docked for revealing ‘trade secrets’ to a games developer. According to US TV network CBS, the seven soldiers, all active members of SEAL Team 6*, spent two days last summer telling Medal of Honor: Warfighter creator Electronic Arts about …

Tony Smith, 09 Nov 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7174_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7174-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/08/31/lohan_update/</link><title>LOHAN rolls out racy rocketry round-up</title><description>LOHAN rolls out racy rocketry round-up

In response to requests from several Reg readers who've been following the progress of our Low Orbit Helium Assisted Navigator (LOHAN) ballocket mission, we've put together a round-up of just where we're at with the various aspects of the project. Click here for a bigger version of the LOHAN graphic The LOHAN team is fighting …

Lester Haines, 31 Aug 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7174_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/03/06/lohan_teaser_space.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7174-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/07/12/lohan_ignition/</link><title>LOHAN to brew thermite for hot ignition action</title><description>LOHAN to brew thermite for hot ignition action

The first rocket motor tests in our magnificent Rocketry Experimental High Altitude Barosimulator (REHAB) rig went with a whimper rather than a bang earlier this week, as both solid propellants failed to ignite. Click here for a bigger version of the LOHAN graphic Despite the best efforts of the SPB's elite team, who occupied …

Lester Haines, 12 Jul 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7174_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7174-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/06/12/tim_peake_aquanaut_asteroid_mission/</link><title>Sole British 'naut Major Tim embarks on NASA deep space mission</title><description>Sole British 'naut Major Tim embarks on NASA deep space mission

Blighty's one and only astronaut, Tim Peake of the European Space Agency, has just embarked on a bold mission into an environment where few human beings have ever ventured: that of the saturation diver, semi-permanently adapted to life under high pressure and able to survive only deep underwater or inside pressurised containers …

Lewis Page, 12 Jun 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7174_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7174-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/06/27/photo_camo/</link><title>US Spec-Ops offered camouflage for a specific site</title><description>US Spec-Ops offered camouflage for a specific site

Everybody knows how obsessive the world's elite special-ops forces are about preparing for a task. Prior to the recent, headline-making raid in which Osama bin Laden was killed, US Navy SEALs built a complete mockup of the compound where he lived and spent weeks practicing attacks on it, for instance. In future, as well as this …

Lewis Page, 27 Jun 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7174_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7174-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/05/11/us_preachers_claim_to_be_navy_seals/</link><title>Plague of US preachers falsely claim to be Navy SEALs</title><description>Plague of US preachers falsely claim to be Navy SEALs

Yet another curious effect of the modern internet media world became apparent this week: the syndrome – particularly common among American clergymen – of falsely claiming to be a former US Navy SEAL has risen to prominence, as the risk of being exposed as such a liar has risen severely. The chest badge worn by qualified US Navy …

Lewis Page, 11 May 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7174_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>