<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7185">constitution of italy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:41:39" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7185-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/11/02/uss_enterprise_scapped/</link><title>USS Enterprise sets out on its final mission</title><description>USS Enterprise sets out on its final mission

The US Navy's first nuclear-powered aircraft carrier, the USS Enterprise, has set sail on her last mission before being consigned to the scrap heap. After 51 years as a serving warship, including multiple circumnavigations of the globe, the Enterprise's final trip will be a short one from its home port of Naval Station Norfolk …

Iain Thomson, 02 Nov 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7185_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7185-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/10/06/italian_wikipedia_down_as_wiretapping_law_debated/</link><title>Users shut down Italian Wikipedia to protest Wiretapping Act</title><description>Users shut down Italian Wikipedia to protest Wiretapping Act

Italian Wikipedia has been hidden in protest at a new Act making its way through the Italian Parliament. The Wiretapping Act or "DDL intercettazioni" could make Wikipedia legally untenable in Italy if it passes into law. Visitors to any page of the Italian Wikipedia site yesterday were redirected to a letter signed "from the …

Anna Leach, 06 Oct 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7185_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7185-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/07/22/saving_the_euro/</link><title>Four illegal ways to sort out the Euro finance crisis</title><description>Four illegal ways to sort out the Euro finance crisis

Saving the euro isn't the easiest of things: solving the current problems actually would be quite easy, if expensive, except for all the laws and regulations that rule out all of the easy ways. The basic problem is well explained here. Don't worry too much about what the Taylor Rule is: just accept that if you're going to have a …

Tim Worstall, 22 Jul 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7185_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7185-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/09/26/italian_law_kills_blog/</link><title>How an Italian judge made the internet illegal</title><description>How an Italian judge made the internet illegal

Italian bloggers are up in arms at a court ruling early this year that suggests almost all Italian blogs are illegal. This month, a senior Italian politician went one step further, warning that most web activity is likely to be against the law. The story begins back in May, when a judge in Modica (in Sicily) found local …

Jane Fae Ozimek, 26 Sep 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7185_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7185-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2004/11/11/gov_indymedia_response/</link><title>We seize servers, you can't complain - US gov</title><description>We seize servers, you can't complain - US gov

The US Government is attempting to block efforts to find out who seized Indymedia's servers in London last month. The Government has filed a motion in San Antonio District Court opposing the Electronic Frontier Foundation's motion to unseal the court order which resulted in the seizures, and arguing among other things that …

John Lettice, 11 Nov 2004</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7185_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7185-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2002/10/14/pc_doldrums_back_to_basics/</link><title>PC doldrums, Back to BASICs, Google's blog skew</title><description>PC doldrums, Back to BASICs, Google's blog skew

: Life can be Krewell - and MDR analyst Kevin Krewell gets a rough reception for the predictions he made here:- Intel 'back in the driver's seat' Nice rosy 'status quo' forecast from Instat/MDR. Here is an alternative prediction. Businesses, realizing there is no need for 3 Ghz machines that run hot, use a lot of power, and …

Andrew Orlowski, 14 Oct 2002</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7185_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>