<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7211">punctuation guide</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:38:55" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7211-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/07/tinder_bot_malware_attack/</link><title>Left swipe! That hot Tinder babe is a malware-flinging ROBOT</title><description>Left swipe! That hot Tinder babe is a malware-flinging ROBOT

Hackers are abusing the popular Tinder dating app to spread malware and survey scams using bots and clever social-engineering trickery. Bots are luring users with tempting profiles and pictures using pictures from an Arizona-based photography studio, according to net security firm BitDefender. Some of these images have also been …

John Leyden, 07 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7211_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/25/trilateration.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7211-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/08/06/nyt_coding_style/</link><title>Can't agree on a coding style? Maybe the NEW YORK TIMES can help</title><description>Can't agree on a coding style? Maybe the NEW YORK TIMES can help

For decades, dour broadsheet the New York Times and its style guide have presided over the world of posh writing: its English usage manual serves as both a bible for upmarket writers and a blunt instrument with which to beat sensationalist tabloid hacks such as your humble correspondent. Now the Grey Lady has turned her hand …

Chris Williams, 06 Aug 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7211_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/08/06/nyt.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7211-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/08/14/ipad_apps/</link><title>119 iPad apps for admins, coders, and geeks</title><description>119 iPad apps for admins, coders, and geeks

Apple's "magical and revolutionary" iPad is not just a toy for Jobsian fanbois — and The Reg has 119 tech-savvy apps to prove it. Today we launch our first installment of a Reg roundup of iPad apps that provide more utility than do fart-sharing, bubble-popping, and "Yo Mama!" joke-telling apps. We'll focus on items that can ease …

Rik Myslewski, 14 Aug 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7211_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7211-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/02/19/review_motorola_droid/</link><title>Motorola Droid - the not quite iPhone killer</title><description>Motorola Droid - the not quite iPhone killer

Motorola's Google-happy Droid handset can be summed up in three words - and a bit of punctuation: "Nice phone, but..." The Droid has been out for some time now in the US, but we got our hands on one only last month. And although our sister site RegHardware has already had their way with its UK counterpart, the Motorola Milestone …

Rik Myslewski, 19 Feb 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7211_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2008/01/09/android_logo.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7211-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/01/25/html_5_em/</link><title>Just how cute are cats? W3C can help</title><description>Just how cute are cats? W3C can help

The recent announcement by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) of the first major overhaul of HTML in ten years was largely greeted with indifference down at the Vulture Central hackery department, where the average journo has trouble telling his &lt;a&gt;s from his &lt;elbow&gt;. However, were they to take the time to peruse the discussion …

Lester Haines, 25 Jan 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7211_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2007/03/12/w3c_logo.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7211-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/02/22/letters_2202/</link><title>Can my clone use my software license?</title><description>Can my clone use my software license?

How much is a website worth? How many Firefox users are there? How long is a piece of string? These, and other puzzlers were given a good going over earlier this week. Our writer warned people not to read to much into download figures of open source software: An interesting article and you are right on the mark about the …

Lucy Sherriff, 22 Feb 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7211_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>