<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7216">salmonella</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:14:17" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7216-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/10/15/touchscreen_disease/</link><title>iPhone, BlackBerry, Droid: purveyors of pestilence</title><description>iPhone, BlackBerry, Droid: purveyors of pestilence

Your smartphone or touchscreen tablet is not your friend — not with flu season approaching. "If you're sharing the device, then you're sharing your influenza with someone else who touches it," warns Stanford University doctoral student Timothy Julian, discussing deadly digital disease-delivery devices with The Sacramento Bee. …

Rik Myslewski, 15 Oct 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7216_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/gen_rack.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7216-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/11/26/turkey_thief/</link><title>Police smoke out 300-pound frozen turkey thief</title><description>Police smoke out 300-pound frozen turkey thief

Police in Michigan are hunting an enormous homeless burglar who swiped a family's Thanksgiving turkey. The Jackson Citizen Patriot reports that the Sobiegray family were left facing a fowl-free Thanksgiving, after the man kicked down their front door and raided their freezer on Tuesday night. The suspect in the theft of the 13- …

Joe Fay, 26 Nov 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7216_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7216-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/08/20/cloud_computing_privacy/</link><title>Cloud computing lets Feds read your email</title><description>Cloud computing lets Feds read your email

When the new iPhone 3G went on sale last week, I was sorely tempted to wait in line for one. (I didn't - no patience.) One of the features of Apple's device that appeals to me is the new MobileMe service, where you can "access and manage your email, contacts, calendar, photos, and files at me.com," according to Apple. More …

Mark Rasch, 20 Aug 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7216_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7216-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/09/27/channel_weekly/</link><title>Channel wins the war, but salmonella wins the bacteria race to space</title><description>Channel wins the war, but salmonella wins the bacteria race to space

The revelation that the channel model wars are over seems like a good place to kickstart our review of the week's news in The Reg. And the even better news is that the channel won. So break out the champagne, sing some rousing songs and hug a total stranger, the enemy has been defeated and victory is yours. For those of you …

Billy MacInnes, 27 Sep 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7216_04_thumb.gif">http://regmedia.co.uk/2005/12/06/reg_75.gif?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7216-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/09/25/salmonella_iss_experiment/</link><title>Space makes germs more deadly</title><description>Space makes germs more deadly

Salmonella likes it in orbit, and not just for the view. According to research conducted on the International Space Station (ISS), the effects of microgravity trip a switch in the bacterium that makes it much more virulent. The findings, which are to be published in PNAS Online Early Edition suggest astronauts could be at …

Lucy Sherriff, 25 Sep 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7216_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7216-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/12/09/bofh_episode_41/</link><title>The Bastard and the IT training budget</title><description>The Bastard and the IT training budget

"I... what?" the PFY sniffles, reading through his email. "Hmm?" I ask. "My attendance at a Linux forum has been canceled because.. the IT Training budget for this quarter has been exceeded?!" "That's ridiculous," I counter. "It's about 10 grand a quarter and we haven't used any of it!" "Well that's what it says," The PFY …

Simon Travaglia, 09 Dec 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7216_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/04/30/bofh.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7216-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2001/08/23/keyboards_spread_disease/</link><title>Keyboards spread disease</title><description>Keyboards spread disease

This is a Register Health Warning: Computer keyboards spread disease. Or so an "alarming Health Zone" experiment conducted by The Mirror claims. Under the headline Taking Your Life in Your Hands, the newspaper writes: "A touch of a computer keyboard or a £10 note brings us into contact with thousands of lethal bacteria." In …

Drew Cullen, 23 Aug 2001</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7216_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>