<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7218">edward kennedy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:29:53" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7218-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/09/29/truthy_truthy/</link><title>Tweety profs offer political smear-meme 'truthiness' ratings</title><description>Tweety profs offer political smear-meme 'truthiness' ratings

Earnest academics in Indiana have set up an internet project designed to thwart evil right-wing internet smear campaigns against Democratic politicians, astroturfing, "and other social pollution". The website, truthy.indiana.edu, uses the Twitter API to identify internet memes and measure their "truthiness" - ie how bullshitty …

Lewis Page, 29 Sep 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7218_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7218-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/08/30/richard_egan_obituary/</link><title>EMC co-founder kills himself</title><description>EMC co-founder kills himself

Richard Egan, the colourful and vigorous co-founder of EMC, went into a linen cupboard of his home at the Four Seasons condominiums on Boylston Street, Boston, and shot himself in the head with a shotgun on Friday, ending his fight against terminal lung cancer. Egan had an amazing life, encompassing involvement in the Apollo …

Chris Mellor, 30 Aug 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7218_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2009/08/30/dick_egan_emc.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7218-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/02/11/wikimadness_uk_germany/</link><title>Prime Minister out-nonsensed by Conservative Wikifiddler</title><description>Prime Minister out-nonsensed by Conservative Wikifiddler

Wikipedia co-founder Jimmy "Jimbo" Wales still hopes to equip his free online encyclopedia with its very own nonsense filter. But at the moment, the Wikinonsense is alive and well. Earlier today, the BBC reports, the UK Conservative party admitted that a member of its staff had changed a Wikipedia entry in an apparent attempt to …

Cade Metz, 11 Feb 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7218_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7218-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/01/22/wikipedia_vandalism_crackdown/</link><title>Jimbo Wales ends death by Wikipedia</title><description>Jimbo Wales ends death by Wikipedia

On Tuesday afternoon, following a Washington luncheon celebrating the inauguration of President Barack Obama, longtime US Senators Ted Kennedy and Robert Byrd kicked the proverbial bucket. At least, that's what happened in Wikiland. In our world, they're still among the living. Ted Kennedy - diagnosed with a brain tumor last …

Cade Metz, 22 Jan 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7218_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7218-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/08/21/what_civil_liberties/</link><title>Bush makes last-minute grab for civil liberties</title><description>Bush makes last-minute grab for civil liberties

US citizens could be investigated without just cause under a new plan from the Justice Department, while those who choose to leave the country will have their records kept for 15 years and available to any litigious attorney. The Justice Department plan won't be unveiled in detail until next month, but the New York Times is …

Bill Ray, 21 Aug 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7218_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7218-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/12/23/wikipedia_gift_spurned/</link><title>'Take out a subscription to The Register. Then cancel it, and sign it Disgusted Wikipedian'</title><description>'Take out a subscription to The Register. Then cancel it, and sign it Disgusted Wikipedian'

"He who feels punctured must have been a bubble - Lao Tsu A funny thing happened last week. Author and broadcaster - and veteran OpenOffice user - Andrew Brown wrote a piece in The Guardian a fortnight ago demolishing some of the more absurd myths around open source software projects. Frustrating bugs went unfixed for years, …

Andrew Orlowski, 23 Dec 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7218_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7218-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/03/29/capps_replacement_in_trouble/</link><title>Passenger screening gimmick stuck at the gate</title><description>Passenger screening gimmick stuck at the gate

The US Transportation Security Administration (TSA) is behind schedule in developing a new terrorist-busting database system called Secure Flight, a report by the Government Accounting Office (GAO) says. After confronting the obvious defects in the old pre-9/11 CAPPS (computer-assisted passenger pre-screening system), which …

Thomas C Greene, 29 Mar 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7218_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7218-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2004/12/02/us_homeland_security_czar_resigns/</link><title>US Homeland Security Czar resigns</title><description>US Homeland Security Czar resigns

Former Pennsylvania Governor and recent Department of Homeland Security (DHS) Secretary Tom Ridge has resigned his post as America's top counterterrorism strategist. Ridge, who is well liked personally by many, has had a controversial tenure in the post. For example, critics have ridiculed his use of a color-coded threat scale …

Thomas C Greene, 02 Dec 2004</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7218_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7218-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2004/11/23/jfk_game/</link><title>JFK assassination game branded 'despicable'</title><description>JFK assassination game branded 'despicable'

A computer game that lets players re-enact the assassination of President John F Kennedy in 1963 has been branded "despicable" by his family. Glasgow-based software outfit Traffic launched the game this week to coincide with the 41st anniversary of JFK's murder in Dallas. The outfit behind JFK: Reloaded reckons this new "docu- …

Tim Richardson, 23 Nov 2004</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7218_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7218-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/1999/11/01/clinton_fears_orwellian_it_future/</link><title>Clinton fears Orwellian IT future</title><description>Clinton fears Orwellian IT future

President Clinton announced a proposed rule to safeguard electronic medical records from abuse by employers, insurers, banks and law enforcement during a White House press conference Friday afternoon. Seizing upon the worst fears of jaded health-care consumers in a wired world, the President boldly declared that "Americans …

Thomas C Greene, 01 Nov 1999</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7218_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>