<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7219">honda insight</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:54:47" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7219-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/03/07/car_week_product_roundup_ten_electrics_cars_and_hybrids/</link><title>Ten... e-cars and hybrids</title><description>Ten... e-cars and hybrids

Reg Hardware Car Week What started out as a dribble in 2011 is becoming a deluge in 2012 as e-cars in the form of pure electrics, range extenders and plug-in hybrids capabilities start to become ever more common. Until we see a major breakthrough in battery tech, the day will belong to the plug-in hybrids and REs, but that’s …

Alun Taylor, 07 Mar 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7219_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/01/12/ampera_2.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7219-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/05/03/review_cars_honda_jazz_hybrid/</link><title>Honda Jazz Hybrid</title><description>Honda Jazz Hybrid

In the last 10 years, Honda has shifted over 3.5m examples of its Jazz hatchback, and now the evergreen runabout so beloved by the over-60s is getting hybrid power. Presumably, Honda, like Toyota with its Auris Hybrid, thinks a familiar exterior will prevent hybrid-fright among it’s more conservative customers. Honda Jazz …

Alun Taylor, 03 May 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7219_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/05/03/jazz_12.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7219-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/12/14/govt_e_car_scheme/</link><title>Govt to grant £5k to e-car buyers</title><description>Govt to grant £5k to e-car buyers

Buy an e-car next year and the government will pay a quarter of the asking price - up to a maximum of £5000. You'll have to buy one of nine named electric vehicles, and your choice will be limited further by the fact that only three of them will actually be available to buy. The e-cars subsidised by the £43m scheme include the …

Tony Smith, 14 Dec 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7219_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7219-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/11/24/review_e_car_toyota_auris/</link><title>Toyota Auris hybrid e-car</title><description>Toyota Auris hybrid e-car

It's hard not to feel a little sorry for Toyota. Over the years the Prius – reviewed here – has not only been a healthy sales success, but the name has become synonymous with hybrid motoring technology. Toyota Auris Hybrid hatch: Toyota's Auris  Yet still, the hard-of-thinking and loud-of-mouth insist on telling anyone …

Alun Taylor, 24 Nov 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7219_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2010/11/22/toyota_auris_2.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7219-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/06/25/preview_e_car_vauxhall_ampera/</link><title>Vauxhall Ampera extended range e-car</title><description>Vauxhall Ampera extended range e-car

The first left-hand drive pre-production examples of the Vauxhall/Opel Ampera extended-range e-car have arrived in the UK. To illustrate the benefits of range extension, one of them was driven from the Vauxhall Heritage Centre in Luton to the assembly plant in Ellesmere Port where Reg Hardware was on hand to take it for a spin …

Alun Taylor, 25 Jun 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7219_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2010/06/23/ampera_7.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7219-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/05/27/review_e_car_honda_cr_z/</link><title>Honda CR-Z sporty hybrid e-car</title><description>Honda CR-Z sporty hybrid e-car

The three major Japanese car makers are taking a distinctly different approach to the imminent arrival of the electric car. Nissan has jumped in with both feet and will launch Leaf, its battery-powered e-car, at the end of the year. Toyota is putting its eggs in the true hybrid basket - its Prius is capable of both battery- and …

Alun Taylor, 27 May 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7219_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2010/05/27/crz_11.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7219-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/01/12/honda_crz/</link><title>Honda beats rivals to hybrid coupé launch</title><description>Honda beats rivals to hybrid coupé launch

Peugeot and Volkswagen each demoed concept hybrid coupés recently, but Honda has trumped both with a soon-to-launch model of its own. Honda_CRZ_01 Honda's hybrid CR-Z coupé: will arrive in Blighty this summer First seen last year and formally unveiled at the ongoing Detroit Motor Show, Honda’s CR-Z - it stands for Compact …

Alun Taylor, 12 Jan 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7219_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2010/01/12/honda_crz_sm.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7219-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/12/03/honda_p_nut/</link><title>Honda goes NUTs for future micro-car</title><description>Honda goes NUTs for future micro-car

Honda has whipped the dust covers of its vision of the small, urban coupé of tomorrow at the LA Auto Show. The Personal Neo Urban Transport - or P-NUT - seats three with the driver amidships and fits within the diminutive footprint of a micro-car. Honda P-NUT Honda's P-NUT: US notion of a micro-car Or rather within the …

Alun Taylor, 03 Dec 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7219_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2009/12/03/p-nut_6.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7219-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/10/13/mitsubishi_px_miev_reveal/</link><title>Mitsubishi preps 'versatile' plug-in hybrid e-car</title><description>Mitsubishi preps 'versatile' plug-in hybrid e-car

Mitsubishi has announced details of the range-extended plug-in hybrid that Reg Hardware first got a sniff of back in July and which will be officially unveiled at the Tokyo Motor Show next week . Called the PX-MiEV, the concept vehicle promises to have one of the most versatile hybrid drive trains yet developed. Mitsubishi PX- …

Alun Taylor, 13 Oct 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7219_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2009/10/13/px-miex_4.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7219-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/10/12/plod_to_get_more_e_cars/</link><title>West Midlands cops to roll out Mitsubishi EVs</title><description>West Midlands cops to roll out Mitsubishi EVs

Britain's police forces are proceeding in an orderly fashion to test Mitsubishi's iMiEV after the company showed off the e-car - reviewed here - at the UK's National Police Show last month. West Midlands Police has already signed up and will take delivery of its first iMiEV cop cars early in 2010, the manufacturer has revealed …

Alun Taylor, 12 Oct 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7219_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2009/10/12/imiev_3.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>