<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7230">council bluffs</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:23:39" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7230-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/06/24/microsoft_677_million_data_center_expansion/</link><title>SUPERSIZE my CLOUD - Microsoft plans $677m data centre embiggening</title><description>SUPERSIZE my CLOUD - Microsoft plans $677m data centre embiggening

Microsoft's throwing $677.6m into an Iowa data centre expansion just as internet rivals Google and Facebook have begun bulking up. State governor Terry Branstad and West Des Moines Mayor Steve Gaer copped to the news here, extending a hearty Midwest welcome to Microsoft - and its jobs and cash - after Redmond's decision to …

Gavin Clarke, 24 Jun 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7230_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7230-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/04/23/facebook_iowa_data_center/</link><title>Facebook plans vast data center in Iowa</title><description>Facebook plans vast data center in Iowa

Facebook's fourth gigantic data center will be in Iowa, a state already favored by major infrastructure operators due to its renewable utility options. The new data center in Altoona, Iowa, will be the company's fourth dedicated bit barn, along with facilities in Prineville, Oregon; Forest City, North Carolina; and Luleå, Sweden …

Jack Clark, 23 Apr 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7230_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/04/23/facebook_iowa_dc.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7230-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/10/15/google_capex_rise/</link><title>Google chucks $757m at data center empire</title><description>Google chucks $757m at data center empire

Google's capital expenditures – the amount of money forked into its worldwide network of data centers – reached $757m in the third quarter, their highest level since early 2008, when the company was erecting at least three new data center facilities in the US. In fact, the first quarter of 2008 was the only quarter in the …

Cade Metz, 15 Oct 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7230_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/03/chandef10.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7230-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/04/11/google_data_center_map/</link><title>Google data centers snub Africa, Oz, and anything near Wyoming</title><description>Google data centers snub Africa, Oz, and anything near Wyoming

A Swedish web-site monitoring company has published a worldwide map of Google's data centers. And people love looking at it. Today, as reported by just about every tech-happy news source on the web, the official Pingdom blog got all graphical with a new Google Data Center FAQ from Data Center Knowledge. Pingdom's Map of All …

Cade Metz, 11 Apr 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7230_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2007/12/28/google_logo.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7230-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/11/28/google_iowa_datacenter/</link><title>Virgin Mary appears in Google's Iowa data center</title><description>Virgin Mary appears in Google's Iowa data center

Who needs religion in middle America when you have Google? Google executive Ken Patchett recently visited Council Bluffs, Iowa and received a hero's welcome. Patchett leads Google's effort to build a $600m data center in corn country, and the locals couldn't be happier to have him around - at least according to propaganda …

Ashlee Vance, 28 Nov 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7230_05_thumb.gif">http://regmedia.co.uk/2007/11/05/google_logo.gif?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7230-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/06/19/google_iowa_datacenter/</link><title>Google cookie cuts $600m data center in Iowa</title><description>Google cookie cuts $600m data center in Iowa

Google will build yet another backwoods data center for $600m – this time in Iowa. Iowa's Governor Chet Culver – you can't make a name like that up – bragged today about his state's good fortune. Google will set up shop in Council Bluffs, Iowa on a 55-acre site. The data center announcement follows similar recent deals in North …

Ashlee Vance, 19 Jun 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7230_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/gen_glare.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>