<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7239">roundabout safety</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:01:58" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7239-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/09/20/steve_bong_syria_ios7/</link><title>iPhone 5S, iOS 7 misery: Only JORDAN HATCH, 19, can SAVE APPLE NOW</title><description>iPhone 5S, iOS 7 misery: Only JORDAN HATCH, 19, can SAVE APPLE NOW

The searing Syrian desert sun glinted off the Kalashnikovs. It was a tense situation – and about to get a lot tenser. I had planned to spend a chilled out August of mediation and blue-sky thinking in Aspen, but had been summoned on urgent and Top Secret business – on a mission so dangerous that even my inseparable assistant …

Steve Bong, 20 Sep 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7239_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/20/jordanhatch.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7239-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/22/verity_stob_songbook/</link><title>Verity's summer songs for programmers: Sing your pals to sleep()</title><description>Verity's summer songs for programmers: Sing your pals to sleep()

"What better way to dispel the rainy gloom of an English summer," mused Ms Stob, in an introduction presumably written some time in March, "than a mass office sing-along to a selection of IT-themed pastiches?" Pretty well anything, we'd have thought. Nevertheless, here is the raw material. Portable Development (Tune: Willow, …

Verity Stob, 22 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7239_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/04/23/verity_stob900.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7239-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/06/07/something_for_the_weekend_tech_city_office/</link><title>Help! I’m trapped inside the Chamber of Hollers</title><description>Help! I’m trapped inside the Chamber of Hollers

There’s this guy in the office who sits ten feet behind me. Lovely bloke, diligent worker, cares passionately about his job, loud voice. Oh yes indeed, a really loud voice. It doesn’t seem to matter that there’s an office divider between us, his voice is as clear and piercing as if he was sitting next to me. It’s not even an …

Alistair Dabbs, 07 Jun 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7239_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/06/07/welly.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7239-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/05/17/something_for_the_weekend_i_said_no_to_tech_city_empire/</link><title>I said ‘no’ to a million-pound Tech City empire</title><description>I said ‘no’ to a million-pound Tech City empire

I have been propositioned in a toilet by a 72-year-old man. He wants me to move in with him and do the business. Ah, it’s possible that I may have phrased this poorly. What I really meant to say is that he is looking to me to arise and provide him with a youthful injection to keep him in the game. No, no, you’re getting the …

Alistair Dabbs, 17 May 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7239_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/12/15/tech_city.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7239-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/12/29/fiveash_year_in_review/</link><title>UK.gov: You didn't trust us with your ID, so we gave it to private biz</title><description>UK.gov: You didn't trust us with your ID, so we gave it to private biz

Earlier this year your correspondent was standing tantalisingly close to Matt Smith in the ACTUAL TARDIS - long story, not gonna Facebook it, never gonna tweet it. However, many Brits are happy to noisily ricochet chunks of their private lives across any number of websites and systems, in a year in which the British government …

Kelly Fiveash, 29 Dec 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7239_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2008/11/12/godzillaattack.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7239-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/12/26/csiro_zebedee_maps_mystery_cave/</link><title>CSIRO mine safety tech becomes archaeological tool</title><description>CSIRO mine safety tech becomes archaeological tool

A 3D mapping technology announced earlier this year by Australia’s science agency CSIRO is being used to help map what might be the world’s oldest cave etchings. During December, CSIRO scientists undertook an exploration on behalf of the Adelaide museum, in which they took the technology known as Zebedee into the delicate …

Richard Chirgwin, 26 Dec 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7239_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2008/05/27/captain_caveman_index.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7239-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/11/28/office_party_mayhem/</link><title>Think Xmas bashes in your biz are scary? Try partying with the Channel</title><description>Think Xmas bashes in your biz are scary? Try partying with the Channel

Etiquette experts Debrett’s has extensive advice for how to negotiate the work Christmas party, including retaining one’s professional gloss and never doing anything one might regret in the morning. Debrett’s has never been to a channel Christmas party. But with a threatened Eurozone double-dip recession, limping distributor …

Steve Bell, 28 Nov 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7239_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/11/11/playmonaut_blondes.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7239-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/04/21/carnegie_mellon_cyber_physical_systems/</link><title>Hefty IT prof develops robot to check that robots are safe</title><description>Hefty IT prof develops robot to check that robots are safe

A Turing-awardwinner* boffin in the States says he has developed new software which can test the safety of computer-controlled railways, air-traffic systems, hospital intensive-care monitors, enormous 600-tonne godzilla lorries and such like - all the many kinds of smart machinery which can kill people. Automated "roundabout" …

Lewis Page, 21 Apr 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7239_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>