<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7241">flight simulators</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:16:55" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7241-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/05/01/ultimate_simulator_shoots_into_living_rooms_this_june/</link><title>Ultimate simulator to streak into living rooms next month</title><description>Ultimate simulator to streak into living rooms next month

Avid fans of simulators may want to save their wages - and then some - for the TL1 Racing Flight and FPS Simulator, which shoots into (large) living rooms this June. Manufactured in co-operation with fast-car maker Ariel, the TL1 is said to house the world's first 180° spherical projector screen and variable driving position …

Caleb Cox, 01 May 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7241_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7241-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/01/06/microsoft_flight_sim_free/</link><title>Microsoft revives flight sim by giving it away free</title><description>Microsoft revives flight sim by giving it away free

Microsoft has said that it will be reviving its Flight Simulator franchise this spring with a free version of the game entitled simply Flight. Redmond is making the game available in a private beta at present, but plans to release it as a free download eventually. The game needs a minimum of 10GB of hard drive space, a dual-core …

Iain Thomson, 06 Jan 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7241_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7241-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/04/06/crm_long_tail/</link><title>One basket only? Proceed to self service</title><description>One basket only? Proceed to self service

In tough economic times having lots of customers to sell to can give you a warm fuzzy feeling. But how many of them bring any real value? That warm glow could soon turn to a cold sweat of panic when you see how much it costs to sell to the low-value customers. “The segmentation of customers is vital,” says Dale Vile of the …

Andrew Charlesworth, 06 Apr 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7241_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7241-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/01/06/unisys_nasa_langley_flightsim/</link><title>NASA taps Unisys for flight sim mission</title><description>NASA taps Unisys for flight sim mission

Here's a job you probably wish you had. Unisys has just been tapped by NASA's Langley Research Center to provide application development and systems integration services for the space agency's simulators and flight research projects. The contract has a potential value of $48.5m. More than a decade ago, NASA Langley (which is …

Timothy Prickett Morgan, 06 Jan 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7241_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7241-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/11/27/nasa_brain_monitor_hats/</link><title>NASA developing brain-monitor hats for airline pilots</title><description>NASA developing brain-monitor hats for airline pilots

US aerospace agency NASA has announced that it is developing a brain-monitoring hat for airline pilots to wear. The idea is that the bonce-clocking headset will know when pilots become "mentally overloaded" and help them to "realise" this. The brain-titfers are being developed at NASA's Glenn Research Center using "functional …

Lewis Page, 27 Nov 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7241_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7241-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/05/24/raf_lan_party_pilots_doom/</link><title>RAF builds massively multiplayer flight sims</title><description>RAF builds massively multiplayer flight sims

A UK defence initiative hopes to link up military flight simulators in the US and UK , allowing British pilots to train for complex multi-aircraft missions together with their American counterparts across the pond. Front line aircrew are now involved in the experimental phase of the £7.8m Mission Training through Distributed …

Lewis Page, 24 May 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7241_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7241-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/07/21/huangyangtan_letters/</link><title>Readers mull Chinese black helicopter mystery</title><description>Readers mull Chinese black helicopter mystery

The mystery Chinese military installation near the village of Huangyangtan this week provoked a bit of a speculationfest among El Reg Google Earth aficionados: Strange goings-on in Huangyangtan So, just what is this remarkable scale model for? Let's consider some possibilities: I think you will find that it is used to help …

Lester Haines, 21 Jul 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7241_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7241-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2004/12/15/letters_1512/</link><title>Ratty pilots worry sci-fi fans</title><description>Ratty pilots worry sci-fi fans

If volume of letters is a reliable guide (and we are not saying it is) then the most important story of the last two week was the discovery that neural cells from a rat could fly a fighter jet. Naturally this news has alarmed many of you. Judgment Day is upon us, and it has whiskers: Eh....hello....."Battlestar Galactica" …

Lucy Sherriff, 15 Dec 2004</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7241_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7241-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2001/09/17/bomb_the_isps_daily_telegraph/</link><title>Bomb the ISPs – Daily Telegraph</title><description>Bomb the ISPs – Daily Telegraph

The Daily Telegraph is calling for the bombing of "uncompliant" ISPs "on foreign territory", in response to the atrocity in America. In an opinion piece, John Keegan, the newspaper's eminent defence correspondent, blames the Internet for facilitating the attacks. "The World Trade Centre outrage was co-ordinated on the internet …

Drew Cullen, 17 Sep 2001</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7241_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7241-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/1999/09/30/cia_recruits_video_game_mogul/</link><title>CIA recruits video game mogul for IT venture</title><description>CIA recruits video game mogul for IT venture

The CIA has smartened its image with the creation of In-Q-It, a high-tech venture capital firm playfully named for the eccentric gadget meister "Q" of James Bond fame. As if to build further on the fun and games motif, the agency has chosen former Spectrum Holobyte and Microprose exec Gilman Louie for its CEO. The new company …

Thomas C Greene, 30 Sep 1999</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7241_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>