<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7242">hague convention</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:37:55" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7242-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/06/11/baidu_lawsuit_democracy_resurrected/</link><title>US judge revives lawsuit vs Baidu and China</title><description>US judge revives lawsuit vs Baidu and China

A US judge has revived a potentially significant anti-censorship lawsuit brought by Stateside pro-democracy activists against Chinese search giant Baidu and the People’s Republic of China. The original complaint was filed by eight New Yorkers back in 2011 in the US District Court in Manhattan. They claimed Baidu, in collusion …

Phil Muncaster, 11 Jun 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7242_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/25/gavel_judgment_channel.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7242-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/03/26/baidu_censorship_suit_thrown_out_china/</link><title>US democracy activists lose case against Baidu and China</title><description>US democracy activists lose case against Baidu and China

Chinese search giant Baidu has seen off a $US16m legal challenge from a group of pro-democracy supporters in New York The unusual lawsuit was filed in the US District Court in Manhattan back in 2011, with the plaintiffs alleging that Baidu effectively acted as an agent of the Chinese state to deliberately suppress their pro- …

Phil Muncaster, 26 Mar 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7242_02_thumb.gif">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/06/18/baidu_logo.gif?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7242-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/08/30/uk_right_to_storm_ecuadorian_embassy/</link><title>UK: 'We're legally bound to arrest Mr Assange'</title><description>UK: 'We're legally bound to arrest Mr Assange'

The UK's Foreign Secretary has refused to rule out storming the Ecuadorian embassy to arrest Julian Assange and pack him off to Sweden. On Tuesday, The Right Honourable William Jefferson Hague met with the vice president of Ecuador over the Assange issue. When questioned about it by the BBC on Wednesday, Hague described the …

Iain Thomson, 30 Aug 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7242_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7242-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/02/04/cyberwar_rules_of_engagement/</link><title>World leaders meet to discuss cyberwar rules of engagement</title><description>World leaders meet to discuss cyberwar rules of engagement

Rules of engagement for the deployment of cyber-weapons need to be developed, an international security conference is due to be told later today. The influential EastWest Institute is due to present proposals for the cyberspace equivalent of the Geneva convention at the Munich Security Conference, which has included a debate on …

John Leyden, 04 Feb 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7242_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7242-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/04/02/killer_robot_ban_call/</link><title>Landmine charity: Ban the killer robots before it's too late!</title><description>Landmine charity: Ban the killer robots before it's too late!

A London-based anti landmine and cluster bomb charity has now widened its remit and is calling for a moratorium on the use of killer robots. "Our concern is that humans, not sensors, should make targeting decisions," said Richard Moyes of Landmine Action, quoted by New Scientist. "We don't want to move towards robots that make …

Lewis Page, 02 Apr 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7242_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7242-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/10/16/de_menezes_dum_dum_explanation/</link><title>Met used 'dum-dum' ammo on de Menezes</title><description>Met used 'dum-dum' ammo on de Menezes

The latest reports from the Stockwell Two trial, in which the Metropolitan Police are corporately in the dock for wrongly shooting dead Jean Charles de Menezes in 2005, have it that the plods used "dum dum" bullets. Even after all this time, the term "dum dum" still carries misty pejorative connotations in the British public …

Lewis Page, 16 Oct 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7242_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7242-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/06/11/sawfish_trade_ban/</link><title>CITES bans international trade in sawfish</title><description>CITES bans international trade in sawfish

A meeting of the Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species (CITES) in the Hague has banned the international trade in sawfish - threatened by demand for their attractive snouts, or rostra, and fins. According to the BBC, the rostra are used as novelty items, in traditional medicine, and (animal lovers look away …

Lester Haines, 11 Jun 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7242_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7242-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/09/06/ec_surveillance_consultation/</link><title>Tell the EC about surveillance</title><description>Tell the EC about surveillance

The European Commission has opened a public consultation on the use of surveillance technology in civil society. At the initiative's heart is the desire to work with industry to create more and better surveillance systems that it can use to monitor the public in order to prevent terrorist attacks. The EC Directorate-General …

Mark Ballard, 06 Sep 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7242_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7242-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/07/15/amd_intel_update/</link><title>Date set for Intel's response to AMD antitrust claims</title><description>Date set for Intel's response to AMD antitrust claims

Lawyers from Intel and AMD will meet for an initial court conference in the first week of August, over a month before Intel must file its response to AMD's allegations, court documents seen by The Register reveal. AMD's legal action against its arch-rival, alleging the chip giant engaged in anti-competitive behaviour in …

Tony Smith, 15 Jul 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7242_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/03/chandef10.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7242-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/03/21/dutch_isp_scientology/</link><title>Dutch AG upholds decision in Scientology case</title><description>Dutch AG upholds decision in Scientology case

The Dutch Attorney-General has endorsed a verdict seen as backing free speech over copyright in the controversial case between the Church of Scientology and writer Karin Spaink, Dutch ISP Xs4all reports. The Dutch Supreme Court, which will rule on this case on 8 July, had asked the Attorney-General for advice. The Church of …

Jan Libbenga, 21 Mar 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7242_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>