<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7261">elvish language</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:50:06" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7261-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/04/17/google_oracle_copyright_on_languages/</link><title>Oracle v Google could clear way for copyright on languages, APIs</title><description>Oracle v Google could clear way for copyright on languages, APIs

Computer languages and software interfaces may fall under copyright protection if Oracle succeeds in its Java lawsuit against Google. Amazingly, "copyfighters" appear to have paid little or no notice to this rare extension of copyright into new realms. But the consequences and costs for the software industry could be enormous. …

Andrew Orlowski, 17 Apr 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7261_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7261-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/11/17/avatar_navi_conlang_on_garmin_satnav/</link><title>Na'vi on your sat-navatar</title><description>Na'vi on your sat-navatar

Na'vi – the constructed language, or conlang, of those big blue dudes with the tails in Avatar – has tipped up on Garmin satnavs, or sat-Na'vis, as we must now call them. Amazingly, Garmin is citing public demand for this feature, which incorporates turn-by-turn instructions in a conlang that maybe 10 or 20 people in the world …

Drew Cullen, 17 Nov 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7261_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7261-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/11/17/languages_of_the_geeks/</link><title>Speak geek: The world of made-up language</title><description>Speak geek: The world of made-up language

The world of invented language is a difficult place to succeed and those who have the patience to create their own tend to have a hard time gathering followers. Klingon and Elvish are notable exceptions, thanks to the huge fan bases for Star Trek and Lord of The Rings. Society tends to regard people who learn these languages …

Caleb Cox, 17 Nov 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7261_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2010/11/17/klingon_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7261-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/11/09/finland_evoting/</link><title>Finland's flawed e-voting scheme - blame the voters?</title><description>Finland's flawed e-voting scheme - blame the voters?

Finland is a small country separated from the rest of Europe by geography and a language of such linguistic intrigue that it is believed to have been used by J R R Tolkien as the basis for High Elvish. But it is also a place where the collision of government and IT has significance for the rest of the world. The Register last …

Jane Fae Ozimek, 09 Nov 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7261_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7261-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2004/03/08/teens_get_classes_in_tolkiens/</link><title>Teens get classes in Tolkien's Elvish</title><description>Teens get classes in Tolkien's Elvish

British parents today face a terrifying new obstacle to understanding their children: JRR Tolkien's Elvish. Students at Turves Green Boys' Technology College in Birmingham can now avail themselves of courses in the language, which are said to "boost their self-esteem" and "develop some very complex skills", according to special …

Lester Haines, 08 Mar 2004</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7261_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>