<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7294">assumption of mary</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:23:58" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7294-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/06/why_your_kids_cant_program_part_1/</link><title>Your kids' chances of becoming programmers? ZERO</title><description>Your kids' chances of becoming programmers? ZERO

Almost overnight in the early 1980s, hordes of British kids embraced programming, as did many adults, delivering the most IT-literate workforce in the world. It was a big reason why the nosediving economy of the '70s and '80s didn’t crash and burn. Well, that or Thatcherism, you choose. Why BASIC? In the early 1970s and early …

Dominic Connor, 06 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7294_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/11/10/zx80.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7294-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/04/07/actuv_command_game/</link><title>Robo-warship sub hunter: Free DARPA crowdsauce game</title><description>Robo-warship sub hunter: Free DARPA crowdsauce game

No doubt regular readers will recall the US military's cunning plan to develop unmanned submarine-hunting robotic frigates - warships which would prowl the oceans like automated Mary Celestes, remorselessly tracking enemy submarines regardless of how their pale, sweaty, malodorous captains* might twist and turn. Screenshot from …

Lewis Page, 07 Apr 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7294_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7294-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/01/11/windows_on_arm/</link><title>Windows on ARM: leading from the rear</title><description>Windows on ARM: leading from the rear

Bill Gates may have long departed, but he's still in charge at Microsoft, in spirit at least. Every year Chairman Bill would return from a "reading week" – I prefer to think that Bill got lost on his annual trip to the shopping mall – having noticed that there were lots of newfangled TVs / watches / phones / pacemakers about, …

Andrew Orlowski, 11 Jan 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7294_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/10/21/arm.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7294-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/02/02/unmanned_frigates/</link><title>US plans crewless automated ghost-frigates</title><description>US plans crewless automated ghost-frigates

Those splendid brainboxes at DARPA - the Pentagon's in-house bazaar of the bizarre - have outdone themselves this time. They now plan an entirely uncrewed, automated ghost frigate able to cruise the oceans of the world for months or years on end without human input. The new project is called Anti-submarine warfare Continuous …

Lewis Page, 02 Feb 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7294_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7294-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/08/13/yelp_sales_pitch/</link><title>Yelp 'pay to play' pitch makes shops scream for help</title><description>Yelp 'pay to play' pitch makes shops scream for help

When it debuted in July of 2004, Yelp reinvented the notion of online city guides, giving "real people" the power to write "real reviews." For many, it represents the best of something called Web 2.0, a site built by you and me and everyone else. But in its struggle to turn clicks into cash, the San Francisco startup has been …

Cade Metz, 13 Aug 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7294_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7294-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/12/10/radiohead_wartime_misery/</link><title>Radiohead backs WW2-style austerity program</title><description>Radiohead backs WW2-style austerity program

Misery will be compulsory, if top rockers Radiohead have their way. The band have thrown their weight behind a "World War 2"-style programme of austerity measures: including restrictions on behaviour, and higher taxes. Last week, two newspaper columnists called for a return to the kind of social coercion only ever seen before in …

Andrew Orlowski, 10 Dec 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7294_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7294-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/01/27/letters/</link><title>97% of readers say surveys are rubbish</title><description>97% of readers say surveys are rubbish

Surveys - where would we be without them? A lot better off, many of you reckon, but more of that a bit later. First up, a couple of fun-sized snippets from the mailbag, starting with two more missives on Thomas C. Greene and his Steve Gibson bashing, as previously discussed in letters: Your readers seem quite correct that …

Lester Haines, 27 Jan 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7294_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7294-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2004/07/30/letters_segway_3007/</link><title>Segways are brilliant, you idiots</title><description>Segways are brilliant, you idiots

Seems young Ashlee upset a few people with his latest article about Segway Polo. Turns out there are a lot of people out there with scooter envy, who take umbrage on behalf of Segway Poloists. We still think its a bit silly, to be honest, but that might just be us. You must be really proud of your ability to pour scorn on …

Lucy Sherriff, 30 Jul 2004</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7294_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>