<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7307">causes of the cold war</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:44:11" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7307-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/09/mi5_boss_net_surveillence_speech/</link><title>MI5 boss: Snowden leaks of GCHQ methods HELPED TERRORISTS</title><description>MI5 boss: Snowden leaks of GCHQ methods HELPED TERRORISTS

MI5's newly appointed boss has suggested that his predecessor might have spoken too much about cyber-attacks rather than conventional terrorism in a speech attempting to justify controversial surveillance programs by GCHQ and the NSA. Andrew Parker, director general of the security service, made the remarks in a speech to the …

John Leyden, 09 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7307_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/10/18/blofeld.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7307-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/24/feature_quatermass_and_the_pit/</link><title>Mars, bringer of WAR: Quatermass and the Pit</title><description>Mars, bringer of WAR: Quatermass and the Pit

“When I wrote the Quatermass stories, I couldn’t help drawing on the forces and the fears that affected people in the 1950s,” wrote Quatermass creator Nigel Kneale in 1996. His inspiration for Professor Bernard Quatermass’ third appearance on television had been the Notting Hill race riots that struck the London suburb during …

Tony Smith, 24 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7307_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/06/27/qmp_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7307-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/01/13/usaf_scramjet_revived/</link><title>US air force has new scramjet hypersonic plane plans</title><description>US air force has new scramjet hypersonic plane plans

Who remembers the Blackswift – the planned hypersonic successor to the legendary SR-71 Blackbird spy plane of Cold War fame? The Blackswift was intended to take off and land from a runway like a normal plane and achieve speeds of Mach 6 on scramjet propulsion (comfortably eclipsing its illustrious turbo/ramjet predecessor's Mach …

Lewis Page, 13 Jan 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7307_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7307-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/07/02/terror_idiocy_outbreak/</link><title>'al-Qaeda' puts on big shoes, red nose, takes custard pie</title><description>'al-Qaeda' puts on big shoes, red nose, takes custard pie

The "car bomber" hysteria gripping much of the British and international media over the weekend has had a bucket of cold water from the Reg already, but just one bucket doesn't seem enough for this kind of outbreak. To recap: an exceptionally incompetent group of troublemakers, unknown to the plods or spooks, decided to bring a …

Lewis Page, 02 Jul 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7307_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/03/chandef7.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7307-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/03/27/letters_2703/</link><title>Blunkett mobilises sheep army to fight global warming</title><description>Blunkett mobilises sheep army to fight global warming

There's a virtual buffet of letters this fine Tuesday, so we've selected a few choice cuts to tickle your taste buds: For starters, broadband's not unlimited if there's a download limit you say, fairly, likening the sorry scenario to an eating establishment: OK, let's say I run a restaurant. Let's say I have in a group of lads …

Tracey Cooper, 27 Mar 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7307_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7307-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/08/22/letters_2208/</link><title>Stupid operating systems or stupid operators?</title><description>Stupid operating systems or stupid operators?

Someone needs to update the rules for modern living to include guidelines on preparing one's inbox for an onslaught of letters after publishing anything about the Windows operating system, and its little quirks. Our (almost) resident grumpy old guru let off a little steam this week after a computer meltdown zapped three hours …

Lucy Sherriff, 22 Aug 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7307_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7307-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/08/23/letters_2308/</link><title>On civil liberties, video violence and hanging offences</title><description>On civil liberties, video violence and hanging offences

A survey of around 1,000 Brits revealed firstly that as a nation, we are apparently quite at home with the idea of our civil liberties being eroded in exchange for a warm fuzzy feeling of security that comes with reactionary legislation. You thought it also showed that if you ask people very specific questions about big issues …

Lucy Sherriff, 23 Aug 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7307_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7307-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/07/15/letters_1507/</link><title>From politics to porn, via Microsoft and the supernatural</title><description>From politics to porn, via Microsoft and the supernatural

Bernie Ebbers shed a tear or two as he was sentenced to 25 years in the nick for his part in the financial disaster that was WorldCom. We'd cry, too, in his shoes, and we suspect a lot of other people would too. But that doesn't necessarily mean there is an awful lot of love out there for him: As I was listening to the news …

Lucy Sherriff, 15 Jul 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7307_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7307-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/01/27/lizard_army_atacks_scotland/</link><title>Lizard Army invades Alaska</title><description>Lizard Army invades Alaska

Those who still doubt our assertion that technology - in the service of the lizard people - is about to turn on humanity and enslave mankind in a post-apocalyptic nuclear winter where the relentless whine of the chill wind will be broken only by the distant screams of naked, hysterical survivors being consumed by murderous …

Lester Haines, 27 Jan 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7307_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7307-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2004/03/30/bt_denies_cable_fire/</link><title>BT denies cable fire was in A-bomb exchange</title><description>BT denies cable fire was in A-bomb exchange

While BT was tackling its underground cable fire yesterday, the burning issue for many Web watchers was whether the blaze was in an old telephone exchange buried deep below Manchester and designed to withstand a twenty-kiloton atom bomb. The Register was flooded with emails yesterday from people convinced that the fire had …

Tim Richardson, 30 Mar 2004</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7307_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/gen_cracked.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>