<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7348">map of the united states</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:29:29" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7348-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/20/australian_sends_planes_to_spot_suspected_mh370_wreckage/</link><title>Planes fail to find 'credible' candidate for flight MH370 wreckage</title><description>Planes fail to find 'credible' candidate for flight MH370 wreckage

Australia has sent planes to the Southern Ocean, some 2,500km south-west of Perth, after analysis of what's been described as “commercial satellite imagery” revealed large objects suspected to be debris from missing Malaysian Airlines flight MH370. The search area, depicted below in a map released by the Australian Maritime …

Simon Sharwood, 20 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7348_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/03/20/mh370_search_zone.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7348-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/18/that_obama_nsa_reform_speech_with_el_reg_annotations/</link><title>Those NSA 'reforms' in full: El Reg translates US Prez Obama's pledges</title><description>Those NSA 'reforms' in full: El Reg translates US Prez Obama's pledges

On Friday, President Obama gave his long-awaited speech on plans to reform the activities of the US intelligence services and how they monitor the rest of the world. You can watch the entire speech here, but words are tricky things – never more so than when national security is involved. As such we've taken a transcript of the …

Iain Thomson, 18 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7348_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2008/10/09/nsaseal.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7348-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/27/the_year_in_space_2013/</link><title>2013: A Space Odyssey - a cosmological review of the year</title><description>2013: A Space Odyssey - a cosmological review of the year

Space this year was dominated by space rocks big and small - whether we want to dodge 'em, mine 'em, or watch 'em explode near the Sun, we sure do love those asteroids, comets, meteors and meteorites. 2013 was also another year in Earthlings' continued obsession with all things Martian. We want to go there and we want to live …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 27 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7348_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/01/02/galctic_geysers.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7348-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/08/18/an_afternoon_with_phil_plait_the_bad_astronomer/</link><title>An afternoon with Phil Plait, the Bad Astronomer</title><description>An afternoon with Phil Plait, the Bad Astronomer

Phil Plait – one-time NASA astronomer, science educator, and author of the Bad Astronomy blog at Slate, recently visited Australia to renew his acquaintance with the Oz confection-cum-dentist's-nightmare Minties. While here, the Bad Astronomer embarked on a multi-city lecture tour, took part in IFLS Live in Sydney, and spent an …

Richard Chirgwin, 18 Aug 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7348_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/08/05/barbie_419x278.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7348-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/06/27/omg_shale/</link><title>UK sitting on top of at least 50 years of shale gas – report</title><description>UK sitting on top of at least 50 years of shale gas – report

The UK is sitting on a cheap energy economic revolution comparable to the heyday of North Sea Oil, the British Geological Survey suggests. The Survey’s estimate of the potential gas reserves of the Bowland–Hodder shale formation - finally published today – indicate that using today’s technology, the rocks should yield 1,329 TCF …

Andrew Orlowski, 27 Jun 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7348_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7348-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/06/24/isc_2013_100_pteaflops_quantum_poll/</link><title>HPC geeks ponder 100 petafloppers and quantum supercomputers</title><description>HPC geeks ponder 100 petafloppers and quantum supercomputers

The next big barrier for supercomputing is punching through 100 petaflops peak performance, which frankly could be done in a heartbeat if someone had a few hundred millions dollars lying around. And now that Google and NASA are monkeying around with a quantum computer, thoughts are turning to how a QC might be deployed to …

Timothy Prickett Morgan, 24 Jun 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7348_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/06/06/tianhe_2_render.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7348-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/06/12/scientists_hack_into_human_brain_to_understand_how_we_learn/</link><title>Wanna be a ROBOT OVERLORD? Boffins pave way with mind-controlled cursor</title><description>Wanna be a ROBOT OVERLORD? Boffins pave way with mind-controlled cursor

Scientists have implanted electrodes in the brains of seven epileptic people in a bid to understand how humans learn new skills. They wanted to see what happened when people learned to use a device called a brain-computer interface, which allows them to interact with computers simply by thinking. This revolutionary technology is …

Jasper Hamill, 12 Jun 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7348_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7348-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/04/02/race_for_space_1/</link><title>Rocket boffinry in pictures: Gulp the Devil's venom and light a match</title><description>Rocket boffinry in pictures: Gulp the Devil's venom and light a match

It's been more than 70 years since the first successful test flight of the German Vergeltungswaffe 2 (V2) - the weapon that paved the way for subsequent rocket-based efforts to escape Earth's surly bonds. On 3 October 1942, a team headed by Wernher von Braun watched its creation rise from the launchpad at Peenemünde, little …

Lester Haines, 02 Apr 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7348_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7348-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/03/04/pirate_bay_north_korea/</link><title>Pirate Bay 'seeks asylum' in, er, 'North Korea'</title><description>Pirate Bay 'seeks asylum' in, er, 'North Korea'

The Pirate Bay says it is relocating to either North Korea (the Democratic People's Republic of Korea) - if you go by the flag in its sails on its homepage - or South Korea (the Republic of Korea), if you go by its statement.* If the file-sharing site's claim relates to the former, it certainly looks spurious given the nation's …

Simon Sharwood, 04 Mar 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7348_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/03/05/north_korean_tpb.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7348-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/02/04/google_schmidt_slams_china/</link><title>Schmidt slams China as world's most prolific hacker</title><description>Schmidt slams China as world's most prolific hacker

Google executive chairman Eric Schmidt has strongly criticised China, claiming the country is the world’s most prolific hacker of foreign firms and predicting that its actions will increasingly drive Western tech vendors closer to their governments. The remarks came in a new book, The New Digital Age, which the Wall Street …

Phil Muncaster, 04 Feb 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7348_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/12/17/eric_schmidt.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>