<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7402">little johnny</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:58:01" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7402-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/12/archaeologic_amstrad_cpc_464/</link><title>You’re NOT fired: The story of Amstrad’s amazing CPC 464</title><description>You’re NOT fired: The story of Amstrad’s amazing CPC 464

It was a home computer that embodied so many contradictions. It was launched months after the British microcomputer boom of the early 1980s had peaked. It was a rush job: the machine that was revealed to the press in the Spring of 1984 hadn’t even existed nine months previously. It was one of the best-produced British micros of …

Tony Smith, 12 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7402_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/01/13/464_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7402-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/30/mobile_year_in_review_2013/</link><title>Apple loses sauce, BlackBerry squashed and Microsoft, er, WinsPhones (Nokia's)</title><description>Apple loses sauce, BlackBerry squashed and Microsoft, er, WinsPhones (Nokia's)

It was a year where Apple slurped down enormous profits but lost some of its bleeding-edge-tech street cred, while Samsung marched inexorably on. But behind the scenes there was much more going on. Here are the year's trends put through the blender. Apple Apple's strategy is quite simple: instead of making products the …

Andrew Orlowski, 30 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7402_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/06/22/apple.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7402-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/19/doctor_who_theme_elements_examined/</link><title>Delia and the Doctor: How to cook up a tune for a Time Lord</title><description>Delia and the Doctor: How to cook up a tune for a Time Lord

As a theme tune, Ron Grainer’s music for Doctor Who needs no introduction. But to describe this unique piece of electronic music as solely Ron Grainer’s composition would be a disservice to the considerable musical contribution made by Delia Derbyshire, who in 1963 set about realising the original score at the BBC’s Radiophonic …

Bob Dormon, 19 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7402_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/07/delia_derbyshire_editing_3.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7402-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/08/23/bofh_2013_episode/</link><title>Nasty BOFHses. It burns us! It burns...

*[BOFHses]: Bastard Operator from Hell</title><description>Nasty BOFHses. It burns us! It burns...

"Where's my car park gone?" I ask Security as I wander into the building in a very irritated manner. "What car park?" Security asks "My Car park. Basement level 2. Right beside the lifts. Now apparently somewhere inside a large concrete room." "Oh, that. Well we can't really talk about that." "How about a hint?" "I... Well …

Simon Travaglia, 23 Aug 2013

*[BOFHses]: Bastard Operator from Hell</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7402_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/08/22/smell.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7402-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/10/asperger_syndrome_beneficial_effects_for_it_clients/</link><title>Asperger's and IT: Why my prejudices are great for your business</title><description>Asperger's and IT: Why my prejudices are great for your business

Recently, Trevor Pott posted an article discussing prejudices in IT. I’ve been thinking hard about this exact problem for several months now. As a consultant to the SME market, every single prejudice I have directly affects my clients' IT infrastructure, potentially for 10 years. Like Trevor, I have a disability. I live every …

Aaron Milne, 10 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7402_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/07/10/moss_index.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7402-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/06/18/review_samsung_galaxy_note_8_tablet/</link><title>Samsung Galaxy Note 8: Proof the pen is mightier?</title><description>Samsung Galaxy Note 8: Proof the pen is mightier?

Bewildering. That’s the best word to describe Samsung’s small tablet range. Since the second half of 2010, the Galaxy Tab, Galaxy Tab 8.9, Galaxy Tab 2 7.0, Tab 7.0 Plus and Tab 7.7 blurred one into the other, much to the confusion of the average customer and me. Thankfully, the Samsung fondleslab now sat on my desk is a Note, …

Alun Taylor, 18 Jun 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7402_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/06/17/note8_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7402-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/05/24/geeks_guide_gchq/</link><title>INSIDE GCHQ: Welcome to Cheltenham's cottage industry</title><description>INSIDE GCHQ: Welcome to Cheltenham's cottage industry

For staff at the Government Communications Headquarters (GCHQ) in Cheltenham, there’s an air of Fight Club about the place. The first rule about GCHQ is you don’t talk about GCHQ. It’s a well observed tradition, even though there are road signs and a bus route directing you to this highly secret establishment, the nerve centre …

Bob Dormon, 24 May 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7402_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/05/20/gchq_benhall_doughnut_aerial_view_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7402-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/02/21/punkspider/</link><title>PunkSPIDER project founder defends 'Google for web app vulns'</title><description>PunkSPIDER project founder defends 'Google for web app vulns'

The founder of a project that aims to offer a global web application vulnerability scanner has defended the potentially controversial technology. The tech is a useful tool to check the security of websites you use for shopping, or to which you've submitted your personal data, but it could equally be a tool for budding VXers - …

John Leyden, 21 Feb 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7402_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7402-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/01/15/windows_phone_boot/</link><title>Titsup Windows Phone 8 orders user to cram 'boot disc' in mobe</title><description>Titsup Windows Phone 8 orders user to cram 'boot disc' in mobe

A Windows Phone 8-using wag claims he provoked his Microsoft handset into asking for an installation DISC - with a boot manager error message familiar to anyone who's wrestled with Windows NT. The offending boot screen At least it didn't do a blue screen of death The error is by no means standard and - we're told - only …

Bill Ray, 15 Jan 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7402_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7402-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/11/09/something_for_the_weekend_passwords_and_keyboards/</link><title>A bitter spill to swallow, or 'how to smeg up your keyboard'</title><description>A bitter spill to swallow, or 'how to smeg up your keyboard'

Trouble at mill. Someone’s password isn’t working. It’s day two for one of the casuals and he’s forgotten what the temporary password is. It’s been an entire 24 hours and his natural creativity doesn’t extend to remembering how to type ‘Passw0rd’. Brilliant. Confused computer keyboard I remind him of his password and he gets …

Alistair Dabbs, 09 Nov 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7402_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/08/03/keys.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>