<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7404">kobe bryant</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:12:34" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7404-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/07/27/olympic_impostors_flood_social_networks/</link><title>Twitter impostors stop at NOTHING to drag athletes through mud</title><description>Twitter impostors stop at NOTHING to drag athletes through mud

Malware-slingers and mischief-makers are ramping up the creation of fake celebrity profiles on social networks in time for the start of the Olympics on Friday. El Reg spoke to "reputation managers" of the stars about the problem. Some of the fake profiles are harmless while others link to pictures of strippers and escorts and …

John Leyden, 27 Jul 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7404_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/twitter_t.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7404-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/02/17/quotw_ending_february_17/</link><title>'The full harm to Apple cannot be calculated'</title><description>'The full harm to Apple cannot be calculated'

This was the week when MySpace, which some of you may remember as once being a social network, came back from the dead thanks to its reinvention as a "meaningful social entertainment experience around content" with a million new users signing on since December last year. Google locked up its Wallet service for now, after two …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 17 Feb 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7404_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7404-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/03/23/yahoo_answers_google_instant/</link><title>Yahoo! answers Google Instant with streaming &lt;strike&gt;web&lt;/strike&gt; search</title><description>Yahoo! answers Google Instant with streaming &lt;strike&gt;web&lt;/strike&gt; search

Yahoo! has unveiled its answer to Google Instant, rolling out a "streaming" search service that it claims is significantly faster than the technology Google debuted last fall. Like Google Instant, it serves up search results as you type. But unlike Mountain View's service, it does not provide results from a relatively complete …

Cade Metz, 23 Mar 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7404_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7404-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2004/12/14/aol_most_searched_2004/</link><title>'Horoscopes' is AOL's most searched word</title><description>'Horoscopes' is AOL's most searched word

America Online today released its most popular search terms, which showed that Britney Spears has reclaimed the title of most searched person of 2004 from rapper 50 Cent. Platinum recording artist and teen movie star Hilary Duff was the most searched person by children and teenagers, while Usher was the most searched male. …

Robin Lettice, 14 Dec 2004</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7404_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7404-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2004/01/05/prince_charles_tops_uk_google/</link><title>Prince Charles tops UK Google 2003 top ten</title><description>Prince Charles tops UK Google 2003 top ten

Prince Charles, tree-hugging heir to the British throne, has topped the Google most wanted list for 2003, according to the search engine. Our Charlie proved the most sought-after subject on the web after scurrilous allegations prompted a fact-starved UK public to scour the Net for tasty titbits. This royal rumpus beat soap …

Lester Haines, 05 Jan 2004</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7404_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>