<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7405">light therapy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:19:47" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7405-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/07/bofh_2014_episode_1/</link><title>BOFH: Attractive person is attractive. Um, why are your eyes bulging?

*[BOFH]: Bastard Operator from Hell</title><description>BOFH: Attractive person is attractive. Um, why are your eyes bulging?

“What brings you down here then?” the PFY asks the Director after he popped through the door unannounced. “Oh, I wanted to give you a heads-up on your new manager.” “Really, has Roy left?” the PFY asks, knowing the answer only too well. “Yes. He messaged me over the break saying he wouldn’t be coming back. Something about …

Simon Travaglia, 07 Feb 2014

*[BOFH]: Bastard Operator from Hell</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7405_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/07/crazy.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7405-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/25/the_register_reviews_four_electronic_cigarettes/</link><title>Reg man inhales the smooth, non-cancerous, taste of USB nicotine</title><description>Reg man inhales the smooth, non-cancerous, taste of USB nicotine

Electronic cigarettes, also known as e-cigs or vapes, sound like a great idea because they deliver a nicotine hit in a familiar form factor, but without the nasty stuff you'll find in conventional smokes. The jury's out on whether they're safe, with a University of Queensland study attracting criticism almost before it began, …

Richard Chirgwin, 25 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7405_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/23/at_the_place_of_shame_2.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7405-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/19/doctor_who_theme_elements_examined/</link><title>Delia and the Doctor: How to cook up a tune for a Time Lord</title><description>Delia and the Doctor: How to cook up a tune for a Time Lord

As a theme tune, Ron Grainer’s music for Doctor Who needs no introduction. But to describe this unique piece of electronic music as solely Ron Grainer’s composition would be a disservice to the considerable musical contribution made by Delia Derbyshire, who in 1963 set about realising the original score at the BBC’s Radiophonic …

Bob Dormon, 19 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7405_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/07/delia_derbyshire_editing_3.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7405-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/08/11/ten_android_games_for_armchair_olympians/</link><title>Ten Android games</title><description>Ten Android games

Not everyone will agree with me that the Nexus 7 tablet is nigh on perfect but I can't imagine anyone seriously questioning its ability as a gaming machine. With a quad-core CPU and a 720p IPS screen, we're off to a good start. It's also the perfect size and weight to hold in both hands but still give your thumbs free range to …

Alun Taylor, 11 Aug 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7405_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/08/10/dead_trigger.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7405-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/03/15/the_charge_of_the_metro_brigade/</link><title>Charge of the Metro brigade: Did Microsoft execs plan to take a hit?</title><description>Charge of the Metro brigade: Did Microsoft execs plan to take a hit?

"Tiles to the right of them, Tiles to left of them, Tiles in front of them"   - Alfred Tennyson, The Charge of the Metro Brigade (1854) It's fair to say that the typical reaction of pundits and analysts to Windows 8 is quite different to yours or mine. Our misgivings are shared, I have discovered, by many Microsoft employees. …

Andrew Orlowski, 15 Mar 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7405_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/08/17/windows8_metro_side_teaser.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7405-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/09/12/best_cat_ever/</link><title>Glow-in-the-dark kittens to help produce cure for AIDS</title><description>Glow-in-the-dark kittens to help produce cure for AIDS

Glow-in-the-dark kittens are science's latest weapon in the war against HIV. The cats, bred at the Mayo Clinic in Minnesota, are resistant to feline AIDS, glow unearthly green under UV light and are an important step towards disrupting the mechanism by which HIV destroys the human immune system. Feline immunodeficiency virus ( …

Anna Leach, 12 Sep 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7405_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7405-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/03/18/apple_christian_conundrum/</link><title>Apple 'gay-cure' app severely slapped</title><description>Apple 'gay-cure' app severely slapped

Apple is today accused of anti-gay discrimination, following the release of an iPhone app that aims to help people find “freedom from homosexuality”. A petition has been launched by Truth Wins Out, which describes itself as a non-profit organisation that fights anti-gay religious extremism on the change.org website, asking Steve …

Jane Fae Ozimek, 18 Mar 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7405_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7405-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/11/05/spotify_exclusive/</link><title>Spotify: The Sutton Coldfield challenge</title><description>Spotify: The Sutton Coldfield challenge

New Spotify figures obtained by El Reg shed some new light on the progress of the music phenomenon. Back in June, we revealed the subscriber and revenue numbers for the startup, which showed that Spotify had exceeded half a million UK users, but was gaining just 14p of advertising revenue per user - not enough to keep the …

Andrew Orlowski, 05 Nov 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7405_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7405-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/01/30/mrsa_killed_by_blue_light/</link><title>Boffins: Blue light kills MRSA 'superbugs'</title><description>Boffins: Blue light kills MRSA 'superbugs'

American medi-boffins say they have developed a way to kill so-called "superbugs" - deadly infections which can't be cured using antibiotics - by simply shining a certain wavelength of blue light on them. They believe the technique could be used safely on patients infected with MRSA*. "It is inspiring that an inexpensive …

Lewis Page, 30 Jan 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7405_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7405-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/12/08/review_gadget_webcam_wowwee_rovio_mobile/</link><title>WowWee Rovio Mobile webcam</title><description>WowWee Rovio Mobile webcam

If the conventional webcam has a failing, it's the lack of an ability to let you wander about and look at things out of the fixed view of the camera. The Rovio aims to correct this limitation. As befits a company whose background is in the robotic toy market, WowWee has gone for the pseudo-military-tech toys-for-boys look with …

Alun Taylor, 08 Dec 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7405_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2008/12/08/rovio_sm.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>