<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7408">tom cruise</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:39:40" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7408-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/07/review_south_park_stick_of_truth/</link><title>'Mommy got me an UltraVibe Pleasure 2000 for Xmas!' South Park: Stick of Truth</title><description>'Mommy got me an UltraVibe Pleasure 2000 for Xmas!' South Park: Stick of Truth

Over the last few seasons South Park has become a bit of a stinker – and, more often than not, licensed video game adaptations are pretty whiffy too. When I first heard rumblings of South Park: The Stick of Truth I was dubious whether it would be any good, despite assurances that the production was being overseen by the creators …

Lucy Orr, 07 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7408_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/03/07/south_park_stick_of_truth_11.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7408-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/16/microsoft_joins_3d_printing_bandwagon_with_free_design_tool/</link><title>Cocky Microsoft strokes soft tool in public for 3D printing on Windows 8.1</title><description>Cocky Microsoft strokes soft tool in public for 3D printing on Windows 8.1

Windows 8.1 users with a yen for 3D printing and a few thousand bucks for a printer can get a free design application from Microsoft – as Redmond seeks to show it's as modern as the rest of them. 3D Builder Basic tool to get you on your 3D feet "I get excited about 3D printing. Really excited. Like Tom Cruise on Oprah’s couch …

Iain Thomson, 16 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7408_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/16/3d_builder.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7408-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/08/01/snowden_vkontakte_job_offer/</link><title>Russian Zuckerberg to Snowden: 'Come work for &lt;del&gt;книга лиц&lt;/del&gt;  VKontakte'</title><description>Russian Zuckerberg to Snowden: 'Come work for &lt;del&gt;книга лиц&lt;/del&gt;  VKontakte'

It isn't clear how NSA leaker Edward Snowden plans to support himself, now that he's been granted 12 months of asylum in Russia. But if he wants a job, the door is open for him at VK, Russia's version of Facebook. Writing that he was proud of Russia for having accepted Snowden's asylum application, Pavel Durov, one of the …

Neil McAllister, 01 Aug 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7408_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/08/01/russian_rubles.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7408-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/05/01/ibm_atom_boy/</link><title>Atoms star in ball-bothering boffins' Big Blue movie</title><description>Atoms star in ball-bothering boffins' Big Blue movie

IBM Research has proved its worth by moving atoms across a screen to create the world's smallest movie. Big Blue has gone much better with its atomic animation A Boy and His Atom. The movie has 242 frames and lasts just under 100 seconds; any more and it would rapidly become turgidly boring, in your humble hack's opinion. Each …

Chris Mellor, 01 May 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7408_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7408-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/04/13/review_oblivion_the_movie/</link><title>Movie review: Oblivion</title><description>Movie review: Oblivion

When the film Oblivion was mentioned in the office recently, my first thoughts were that it was a prequel to The Hangover series. I couldn’t have been more wrong... or was I? After all, this Tom Cruise sci-fi caper has loss of memory as one of its key themes, which, booze fueled forays aside, immediately has me thinking of some …

Bob Dormon, 13 Apr 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7408_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/04/12/oblivion_movie_drone.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7408-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/04/12/surrey_police_system/</link><title>Brit cops blow £14m on software - then just flush it down the bogs</title><description>Brit cops blow £14m on software - then just flush it down the bogs

Surrey Police has pulled the plug on a multi-million-pound computer system it spent years developing. Way back in 2005, the force began overhauling its criminal intelligence setup. Since then it has spent £14.8m developing gear called the Surrey Integrated Reporting Enterprise Network (Siren). It is unclear how much of this dosh …

Jasper Hamill, 12 Apr 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7408_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/07/06/toilet_flush_big.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7408-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/02/21/scientology_internet_threat/</link><title>John Sweeney: Why Church of Scientology's gravest threat is the 'net</title><description>John Sweeney: Why Church of Scientology's gravest threat is the 'net

Back in 1995, when the net was still young, the late Robert Vaughn Young, an ex-scientologist, said the internet would be to Scientology what Vietnam was to the US: an unwinnable war. Vaughn Young, a former spokesman for the controversial organisation, believed that the internet would create the first place where Scientology …

Ollie Henry, 21 Feb 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7408_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/07/05/anonymousxenucake.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7408-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/11/16/dell_top_gun/</link><title>Dell starts up 'Top Gun' for channel hotshots, leather jackets and all</title><description>Dell starts up 'Top Gun' for channel hotshots, leather jackets and all

Dell's chief storage guy, ex-fighter pilot Darren Thomas, has a new strategy to encourage the troops and get storage geeks to fly: make them Storage Top Guns with leather flying jackets to go with it. Certified Dell and channel storage folks get a leather pilot's jacket emblazoned with badges, like a Storage Domain Champion with …

Chris Mellor, 16 Nov 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7408_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/11/15/mcgillis_topgun.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7408-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/11/12/michael_arndt_star_wars_writer/</link><title>Star Wars VII: The Disney Movie signs Toy Story III script genius</title><description>Star Wars VII: The Disney Movie signs Toy Story III script genius

Disney's newest, shiniest cash-cow, Star Wars VII, has picked up a writer in the shape of Little Miss Sunshine director Michael Arndt. The Hunger Games II scribe, who has also recently co-written a sci-fi movie for Tom Cruise, has apparently been working on a "treatment" for the movie for a couple of months, The Hollywood …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 12 Nov 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7408_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7408-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/09/11/mcafee_watson_dangerous_celebrity/</link><title>McAfee: Emma Watson riskiest celebrity search</title><description>McAfee: Emma Watson riskiest celebrity search

In McAfee's latest survey of the celebrity searches most likely to lead to malware infection, Emma Watson – perhaps best known as Hermione Granger in the Harry Potter films – has taken the top spot, knocking off model Heidi Klum from last year's most-likely-to-infect honors. emma watson Be careful what you search for... …

Iain Thomson, 11 Sep 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7408_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>