<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7415">most anticipated games of 2013</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:01:55" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7415-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/01/grand_theft_auto_online_launch_hits_server_speed_bumps/</link><title>GTA V Online hits speed bumps: Short wait before you can rough up that hooker</title><description>GTA V Online hits speed bumps: Short wait before you can rough up that hooker

Gamers keen to get online and play Grand Theft Auto V against humans rather than machine intelligence have had to wait after server problems left them stymied. Grand Theft Auto Online: We are aware that some users are experiencing issues and we are working with @RockstarGames to resolve — PlayStation (@PlayStation) October 1, …

Iain Thomson, 01 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7415_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2009/05/07/gta_screenshot.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7415-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/12/31/2012_review/</link><title>2012 in tech: Apple up the Cook without a paddle, ARM, slab wars... and MORE</title><description>2012 in tech: Apple up the Cook without a paddle, ARM, slab wars... and MORE

Great Britain reminded the world who invented the web at London 2012 Olympics, Apple cocked up its maps, Microsoft returned to hardware with Surface, we saw a rise of the machines on Wall Street and many of us rubbed our hands with glee as Facebook IPO's deflated. This was the last 12 months in technology. So put the in-laws on …

Gavin Clarke, 31 Dec 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7415_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/12/27/berner_lee_olympics_opening_ceremony.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7415-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/12/01/ouya_console_giveaway/</link><title>Ouya gaming project announces console giveaway</title><description>Ouya gaming project announces console giveaway

The makers of the hotly anticipated Ouya Android-based gaming console say they're on track to ship their first development consoles by the end of the year, and a few lucky developers will be able to get their hands on them for free. According to an update posted to the project's Kickstarter page on Friday, early versions of the …

Neil McAllister, 01 Dec 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7415_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7415-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/09/13/gaming_downunder_gets_new_classifications/</link><title>Australian gamers can get high and naked</title><description>Australian gamers can get high and naked

Australian gamers will soon be able to legally indulge in violent, nude and drug fuelled games, thanks to the publication of new, long-anticipated Guidelines for the Classification of Computer Games that for the first time include an R18+ classification for games that can only be sold to adults. From January 2013, Australia will …

Natalie Apostolou, 13 Sep 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7415_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2010/09/10/gta_chinatown_hd.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7415-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/06/08/e3_2012_roundup/</link><title>E3 2012: Prepare to have your buttons pushed</title><description>E3 2012: Prepare to have your buttons pushed

With current-gen consoles entering their twilight years and most next-gen consoles still merely dots in the distance, you'd expect 2012's Electronic Entertainment Expo in LA to be a fairly quiet show in comparison to last year. Fortunately, this wasn't the case and there was plenty to keep gaming's fanbois drooling. Super Mario …

Caleb Cox, 08 Jun 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7415_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/06/10/e3.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7415-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/05/14/tomb_raider_delayed_for_quality_improvement/</link><title>Tomb Raider delayed for quality improvement</title><description>Tomb Raider delayed for quality improvement

Lara Croft's rousing return to current-gen consoles has been pushed back to 2013, so developers at Crystal Dynamics can make Tomb Raider "the best game of their careers", apparently. The latest instalment of Tomb Raider was pegged for release this autumn, and while fresh content will be revealed at next month's E3 expo, the team …

Caleb Cox, 14 May 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7415_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/11/16/vg.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>