<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7432">ticket to mars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:31:02" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7432-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/18/rosetta_comet_chaser_due_to_wake_up_for_final_rendezvous_on_monday/</link><title>Rosetta comet chaser due to wake up for final rendezvous on Monday</title><description>Rosetta comet chaser due to wake up for final rendezvous on Monday

Scientists at the European Space Agency and NASA are facing a nervous weekend as the Rosetta spacecraft prepares to power up after three years of hibernation on Monday morning. Rosetta Rosetta could unlock the language of cometary life The billion-Euro spacecraft, launched in 2004, is approaching comet 67P/Churyumov- …

Iain Thomson, 18 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7432_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/01/18/rosetta.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7432-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/10/mars_ones_privately_funded_red_planet_trek_is_still_on_ndash_but_not_until_2018/</link><title>Mars One's Red Planet foray is still on – but not until 2018</title><description>Mars One's Red Planet foray is still on – but not until 2018

Mars One, the not-for-profit foundation dedicated to establishing a human colony on Mars, won't be able to launch its first mission to the Red Planet until later than originally planned. In an announcement issued on Tuesday, the group said it now expects to send an unmanned mission to Mars in 2018, rather than in 2016 as it had …

Neil McAllister, 10 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7432_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/20/mars_asteroids_nasa.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7432-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/01/quotw_ending_november_1/</link><title>'It seems that the OSes and devices are based on the Devil'</title><description>'It seems that the OSes and devices are based on the Devil'

This was the week when Dell received a flood of complaints about the fact that its Latitude 6430u Ultrabook literally stinks. The whiffy laptops were shipped out to users smelling distinctly of feline urine. Owners took to Dell's support forums to start complaining: So a few weeks ago I got a new Lattitude 6430u for work. The …

Team Register, 01 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7432_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/12/cat_index_picture.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7432-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/08/12/mars_one_hundred_thousand_applications/</link><title>100,000+ Earthlings star in 'reality TV contest' for ONE-WAY ticket to MARS</title><description>100,000+ Earthlings star in 'reality TV contest' for ONE-WAY ticket to MARS

More than 100,000 people want to go to Mars and never, ever come back, according to the non-profit organising a trip to the dust world. Mars One first landers Mars One (of a kind) ... how its landers might look Mars One's mission to colonise the Red Planet from 2022 has attracted thousands of applicants for the coveted four …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 12 Aug 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7432_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/04/17/mars_one_landers.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7432-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/05/bbc_cuts_3d_tv_service/</link><title>BBC abandons 3D TV, cites 'disappointing' results</title><description>BBC abandons 3D TV, cites 'disappointing' results

The BBC will suspend its 3D TV transmissions indefinitely, citing poor demand among viewers – its last hurrah will be a Dr. Who anniversary special in November. "I have never seen a very big appetite for 3D television in the UK," said Kim Shillinglaw, the BBC's head of 3D. "After that we will see what happens when the recession …

Iain Thomson, 05 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7432_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/07/05/3d_tv.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7432-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/12/30/2012_year_end_what_is_the_it_angle_quiz/</link><title>From post-coital squid to high-res Playboy bunnies: The 2012 'IT angle?!' quiz</title><description>From post-coital squid to high-res Playboy bunnies: The 2012 'IT angle?!' quiz

How much do you remember about what really mattered in 2012? You're about to find out. Last year The Reg chronicled more than just the birth of Windows 8, the rise of ARM, the battle between iOS and Android, the genesis of the buzzword de l'année "big data", Apple's crap Maps app flap, and other communiqués from the front lines …

Rik Myslewski, 30 Dec 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7432_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/12/30/question_vulture.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7432-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/11/27/musk_mars_colony/</link><title>Elon Musk envisions small town of VEGETARIANS ON MARS</title><description>Elon Musk envisions small town of VEGETARIANS ON MARS

Billionaire space pioneer Elon Musk wants to get a Martian colony of 80,000 people up and running by ferrying folks out there for $500,000 a trip. Mars Musk wants to start his colony on Mars with just ten people or so, who would fly to the planet on a huge reusable rocket powered by liquid oxygen and methane. "At Mars, you …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 27 Nov 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7432_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7432-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/11/08/verity_stob_on_quatermass/</link><title>Stob on Quatermass: Was this British TV's finest sci-fi hour?</title><description>Stob on Quatermass: Was this British TV's finest sci-fi hour?

In the pub, with my editor. "Those sci-fi classics of the fifties," he mused. "Not the Hammer remakes - the originals. Are they really classics? How do they compare with modern Doctor Who? Are they even watchable?" [Dissolve to Stob's flat. A portable computing machine is displaying the Amazon website's DVD section. Pan to a TV …

Verity Stob, 08 Nov 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7432_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/11/07/the_fly.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7432-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/07/25/street_view_bust/</link><title>Cops slap ticket on Street View spycar</title><description>Cops slap ticket on Street View spycar

You'll enjoy this: Here's evidence that not even the might of Google permits it to park vehicles from its Orwellian Opel spycar fleet in reserved doctor spots: Police dine Street View car for parking in reserved doctor spot Good work there by a vigilant Adam Ranshaw, and indeed the Boys in Blue, who apparently slapped the …

Lester Haines, 25 Jul 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7432_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7432-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2004/10/26/rutan_remembers_von_braun/</link><title>Burt Rutan takes a V2-powered wander down memory lane</title><description>Burt Rutan takes a V2-powered wander down memory lane

Aviation pioneer Burt Rutan has been fondly remembering on the BBC his childhood hero - German rocket scientist Wernher von Braun. The X-Prize victor recently hooked up with two surviving members of von Braun's V2 team and admitted that von Braun's dreams of space travel had inspired him on his own quest to escape Earth's …

Lester Haines, 26 Oct 2004</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7432_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>