<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7433">747-8</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:44:05" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7433-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/09/solarpowered_aircraft_unveiled_for_roundtheworld_flight/</link><title>Solar-powered aircraft unveiled for round-the-world flight</title><description>Solar-powered aircraft unveiled for round-the-world flight

After 12 years of research and testing, the Swiss engineering team Solar Impulse has unveiled the craft that will take a round-the-world- trip powered solely by photovoltaic power cells. Solar Impulse 2 Coming soon to a skyline near you "A vision counts for nothing unless it is backed up by action," said Bertrand Piccard, …

Iain Thomson, 09 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7433_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/04/09/solar_impulse.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7433-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/03/29/solar_impulse_arrives_in_san_francisco_bay_area/</link><title>Giant solar-powered aircraft to begin cross-country flight</title><description>Giant solar-powered aircraft to begin cross-country flight

The photovoltaics-powered Solar Impulse HB-SIA aircraft has arrived at the NASA Ames Research Center in Silicon Valley's Moffett Field to prepare for a flight across the US. After it has been offloaded in pieces from its Boeing 747-100 transporter, the Swiss-made HB-SIA will be reassembled in a Moffett Field hanger, then embark …

Rik Myslewski, 29 Mar 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7433_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/03/29/solar_impulse_419x278.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7433-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/11/23/test_template/</link><title>The early days of PCs as seen through DEAD TREES</title><description>The early days of PCs as seen through DEAD TREES

Thirty years ago, Time Magazine broke its 86-year tradition of naming a Man of the Year, and instead anointed its first Machine of the Year: The Computer. Time didn't deliver this news via www.time.com nor an HTML-encrusted email blast, but rather by macerated wood pulp pressed into sheets and coated with ink, cut into …

Rik Myslewski, 23 Nov 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7433_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7433-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/10/16/australian_surface_pricing/</link><title>Microsoft gouges Australia lightly on Surface</title><description>Microsoft gouges Australia lightly on Surface

Australian punters frustrated by the fact they pay more than their North American brethren for Apple gadgets, despite the Australian Dollar currently buying more than one US Dollar, can now get just a little bit mad with Microsoft too, after the company today announced prices for its Surface tablets that exceed US prices. …

Simon Sharwood, 16 Oct 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7433_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/microsoft_surface.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7433-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/09/21/space_shuttle_endeavour_california_tour/</link><title>Space shuttle to slip surly bonds of Earth one last time over California</title><description>Space shuttle to slip surly bonds of Earth one last time over California

Retired space shuttle Endeavour is set for a sightseeing tour of California and LA today, in a whistle-stop flyover of the state. Space shuttle Endeavour over Reliant Stadium and Astrodome The shuttle, piggybacking on its 747 jumbo-jet, will fly over the north of the state and a large part of the Los Angeles basin, buzzing …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 21 Sep 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7433_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7433-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/06/19/xeon_e7_analysis/</link><title>Xeon E7 servers run with the big dogs</title><description>Xeon E7 servers run with the big dogs

Intel has come a long way in the server racket, and the new "Westmere-EX" Xeon E7 processor, launched in April and making its way into systems now, is arguably its most sophisticated processor for servers to date. The Xeon E7 processors cram ten cores onto a single die, but the Xeon E7 design is a bit more than taking an eight- …

Timothy Prickett Morgan, 19 Jun 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7433_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/gen_hd.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7433-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/06/01/endeavour_retrospective/</link><title>Space shuttle Endeavour: 'An incredible ship'</title><description>Space shuttle Endeavour: 'An incredible ship'

Space shuttle Endeavour flew into retirement yesterday when it touched down at Kennedy Space Center at the end of its 25th and final flight. Speaking from Mission Control in Houston, astronaut Barry Wilmore told commander Mark Kelly: "Your landing ends a vibrant legacy for this amazing vehicle that will long be remembered. …

Lester Haines, 01 Jun 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7433_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7433-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/02/23/plastic_electronics/</link><title>Chemists create current-bearing plastic</title><description>Chemists create current-bearing plastic

Chemists have found a new way of producing plastic that conducts electricity, potentially paving the way to cheaper, more robust and er, more plasticky computers. Polymer electronics isn't new, and the printed electronics business is reckoned to be worth around $2bn, although not all the printing goes onto polymers. But with all …

Andrew Orlowski, 23 Feb 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7433_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7433-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/12/03/ten_essential_cheap_voice_phones/</link><title>Ten... dirt-cheap voice phones</title><description>Ten... dirt-cheap voice phones

World+Dog may be falling in love with smartphones faster than a large lass on a date with George Clooney, but there is still a place for the cheap and cheerful voice-centric handset. To start with, basic phones shorn of the extravagances of 3G, GPS, Wi-Fi, football pitch-sized hi-res screens and always-on connectivity can often …

Alun Taylor, 03 Dec 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7433_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2010/11/15/budget_phones_11.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7433-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/10/13/server_sap_sd_tests/</link><title>Big iron makers test their metal on SAP</title><description>Big iron makers test their metal on SAP

The server makers of the world have been busy little benchmarketeers in the past few weeks and have released a slew of test results that show the prowess their machines have supporting SAP's ERP software. Even IT shops that don't run SAP software take a hard look at the Sales &amp; Distribution (SD) benchmark tests because a wide …

Timothy Prickett Morgan, 13 Oct 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7433_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/03/chandef3.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>