<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7439">make crown</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:28:56" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7439-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/16/european_atlas_of_ict_activity_rates_munich_ahead_of_london/</link><title>Sorry London, Europe's top tech city is Munich</title><description>Sorry London, Europe's top tech city is Munich

The European Commission has decided Munich, not London, is Europe's top technology hub. The judgement is delivered in a new Atlas of ICT Activity in Europe released this week. The Atlas rates Europe's “ICT Poles of Excellence”using an “empirical framework” that considers over 40 factors to measure the following: R&amp;D activities …

Simon Sharwood, 16 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7439_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/06/29/battery_beer_stein1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7439-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/11/hp_on_lenovo/</link><title>HP: Lenovo's buy of IBM x86 biz is bad, bad, bad...</title><description>HP: Lenovo's buy of IBM x86 biz is bad, bad, bad...

The volume of noise from anxious biz customers and some channel types over Lenovo's buy of IBM's x86 server biz is deafening the ears of those gentle folk at HP. At least that is what Bill Veghte, global boss of HP's enterprise biz, told us, and given rivals' efforts to highlight HP's slips in recent years who can blame him for …

Paul Kunert, 11 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7439_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/server_room.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7439-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/08/hp_brenkel_global_sku_match_making/</link><title>HP: We're holding nothing back from partners now, coos firm</title><description>HP: We're holding nothing back from partners now, coos firm

The new, channel-friendlier HP - jolted into action by CEO Meg Whitman and losing the PC crown to Lenovo - is trying to help rather than hinder partners efforts to build global sales business with customers. A year ago Whitman told a gathering of resellers, integrators and providers of services at its global partner knees-up …

Paul Kunert, 08 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7439_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/13/love.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7439-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/03/whitehall_microsoft_winxp_security_lifeline/</link><title>Microsoft in 1-year Windows XP survival deal with UK govt</title><description>Microsoft in 1-year Windows XP survival deal with UK govt

Whitehall and Microsoft have struck a deal providing emergency cover to tens of thousands of government PCs still running Windows XP after next week’s support cutoff for the ageing OS. A one-year deal, revealed first by The Register, will see Microsoft release security patches to Windows XP users in the public sector until April …

Gavin Clarke, 03 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7439_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2007/12/18/sir_humphrey.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7439-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/31/phone_scam_operator_fined/</link><title>Boss at 'Microsoft' scam support biz told to cough £000s in comp</title><description>Boss at 'Microsoft' scam support biz told to cough £000s in comp

A fraudster who conned consumers, particularly silver surfers, into parting with cash to fix phantom PC bugs was handed a suspended sentence on Friday and ordered to pay thousands of pounds in costs and compensation. The national e-crime squad based in Yorkshire, together with ActionFraud, brought the case against Mohammed …

Paul Kunert, 31 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7439_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/28/balaclava_thief_burglar.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7439-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/27/microsoft_office_apps_ipad/</link><title>FINALLY Microsoft releases Office for iPad – but wait there's a CATCH</title><description>FINALLY Microsoft releases Office for iPad – but wait there's a CATCH

Microsoft has, after years of speculation, released some of its Office applications for Apple iPad owners – but you'll need an Office 365 subscription to use them in anything other than a lobotomized form. Nadella Nadella holds his first press conference since taking former CEO Steve Ballmer's crown The Apple App Store now …

Iain Thomson, 27 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7439_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/03/27/nadella.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7439-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/04/data_centre_world_2014_show_report/</link><title>Data Centre World: It's hard work cooling off those hot racks</title><description>Data Centre World: It's hard work cooling off those hot racks

At the Excel Centre in London last week, co-location of a different sort was in evidence with Cloud Expo Europe and Data Centre World sharing floorspace under the same roof. It was the first time that the two events had run simultaneously and, at first glance, co-habitation seemed to make a lot of sense. Yet wandering around …

Bob Dormon, 04 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7439_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/27/coolemall_christmann_hardware_testing.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7439-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/22/the_land_of_licensing/</link><title>Something rotten stalks the Cloud Kingdom</title><description>Something rotten stalks the Cloud Kingdom

A good lord builds his castle to both serve as the center of commerce for his lands and to offer protection to his people in case of an attack. The peasants have neither the resources nor the knowledge to defend themselves, and they look to their lords for help. Against most foes, this model works well. Should the land come …

Trevor Pott, 22 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7439_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/25/win7eula.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7439-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/21/tmv_public_sector_sits_13/</link><title>Big 20 cash hoovers: Slurp. Floop. Darn. Sluurrrp. Where's our public sector IT dosh?</title><description>Big 20 cash hoovers: Slurp. Floop. Darn. Sluurrrp. Where's our public sector IT dosh?

Half of the top 20 software and IT services (SITS) suppliers to UK.gov saw their public sector biz decline last year as Cabinet Office Minister Francis Maude and his merry band of axemen waged war on the oligopoly. The names on the list collated by TechMarketView remains unchanged on a year ago but the proportion of revenues …

Paul Kunert, 21 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7439_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/07/23/downing_street.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7439-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/11/book_review_empire_of_the_bs_charles_band/</link><title>Empire of The 'B’s: The Mad Movie World of Charles Band</title><description>Empire of The 'B’s: The Mad Movie World of Charles Band

There’s definitely a buzz around B movies these days, with the genre seemingly, er, healthier than ever. Take Sharknado, which aired on SyFy and became a Twitter sensation. I think the only thing I managed to tweet last year was “My feed is full of Sharknado". This low budget movie has now clocked up millions of viewings and to …

Lucy Orr, 11 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7439_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/10/empire_of_the_bs_robot_jox_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>