<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7445">marathon training</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:13:16" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7445-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/14/breivik_video_game_torture/</link><title>Imprisoned Norwegian mass murderer says PlayStation 2 is 'KILLING HIM'</title><description>Imprisoned Norwegian mass murderer says PlayStation 2 is 'KILLING HIM'

Norwegian convicted mass murderer Anders Behring Breivik has threatened a hunger strike if prison authorities don't upgrade his video game system to a PlayStation 3, among other demands. "You've put me in hell," Breivik wrote to officials in November in a letter obtained by Agence France-Presse, "and I won't manage to survive …

Neil McAllister, 14 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7445_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/14/rayman_revolution.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7445-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/04/18/tomtom_satnav_sportswatch/</link><title>TomTom brandishes new strap-on in Amsterdam: The wristnav</title><description>TomTom brandishes new strap-on in Amsterdam: The wristnav

Satnav maker TomTom guided the press - along with automotive and retail partners from all corners of the globe - to Amsterdam on Tuesday for the launch of its next gen satnavs and a new sporty lifestyle product range. The company has form with fitness gear, having teamed up with Nike to deliver its strap-on range of Nike+ GPS …

Bob Dormon, 18 Apr 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7445_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/04/17/tomtom_runner.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7445-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/05/31/windows_8_metro_and_multitasking/</link><title>I need to multitask, but Windows 8's Metro won't let me</title><description>I need to multitask, but Windows 8's Metro won't let me

What is multitasking? Different people seem to mean different things when they use the word multitasking. The definition chosen has implications for accepting or rejecting the prevailing design choices of modern user interfaces. I have been a vocal critic of Windows 8's Metro interface. My chief complaint is that it does not …

Trevor Pott, 31 May 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7445_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/gen_cd.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7445-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/11/29/marathon_send_robots_to_us/</link><title>Oz robo-soldiers in US Marines' firing line</title><description>Oz robo-soldiers in US Marines' firing line

Sydney based robotics manufacturer Marathon Targets has delivered its first cyber troops to the US Marine Corp as part of a multi-million dollar contract. Marathon Targets won the $AU57 million contract last year with the US Marine Corps Systems Command to trial its advanced robot technology. Following certification, eight …

Natalie Apostolou, 29 Nov 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7445_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7445-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/11/09/student_cluster_competition_university_profiles/</link><title>Student Cluster Competition: The runners and riders</title><description>Student Cluster Competition: The runners and riders

Eight university teams - six from the US, one from Russia and one from Taiwan descend on the SC10 supercomputing show in New Orleans next week to take part in the Student Cluster Competition (SCC). The students bring their own self-designed and built clusters to the show, re-assemble them, and race to complete a set of …

Dan Olds, Gabriel Consulting, 09 Nov 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7445_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/gen_glare.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7445-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/12/12/dellconnect_tech_gets_frisky/</link><title>Dell tech flashes woman with (her own) jubblies</title><description>Dell tech flashes woman with (her own) jubblies

A DellConnect IT specialist has been accused of intercontinental sexual hijinx for remotely flashing a woman client with a nude photo - of herself. According to a report in The Orange County Register out of Santa Ana, California, 45-year-old Stacy Gore received the boobular surprise when she was working with an India-based Dell …

Rik Myslewski, 12 Dec 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7445_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7445-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/04/07/gaming_pills/</link><title>Gamers punted performance-enhancing pills</title><description>Gamers punted performance-enhancing pills

Marathon gaming sessions usually end only when all the pizza and pop has been devoured - or your opponent has fallen asleep. But a Japanese retailer thinks it can boost your videogame performance and staying power by offering you some pills to pop. gaming_pills1 The Blueberry pill: improve gaming performance? If long-lasting …

James Sherwood, 07 Apr 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7445_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2008/04/07/gaming_pills_sm.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7445-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/01/30/samsung_cystic_fibrosis_marathon/</link><title>Samsung gears up to battle Cystic Fibrosis</title><description>Samsung gears up to battle Cystic Fibrosis

For once, Samsung’s latest announcement isn’t about yet another phone, camera or HD TV. Instead, the company’s unveiled its latest sponsorship scheme: raising funds for the fight against Cystic Fibrosis. Samsungs_Mitchinson Samsung's Mark Mitchinson (centre) gets in training Throughout 2008, the company will be holding …

James Sherwood, 30 Jan 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7445_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2008/01/30/samsungs_mitchinson_sm.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7445-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/11/22/koreans_online_bootcamp/</link><title>Korean cyber junkies march off to bootcamp</title><description>Korean cyber junkies march off to bootcamp

Tired of its citizens dropping dead forehead to keyboard after marathon online sessions, the South Korean government has decided to follow China's lead with a tough-love approach, the New York Times noted this week. It recently opened a government-funded, Chinese-style juvenile boot camp, tailored to the special needs of the …

Burke Hansen, 22 Nov 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7445_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7445-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/10/05/bofh_episode_34/</link><title>BOFH: Skip diplomacy

*[BOFH]: Bastard Operator from Hell</title><description>BOFH: Skip diplomacy

"Hurry up and get the door open!" I gasp as the PFY fumbles with his swipe card at the back door of the building. "Ok, ok," the PFY whispers back. "I'm working as fast as I can! &gt;swip&lt; Got it!" &gt;bip&lt; &gt;bip&lt; &gt;bip&lt; &gt;bip&lt; &gt;bip&lt; &gt;click&lt; "Right, I'll hold the door, you pick up that lot." "Okay," the PFY says, hefting up a bunch …

Simon Travaglia, 05 Oct 2007

*[BOFH]: Bastard Operator from Hell</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7445_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2008/06/06/bofh_bofh-copy.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>