<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7447">running shoes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:25:02" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7447-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/31/commvaults_vm_transubstantiation_technology/</link><title>C'mon, Commvault: You have the tech to build VM mutants...</title><description>C'mon, Commvault: You have the tech to build VM mutants...

Commvault, the arch archiver and backup biz, appears to have a virtual machine "mutation" facility, and this has prompted some speculation here at El Reg storage desk. A quick recap. Simpana 10 can back up physical and virtual servers and virtual machines (VMs) from VMware and Hyper-V. It supports cross-platform data protection …

Chris Mellor, 31 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7447_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/03/31/mystique3.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7447-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/03/review_asus_transformer_trio/</link><title>This THREESOME is a HANDFUL: It’s the Asus Transformer Book Trio</title><description>This THREESOME is a HANDFUL: It’s the Asus Transformer Book Trio

No matter what sort of tablet you prefer, be it an iPad or an Android slate, there will be times when you will also need a good old-fashioned Windows laptop too. Asus, which has form when it comes to cooking up strange combo designs - witness the PadFone - obviously thinks that’s the case as the new Transformer Book Trio is both …

Alun Taylor, 03 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7447_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/03/trio_2.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7447-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/20/quotw_ending_december_20/</link><title>Winklevoss: I have put my MOUTH where my MONEY IS</title><description>Winklevoss: I have put my MOUTH where my MONEY IS

It's the week before the holidays and all through the tech world barely a mouse has been stirring: but one of the Winklevoss twins did take some time out from Christmas shopping to let everyone know that they should be buying Bitcoins. Cameron Winklevoss told Redditors: Small bull case scenario for Bitcoin is a $400bn market …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 20 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7447_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/05/17/winklevoss.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7447-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/12/review_misfit_wearables_shine/</link><title>Heart part more art than state-of-the-art: Shine wearable activity sensor</title><description>Heart part more art than state-of-the-art: Shine wearable activity sensor

I’m not a fitness fan. I don’t jog and I’m more likely to be seen at the swimming baths picking up my kids after lessons than doing lanes myself. But with the big 5-0 coming close, and working as I do in a trade that has me sitting on my bum all day, I find I have a keener interest in my personal well-being than I did when I was …

Tony Smith, 12 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7447_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/12/09/shine_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7447-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/22/wallace_computer_contracts/</link><title>Best Start Schools 'superhead' quits amid probe into tech contracts</title><description>Best Start Schools 'superhead' quits amid probe into tech contracts

The man dubbed a "superhead" in charge of five London schools has resigned months after being suspended as Hackney Council continues to probe the distribution of tech contracts. This comes after Hackney Learning Trust voiced "concerns" about the computer contracts in the schools as well as Best Start Schools federation chief …

Paul Kunert, 22 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7447_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/06/17/i_quit_419x278.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7447-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/20/instagram_act_latest_uk_gov_landgrab_stymied/</link><title>Instagram Act: UK.gov's latest copyright landgrab stymied - for now</title><description>Instagram Act: UK.gov's latest copyright landgrab stymied - for now

Remember the notorious ‘Instagram Act’? If you recall, clauses smuggled into April’s Enterprise and Regulatory Reform Act (ERRA) - in the name of allowing reuse of orphan works - paved the way for the Government to grab your photographs and other visual images, in breach of international conventions. The mechanics of the scheme …

Andrew Orlowski, 20 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7447_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/10/30/beagle_boys.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7447-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/04/surface_2_nearly_sold_out/</link><title>Microsoft: We're nearly OUT OF STOCK of Surface 2 and Pro 2</title><description>Microsoft: We're nearly OUT OF STOCK of Surface 2 and Pro 2

Microsoft says it is nearly out of stock of its forthcoming Surface 2 and Surface Pro 2 fondleslabs, though what that means in terms of actual sales figures is anybody's guess. Surface 2 and Surface Pro 2 are close to selling out. All those buyers are gonna need apps. Your move: http://t.co/YGWmjklfuB — Microsoft Developer (@ …

Neil McAllister, 04 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7447_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/23/surface_pro_2.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7447-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/09/27/broadcom_throws_chips_into_infotainment_business/</link><title>Broadcom fries up '5G' Wi-Fi chips to chuck in your connected car</title><description>Broadcom fries up '5G' Wi-Fi chips to chuck in your connected car

Broadcom's latest chippery supports 802.11ac and Bluetooth LE too – which the company reckons is good enough to warrant calling it "5G" and snatching a chunk of the automotive market. The claim comes because of the Wi-Fi support, which has a theoretical top speed of 1Gb/sec, and despite the fact that this number was once the …

Bill Ray, 27 Sep 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7447_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/04/22/nvidia_dashboard_vision.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7447-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/09/20/3d_printing_bonanza_makes_mini_me_a_reality_100_per_cent_design_expo/</link><title>Mini-Me, stop humping the 'L-A-S-E-R': New 3D tech can make a Mini-You</title><description>Mini-Me, stop humping the 'L-A-S-E-R': New 3D tech can make a Mini-You

The way 3D printing enables ideas to move from the drawing board and become actual objects in a matter of hours has certainly inspired designers. To highlight this point, London-based 3D printer supplier iMakr appealed to visitors' egos at the 100% Design trade show in London's Earls Court this week. iMakr 3D printing examples …

Bob Dormon, 20 Sep 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7447_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/20/imakr_3d_printing_booth_pankaj_raut_with_model.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7447-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/08/29/women_in_it_column/</link><title>Women in IT: ‘If you want to be taken seriously, dress like a man’</title><description>Women in IT: ‘If you want to be taken seriously, dress like a man’

I am female, and I work in IT. I’m not in sales or in management; I am a systems engineer on a team that maintains and supports critical systems for an international, multi-billion-dollar company. I fight the fires, troubleshoot the issues and design systems. So much has been written about the need for more women in IT, but I’ve …

Phoummala Schmitt, 29 Aug 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7447_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/08/09/business_suit_woman.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>