<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7451">buy animal farm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:45:03" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7451-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/03/05/feature_ten_arcade_classics/</link><title>Twenty classic arcade games</title><description>Twenty classic arcade games

I’d better say it from the outset: picking 20 all-time arcade game classics is a nightmarish task, not simply because of the almost endless array of titles available to choose from, but because of all the really good ones you have to omit. Space Invader Here then, are the titles that made the cut, either because they have had …

Giles Hill, 05 Mar 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7451_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/03/04/invader.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7451-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/05/01/dell_poweredge_m420_for_render_farms/</link><title>Dell's rapier-thin PowerEdge M420 to render Hobbits?</title><description>Dell's rapier-thin PowerEdge M420 to render Hobbits?

Dell has disclosed a few more details of the rapier-thin PowerEdge M420 server we spotted back in February. One of those details is that the server isn't literally rapier-thin. Baseball-bat thin is a better description, as we hope is conveyed in the photo at the bottom of this story. We took that snap at the new Dell Solutions …

Simon Sharwood, 01 May 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7451_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/gen_serverroom.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7451-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/08/12/defra_rural_payments_ibm/</link><title>Defra gifts £22m to payments quango</title><description>Defra gifts £22m to payments quango

An answer sneaked out in the last days before parliament’s summer recess raises questions as to just what the Department for the Environment, Food and Rural Affairs (Defra) is spending its ICT budget on. Because alongside a few tens of thousands spent on IT for sustainable development and animal health, and a slightly more …

Jane Fae Ozimek, 12 Aug 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7451_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7451-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/11/15/letters_1511/</link><title>IT projects collapse, space stations defunded and Dr. Who repells ex-pats?</title><description>IT projects collapse, space stations defunded and Dr. Who repells ex-pats?

If the volume of your correspondence is a true measure of the importance of a story then the world is in serious trouble. The most pressing issue this week was clearly the tipability of cows. Still, before we get to that, why don't we wander past a disintegrating government IT project and look at the broken bits? Which one? …

Lucy Sherriff, 15 Nov 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7451_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7451-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/11/02/ptea_prez_auction/</link><title>PETA prez sells herself on eBay</title><description>PETA prez sells herself on eBay

In the great tradition of "buy my services for a day and do with me what you will", the president of animal-hugging pressure group PETA is auctioning her services on eBay. The blurb explains: Here’s a unique chance to hire hands-on corporate administrator and founder Ingrid Newkirk, president of People for the Ethical …

Lester Haines, 02 Nov 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7451_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7451-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/06/02/bird_flu/</link><title>Bird flu: we're all going to die</title><description>Bird flu: we're all going to die

The theme of the person awaking from a deep sleep or coma to find a world utterly changed is a popular one in science fiction. From John Wyndham's book The Day of The Triffids through The Omega Man to the recent film 28 Days Later, the trope of the man arising from his hospital bed to find that nothing is as it was has become …

Charles Arthur, 02 Jun 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7451_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7451-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/1998/08/13/mindrollers_beware_minkies_flying_out/</link><title>Mindrollers beware, minkies flying out of our bitt</title><description>Mindrollers beware, minkies flying out of our bitt

Just say no, Intel. Some strange but true facts emerge about Mendocino. It's the preferred drug of choice in the film Spinal Tap, described there as Mendocino Rocket Fuel. Worse (or better?) than that, the town of Mendocino is where the late lamented Lucille Ball was born... An employee of Intel Brazil -- of all places -- we …

Mike Magee, 13 Aug 1998</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7451_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>