<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7456">gps reviews</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:12:06" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7456-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/05/apples_smart_dock_patent_filing_makes_siri_your_new_roommate/</link><title>Apple's 'Smart Dock' patent filing makes Siri your new roommate</title><description>Apple's 'Smart Dock' patent filing makes Siri your new roommate

Apple has filed a patent for a "Smart Dock" that essentially extends the range and expands the capabilities of its iOS Siri voice recognition, request, and command feature, giving the somewhat dim young thing a greater role in your home life. The US Patent and Trademark Office application, entitled "Smart Dock for Activating a …

Rik Myslewski, 05 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7456_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/12/05/siri_logo.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7456-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/12/31/2012_review/</link><title>2012 in tech: Apple up the Cook without a paddle, ARM, slab wars... and MORE</title><description>2012 in tech: Apple up the Cook without a paddle, ARM, slab wars... and MORE

Great Britain reminded the world who invented the web at London 2012 Olympics, Apple cocked up its maps, Microsoft returned to hardware with Surface, we saw a rise of the machines on Wall Street and many of us rubbed our hands with glee as Facebook IPO's deflated. This was the last 12 months in technology. So put the in-laws on …

Gavin Clarke, 31 Dec 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7456_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/12/27/berner_lee_olympics_opening_ceremony.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7456-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/12/26/ten_technology_cockups_2012/</link><title>Ten… top tech cock-ups of 2012</title><description>Ten… top tech cock-ups of 2012

The past year provided us with some wonderful tales of innovation and expertise, but we all like to see a car crash as much as success story, right? So here's a roundup of the most colossal cock-ups of the last 12 months, including face-plants by Google, Facebook, Apple, and others who succumbed to that most universal of human …

Iain Thomson, 26 Dec 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7456_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/12/25/dunce.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7456-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/12/13/google_maps_back_to_iphone/</link><title>Google maps app is BACK on iPhones, fanbois spared death</title><description>Google maps app is BACK on iPhones, fanbois spared death

Google's maps app for iPhones, iPads and iPods is back less than three months after Apple booted it out of the iOS platform. In that period, the Cupertino giant publicly apologised for replacing its rival's mapping application with its own shoddy satnav-like software; the top exec behind Apple's crap map app, Scott Forstall, …

Anna Leach, 13 Dec 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7456_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7456-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/11/23/review_samsung_google_nexus_10_android_tablet/</link><title>Samsung Google Nexus 10 tablet review</title><description>Samsung Google Nexus 10 tablet review

Why would you buy a tablet other than an iPad? Obviously, some don’t care for Apple’s locked-in system and others like the way users can dig more deeply into the workings of Android. Good enough reasons, sure, but the truth is that until the day dawns when a tablet is of comparable specification, but substantially cheaper than …

David Phelan, 23 Nov 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7456_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/11/22/samsung_google_nexus_10_android_tablet_132x200.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7456-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/11/08/apple_ipad_4_wifi_only_review/</link><title>Apple iPad 4 Wi-Fi only tablet review</title><description>Apple iPad 4 Wi-Fi only tablet review

I didn’t get the iPad at first. When the tablet was first announced, I was interested but couldn’t see the value to me. I had an e-book reader, I had a phone on which I could watch films while travelling and listen to music, and I had a laptop for everything else. Why, I wondered, did I need a tablet too? I was happy to take …

Tony Smith, 08 Nov 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7456_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/03/08/ipad3_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7456-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/09/07/review_mio_spirit_695_lm_satnav/</link><title>Mio Spirit 695 LM satnav review</title><description>Mio Spirit 695 LM satnav review

These be tough times for satnav makers when, for under £100, you can pick up a good 4in smartphone like the Huawei Ascend G300 which comes with Google’s ever-evolving and improving free navigation, and even entry-level eight grand motors, like VW’s new Up!, feature low-cost optional navigation packages. To compete satnav makers …

Alun Taylor, 07 Sep 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7456_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/05/mio_spirit_695_lm_satnav_75.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7456-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/09/04/review_nokia_asha_311_series_40_phone/</link><title>Nokia Asha 311 budget smartphone review</title><description>Nokia Asha 311 budget smartphone review

Nokia’s smartphone sales may be in the toilet at the moment but it still flogs a fair number of handsets under the Asha brand of feature phones. Newest to the ranks is the Asha 311 which looks and behaves a bit like a smartphone but has a far lower purchase price – around £100 unlocked and SIM-free. Nokia Asha 311 budget …

Alun Taylor, 04 Sep 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7456_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/nokia_asha_311_budget_smartphone.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7456-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/08/14/review_asus_transformer_pad_infinity_tf700t_64gb_android_tablet/</link><title>Asus Transformer Pad Infinity 64GB Android tablet review</title><description>Asus Transformer Pad Infinity 64GB Android tablet review

When it comes to tablets, it seems Asus is on a bit of a roll. In my estimation, its Transformer Pad is the best value 10-incher on the market and, lest we forget the company makes the altogether excellent Nexus 7 for Google. There is no sign of Asus resting on its laurels either, if its latest Transformer device is anything to …

Alun Taylor, 14 Aug 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7456_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/08/13/asus_transformer_pad_infinity_64gb_android_tablet_75.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7456-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/07/31/mitt_romney_vp_app/</link><title>Romney promises to announce VP choice via mobile app</title><description>Romney promises to announce VP choice via mobile app

Republican presidential nominee Mitt Romney has yet to announce his choice for vice president, but when he does, he says smartphone users will be the first to hear about it. On Tuesday, Romney's official campaign website unveiled Mitt's VP, an app that promises to send a push alert to Android and iOS devices as soon as the …

Neil McAllister, 31 Jul 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7456_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>