<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7457">the music man lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:27:32" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7457-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/10/neil_young_touts_mp3_player_thats_no_piece_of_crap/</link><title>Neil Young touts MP3 player that's no Piece of Crap</title><description>Neil Young touts MP3 player that's no Piece of Crap

Decades of performing may have left Neil Young somewhat shy of the hearing of a 20-year-old, but the poor quality of MP3 still irritates the crazy horse enough to try and do something about it. Meet PonoMusic, which Young hopes will “unleash” all the unheard detail that MP3 (or even, if you believe what's on the company's site, …

Richard Chirgwin, 10 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7457_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/06/airmec_frequency_control_knob.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7457-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/01/31/rip_barry/</link><title>John Barry dies at 77</title><description>John Barry dies at 77

Composer John Barry has died at the age of 77, following an illustrious career which encompassed work on The Ipcress File, Midnight Cowboy, Zulu, Born Free and Dances With Wolves. His family announced in a statement: "It is with great sadness that the family of composer John Barry announce his passing on the 30th of January 2011 …

Lester Haines, 31 Jan 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7457_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7457-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/01/06/swat_drama/</link><title>SWAT team besieges Illinois school in 'butt dialling' incident</title><description>SWAT team besieges Illinois school in 'butt dialling' incident

An Illinois man prompted a full-scale SWAT intervention on Monday afternoon by inadvertently "butt-dialling" his wife, who quickly became convinced the "garbled" call was evidence he was being held hostage. The unnamed chap was driving home from his job at Carleton Washburne School in Winnetka when "his touch screen phone …

Lester Haines, 06 Jan 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7457_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7457-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/06/21/mood_music/</link><title>Getting women's phone numbers a matter of mood music</title><description>Getting women's phone numbers a matter of mood music

It's official: if you want to extract a woman's phone number, then picking the right soundtrack for the attempt will significantly increase your chances of scoring. That's according to French psychologists, who found that an "average-looking man" doubled his chances of success when the object of his desire had been softened up …

Lester Haines, 21 Jun 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7457_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7457-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/05/25/stupid_and_smart_iphone_apps/</link><title>iPhone apps - the 10 smartest and the 10 stupidest</title><description>iPhone apps - the 10 smartest and the 10 stupidest

The soon-to-be-released iPhone 3.0 software will offer a slew of new capabilities to iPhone developers. With that sea change in mind, we thought now would be a good time to take a look at the highs and lows of the current crop of apps for the iPhone and iPod touch. Not merely the best and worst, but rather two Reg-ratified Top …

Rik Myslewski, 25 May 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7457_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7457-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/04/16/dagger_danger/</link><title>Jamaica cracks down on 'daggering' after broken todger upswing</title><description>Jamaica cracks down on 'daggering' after broken todger upswing

Jamaican doctors have warned of the dangers of daggering, after being presented with a forest of fractured penises over the last year. According to reports, daggering appears to be either a bizarre sexual practice or a music and dance craze. Or possibly both at the same time, if these videos are any thing to go by. Either way, …

Joe Fay, 16 Apr 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7457_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7457-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/03/05/sarah_lacy_yahoo/</link><title>Yahoo! deflects Microsoft bid with iPhone dominatrix</title><description>Yahoo! deflects Microsoft bid with iPhone dominatrix

Shortly before nightfall, the small man emerged from his house, checked on his goats and prayed. His most pressing plea to the higher power? Stop the clowns from scaring his children and stop his children from scaring the goats - Julio Stantore, The Diving Bell and the Cabrito Buffet A number of organs today filled their pages …

Otto Z. Stern, 05 Mar 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7457_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7457-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/08/10/pearl_jam_censorship/</link><title>AT&amp;T censors Pearl Jam's anti-Bush sing-along</title><description>AT&amp;T censors Pearl Jam's anti-Bush sing-along

AT&amp;T has apologized for the censorship of lyrics that were critical of US President George W. Bush during a webcast of a performance by rock band Pearl Jam at a recent Lollapalooza festival. During a performance of the song "Daughter" on Sunday in Chicago, the band segued into an improvised version of Pink Floyd's "Another …

Dan Goodin, 10 Aug 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7457_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7457-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/12/22/iptv_future/</link><title>IPTV/VoD: Fast forward to Christmas future</title><description>IPTV/VoD: Fast forward to Christmas future

It's the Friday before Christmas. The very first thing I hear at 6am is the latest Crazy Frog jingle at full volume that's been remotely programmed into my alarm clock as a hilariously mischievous prank by my girlfriend. I'm tempted to smash the thing, but that would mean buying the fifth one this year. At least it's nice and …

Alex Cameron, 22 Dec 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7457_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/gen_sgi.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7457-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/06/14/army_investigates_singing_squaddy/</link><title>US Marines investigate singing squaddie</title><description>US Marines investigate singing squaddie

The US army is investigating whether a video which purports to show a serving Marine singing and playing the guitar on YouTube is genuine. The clip appears to show a chubby US soldier playing acoustic guitar and singing into a microphone in front of an audience. The man's voice might upset Simon Cowell, but it is hardly the …

John Oates, 14 Jun 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7457_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>