<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7459">little johnny jokes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:48:35" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7459-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/09/01/letters_0109/</link><title>Banning things, thought crimes, and dangerous guitarring</title><description>Banning things, thought crimes, and dangerous guitarring

We've got a bumper letters bag today, covering an almost ludicrously diverse range of topics. We've got renegade planets, flaming guitars, pornography legislation and literal pontification. So, get a cup of tea, settle down and enjoy. We'll start with the very popular news that the record industry has decided that tabulature …

Lucy Sherriff, 01 Sep 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7459_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7459-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/12/12/otto_linux_flyletters/</link><title>Linux zealots proud to be as miserable as planes</title><description>Linux zealots proud to be as miserable as planes

What's the difference between an open source zealot and a 747? That's how one of the more famous jokes in the technology industry begins, and we explored the underpinnings of the laugher in my astonishing column penned last month. Slow planes stink. Crap pieces of open source code stink just as much. All it took was me pointing …

Otto Z. Stern, 12 Dec 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7459_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7459-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/09/23/letters_2309/</link><title>Martian snowboarders download imaginary nipples</title><description>Martian snowboarders download imaginary nipples

A very musical haul in today's Letters round-up. That tends to spill over into questions of civil liberties and freedoms, and we've got a few thoughts on those subjects too. In between the issues, some of you were upset that we teased Nokia about selling its billionth phone in Nigeria, others were less than impressed with …

Lucy Sherriff, 23 Sep 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7459_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>