<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7463">hollywood actress</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:00:48" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7463-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/08/guccifer_webmail_hacker/</link><title>Prez Bush email hacker Guccifer is BACK: A-list celebs' inboxes 'raided'</title><description>Prez Bush email hacker Guccifer is BACK: A-list celebs' inboxes 'raided'

A webmail hacker called Guccifer – most famous for raiding the email inboxes of former US president George H W Bush's family – has been exceptional busy of late. Crime news website The Smoking Gun reports that Guccifer has handed over a cache of documents – which, we're told, reveal that he broke into the private email accounts …

John Leyden, 08 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7463_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/28/balaclava_thief_burglar.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7463-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/01/28/doctor_who_twit_jacked/</link><title>Spammers joyride Doctor Who's Twitter TARDIS, turn man into Shirley Temple</title><description>Spammers joyride Doctor Who's Twitter TARDIS, turn man into Shirley Temple

Yet another Doctor Who star's Twitter account has been hijacked to tout dodgy diet pills: this time it's Colin Baker, who played the sixth incarnation of the hero time lord. Baker's @SawbonesHex account was taken for a joyride just a fortnight after the Twitter feed of actress Karen Gillan, who played Doctor Who companion Amy …

John Leyden, 28 Jan 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7463_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7463-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/01/11/razzie_nominations/</link><title>Razzies set to torpedo pop minx Rihanna's Battleship</title><description>Razzies set to torpedo pop minx Rihanna's Battleship

This year's Razzies look set to be a head-to-head between Battleship and Twilight: Breaking Dawn Part 2 to see which movie can walk away with the most gongs for serious celluloid undertainment. Rihanna in Battleship Rihanna: Good Girl Gone Bad, Bad Actress The annual celebration of the cinematically dire sees seven …

Lester Haines, 11 Jan 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7463_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7463-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/11/02/bond_quiz/</link><title>Bond fans: Test your 007 trivia, now!</title><description>Bond fans: Test your 007 trivia, now!

As the dust settles on on our recent round of Bond polls - in which readers voted Ernst Stavro Blofeld, Sean Connery and Casino Royale the vilest Bond villain, the ultimate movie Bond and the best Bond film, respectively - we're offering fans the chance to see if they've really got what it takes to hold the coveted 00 number. …

Lester Haines, 02 Nov 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7463_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7463-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/05/23/jailed_facebook_brit_targeted_bieber_girlfriend/</link><title>Jailed Facebook hack Brit targeted Justin Bieber's girlfriend</title><description>Jailed Facebook hack Brit targeted Justin Bieber's girlfriend

A British man jailed for a year after hacking into a private Facebook account targeted Justin Bieber's actress-turned-singer girlfriend, it has emerged. Gareth Crosskey, 21, of Lancing in West Sussex, was sentenced to 12 months behind bars by London's Southwark Crown Court last week. Crosskey had pleaded guilty to two computer …

John Leyden, 23 May 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7463_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7463-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/03/21/new_dr_who_companion/</link><title>Dr Who scores new companion from Emmerdale</title><description>Dr Who scores new companion from Emmerdale

Former Emmerdale actress Jenna-Louise Coleman has been selected to play the latest assistant to Gallifreyan Time Lord Dr Who, beginning with the 50th anniversary Christmas special at the end of the year. Coleman is best known for her four-year stint as Jasmine Thomas, the recalcitrant school-girl turned journalist who battered …

Iain Thomson, 21 Mar 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7463_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7463-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/11/30/hedy_lamarr_invented_spread_spectrum_frequency_hopping_details_new_book/</link><title>Hollywood siren invented key phone tech TRUE</title><description>Hollywood siren invented key phone tech TRUE

Here's a fascinating notion: that sultry Hollywood sex goddess Hedy Lamarr invented radio technology employed by every mobile phone in use today. The tech in question is the notion of spread-spectrum frequency hopping, a concept devised by Lamarr during World War II after learning German U-Boats had sunk a cruise ship and …

Tony Smith, 30 Nov 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7463_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/11/30/hl_4.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7463-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/11/02/scarlett_johansson_hacker_denial/</link><title>Accused Hollywood hacker does about face, pleads not guilty</title><description>Accused Hollywood hacker does about face, pleads not guilty

A Florida man has pleaded not guilty to charges he broke into the email accounts of actresses Scarlett Johansson and Mila Kunis, and as many as 50 other celebrities, and made off with nude photos and personal information. Christopher Chaney, 35, of Jacksonville, Florida, denied the allegations contained in a 26-count indictment …

Dan Goodin, 02 Nov 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7463_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7463-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/07/12/marine_kunis_date/</link><title>US Marine gets date with Meg Griffin on YouTube</title><description>US Marine gets date with Meg Griffin on YouTube

A US Marine serving in Afghanistan has successfully obtained a date with Hollywood star Mila Kunis by asking her out in a YouTube video. Sergeant Scott Moore can be seen below making his digital move on the actress, famous as the voice of Meg Griffin in Family Guy and as Mona Sax in gamebased offering Max Payne. Kunis was also …

Team Register, 12 Jul 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7463_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7463-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/03/30/berlusconi_clooney/</link><title>Berlusconi calls George Clooney to his defence</title><description>Berlusconi calls George Clooney to his defence

Silvio Berlusconi has named George Clooney as a defence witness in his forthcoming trial for sleeping with an under-aged prostitute, Reuters reports. The lively Italian PM is accused of bedding 17-year-old Moroccan night-club dancer Karima el Mahroug, aka "Ruby the Heartstealer", at a "bunga bunga" party at his villa near Milan …

Lester Haines, 30 Mar 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7463_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>