<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7470">is sugar poison</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:23:28" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7470-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/03/26/us_smart_meters/</link><title>Americans resort to padlocking their dumb meters</title><description>Americans resort to padlocking their dumb meters

Campaigners across America are resorting to padlocks and metal cages to protect their 'leccy meters, convinced that the smart versions will damage their health. The Georgia Senate is busy passing a bill allowing customers to opt out of having a smart meter fitted, and without cost, but some of the locals are concerned that while …

Bill Ray, 26 Mar 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7470_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7470-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/01/10/tax_on_soft_drinks/</link><title>Profs call for harsh taxes on sweet carbonated beverages</title><description>Profs call for harsh taxes on sweet carbonated beverages

Medical scientists in San Francisco have sent a chill wind blowing through the IT industry as they issue a call for swingeing taxes on "soda, fruit punch, sweet tea, sports drinks, and other sweetened beverages". A collection of health profs and other researchers led by Kirsten Bibbins-Domingo (associate professor of medicine …

Lewis Page, 10 Jan 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7470_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7470-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/11/16/swine_flu_spam/</link><title>Spammers aim to profit from swine flu pandemic</title><description>Spammers aim to profit from swine flu pandemic

Russian cybercrooks have laid the groundwork needed to build a business cashing in on swine flu panic-buying. Tamiflu sales from dodgy unlicensed pharmaceutical websites are being promoted through spam email, search engine manipulation and a variety of other underhand techniques. Web affiliates, commonly based in Russia where …

John Leyden, 16 Nov 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7470_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7470-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2004/02/20/are_apples_healthier_than_pepsi/</link><title>Are Apples healthier than Pepsi?</title><description>Are Apples healthier than Pepsi?

Fortunately, in addition to the tonnage of email we received about the recent coverage of the Swastika-removing patch issued by Microsoft, there are other issues which you, our readers, have taken the time to write to us about. In a week where spam seemed to be everywhere – inboxes and headlines alike – the following seems like …

Lucy Sherriff, 20 Feb 2004</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7470_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7470-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2004/01/14/stob_why_men_buy_blue/</link><title>Stob: Why men buy blue pills</title><description>Stob: Why men buy blue pills

(Previously: Sam "The Spam" Osborne, the notorious spamillionaire, has improbably represented himself as a philanthropist.) Time for the interview proper. Did he admit spamming was immoral? "Spamming? Immoral?" He was amazed. "You’ve seen my operation. I’m providing a public service!" In what sense, I wondered, was it a …

Verity Stob, 14 Jan 2004</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7470_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7470-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2002/07/16/nai_sweetens_mcafee_com_bid/</link><title>NAI sweetens McAfee.com bid</title><description>NAI sweetens McAfee.com bid

ComputerWire: IT Industry Intelligence Network Associates Inc said yesterday it is prepared to raise the amount it is offering to buy the 25% of McAfee.com Corp it does not already own by 15.5% in order to get approval from a Special Committee of the anti-virus firm's board. The company said it is prepared to offer 0.9 NAI …

ComputerWire, 16 Jul 2002</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7470_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>