<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7472">python re tutorial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:31:24" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7472-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/25/review_electric_imp_internet_of_things_card/</link><title>Little devil: Electric Imp is an Internet of Things Wi-Fi PC-ON-AN-SD-CARD</title><description>Little devil: Electric Imp is an Internet of Things Wi-Fi PC-ON-AN-SD-CARD

Most products’ origins are prosaic: an inventor or a suit spots a gap in the market and attempts to fill it. Other products, however, have rather more bizarre beginnings. A case in point: Electric Imp came about because co-founder Hugo Fiennes wanted to connect the lights in his new bathroom to the internet. That’s just the kind …

Tony Smith, 25 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7472_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/20/imp_8.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7472-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/11/review_raspberry_pi_fuze_case_and_kit/</link><title>RETRO-GASM: The Fuze electronics kit for the Raspberry Pi</title><description>RETRO-GASM: The Fuze electronics kit for the Raspberry Pi

Back in the day of the board computers of the late 1970s - your Scrumpi, your Nascom 1, your UK-101 et al - it was customary to build a case for it out of wood. If you were a better equipped "constructor" - what we used to call "makers" in those days - you’d build a box out of metal. Folk like Tangerine offered optional cases, …

Tony Smith, 11 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7472_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/06/fuze_8.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7472-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/04/18/feature_getting_into_the_raspberry_pi_books/</link><title>Manual override: Raspberry Pi beginners' books</title><description>Manual override: Raspberry Pi beginners' books

The Raspberry Pi has been out for just over a year now. It has undergone a couple of revisions during that time, most recently around October 2012, but a short while ago I decided it was time I ought to try it out and see what the diminutive, Linux-running micro can do. Entirely coincidentally, the Raspberry Pi Owners’ Workshop …

Tony Smith, 18 Apr 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7472_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/06/pi.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7472-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/09/21/something_for_the_weekend_digital_photo_freedom/</link><title>Hapless Kate topless, toothless law useless</title><description>Hapless Kate topless, toothless law useless

I rush back from town mid-afternoon in order to participate in an online conference, or what they prefer me to call a "webinar". At home, I discover that my son is sitting at his computer. It’s a school day. This might not be such a bad thing: since his school doesn’t teach about computers any more - see 'Emotional Baggage' - it …

Alistair Dabbs, 21 Sep 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7472_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/04/05/sww_5.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7472-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/05/05/google_web_app_security_course/</link><title>Google tutorial lets developers play malicious hacker</title><description>Google tutorial lets developers play malicious hacker

Google has released a free online tutorial that gives developers the chance to play the role of malicious hacker by exploiting real security bugs in a mock web application. The codelab is premised on a "small, cheesy web application" dubbed Jarlsberg that is chock-full of bugs that can be exploited to take down webservers, …

Dan Goodin, 05 May 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7472_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7472-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/10/06/dziuba_android/</link><title>Sergey Brin descends from Mount Sinai with Android API</title><description>Sergey Brin descends from Mount Sinai with Android API

If there's one thing that's never affected by economic downturn, it's the mobile handset market. This phenomenon is most evident at the underground parties and dive bars in San Francisco, where it is a well known yet unspoken tradition that in any given group of hipsters, the one with the cheapest phone must always buy the first …

Ted Dziuba, 06 Oct 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7472_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7472-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/11/01/learning_ruby_book_review/</link><title>Learning Ruby</title><description>Learning Ruby

To some, Ruby is going to take over the world. With prominent Java developers and propagandists jumping ship, there has seemed to be no stopping its momentum, particularly in web development. Part of the reason for the popularity with hackers (in the programming sense of the word), is that it's easy for a programmer in an …

Dr Pan Pantziarka, 01 Nov 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7472_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/03/chandef10.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7472-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/10/25/groovy_mysql/</link><title>Groovy way to MySQL</title><description>Groovy way to MySQL

A very traditional niche of scripting languages, (such as Perl, Python or Ruby), has been in the ad hoc manipulation of databases – from grabbing data, transforming it, performing bulk updates, right on through to full-on data migration projects that move data from one platform or RDBMS to another. Scripting languages are …

Dr Pan Pantziarka, 25 Oct 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7472_08_thumb.gif">http://regmedia.co.uk/2005/12/15/mysql_75.gif?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7472-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/07/05/old_new/</link><title>Old lamps for new</title><description>Old lamps for new

A couple of items in Reg Developer have prompted responses that continue a theme raised here before – that old software technologies that were developed years ago to solve perennial business management problems are still probably the best solution and should therefore be resuscitated - or perhaps unknowlingly re-invented. For …

Martin Banks, 05 Jul 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7472_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>