<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7475">software consultant work at home</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:45:52" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7475-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/25/from_corporate_to_startup_lessons_learned/</link><title>From corporate bod to startup star: The 10-month gig that changed everything</title><description>From corporate bod to startup star: The 10-month gig that changed everything

For pretty much my entire career as a techie (variously a developer, manager, and consultant) I’ve worked for very large, usually global, companies, most of them in the financial industry. A couple of years ago I decided I needed a break from that world. After taking some time off to de-stress and pursue a few personal projects …

Dave Mandl, 25 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7475_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2008/04/10/arrington_cigar.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7475-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/12/archaeologic_sinclair_ql/</link><title>Sinclair’s 1984 big shot at business: The QL is 30 years old</title><description>Sinclair’s 1984 big shot at business: The QL is 30 years old

In May 1983, Sinclair Research Managing Director Nigel Searle began briefing the press about the successful British micro maker’s next big release. It was 13 months after the company had launched the Spectrum and although that machine had become a huge success, punters and market-watchers were keen to hear about what Sinclair …

Tony Smith, 12 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7475_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/12/13/ql_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7475-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/09/17/20_years_of_the_apple_newton/</link><title>Stylus counsel: The rise and fall of the Apple Newton MessagePad</title><description>Stylus counsel: The rise and fall of the Apple Newton MessagePad

It will forever be remembered as the butt of a-thousand-and-one jokes about its poor handwriting recognition, but Apple’s MessagePad was bold in its conception. Its legacy is ARM’s conquest of the mobile microprocessor world. The company said on 8 August 1993: The Newton MessagePad is the first in a family of communications …

Tony Smith, 17 Sep 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7475_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/16/mp_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7475-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/08/02/ibm_cio_techie_among_techies/</link><title>IBM CIO's Great Refresh: No, Sales Guy, you can't JUST use DropBox</title><description>IBM CIO's Great Refresh: No, Sales Guy, you can't JUST use DropBox

She might be CIO of IBM, but Jeanette Horan is just like you: replacing Windows XP with Windows 7, ripping out Internet Explorer 6 and floating a growing amount of software on the cloud. She also has to contend with staffers begging her for the ability to share information using third-party sync 'n' share apps like DropBox. …

Gavin Clarke, 02 Aug 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7475_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/07/30/jeanette_horan.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7475-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/07/01/it_asset_management_five_constants/</link><title>The five constants of IT asset management</title><description>The five constants of IT asset management

Kylie Fowler got controversial when she spoke last month to an audience of asset management and configuration management professionals at the BCS CMSG Conference in London about the five constants she always encounters in her 10-plus years of working as an IT asset management consultant. While these constants may always hold …

Eira Hayward, 01 Jul 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7475_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/06/05/kylie_fowler_headshot.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7475-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/04/09/martin_hellawell_profile/</link><title>McDonalds-card-toting Softcat boss: I couldn't tell you how a computer works</title><description>McDonalds-card-toting Softcat boss: I couldn't tell you how a computer works

The much-lauded chairman of software reseller Softcat has carved out a high-flying career selling tech - but paradoxically Martin Hellawell can't explain how a computer computes nor the inner workings of a mainframe. Still wet behind the ears and straight out of uni in 1988, Hellawell made an inauspicious entry into the world of …

Paul Kunert, 09 Apr 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7475_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/04/08/martin_hellawell_olympics.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7475-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/03/27/geeks_guide_leo/</link><title>Blighty's revolutionary Cold War teashop computer - and Nigella Lawson</title><description>Blighty's revolutionary Cold War teashop computer - and Nigella Lawson

The Victorian offices were bulldozed long ago for a stack of flats and mirrored offices, and there's not a single indication to the significance of this site - or what happened here. This isn't the scene of a lost battle, and the bones of a missing Plantagenet king do not slumber beneath the car park serving the offices. Sixty- …

Gavin Clarke, 27 Mar 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7475_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/03/25/reading_tape_leo_ii_computer.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7475-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/01/28/the_oric_1_is_30_years_old/</link><title>The Oric-1 is 30</title><description>The Oric-1 is 30

The Oric-1, which was formally launched 30 years ago this week, was produced with one thing in mind: to take on Sir Clive Sinclair at his own game. “The Oric is a competitor for the Spectrum,” one of Oric developer Tangerine Computer Systems’ software team, Paul Kaufman, emphatically told members of the press. “We are convinced …

Tony Smith, 28 Jan 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7475_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/04/12/t8m_13.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7475-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/12/18/search_engines_we_have_known/</link><title>Search engines we have known ... before Google crushed them</title><description>Search engines we have known ... before Google crushed them

Remember when the internet was young, moving your bulky monitor was a two-person job and 1.4MB disks didn't look like a typo? Back then (most) people didn't have to choose which web search engine they were going to use: it came prepared by the operating system maker, such as Microsoft and MSN Search, or the folks you got your …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 18 Dec 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7475_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/12/17/altavvista2.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7475-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/11/28/peter_moore_iraq_interview_part_two/</link><title>Peter Moore: IT consultant, Iraq hostage - Part Two</title><description>Peter Moore: IT consultant, Iraq hostage - Part Two

When we last left IT consultant point Peter Moore, he had spent over a year in the hands of an Iraqi Shi'ite militia, being shuffled around from building to building as his captors sought to evade coalition forces. Moore spent much of his time chained, handcuffed, blindfolded, and separated from the four British guards with whom …

Iain Thomson, 28 Nov 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7475_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/11/28/bars.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>