<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7477">china bird flu</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:16:14" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7477-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/10/25/love_life_of_the_average_brit_on_statistics_day/</link><title>How average is your sex life?</title><description>How average is your sex life?

Last week was a fairly average week – and Wednesday a fairly average day. Hardly surprising, since Wednesday was actually World Statistics Day. This was, however, no ordinary statistics day. Sponsored by the UN, it was the very first such day, dedicated, according to the official site, to encouraging "the international community …

Jane Fae Ozimek, 25 Oct 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7477_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7477-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/02/05/bird_flu_arrives/</link><title>Hunt for bird flu source goes on</title><description>Hunt for bird flu source goes on

Government investigators are racing to uncover the source of the Suffolk bird flu outbreak which has seen 160,000 turkeys slaughtered in a mass cull expected to end this morning. Identifying the source of the virus is key to containing its further spread. Suspicion has naturally fallen on the most recent European appearance of …

Christopher Williams, 05 Feb 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7477_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7477-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/12/22/end_of_year_quiz/</link><title>El Reg presents the great End of Year Quiz</title><description>El Reg presents the great End of Year Quiz

The party's over, the lights are dim, and you're wondering whether to buy that bumper pack of Alka Seltzer. What to do with those last precious moments of the year? Just cast your mind back over the last 12 months and give your brain a workout in the Great Register Quiz. No deadlines, no prizes, no stamped addressed envelopes. …

John Oates, 22 Dec 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7477_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7477-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/11/06/bird_flu_gene/</link><title>Scientists collar bird flu's 'killer' gene</title><description>Scientists collar bird flu's 'killer' gene

Scientists in China report that they have identified the gene which determines the virulence of the H5N1, or bird flu, virus in poultry. The breakthrough could pave the way for new vaccines, the scientists claim. Some strains of H5N1 kill more than half those they infect, while others leave virtually all their victims standing …

Lucy Sherriff, 06 Nov 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7477_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7477-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/06/14/g8_bird_flu/</link><title>G8 warned not to be blinkered by bird flu</title><description>G8 warned not to be blinkered by bird flu

Scientists around the world have urged the G8 leaders not to get so caught up in the threat of bird flu that they divert their attention from the real global killers: TB, HIV/AIDS and malaria. The World Health Organisation (WHO) estimates that between them the three kill around six million people every year. An assemblage of …

Christopher Williams, 14 Jun 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7477_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7477-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/03/01/royal_soc_bird_flu/</link><title>Bird flu: your painful death not inevitable</title><description>Bird flu: your painful death not inevitable

A leading virus expert has said that anyone claiming a human pandemic of bird flu is inevitable "is saying more than they can possibly know". Sir John Skehel made his comments at the Royal Society in London, at the launch of the society's new joint investigation with the Academy of Medical Sciences into the science behind the …

Christopher Williams, 01 Mar 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7477_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7477-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/10/21/letters_2110/</link><title>Yellow dots a symptom of technology bird-flu?</title><description>Yellow dots a symptom of technology bird-flu?

Here's a weird thing we found out this week: if you are Cuban, and want to buy a mobile phone in Cuba, you need a foreigner to sign up for one for you. How's that for user-friendly? Almost as good as the Qatar city of Doha where, in the 1980's at least, you had to be a registered alcoholic in order to buy a drink: Exactly how …

Lucy Sherriff, 21 Oct 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7477_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7477-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/10/13/eu_bird_flu_outbreak/</link><title>Deadly bird flu strain confirmed in Turkey (the country)</title><description>Deadly bird flu strain confirmed in Turkey (the country)

A small outbreak of avian flu found in Turkish poultry has been confirmed as the deadly H5N1 strain, prompting EU health officials to warn of an impending pandemic. Meanwhile, bird flu has also been confirmed in ducks in Romania, although the strain has yet to be identified, according to the European Commission. The EU has …

Lucy Sherriff, 13 Oct 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7477_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7477-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/10/07/dell_linux_tough/</link><title>Reg readers take the Dell 'Open-source PC' challenge</title><description>Reg readers take the Dell 'Open-source PC' challenge

Once upon a time, Michael Dell heard about this thing called Linux. The open-source operating system promised to sweep across PCs all over the world. Ever the low-cost, high-volume guy, Mikey figured he could sell a heck of lot of systems with Linux, and set to work pumping companies such as Red Hat and Eazel with money from …

Ashlee Vance, 07 Oct 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7477_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/03/chandef8.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7477-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/08/26/letters_2608/</link><title>Fat is a technologist issue</title><description>Fat is a technologist issue

Let's kick off with an easy one. How fat is fat? New figures from the states suggest fat is really quite fat and likely to get fatter, as obesity levels soar. However, the ever sceptical Reg reader is not taking this kind of statistic waving lying down. Not when there are generalisations to be made, and bizarre experiments to …

Lucy Sherriff, 26 Aug 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7477_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>