<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7478">protect kids online</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:30:15" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7478-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/28/media_watchdog_claims_44000_kids_exposed_to_online_smut/</link><title>Say WHAT? ATVOD claims 44k Brit primary school kids look at smut online each month</title><description>Say WHAT? ATVOD claims 44k Brit primary school kids look at smut online each month

Online age verification is the Tory-led coalition government's latest obsession, after it lobbied hard for flaccid network-level filtering to be introduced by the UK's biggest ISPs over the course of the last few years. To support Whitehall's latest crusade against smut, Britain's video on demand services regulator is calling …

Kelly Fiveash, 28 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7478_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/13/kid_f_off.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7478-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/13/uk_kids_to_be_schooled_in_cyber_security/</link><title>UK.gov to train up 11-year-old cyberwarriors</title><description>UK.gov to train up 11-year-old cyberwarriors

British schoolkids as young as 11 will be trained in cyber security as part of a new drive to protect the UK from digital threats. The government will produce learning materials designed to get 11- to 14-year-olds up to speed on cyber security. If the kids show a willingness to strap on a keyboard and fight in some foreign …

Jasper Hamill, 13 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7478_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/11/10/film_5.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7478-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/31/end_of_year_review_2013/</link><title>Glassholes, snapt**ts, #blabbergasms, selfies and PRISM: The Reg's review of 2013</title><description>Glassholes, snapt**ts, #blabbergasms, selfies and PRISM: The Reg's review of 2013

"Selfie" is the Oxford English Dictionary's word of the year. There's nothing new about a "selfie" - it's a self-portrait - but a perfect storm of social networks and smartphones has given popularity to a word and an act even world leaders feel it's OK to do on really serious occasions. In keeping with a long tradition here at …

Gavin Clarke, 31 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7478_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/03/09/google_glass.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7478-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/23/bt_changes_wording_of_education_filter_after_complaints/</link><title>BT tweaks WORDING of sex-ed web block after complaints</title><description>BT tweaks WORDING of sex-ed web block after complaints

BT has adjusted the wording of one of its web-filtering categories, following The Register's story late on Friday when the telecoms giant admitted that UK parents who don't want their kids to seek advice about their sexuality online could block access over its network. However, while BT continues to offer that control to its …

Kelly Fiveash, 23 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7478_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2010/10/27/kids_laptops_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7478-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/19/network_level_filters_and_how_ofcom_plans_to_get_involved/</link><title>World+dog: Network level filters block LEGIT sex ed sites. Ofcom: Meh</title><description>World+dog: Network level filters block LEGIT sex ed sites. Ofcom: Meh

Inevitably, as network-level filters are switched on by Britain's biggest telcos, reports are suggesting that the systems are wrongly blocking sex education websites. BSkyB, BT and TalkTalk have each said publicly and repeatedly that the technology is not perfect and relies on interaction from parents who want to protect their …

Kelly Fiveash, 19 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7478_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2010/12/03/kevin_the_teenager_48x48.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7478-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/17/bt_parental_controls_will_block_proxies_and_anonymiser_sites/</link><title>No anon pr0n for you: BT's network-level 'smut' filters will catch proxy servers too</title><description>No anon pr0n for you: BT's network-level 'smut' filters will catch proxy servers too

BT's new network-level nudie no-no filter system will block access to sites promoting proxies and anonymisers, The Register has learned. However, the one-time national telco has insisted that it won't choke VPN connections over its network now that its Parental Controls service, using DNS lookup technology, is in place. On …

Kelly Fiveash, 17 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7478_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/12/16/bridget_jones_kickers.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7478-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/16/end_xmas_prezzie_indecision_misery_with_el_regs_lastminute_gift_guide/</link><title>Excise Xmas prezzie indecision MISERY with El Reg’s gift guide²</title><description>Excise Xmas prezzie indecision MISERY with El Reg’s gift guide²

Christmas is special. When else will you spending lots of money you don’t have buying things they don’t deserve for people you don’t like? That said, we all grudgingly accept that you may want to buy some presents for people this year – bah humbug – even if you haven’t an earthly what to buy them. To help you out, we’ve come up …

Nigel Whitfield, 16 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7478_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/08/16/red_gift.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7478-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/13/bt_network_level_filter_lands/</link><title>BT network-level STOCKINGs-n-suspenders KILLER arrives in time for Xmas</title><description>BT network-level STOCKINGs-n-suspenders KILLER arrives in time for Xmas

BT has flicked the switch on its promised network-level filter system in a move to swerve regulatory meddling from Whitehall. Next year, it will nag existing customers to make a choice about what content they want access to via BT's broadband network. The system will censor clumps of the web - such as pornography and self-harm …

Kelly Fiveash, 13 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7478_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/05/13/chelsea_charms.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7478-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/18/child_abuse_images_microsoft_google_search/</link><title>Google, Microsoft to drop child sex abuse from basic web search</title><description>Google, Microsoft to drop child sex abuse from basic web search

Google and Microsoft have bent to political pressure in the UK – by agreeing to tweak their search engines to not only make it a little harder for sickos to find child abuse images online, but to also prevent regulatory intervention. UK Prime Minister David Cameron said that "significant progress" had been made since the summer …

Kelly Fiveash, 18 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7478_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/04/03/child_catcher.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7478-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/15/bskyb_installs_network_level_filters/</link><title>Murdoch stands between your kids and filth with BSkyB network-level SHIELD</title><description>Murdoch stands between your kids and filth with BSkyB network-level SHIELD

BSkyB's network-level filters are now in place 10 months after it first confirmed plans to follow TalkTalk's strategy that allows subscribers to censor large lumps of the web. And it looks like, at least for now, existing subscribers who wish to avoid the smut 'n' security block will be unable to opt out altogether, and will …

Kelly Fiveash, 15 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7478_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/15/surf_for_porn.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>