<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7482">popular twitter stars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:46:54" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7482-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/04/ellen_degeneres_samsung_iphone/</link><title>Oscars backer Samsung can't catch a break: Host Ellen snaps stars on iOS</title><description>Oscars backer Samsung can't catch a break: Host Ellen snaps stars on iOS

High fives all round, no doubt, at Oscars sponsor Samsung after the awards-night host Ellen Degeneres repeatedly mentioned the chaebol on stage and used a Galaxy S5 during the show to tweet the world's most popular selfie. But The Reg wonders how the South Korean electronics giant reacted when it realized the comedian was …

Shaun Nichols, 04 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7482_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/04/18/apple_samsung.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7482-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/09/02/science_fiction_titan_frederik_pohl_dies_aged_93/</link><title>Science fiction titan Frederik Pohl dies, aged 93</title><description>Science fiction titan Frederik Pohl dies, aged 93

Science fiction Grand Master Frederik Pohl has died, aged 93. Pohl was one of last survivors of Science Fiction's “golden age” of the late 1930s and early 1940s, a time when he contributed to and edited pulp fiction magazines. He was also an important figure in the emergence of fandom, founding the “Futurians”. A contemporary …

Simon Sharwood, 02 Sep 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7482_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/02/frederik_pohl.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7482-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/12/25/esports_career/</link><title>Red-faced, sweating and still in your chair: Welcome to eSports</title><description>Red-faced, sweating and still in your chair: Welcome to eSports

Video games are believed by many to be a waste of time - but this is something consistently being challenged by the people who love them. And despite the fact that video games just can't seem shrug off the label of "just for kids", new research (PDF) would suggest that you're never too old for them. And as the debate over the …

Trevor Pott and Josh Folland, 25 Dec 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7482_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/12/20/league_of_legends.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7482-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/07/27/olympic_impostors_flood_social_networks/</link><title>Twitter impostors stop at NOTHING to drag athletes through mud</title><description>Twitter impostors stop at NOTHING to drag athletes through mud

Malware-slingers and mischief-makers are ramping up the creation of fake celebrity profiles on social networks in time for the start of the Olympics on Friday. El Reg spoke to "reputation managers" of the stars about the problem. Some of the fake profiles are harmless while others link to pictures of strippers and escorts and …

John Leyden, 27 Jul 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7482_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/twitter_t.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7482-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/03/23/el_reg_forums_faq/</link><title>El Reg Forums FAQ</title><description>El Reg Forums FAQ

First of all Read the house rules. &lt; Forums FAQ Badges In November 2012, The Register introduced gold, silver and bronze badges for commentards, along with forum privileges for each badge. The qualifying thresholds for badges are: Bronze More than one year members and more than 100 posts in the last 12 months. Silver …

Drew Cullen, 23 Mar 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7482_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7482-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/02/01/register_comments_guidelines/</link><title>The Register Comments Guidelines, 2012</title><description>The Register Comments Guidelines, 2012

The Register operates a hybrid moderation policy. Here's how it works. The vast majority of comments will appear on the site automatically. This is because we trust you to follow the house rules. But just in case ... we have a mechanism for readers to report comments. The moderators will continue to deal with any comments and/ …

Joe Fay, 01 Feb 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7482_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/01/17/reg_sidey_vulture.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7482-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/11/24/gavin_rotheray_interview/</link><title>We talk to Moon designer about ULTIMATE sci-fi ship</title><description>We talk to Moon designer about ULTIMATE sci-fi ship

Gavin Rothery was visual effects supervisor on the British sci-fi smash Moon, and has been a creative force on a welter of hit video games, and so has a lot to say on the subject of spacecraft design. So much, in fact, that I couldn’t bear to just cut a couple of quotes into my article on sci-fi spaceship design. So, here, in …

Michael Moran, 24 Nov 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7482_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7482-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/07/04/bbc_twitter_talent_ban_mulled/</link><title>BBC mulls talent Twitter ban to prevent storyline spoilers</title><description>BBC mulls talent Twitter ban to prevent storyline spoilers

A ban on the use of Twitter and other public forums is being considered by BBC bosses, in an effort to prevent stars and writers from talking about details of the broadcaster's confidential upcoming productions online. The Guardian, which cites senior sources, reports that BBC execs are mulling over the possibility of tweaking …

Kelly Fiveash, 04 Jul 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7482_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7482-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/04/01/silicon_roundabout_the_register_guide/</link><title>The Register Guide to London's Silicon Roundabout Tech Startups</title><description>The Register Guide to London's Silicon Roundabout Tech Startups

Prime Minister David Cameron hails them as the young, wealth-creating foundation of tomorrow's economy. But who are they? Here's El Reg's guide to the stars of London's vibrant tech startup scene - whose drive and energy is already ripping up the rules of government, and traditional profit-loss accounting methods. The Serial …

Team Register, 01 Apr 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7482_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7482-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/09/20/parc_40th_anniversary/</link><title>PARC turns 40: mice, money, and the new interwebs</title><description>PARC turns 40: mice, money, and the new interwebs

Mention "Xerox" and "PARC," and you'll likely be greeted by a rolling of the eyes or an off-hand comment like: "Didn't they invent the mouse and let Microsoft make all the money?" That happened to me more than once when I mentioned I was heading to the Palo Alto Research Center to interview a few folks for the iconic institution …

Gavin Clarke, 20 Sep 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7482_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>