<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7483">facebook paying?</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:58:27" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7483-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/09/review_dell_wyse_cloud_connect_android_ultrathin_client/</link><title>Dell Wyse Cloud Connect: Pocket Android desktop</title><description>Dell Wyse Cloud Connect: Pocket Android desktop

When somebody hands you a dongle-sized computer, you might, for a moment, be impressed. But when they then put it in a bag with a Bluetooth keyboard and mouse and suggest you find a monitor somewhere, you might wonder what exactly it is they are trying to sell you. Dell Wyse Cloud Connect Android dongle Mini USB – fancy seeing …

Bob Dormon, 09 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7483_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/03/12/dell_wyse_cloud_connect.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7483-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/07/ibm_s_360_50_anniversary/</link><title>Why won't you DIE? IBM's S/360 and its legacy at 50</title><description>Why won't you DIE? IBM's S/360 and its legacy at 50

IBM's System 360 mainframe, celebrating its 50th anniversary on Monday, was more than a just another computer. The S/360 changed IBM just as it changed computing and the technology industry. The digital computers that were to become known as mainframes were already being sold by companies during the 1950s and 1960s - so the S/ …

Gavin Clarke, 07 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7483_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/07/01/ibm_system_360_model_50.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7483-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/03/facebook_paid_out_15m_last_year_to_independent_security_researchers/</link><title>How much is a security bug report worth to Facebook? About $2,100</title><description>How much is a security bug report worth to Facebook? About $2,100

Facebook wasn't the first to offer security researchers bounties for reporting vulnerabilities – but the social network reports it paid out $1.5m in 2013 for bug reports, and says it is increasing the amount of cash on offer in the coming year. According to the advertising giant, it received 14,763 reports of suspected flaws …

Iain Thomson, 03 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7483_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/05/bounty_hunters.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7483-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/14/appnet_no_twitter_also_ran/</link><title>App.net 'not just a way for nerds to talk to each other', boss tells nerds</title><description>App.net 'not just a way for nerds to talk to each other', boss tells nerds

It has never been quite accurate to describe the social network App.net, founded by developer and entrepreneur Dalton Caldwell a little over a year ago, as simply a Twitter also-ran. True, the similarities between the two are impossible to miss: App.net users have accounts prefixed by “@” from which they post (not tweet) …

Dave Mandl, 14 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7483_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/07/05/twitter-data_centre.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7483-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/10/google_apps_referral_program/</link><title>Wanna make 15 bucks? Assimilate someone into the Google Apps BORG</title><description>Wanna make 15 bucks? Assimilate someone into the Google Apps BORG

Google is offering an incentive for Google Apps users in the US and Canada to spread the word about the online productivity suite, in the form of a cash reward for each new customer they refer. The online ad-slinger will pay a $15 referral bonus each time a new user signs up for Google Apps using an existing customer's unique …

Neil McAllister, 10 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7483_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/06/13/cash_suitcase.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7483-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/05/john_lewis_christmas_erp_rollout/</link><title>John Lewis to respray with coat of Oracle ERP: Don't worry, we won't be 'wall to wall' Larry</title><description>John Lewis to respray with coat of Oracle ERP: Don't worry, we won't be 'wall to wall' Larry

The CIO of John Lewis makes no apologies for what he’s about to do. Quite the contrary. I’m meeting Paul Coby at John Lewis's offices in Victoria, a concrete tower fitted with JL’s fittings and furniture that overlooks the jumbled innards of London's £700m upgrade of the Victoria underground line. It's also a tube-strike day. It …

Gavin Clarke, 05 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7483_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/03/03/john_lewis_inside_magna_park.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7483-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/03/01/facebook_post_by_mouthy_daughter_costs_florida_parents_80000/</link><title>How a Facebook post by blabbermouth daughter cost her parents $80,000</title><description>How a Facebook post by blabbermouth daughter cost her parents $80,000

A Florida dad is $80,000 poorer after his daughter went on Facebook to brag about a court settlement he received – and lost him the lot. Patrick Snay is the former headmaster of Gulliver Preparatory School in Miami, and in 2011 he launched legal action against his old employers after his contract was not renewed. Snay claimed he …

Iain Thomson, 01 Mar 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7483_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/09/25/dunce_cap.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7483-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/28/something_for_the_weekend_facebook_whatsapp_and_dotcom_fatcats/</link><title>But... you work in IT... Why aren't we RICH?</title><description>But... you work in IT... Why aren't we RICH?

“Monetizing is not the goal; growing is.” And with that explanation for his company’s decision to put another £11.5bn of someone else’s money through the shredder, Mark Zuckerberg fired the starting gun for the race to the next dot-com crash. Facebook’s acquisition of WhatsApp was not ludicrous, however. Nor was it genius, nor …

Alistair Dabbs, 28 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7483_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/28/balloon.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7483-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/20/facebook_whatsapp_19bn_buy_also_45_for_your_phonebook/</link><title>Facebook pays $19bn for WhatsApp. Yep. $45 for YOUR phone book</title><description>Facebook pays $19bn for WhatsApp. Yep. $45 for YOUR phone book

Putting a man on the Moon cost less than what Facebook paid for WhatsApp, a generic chat app. So why is Facebook paying $45 per user to gain functionality it already has? The silly numbers look even sillier when you consider Facebook's own Messenger only lags narrowly behind WhatsApp in terms of usage. Facebook Messenger …

Andrew Orlowski, 20 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7483_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/12/03/stolen_mobile_phone_shutterstock.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7483-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/20/facebook_hardware_feature/</link><title>How Facebook flipped the data centre hardware market</title><description>How Facebook flipped the data centre hardware market

The rise of Facebook helped to ruin the data centre hardware market, caused IBM to sell its x86 business to Lenovo, spurred HP to embark on an ambitious "Moonshot" server, and encouraged Dell to go private. With the recent acquisition of WhatsApp, it's also adding momentum to the drive of OTT mobile messaging, which is …

Jack Clark, 20 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7483_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/04/09/facebook_home.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>