<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7484">earthquake</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:11:29" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7484-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/17/mit_floating_nuclear_plant_fukushima/</link><title>MIT boffins moot tsunami-proof floating nuke power plants</title><description>MIT boffins moot tsunami-proof floating nuke power plants

Boffins at MIT have mooted a new concept for nuclear power plants which would see the entire facility towed several miles out to sea and moored in a similar way to offshore oil and gas platforms. The proposals would see nuke power plants built in shipyards and then moored or anchored a few miles off the coast, linked to the …

Phil Muncaster, 17 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7484_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/03/15/fukushima_sidey.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7484-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/10/boffins_identify_ancient_earth_asteroid_strike_that_dwarfed_later_dinosaur_killer/</link><title>Ancient Earth asteroid strike that dwarfed dinosaur killer still felt today</title><description>Ancient Earth asteroid strike that dwarfed dinosaur killer still felt today

Scientists say they have reconstructed an asteroid impact on Earth that was at least three times as massive as the strike that is thought to have wiped out the dinosaurs and the new monster had effects that are still being felt today. Asteroid impact A massive headache for Earth (click to enlarge) The research, published …

Iain Thomson, 10 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7484_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/10/10/watery_asteroid_419x278.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7484-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/26/fukushima_radioactivity_a_complete_nonissue_on_west_coast_also_for_fukushima_locals_in_fact/</link><title>Fukushima radioactivity a complete non-issue on West Coast: Also for Fukushima locals, in fact</title><description>Fukushima radioactivity a complete non-issue on West Coast: Also for Fukushima locals, in fact

A new study carried out in the "radiation zone" areas just outside the Fukushima nuclear powerplant in Japan has confirmed that the lifetime health risk to people living there from the damaged powerplant is so small as to be undetectable. Naturally, Californians almost 5,000 miles away are still terrified for their own safety. …

Lewis Page, 26 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7484_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/26/fukushima_ocean_o_noes.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7484-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/21/robot_world_cup_fifa_packbot/</link><title>Robot army to police football World Cup</title><description>Robot army to police football World Cup

Hooligans planning to disrupt the FIFA World Cup in Brazil this summer will have to arm themselves against an unusual foe, after the South American country announced plans to police venues with military-grade robots. The Brazilian government has signed a $7.2 million deal to buy 30 so-called PackBots from Massachusetts-based biz …

Phil Muncaster, 21 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7484_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/24/football_field.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7484-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/10/fukushima_meltdown_experiment/</link><title>Don't panic! Japan to send nuke fuel rod into MELTDOWN in Fukushima probe</title><description>Don't panic! Japan to send nuke fuel rod into MELTDOWN in Fukushima probe

Japan’s Atomic Energy Agency (JAEA) will deliberately send a nuclear fuel rod into meltdown after April this year in a bid to learn more about the events leading up to the Fukushima disaster of March 2011. The experiment will take place at the Nuclear Safety Research Reactor in Tokai, Ibaraki Prefecture, in order to give …

Phil Muncaster, 10 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7484_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/08/17/nuclear_explosion.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7484-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/06/scientists_discover_the_trigger_that_could_set_off_a_supervolcano/</link><title>Scientists discover supervolcano trigger that could herald humanity's doom</title><description>Scientists discover supervolcano trigger that could herald humanity's doom

European scientists think they've found the trigger mechanism for the eruption of supervolcanoes, the most violent and dangerous natural disasters on Earth. magma Earth's forever blowing bubbles Unlike traditional volcanoes, which are easily identifiable by their mountainous shape, supervolcanoes lurk far underneath the Earth …

Iain Thomson, 06 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7484_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/01/06/volcano.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7484-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/09/feature_network_function_virtualisation/</link><title>WTF is... NFV: All your basestations are belong to us</title><description>WTF is... NFV: All your basestations are belong to us

Mobile network operators would have had an easier life if it wasn’t for smartphones and the flood of data traffic they initiated. Apps have led to a massive increase in the volume of data moving back and forth over phone networks - not just from users; the ads in free apps helped too - and operators are struggling to cope. And …

Tony Smith, 09 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7484_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/04/07/racks_small.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7484-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/25/haitian_snapper_humbles_giants_in_copyright_victory/</link><title>Haitian snapper humbles photo giants AFP, Getty Images in $1.2m copyright victory</title><description>Haitian snapper humbles photo giants AFP, Getty Images in $1.2m copyright victory

Photographers have won a landmark victory after a US federal jury awarded $1.2m to freelance photojournalist Daniel Morel after media giants uploaded and credited to themselves some shots he had posted on Twitter. A New York jury decisively backed a Haitian photojournalist Morel in a copyright case against photo agency Getty and …

Andrew Orlowski, 25 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7484_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/25/camera.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7484-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/18/twitter_alert_system_uk_ireland/</link><title>#ALERT! There'll be EMERGENCIES on TWITTER for UK, Ireland</title><description>#ALERT! There'll be EMERGENCIES on TWITTER for UK, Ireland

Twitter has brought its emergency alert system to the UK and Ireland after it kicked off in the US, Japan and South Korea in September. The microblogging site has signed up Blighty's coppers, firefighters and other government agencies so they can tweet urgent messages at the country in times of crisis, or at least the small …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 18 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7484_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/01/19/twicon_2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7484-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/15/fukushima_fearmongers_its_your_fault_japan_has_dumped_co2_targets/</link><title>Fukushima fearmongers: It's YOUR FAULT Japan DUMPED CO2 targets</title><description>Fukushima fearmongers: It's YOUR FAULT Japan DUMPED CO2 targets

If the Fukushima crisis has proved one thing, it's that nuclear power is safe. Everything that could possibly go wrong did, the accident was agreed to be at the top of the international scale for seriousness, and yet in decades to come scientists will not be able to attribute any deaths to radiation released from the Daiichi …

Lewis Page, 15 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7484_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/23/channel_nuke.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>