<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7486">board games teenagers</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:28:46" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7486-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/16/archaeologic_ian_williamson/</link><title>Ian Williamson: The engineer who gave Sinclair his first micro</title><description>Ian Williamson: The engineer who gave Sinclair his first micro

Before Sinclair Research and the QL, the Spectrum and the ZX81, before even Sinclair Computers and the ZX80, there was Science of Cambridge and the MK14 microprocessor kit. Released in February 1978 - that’s when the first adverts for the mail-order-only offering appeared, at least - the MK14 entered the SoC pipeline late in the …

Tony Smith, 16 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7486_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/01/14/iw_3.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7486-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/10/08/raspberry_pi_sony_plant_million_machine_milestone/</link><title>UK plant bakes its millionth Raspberry Pi</title><description>UK plant bakes its millionth Raspberry Pi

A Sony-owned factory in South Wales has now punched out more than a million Raspberry Pi board computers. This is laudable, but it shouldn’t be taken as a sign that Britain is going to ride to economic recovery on the back of a new generation of young programmers. The Raspberry Pi is a fortysomething’s wet dream of early 1980s …

Tony Smith, 08 Oct 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7486_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/10/08/pi.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7486-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/06/30/review_ten_mid_range_android_smartphones/</link><title>Ten... Androids for under 200 quid</title><description>Ten... Androids for under 200 quid

At the Mobile World Congress conference in Barcelona earlier this year, Google chief Eric Schmidt famously said that he expected Android smartphones to be as cheap as normal phones as soon as 2013. The current sub-£200 Sim-free sweet spot in 2012 means you can expect large screens and a variety of processors. Yet don't expect …

Richard Melville, 30 Jun 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7486_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/02/20/motorola_motoluxe_android_smartphone.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7486-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2012/06/14/investors_leave_habbo_hotel/</link><title>Another investor pulls out of Habbo Hotel after grooming claims</title><description>Another investor pulls out of Habbo Hotel after grooming claims

Investors are pulling out of Finnish social networking firm Sulake and its teen-aimed website Habbo Hotel after revelations that Habbo was hosting illicit content. Private equity firm 3i announced today that it had left Sulake's board and was ditching its 16 per cent stake in Habbo Hotel, a social gaming network and online …

Brid-Aine Parnell, 14 Jun 2012</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7486_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7486-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/11/28/raspberry_pi/</link><title>Psst, kid... Wanna learn how to hack?</title><description>Psst, kid... Wanna learn how to hack?

Despite all the excitement and expectation encompassing the RaspberryPi, the most remarkable thing about this low-power credit card-sized computer is its price tag: little more than £20 for a fully functional system capable of, among many things, 1080p video playback and hardware-accelerated graphics. The British-designed Pi is …

Chris Williams, 28 Nov 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7486_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/11/23/rpi_alphaboard_thumb.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7486-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/07/07/anonymous_feature/</link><title>ANONYMOUS: Behind the mask, inside the Hivemind</title><description>ANONYMOUS: Behind the mask, inside the Hivemind

On a frigidly cold morning in early 2008, two dozen complete strangers arranged to meet for the first time. They had travelled from all over the metro area, some taking over two hours to reach their destination. Coffee and doughnuts were sacrificed to the ritual of placing online handles to faces. The first meeting of the …

Trevor Pott, 07 Jul 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7486_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7486-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/12/16/psn_vs_xbl/</link><title>Sony PlayStation Network vs MS Xbox Live</title><description>Sony PlayStation Network vs MS Xbox Live

The online functionality of games consoles has come a long way. Unrecognisable from the 14.4Kb/s modem sideshow curios on the SNES and Megadrive, and a quantum leap over Sega's iconoclastic Dreamcast, the Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3's online services can alone inform purchasing decisions. So if you're contemplating buying either …

Andrew Bailey, 16 Dec 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7486_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2010/12/03/games_of_the_year_9.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7486-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/09/15/review_media_player_apple_ipod_nano/</link><title>Apple iPod Nano 5G</title><description>Apple iPod Nano 5G

Apple rarely - if ever - praises the products of rival companies, but the recent launch of the new iPod range included an unexpected tribute to the merits of the compact and easy-to-use Flip camcorder. “That’s a market we want to get into,” said Apple CEO Steve Jobs before confirming that Apple has added a video camera to the …

Stephen Dean, 15 Sep 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7486_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2009/09/15/nano_5g_7.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7486-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/01/26/review_mobile_phone_nokia_n79/</link><title>Nokia N79 smartphone</title><description>Nokia N79 smartphone

We reviewed Nokia's N78 back in the summer of 2008 and even in the quick turnover world of mobile phones it almost seems a little too soon to be looking at its successor. But here it is, looking leaner, fitter and offering some significant improvements – it's almost as if Nokia just couldn't wait to get it out there. Nokia N79 …

Dave Oliver, 26 Jan 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7486_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2009/01/23/n79_sm.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7486-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/01/13/congressman_proposes_video_game_health_warning_bill/</link><title>US lawmaker wants health warnings on video games</title><description>US lawmaker wants health warnings on video games

A California congressman has proposed legislation that would require cigarette-like health warning labels be placed on video games made for mature audiences. Exposure to this picture may cause aggression As Reg Hardware reported earlier today, Democrat Congressman Joe Baca introduced "The Video Game Health Labeling Act of 2009 …

Austin Modine, 13 Jan 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7486_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>