<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7487">april fools day ideas</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:43:20" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7487-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/12/archaeologic_sinclair_ql/</link><title>Sinclair’s 1984 big shot at business: The QL is 30 years old</title><description>Sinclair’s 1984 big shot at business: The QL is 30 years old

In May 1983, Sinclair Research Managing Director Nigel Searle began briefing the press about the successful British micro maker’s next big release. It was 13 months after the company had launched the Spectrum and although that machine had become a huge success, punters and market-watchers were keen to hear about what Sinclair …

Tony Smith, 12 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7487_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/12/13/ql_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7487-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/10/06/steve_jobs_bio_1/</link><title>The life and times of Steven Paul Jobs, Part One</title><description>The life and times of Steven Paul Jobs, Part One

When sober, F. Scott Fitzgerald may have been devastatingly intelligent, but he got it dead wrong when he wrote "there are no second acts in American lives". Think Elvis, for example. Or lefty sinkerballer Tommy John of the eponymous surgery. Or, for that matter, Grover Cleveland, whose two acts as US president were separated by …

Rik Myslewski, 06 Oct 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7487_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/04/gen_diskleds.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7487-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/02/08/steve_woz_apple_legacy/</link><title>Steve Woz: From wooden Apples to iPhone love</title><description>Steve Woz: From wooden Apples to iPhone love

Steve Wozniak loves computers. He really loves computers. Apple's cofounder is currently using six in-car navigation systems, trying to decide which one plots the best route, and he carries as many as six cell phones. Each time one of his handsets is spotted in public, it generates fresh buzz among those desperate to find hidden …

Gavin Clarke, 08 Feb 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7487_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7487-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/04/01/new_reg_comments/</link><title>New Reg comments system ready to launch</title><description>New Reg comments system ready to launch

Exciting news from Vulture Towers - we're overhauling your comments system to make it more accessible and satisfying for you to use. After an extensive consultation with our valued board of 'tame' commentards - those of you who responded eagerly to our call for comment consultants last year - and weekly all-staff comments …

Team Register, 01 Apr 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7487_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7487-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/04/06/letters_0504/</link><title>IKEA hoax a bright spot in dystopian week</title><description>IKEA hoax a bright spot in dystopian week

We ran an article this week that posed the question "Is open source strategic?". The author argued that if it is, it is probably bad news for open source enthusiasts because it would expose the open source suppliers to the same scrutiny as commercial software vendors. A number of you wrote in saying that this wasn't quite the …

Lucy Sherriff, 06 Apr 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7487_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7487-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2001/04/12/bt_and_dixons_named_as/</link><title>BT and Dixons named as May Day protest targets</title><description>BT and Dixons named as May Day protest targets

Police are preparing to meet the threat posed by anti-capitalist protestors in London on 1 May by monitoring their evolving plans on the Internet. Tactics for the loose confederation of anti-capitalist, green and anarchist groups who are planning rallies in May remain unclear. Because of this police are keeping an open mind …

John Leyden, 12 Apr 2001</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7487_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>