<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7490">convert wav mp3</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:54:06" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7490-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/11/05/ten_3d_blu_ray_disc_players/</link><title>Ten... Blu-ray disc players</title><description>Ten... Blu-ray disc players

On mainstream Blu-ray players, 3D is fast becoming just another feature, so whether you want it or not, we couldn't really avoid it in this round-up – but don't let that put you off. Here we have models ranging from the impulse buy to high-end kit, and you’ll find dimensional compatibility listed alongside other attractions …

Steve May, 05 Nov 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7490_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/09/26/bd670_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7490-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/11/22/ten_essential_mp3_players/</link><title>Ten... sub-£50 budget MP3 players</title><description>Ten... sub-£50 budget MP3 players

Some might argue that, with music playback now integrated into most mobile devices, low-cost MP3 players are fast becoming surplus to requirements. Yet, despite a decline in sales, budget audio kit is still very much in demand this time of year, and manufacturers continue to bring new models out in a bid to compete with Apple’s …

Caleb Cox, 22 Nov 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7490_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2010/09/22/shuffle_4g_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7490-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/06/22/review_phone_samsung_wave/</link><title>Samsung Wave smartphone</title><description>Samsung Wave smartphone

Samsung is one of those manufacturers that seems to grind out decent, capable handsets with great frequency, yet few of its many iterations tend to stick in the memory, or appear to set the pace. Samsung Wave Samsung's Wave: New OS, but revamped TouchWiz UI Yet with the Wave, Samsung hopes to change all that. The Korean …

Dave Oliver, 22 Jun 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7490_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2010/06/16/samsung_wave_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7490-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/07/29/review_media_player_cowon_d2_plus_dab/</link><title>Cowon D2+ DAB</title><description>Cowon D2+ DAB

The portable media player market ranges from the cheapest, smallest screen players, aimed primarily for playing music, to palm-sized, PDA-style pads, more than suitable for watching films and time-shifted TV. The Cowon D2+ DAB is definitely at the smaller end of the scale, but still offers a good range of programme sources …

Simon Williams, 29 Jul 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7490_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2009/07/28/cowon_d2_plus_dab_1.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7490-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/04/01/review_phone_motorola_aura/</link><title>Motorola Aura</title><description>Motorola Aura

It's a moot point whether releasing an unashamedly style-led handset costing over a grand - yes, more than one thousand of your Earth poundingtons - at the present time is recession busting - or recession baiting. The kind of cash that's required to trouser this high-end, low-spec phone could well engender the sort of spending …

Dave Oliver, 01 Apr 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7490_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2009/03/31/aura_7.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7490-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/02/13/apple_tv_hacking_part_2/</link><title>Hacking the Apple TV</title><description>Hacking the Apple TV

Apple’s Apple TV set-top box supports all the audio and video file formats that iTunes, iPods and iPhones can handle. That’s plenty for many folk, but for those who favour less mainstream formats or widespread ones that Apple’s not keen on — DivX, for one — it severely limits the value of the machine. Fortunately, once the Apple …

Nick Hawkesmoor, 13 Feb 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7490_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2008/12/19/apple_tv_sm.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7490-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/02/08/review_baylis_eco_media_player_ep_mx71/</link><title>Baylis Eco EP-MX71 hand-cranked media player</title><description>Baylis Eco EP-MX71 hand-cranked media player

Trevor Baylis, he of wind-up radio fame, now has a range of hand-cranked products, including this, the world's first wind-up multimedia player. It comes down to whether you're concerned by green issues - and you should be, unless you plan to move to another planet any time soon. First seen in August last year, the Baylis Eco …

Lewis Caliburn, 08 Feb 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7490_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2008/02/08/baylis_index.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7490-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/05/02/review_ion_usb_turntable/</link><title>ION USB turntable</title><description>ION USB turntable

The next generation of DJs are forsaking traditional 12-inchers in favour of digital means to create their sounds. If you think today's tunes could benefit from some seasoned samples, or even if you want to transfer your vintage vinyl to a digital music player, then this could be a worthwhile investment. The ION USB turntable is …

Scott Snowden, 02 May 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7490_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2007/05/02/ion_usb_turntable_thumb.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7490-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/08/19/review_hifidelio/</link><title>Hermstedt Hifidelio wireless music centre</title><description>Hermstedt Hifidelio wireless music centre

Germany's Hermstedt isn't a name you'd usually associate with hi-fi or digital music. The firm is better known for its ISDN-based file-transfer solutions for media companies, so the Hifidelio Music Centre marks something of a departure - I suspect the hand of a company staffer who had the product developed because he or she …

Tony Smith, 19 Aug 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7490_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7490-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/02/11/review_apple_ipod_shuffle/</link><title>Apple iPod Shuffle</title><description>Apple iPod Shuffle

Many people listen to their digital music in no particular order at all: album tracklists are becoming a thing of the past, 'shuffle' play (making random selections from a huge collection of hundreds or thousands of songs) is the norm, and to hell with imposed order. Apple, with the iPod Shuffle, says that's how life should be …

Charles Arthur, 11 Feb 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7490_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>