<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7496">why IEEE member</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:27:52" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7496-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/29/something_for_the_weekend_internet_of_furbys/</link><title>Shouldn't we have self calibrating Y-fronts and smart bog roll by now?</title><description>Shouldn't we have self calibrating Y-fronts and smart bog roll by now?

Regular readers of this column, those of you who have have suspiciously too much time on their hands on a Friday afternoon will be aware that I am a IT fraud. Compooters are kinda fun and my second-favourite idea for a perfect Sunday afternoon might involve a bit of screwdriver surgery on a troublesome device, but I don't really …

Alistair Dabbs, 29 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7496_01_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2009/11/20/google_toilet_paper.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7496-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/21/forget_terabit_ethernet_the_next_step_is_400_gig_if_we_can_afford_it/</link><title>Forget terabit Ethernet, the next step is 400 gig – if we can afford the R&amp;D</title><description>Forget terabit Ethernet, the next step is 400 gig – if we can afford the R&amp;D

The current top-end Ethernet standard may be 100 gigabits per second, but don't expect the next step up to be one terabit per second. The days of Ethernet speeds improving by an order of magnitude are gone. Why? Because nobody wants to pay for the necessary research and development – nobody in the US or the EU, that is. "My view …

Rik Myslewski, 21 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7496_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/11/21/qsfp.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7496-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/11/20/ibm_system_r_making_relational_really_real/</link><title>Codd almighty! How IBM cracked System R</title><description>Codd almighty! How IBM cracked System R

Few teams have maintained such a fierce community spirit as the IBM pioneers of System R. In Silicon Valley in the early 1970s, this pioneering team proved that a relational database could actually work. It's a fascinating story, best known today because IBM failed to capitalise on its research. But it's also a timeless one, …

Andrew Orlowski, 20 Nov 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7496_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/08/22/ibm-sj-ad-1962.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7496-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/02/05/feature_powerline_networking_the_next_generation/</link><title>Socket to 'em: It's the HomeGrid vs HomePlug powerline prizefight</title><description>Socket to 'em: It's the HomeGrid vs HomePlug powerline prizefight

“Two standards, both alike in dignity, In fair Vegas, where we lay our scene, From ancient grudge break to new mutiny, Where civil blood makes civil hands unclean.” The backers of rival next-generation in-home mains power networking standards may not have come to physical blows in defence of their favoured technologies, but …

Tony Smith, 05 Feb 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7496_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2009/03/03/ghn_336x204.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7496-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/11/01/snia_cloud_archive_best_practices/</link><title>Archiving and the cloud</title><description>Archiving and the cloud

Cloud is everywhere. Every day we read news about new cloud applications and new cloud providers. But will it really solve all our problems? When we need more processing power or software services, we use Software as a Service (SaaS) providers. What if we need more storage space? We use Data Storage as a Service (DaaS) providers …

Sebastian Zangaro, 01 Nov 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7496_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7496-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/09/19/educating_stob_ieee_enquiry/</link><title>Stob latest: IEEE flags dodgy paper</title><description>Stob latest: IEEE flags dodgy paper

For the past few weeks I've been trying to piece together an explanation for Verity Stob's extraordinary adventure in academia, published here on Monday. Why did the Open University set as a marked assessment for postgraduate students a plagiarized piece of garbage, then admit they hadn't really read it? Why had a prestigious …

Andrew Orlowski, 19 Sep 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7496_06_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7496-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2007/04/15/nextwave_ip_wireless/</link><title>Nextwave plan begins to take shape – as IP Wireless finds a home</title><description>Nextwave plan begins to take shape – as IP Wireless finds a home

Rags to riches broadband wireless operator NextWave has acquired TDD pioneer IP Wireless, completing a cluster of acquisitions that make a nonsense out of the age-old rule that operators should not own the technology they use. IP Wireless, a California based start-up with much of its operations in the UK, is a leader in time …

Faultline, 15 Apr 2007</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7496_07_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7496-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2006/12/27/wimax_poliltics/</link><title>Enemies dig in for WiMAX-on-cell phone trench war</title><description>Enemies dig in for WiMAX-on-cell phone trench war

As the WiMax hype machine moves into high gear ahead of next month's 802.20 working group meeting in London, UK, workers on the various wireless standards are anxious to calm down negative reports about the problems they might have on making this family of wireless work in true mobile fashion. One of the problems facing WiMax …

Guy Kewney, 27 Dec 2006</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7496_08_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7496-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2005/05/04/bluetooth_uwb/</link><title>Bluetooth to evolve via UWB</title><description>Bluetooth to evolve via UWB

The Bluetooth Special Interest Group - the body that controls the wireless connectivity standard - has formally chosen ultrawideband as the foundation for future versions of the technology. It comes as no great surprise. Over a year ago, at Intel Developer Forum, it was made clear that Bluetooth would ultimately establish …

Tony Smith, 04 May 2005</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7496_09_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7496-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2004/11/18/uwb_radio_spec/</link><title>UWB approved, standard imminent</title><description>UWB approved, standard imminent

It's supposed to be official that UWB (ultra-wide band) wireless is approved, and a standard is being agreed. If you believe any such thing, you're horribly gullible; and the dispute inside the wideband club (MBOA) has reached the point where there are people saying: "It will never get sorted." And amongst those sceptics, I hear …

Guy Kewney, 18 Nov 2004</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7496_10_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>