<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7499">gold price</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:54:13" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7499-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/09/insight_ceo_cloud/</link><title>Insight CEO: Everything that's cloudy is GOLD</title><description>Insight CEO: Everything that's cloudy is GOLD

A "sickness" at the core of the IT channel - an over reliance on back-end-loaded vendor rebates - threatens to render many tech suppliers irrelevant. But there is a cure, it is fluffy, white and called the cloud. Or so says Wolfgang Ebermann, the EMEA president at Insight, who after 23 years at Microsoft in various senior roles …

Paul Kunert, 09 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7499_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/04/09/ken_lamneck_insight_ceo.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7499-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/08/hp_brenkel_global_sku_match_making/</link><title>HP: We're holding nothing back from partners now, coos firm</title><description>HP: We're holding nothing back from partners now, coos firm

The new, channel-friendlier HP - jolted into action by CEO Meg Whitman and losing the PC crown to Lenovo - is trying to help rather than hinder partners efforts to build global sales business with customers. A year ago Whitman told a gathering of resellers, integrators and providers of services at its global partner knees-up …

Paul Kunert, 08 Apr 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7499_02_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/13/love.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7499-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/20/hp_q1_2014/</link><title>HP rides data center growth out of sludgy IT market</title><description>HP rides data center growth out of sludgy IT market

HP has reported better than expected financial results on the back of strong server sales and – unexpectedly – good performance in the struggling PC market. The IT company reported an earnings-per-share of $0.90 and a net revenue of $28.2 billion on Thursday for its first fiscal quarter results, beating analyst expectations of $ …

Jack Clark, 20 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7499_03_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/06/12/hp_cloud.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7499-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/14/phoenix_misco_network_ops_centre/</link><title>Misco set to snap up Phoenix's network ops centre AND its staff</title><description>Misco set to snap up Phoenix's network ops centre AND its staff

Phoenix IT Group is set to offload its network operations centre in High Wycombe to Misco, TUPEing across six staff in the process. The lease on the building is expected to be assumed by direct marketing reseller Misco, which, under the guidance of former Dell exec Pim Dale, is trying to rely less on tin shifting by building a …

Paul Kunert, 14 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7499_04_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/08/01/exit_you_out_noooow.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7499-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/11/digitalocean_singapore_expansion/</link><title>Cut-price Linode competitor spins up Singapore bit barn</title><description>Cut-price Linode competitor spins up Singapore bit barn

Scrappy cloud provider DigitalOcean has started selling cloud servers out of a Singapore data center, giving the cut-price Linode competitor a globe-spanning service. The new facility will sit alongside existing data centers in New York, San Francisco, and Amsterdam, the company announced on Tuesday. What sets DigitalOcean …

Jack Clark, 11 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7499_05_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/07/27/thumbs_up_results_story.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7499-06"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/02/04/feature_survival_gaming_genre_growth/</link><title>The revival of survival – the gaming genre that refuses to die</title><description>The revival of survival – the gaming genre that refuses to die

In these times of austerity it seems ironic that my free time is being taken up with trying to survive death by hunger and cold. Next I'll be nicked for dumpster diving behind Iceland. I am, of course, in the grips of day 48 of Don't Starve, a perfect gem in the rash of survival games popping up on Steam. Early Access on Steam …

Lucy Orr, 04 Feb 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7499_06_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2014/02/03/dayz_survivor.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7499-07"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/24/sap_ibm_cloud_set_backs/</link><title>IBM and SAP: Looks like we're STUCK forever on the cloud highway</title><description>IBM and SAP: Looks like we're STUCK forever on the cloud highway

Earnings from SAP and IBM – two giants in enterprise IT - proved that both companies are struggling to cope with the move to the cloud and show that success in hosted computing is receding for them. While it's true that the big growth for SAP was in its cloud-related business – up 66 per cent for the fourth quarter and 158 per …

Gavin Clarke, 24 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7499_07_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/11/04/stuart_highway.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7499-08"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/21/emc_channel_pricing/</link><title>Buying EMC? Better get a quote from a channel partner</title><description>Buying EMC? Better get a quote from a channel partner

EMC execs aim to crush any lingering conflict in the technology business channel* by preventing internal reps from quoting configuration and prices to all bar the largest customers that it sells to directly. The storage giant cemented its love-in with resellers, service providers and integrators with a rules of engagement …

Paul Kunert, 21 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7499_08_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/09/13/romance_date_dating.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7499-09"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2014/01/07/intel_strikes_sensible_stance_over_conflict_minerals/</link><title>Has Intel side-stepped NGOs on conflict minerals in its chips?</title><description>Has Intel side-stepped NGOs on conflict minerals in its chips?

Intel has just announced that it is the proud producer of the world's first conflict-free processors. What they actually mean is that they are making their processors without the use of “conflict minerals”, which is a handy term for materials that come from the dodgy bastards who enslave people in Eastern Congo. This is a jolly …

Tim Worstall, 07 Jan 2014</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7499_09_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2011/11/11/tantalum_capacitor.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7499-10"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2013/12/02/online_shopping_tax_slug_not_worth_the_effort_nab/</link><title>Online shopping tax slug not worth the effort: National Australia Bank</title><description>Online shopping tax slug not worth the effort: National Australia Bank

State and federal governments lovingly eyeing off a billion-dollar windfall if the GST threshold on online purchases is lowered are deluding themselves, according to a former Treasury economist now with the National Australia Bank. The NAB conducts a long-running research series into online commerce in Australia, giving weight …

Richard Chirgwin, 02 Dec 2013</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7499_10_thumb.jpg">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/10/23/haha.jpg?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>