<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7500">roof isolation</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:06:11" name="The Register" id="FW14-e112"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e112-7500-01"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2011/02/17/nokia_microsoft_positives/</link><title>Five Reasons to be cheerful about Nokia-Microsoft</title><description>Five Reasons to be cheerful about Nokia-Microsoft

Elopocalypse, Day Six: The Nokia-Microsoft deal has by now been thoroughly flogged to death analysed from every quarter, with much of the emphasis on the risks and the negatives. Yet there are some positives. Here is a selection, ranging from the flippant to the frivolous. 5\. Dave Stewart Will No Longer Be An Agent of Change …

Andrew Orlowski, 17 Feb 2011</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7500_01_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7500-02"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2010/11/24/diy_insulation_with_aerogel/</link><title>How I used Space Shuttle tech to insulate the living room</title><description>How I used Space Shuttle tech to insulate the living room

Now that the Space Shuttle is being decommissioned, what are we to do with all that lovely high-performance insulation that protects it from the heat of re-entry? Silica aerogel is an amazing material: a solid foam consisting of over 95 per cent air, about the least material and the most 'hole' per unit volume and thus the …

Damon Hart-Davis, 24 Nov 2010</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7500_02_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7500-03"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/10/16/everything_as_a_service/</link><title>Everything as a service</title><description>Everything as a service

The influence of IT in everyday business operations continues to increase. Until a few years ago business operations could be conveniently split between those that involved computer systems somewhere in the business process and those that had no dependence on them at all. Sure there was overlap in, for example, manufacturing …

Tony Lock, 16 Oct 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7500_03_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7500-04"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2009/02/12/fast_compliance_manager/</link><title>Copyright cops launch MS-happy software compliance tool</title><description>Copyright cops launch MS-happy software compliance tool

Fast Consultancy Services has begun selling a software compliance tool aimed at small to medium-sized businesses in the UK that run Windows-based machines, have Internet Explorer as their default browser and £3,500 to spare. The company, which is a spin off from the Federation Against Software Theft, launched the Fast Compliance …

Kelly Fiveash, 12 Feb 2009</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7500_04_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2012/05/03/chandef7.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e112-7500-05"><link>http://search.theregister.co.uk/2008/09/23/california_academy_of_sciences/</link><title>California Academy of Sciences: A new lease on life</title><description>California Academy of Sciences: A new lease on life

The grand dame of natural history museums in the American west gave a sneak peak to the press last week, after a multi-year green reconstruction and all-around face lift. The results are impressive: One of the ten largest natural science museums in the world, San Francisco’s California Academy of Sciences has - for the second …

Burke Hansen, 23 Sep 2008</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e112/7500_05_thumb.png">http://regmedia.co.uk/2013/02/05/default_image-2.png?x=130&amp;y=86&amp;crop=1</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>