<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7004">z-machine</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:41:30" name="Games.com" id="FW14-e048"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e048-7004-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7004_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:41:31">http://www.games.com/game/slixmedia/truck-wars</link><title>Truck Wars</title><description>Gear up and choose your favorite four wheel war machine to race across the wildest terrain performing extreme stunts! Hop in the drivers seat and out perform all the other racers buy destroying them. Don't forget to press the Z button when jumping off ramps to gain massive air!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7004_01_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/games.mochiads.com/c/g/truck-wars/_thumb_200x200.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7004-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7004_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:42:07">http://www.games.com/game/z2live/metalstorm-online</link><title>MetalStorm: Online</title><description>Dominate the skies and master the world’s most advanced combat aircraft as you experience the best looking, most action packed jet fighting game for iOS - MetalStorm: Online! MULTIPLE GAME MODES: • Campaign – Experience an epic storyline spanning several single player missions. • Versus Mode – Challenge your friends and enemies in a one-on-one duel! • Survival Mode –Destroy wave upon wave of enemy aircraft with a friend in co-op or on your own! FEATURES: • Next-Gen 3D graphics with Retina Display • Gyroscope enabled controls enable full 360-degree flight in 3D space • Perform advanced evasive maneuvers by swiping different directions • Real Time Multiplayer over 3G and Wi-Fi • Play on your TV with AirPlay and an Apple TV for a true HD gaming experience • Customize your aircraft with advanced missiles, machine guns and a deep tech tree • Talk with other players via the optional in-game Voice Chat system • Invite a Game Center friend to help you complete difficult missions MetalStorm: Online requires an internet connection to play (WiFi or 3G).</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7004_02_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple4/v4/5b/98/e9/5b98e998-33b6-0230-d726-29fe05b9f100/mzl.gpsvjhrk.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7004-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7004_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:42:33">http://www.games.com/game/inedible-software/slot-z</link><title>Slot-Z</title><description>Slot-Z merges elements of Poker with a variety of features associated with electronic slot machines to form a truly unique experience and we have been hard at work to make that experience even better. How To Play: Compose a Poker-type hand by using adjacent slots. Your top three available scoring options will be displayed and you may select the one that you desire. Each scoring option may only be used once per round. Exploiting bonuses can greatly increase the quantity of points rewarded and aid you in advancing to the next round. GAME FEATURES: GREAT NEW LOOK Play the same great game that you have grown to love on the web with a new design and some great new features. FAST PACED FUN New automatic checks insure that you no longer need to waste time with unnecessary searching. CHALLENGE YOURSELF Play using the Texas Hold'em three slot hand for a even more challenging experience. NEW GAMEPLAY MODES Vegas frenzy and Casino Crush give you more ways to play, more risk, and more rewards. EVERYONE IS IN ON THE FUN Compete against your friends with OpenFient enabled leader-boards and achievements! IN THE PALM OF YOUR HAND All new layout and controls make playing on-the-go better than ever. One build covers all your iOS devices!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7004_03_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/b7/eb/3e/b7eb3e67-4fc5-9e20-5e33-319f13d7bdcb/3ZYJWabUzB1hyWcUIglQrg-temp-upload.lushyzmi.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7004-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7004_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:42:56">http://www.games.com/game/jdl-studios/rise-of-the-zombies-lite</link><title>Rise of the Zombies Lite</title><description>***Free LITE version gives you access to play 5 levels from the first zone, Suburbia*** Designed from the ground up for Apple iOS devices including iPhone 5 and iPod Touch 5th generation, Rise of the Zombies (R.o.t.Z.) is a 3D defense-style strategy game in which you repel the zombie hordes who want nothing more than to destroy sensitive targets across a range of environments. Key features include (both LITE and full versions): \- Beautiful on the new iPhone 5 and iPod Touch 5th generation screens! \- Optimized to run smoothly on iPhone 5, iPhone 4S, iPhone 4, and iPhone 3GS \- Fully rendered 3D environments allow for up-close angles to observe your zombie destruction, or zoom out to plan your strategy \- Enjoy the fluid 3D carnage as dozens of beautifully animated zombies come in range of your defenses. Hilarity will ensue as Zombies attack their targets in unconventional ways, often opting for their heads as the weapon of choice \- LITE version includes 5 levels in zone 1 Suburbia, which unlock as you play \- Speed things up or increase the flow of zombies on-the-fly for a greater challenge, and more bonus points \- Unlock numerous additional tower categories, each with many different tower upgrades to destroy your enemies \- Towers include missile launchers, machine guns, circular saw guns, lasers, flying saucers, and more. Many more available in the full version. \- Score tracking via Game Center allows for competition with your friends and family, and with people all over the world \- Creative gamecenter achievements across a range of categories, including score-based achievements as well as particularly challenging maneuvers accomplished during game play that will earn you bragging rights! The full iPhone and HD version for iPad include the following additional features: \- 35 more levels across 4 themed level zones, including "Suburbia", “Outskirts”, “Wild West”, and “Downtown” \- Multiple game modes including endless and sandbox that allow for more casual and open-ended zombie destruction! \- Unlock many more devastatingly powerful and elaborate towers that will annihilate your enemies and enable you to maximize your score \- Build barriers to stop zombies in their tracks  \- Call in an airstrike to take out a large group of zombies at once \- Summon robot defenders who use flame throwers to “cook” the oncoming zombie hordes and protect the target \- Activate satellite-based laser weaponry causing zombies to catch on fire and suffer damage over time \- Set off an earthquake that greatly slows the zombies, allowing for more effective zombie killing</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7004_04_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/7e/a3/d5/7ea3d5c6-f81b-f887-8c43-20a788be8db9/mzm.hfnkmdlz.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7004-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7004_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:43:21">http://www.games.com/game/appsalliance/touch-dance-2</link><title>Touch Dance™ 2</title><description>Touch Dance 2 is a breathtaking dance game available exclusively for iPhone, iPad &amp; iPod Touch. If you are a frequent nightclub visitor and your home is on the dance floor, then you must check this out. Our focus was on creating the best dance experience on mobile devices and YES we succeeded! You should warm up your fingers before playing since this is the real beat tapping &amp; finger positioning game.   Touch Dance 2 contains over 60.000 unique dance tracks added by other players and we are growing stronger every day. Don't miss out joining the dance generation. We don't distribute any music with Touch Dance 2 since it has been developed to use ANY music available on your device. That is you are dancing to your favorite sound tracks. This is possible through our genius dance track editor available when visiting the Dance Studio in the game. The game syncs easily with your iPod library &amp; has some great visual effects, and best of all a genius dance floor implemented using multi-touch. Over 2.000.000 downloads and 110.000 registered players so far today and we are growing faster than ever! Join us on Facebook for latest news or check out the gameplay video on YouTube. Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/pages/Touch-Dance-Revolving/221642031718 YouTube: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ft1FfqwSqhs Some of the artists with available dance patterns: # 2NE1, 2PM, 3OH!3, 4Minute, 50 Cent A Aaron Carter, Adam Lambert, Akon, Alesha Dixon, Alexis Jordan, Alicia Keys, Armin van Buuren, Ashlee Simpson, Ashley Tisdale, Avril Lavigne B B.o.B, B2ST, Backstreet Boys, Basshunter, Benny Benassi, Beyoncé, Black Eyed Peas, Blink-182, Bon Jovi, Britney Spears, Britt Nicole, Brown Eyed Girls, Bruno Mars C Céline Dion, Calvin Harris, Camila, Cascada, Cee Lo Green, Cher Lloyd, Cheryl Cole, Chris Brown, Chrisette Michele, Christina Aguilera, Ciara, Cody Simpson, Colbie, Coldplay D Daft Punk, Daughtry, David Archuleta, David Guetta, Def Leppard, Demi Lovato, Depeche Mode, Dj Tiesto, Drake, Duck Sauce E Edward Maya, Ellie Goulding, Emily Osment, Eminem, Enrique Iglesias, Evanescence F Fall Out Boy, Far East Movement, Farruko, Fefe Dobson, Fergie, Flo Rida, Florence + The Machine, Flyleaf G G.E.M, GD &amp; TOP, Girl's Generation, Glee Cast, Good Charlotte, Gorillaz, Green Day, Greyson Chance, Guns N' Roses, Gwen Stefani H Hannah Montana, Hedley, Hilary Duff, Hollywood Undead, Hurts I Infected Mushroom J Jackson 5, Jamie Foxx, Jason Aldean, Jason Derülo, Jason Mraz, Jay Sean, Jay-Z, Jennifer Lopez, Jessica Jarrell, Jonas Brothers, Justin Bieber, Justin Timberlake K Katy Perry, Ke$ha, Kelly Clarkson, Keri Hilson, Kevin Rudolf, Kings of Leon, Kraftwerk, Kylie Minogue L La Roux, Lady GaGa, Lenka, Leona Lewis, Lil Wayne, Lily Allen, Linkin Park, Lloyd, LMFAO, Ludacris M Madonna, Mariah Carey, Marianas Trench, Michael Jackson, Miley Cyrus, Miranda Cosgrove, Miranda Lambert, Miss A, Missy Elliott N N-Dubz, Nelly, Neon Trees, New Boyz, Ne-Yo, Nick Jonas, Nickelback, Nicki Minaj, Nightwish, Nirvana O One Republic, Orianthi, Owl City P P!nk, Paramore, Parry Gripp, Pet Shop Boys, Pitbull, Plan B, Prince Royce Q Queen R R. Kelly, Red Hot Chili Peppers, Rick Ross, Rihanna, Robbie Williams S Se7en, Sean Kingston, Selena Gomez &amp; The Scene, Shakira, SHINee, Simple Plan, Skillet, Slipknot, SS501 T Taio Cruz, T-ara, Taylor Swift, The Band Perry, The Beatles, The Pussycat Dolls, Timbaland, T-Pain, Train, Travis Porter, Trey Songz U Usher V Vampire Weekend, Van Halen, Victoria Justice, Victorious Cast W We the Kings, Westlife, Whitney Houston, Willow Smith, Wisin &amp; Yandel, Wiz Khalifa Y Yolanda Be Cool &amp; Dcup, Young Money Z Zion &amp; Lennox</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7004_05_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple2/v4/95/d4/36/95d436af-34c8-c621-4021-8cc82d9a7467/mzl.nmzxqyzc.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7004-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7004_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:43:48">http://www.games.com/game/appsalliance/touch-dance-2-for-ipad</link><title>Touch Dance™ 2 for iPad</title><description>Touch Dance 2 is a breathtaking dance game available exclusively for iPhone, iPad &amp; iPod Touch. If you are a frequent nightclub visitor and your home is on the dance floor, then you must check this out. Our focus was on creating the best dance experience on mobile devices and YES we succeeded! You should warm up your fingers before playing since this is the real beat tapping &amp; finger positioning game.   Touch Dance 2 contains over 60.000 unique dance tracks added by other players and we are growing stronger every day. Don't miss out joining the dance generation. We don't distribute any music with Touch Dance 2 since it has been developed to use ANY music available on your device. That is you are dancing to your favorite sound tracks. This is possible through our genius dance track editor available when visiting the Dance Studio in the game. The game syncs easily with your iPod library &amp; has some great visual effects, and best of all a genius dance floor implemented using multi-touch. Over 2.000.000 downloads and 110.000 registered players so far today and we are growing faster than ever! Join us on Facebook for latest news or check out the gameplay video on YouTube. Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/pages/Touch-Dance-Revolving/221642031718 YouTube: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ft1FfqwSqhs Some of the artists with available dance patterns: # 2NE1, 2PM, 3OH!3, 4Minute, 50 Cent A Aaron Carter, Adam Lambert, Akon, Alesha Dixon, Alexis Jordan, Alicia Keys, Armin van Buuren, Ashlee Simpson, Ashley Tisdale, Avril Lavigne B B.o.B, B2ST, Backstreet Boys, Basshunter, Benny Benassi, Beyoncé, Black Eyed Peas, Blink-182, Bon Jovi, Britney Spears, Britt Nicole, Brown Eyed Girls, Bruno Mars C Céline Dion, Calvin Harris, Camila, Cascada, Cee Lo Green, Cher Lloyd, Cheryl Cole, Chris Brown, Chrisette Michele, Christina Aguilera, Ciara, Cody Simpson, Colbie, Coldplay D Daft Punk, Daughtry, David Archuleta, David Guetta, Def Leppard, Demi Lovato, Depeche Mode, Dj Tiesto, Drake, Duck Sauce E Edward Maya, Ellie Goulding, Emily Osment, Eminem, Enrique Iglesias, Evanescence F Fall Out Boy, Far East Movement, Farruko, Fefe Dobson, Fergie, Flo Rida, Florence + The Machine, Flyleaf G G.E.M, GD &amp; TOP, Girl's Generation, Glee Cast, Good Charlotte, Gorillaz, Green Day, Greyson Chance, Guns N' Roses, Gwen Stefani H Hannah Montana, Hedley, Hilary Duff, Hollywood Undead, Hurts I Infected Mushroom J Jackson 5, Jamie Foxx, Jason Aldean, Jason Derülo, Jason Mraz, Jay Sean, Jay-Z, Jennifer Lopez, Jessica Jarrell, Jonas Brothers, Justin Bieber, Justin Timberlake K Katy Perry, Ke$ha, Kelly Clarkson, Keri Hilson, Kevin Rudolf, Kings of Leon, Kraftwerk, Kylie Minogue L La Roux, Lady GaGa, Lenka, Leona Lewis, Lil Wayne, Lily Allen, Linkin Park, Lloyd, LMFAO, Ludacris M Madonna, Mariah Carey, Marianas Trench, Michael Jackson, Miley Cyrus, Miranda Cosgrove, Miranda Lambert, Miss A, Missy Elliott N N-Dubz, Nelly, Neon Trees, New Boyz, Ne-Yo, Nick Jonas, Nickelback, Nicki Minaj, Nightwish, Nirvana O One Republic, Orianthi, Owl City P P!nk, Paramore, Parry Gripp, Pet Shop Boys, Pitbull, Plan B, Prince Royce Q Queen R R. Kelly, Red Hot Chili Peppers, Rick Ross, Rihanna, Robbie Williams S Se7en, Sean Kingston, Selena Gomez &amp; The Scene, Shakira, SHINee, Simple Plan, Skillet, Slipknot, SS501 T Taio Cruz, T-ara, Taylor Swift, The Band Perry, The Beatles, The Pussycat Dolls, Timbaland, T-Pain, Train, Travis Porter, Trey Songz U Usher V Vampire Weekend, Van Halen, Victoria Justice, Victorious Cast W We the Kings, Westlife, Whitney Houston, Willow Smith, Wisin &amp; Yandel, Wiz Khalifa Y Yolanda Be Cool &amp; Dcup, Young Money Z Zion &amp; Lennox</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7004_06_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple2/v4/0a/cb/6d/0acb6d7a-84fa-3b96-5d31-26df3da5e254/mzl.hycgpgit.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7004-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7004_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:43:49">http://www.games.com/game/harmony-melody-studio/piano-music-reading-free</link><title>Piano Music Reading Free</title><description>*Top 1 Piano Reading Game *Top Music Game Learn to read piano music or sight reading and play piano with our fun and interactive game. This game will help you improve on your piano playing and music reading skills. Challenge yourself with the low and high notes on ledger lines. You can even compete with other fans to see who score the highest. Listen to the music pitch while you try to identify the notes. You will like this free game. Upgrade now to complete version of music reading game. Piano music reading game is a virtual piano game that allows you to improve on your music reading skills. It lets you listen to MIDI files and recognize different pitches and notes. It features a new innovative way to identify intervals and thus helps with note recognition. It comes with three different levels; beginner, advanced, master. You can even record your scores. If you need to master classical music, it is important to have good sight reading/read music techniques. Whether it is a.Fur Elise (by Beethoven), b.Canon in D maj (Johann Pachelbel), c.Clair De Lune (Claude Debussy), d.Moonlight Sonata, e.Turkish March (By Mozart), f.Fantaisie Impromptu (by Chopin), etudes, or any other classical music. Please visit http://www.harmonyandmelodystudio.com for support and more piano courses and softwares. Related Words: Octave tempo position keyboard size complex songs metronome recording sequence piano sounds piano sharps audio composing composer compose ifart pocket piano finger fingering black keys white keys Funny Fun Game Adult School Age College Major School Student Play Piano Lesson Machine Joy Learning Langauge Music Learn Updated Family Type Letter Alphabet Words Read Word Singing Song Photo Guitar Picture IQ 3D Girls Boys Percussion Rhythm Instruments Voice Vocal Improve Read Violin Viola String Band Instruments By Ear Sheet Music Tap Singing Read Notes Music Scores Music Sheet Christmas Songs Rockstar Band Pocket Piano Octaves Treble Clef Bass Clef G Clef F Clef tunes Major Chord Minor Chord Augmented Chord Diminished Chords Arpeggios Scales Practice Repertoire Ear Training Camera Zoom I Dig It Tic Tac Toe Pandora Radio RopeNFly Harbor Master Lyrics Ifitness Loops Scrapple Guitar ToolKit Ipod Songtext Lyrics Simplify Music Z Pocket Tunes Radio FingerBeat BeatMaker Channel</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7004_07_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/33/ac/c0/mzl.bbzcdxfd.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7004-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7004_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:47:48">http://www.games.com/game/picsoft-studio/tiny-defense</link><title>Tiny Defense</title><description>• Top 10 Strategy Game in over 90 countries! • No.1 Strategy Game in 25 countries! • No.1 Overall iPad App in Singapore! Green Planet is a beautiful home of the little mechanical life forms known as “Minirobots”. While living peacefully, their planet was invaded by an army of robot troops calling themselves “The Machines”. These machines tried to turn Green Planet into a space resort and had captured many of the Minirobots, but now they are fighting back! ********************** “Tiny Defense takes the tried and tested tower defense genre and puts it onto a 2D playing field. It works a treat and comes out as one of the very best in its class.” – 148Apps.com "This tactical defense game is entertaining and addictive. There is nothing not to love about it." – AppAdvice.com “If you’re a fan of games like Plants vs Zombies and you’re looking to try anything with a remotely similar gameplay experience, then Tiny Defense will certainly satisfy that urge.” – TouchArcade “Tiny Defense is one of the first tower defense titles that I’ve played that meets up to the expectations of P vs Z.” – AppStoreArcade “I like it! Cute, Mario-esque graphics, PvZ gameplay, ample content.” – ArcadeLife ********************** Use your wit and tactics to overcome the obstacles and save the gorgeous Green Planet! Collect energy crystal to build your army of robot and fight to rescue your friends. Beware! The enemies are everywhere; on the ground, in the sky, over the sea and even under there! Tiny Defense features bright cartoony graphics with funny characters, easy-to-learn gameplay with a good depth to please strategy fans, a vast number of levels and mini-games with challenging boss fight. Stand united and prove that size doesn't matter in Tiny Defense, a playful challenge for strategy game lovers! ▼ Features \---------------- ▷ Unique side-view, grid base defense game ▷ 150 magnificent levels ▷ 3 episodes with distinguished gameplay ▷ 40 cute robot types to choose from ▷ 32 types of ruthless enemy ▷ 5 different areas (Glass Land, Desert, Underwater, Glacier, Iron Fortress) ▷ 30 fun action/arcade style mini-games ▷ Tons of upgrades, unlockables, and achievements ▷ Over 20 hours of gameplay! *** TIPS: Story Mode continue after the first 50 levels 2 times! Extend the fun to the total of 150 levels! ▼ Requirements (Please check before download!) \---------------- Compatible with iPhone 3GS, iPhone 4, iPhone 4S, iPhone 5, iPod touch (3rd, 4th, 5th gen), iPad, iPad 2, The New iPad and iPad Mini. Requires iOS 4.3 or later ******************* ▼ Get in Touch \---------------- ▷ Follow us! : twitter.com/TinyDefense ▷ Join our fan page : facebook.com/TinyDefense ▷ Tiny Defense Community : pic-soft.com/forum</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7004_08_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/67/49/46/67494664-4ea9-8616-4f67-2529a22d8a00/mzl.bdepkkgk.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7004-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7004_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:49:19">http://www.games.com/game/big-daddys-creations/neuroshima-hex</link><title>Neuroshima Hex</title><description>AWARDS: "iOS Game of the Year" Game Shark "Best Card/Board Game - Runner Up" TouchGen PRESS QUOTES: "With great production values the board game has been translated to perfection." TouchGen (9/10, Editor's Choice) "Would I Buy Again: Absolutely." What's On iPhone (9/10) "Neuroshima Hex is a board game that almost seems like it was destined for the App Store […]" App Spy (4/5) "Neuroshima Hex is hard not to recommend" Games Uncovered (Grade: 'Great') "Creative game world; deep strategy" Slide To Play (3/4) "It's a deeply satisfying game that forces you to have a tactical mind in order to win, and it's incredibly fulfilling when you do." GameZebo (4/5) Neuroshima Hex is a fast paced, tactical board game where up to 4 players (human or AI) lead their troops to victory. Every player controls one of the four armies struggling for influence and survival in the world destroyed in a 30 years long war. March with the machines of Moloch, leading its army towards setting the new world order. Become Borgo and unite the forces of the mutants who spread terror in the wastelands. Lead The Outpost - humanity's last and only hope and try to beat the machines in an uneven guerrilla war. Be the boss of The Hegemony - land of gangers not caring about the fate of others and living only for violence and their mad entertainment. In the world of Neuroshima Hex you need to prove you have what it takes to survive. Neuroshima Hex is well known in the board game community. Neuroshima Hex holds 100th place in the prestige BoardGameGeek ranking (which contains almost 50,000 games from around the world). In May 2007 Neuroshima Hex was awarded a special jury distinction for the Best Polish Designer Game published in 2006. Neuroshima Hex was also published in the US (by Z-Man Games) and France (by IELLO). FEATURES \- Official Neuroshima Hex game with original artwork \- 4 different armies with unique strategies (next 8 available for purchase) \- Up to 4 players (human or AI) \- asynchronous online multiplayer \- 3 AI difficulty levels \- In-game tutorial &amp; manual \- Tons of gameplay \- Easy to learn, hard to master</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7004_09_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/74/8d/14/748d14c6-d77a-3ce8-7005-905bc5b58233/mzl.plwlydra.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7004-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7004_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:50:40">http://www.games.com/game/khor-chin-heong/disassembly-3d-ultimate-stereoscopic-destruction</link><title>Disassembly 3D: Ultimate Stereoscopic Destruction</title><description>Love taking things apart? This app lets you do so! Plus you can blow it up at the end! Disassembly 3D simulates the experience of taking everyday objects apart. Remove screws, bolts, nuts and every single part with your bare hands. All with realistic disassembly physics! First six levels are free, the rest are available via in-app purchase. *** New Item Pack 10 - Twin destruction! Demolish one of the tallest buildings in the world and watch it collapse! With real-time dynamic fracture!!! *** *** "How parts falling down in slow motion is a masterpiece." - iPhonePEOPLE review *** *** "I am really having a good time with Disassembly 3D on my new iPad, and that is where it belongs." - TouchGen.Net review 3.5 stars! *** *** Top #100 Puzzle &amp; Simulation game in the US!!! *** *** Top #2 Puzzle &amp; Simulation iPad game in Japan!!! - Dec 2011, Apr 2012 *** *** Top #8 Puzzle iPhone game in Italy!!! - Nov 2011 *** *** Top #50 Puzzle/Simulation iPad game in Australia, New Zealand, Japan, Hong Kong, Italy, Switzerland, France, Germany, Spain, Belgium, UK, and dozens more!!! *** Features: * 33 objects ranging from furniture, appliances, electronics, to the super jumbo A380! Modelled in extreme detail, right down to the final screw! * Realistic physics - touch and drag parts to disassemble, move or drop them! * Interactive objects - operate a blender or coffee machine, open doors and handles, and much more! * Realistic destruction - bomb mode becomes unlocked once you successfully disassemble an object. Place the bomb then blow things up in slow motion 'bullet' time! * Stereoscopic 3D mode - glasses free! wiggle, parallel eye and cross eye modes! Compatible with TOYin3D viewer! (www.toyin3d.com) * High replay value - explore alternate ways to disassemble an object, or just blow it up for the fun of it! * Facebook integration - share the fruits of your destruction with your friends! * Universal app - works on iPod Touch 3G/4G, iPhone 3GS,4,4S,5,5C,5S and all iPads! * Supports iPad and iPhone 5 Retina display! With ultra-high resolution textures! * Real-time dynamic shadows and realistic water simulation! (not supported on iPhone 3GS, 4 and iPad 1st gen) List of objects: * Sidetable, Lamp, Speaker * Pocket Knife, Microscope, Antique Car * Robot, Safe, Bicycle * Chair, Water Heater, House * Hard Disk, Blender, Coffee Machine * Sink, Lego Van, Hellfire Missile * Screw Driver, Rice Cooker, Titanic * Phone, Jig saw, Car * Toaster, Coffee Grinder, Airplane * Flashlight, Elevator, Train * Tablet, DVD Player, Skyscraper Facebook Page: http://www.facebook.com/disassembly3d YouTube Item Pack 8 Airplane Trailer: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RlelUYN9z5s YouTube Item Pack 7 Car Trailer: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z_jEnuwNJ94 YouTube Titanic Trailer: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w916chLRz2s</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7004_10_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/fe/dc/9d/fedc9dfa-b4ca-32dd-4922-308c300f164f/mzl.rpeexwzz.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>