<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7024">reinforcement learning</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:31:06" name="Games.com" id="FW14-e048"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e048-7024-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7024_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:31:07">http://www.games.com/game/kevin-bradford/preschool-learning-fun</link><title>Preschool Learning Fun</title><description>8 fun and original games Voice narration to reinforce learning Colorful graphics and animations Collect hundreds of stickers</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7024_01_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/71ejAVtr2AL._SL160_.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7024-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7024_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:32:12">http://www.games.com/game/intellijoy/kids-abc-phonics</link><title>Kids ABC Phonics</title><description>Learn ABC phonics via four kid-friendly activities: In Learn Letter Sounds, children can turn a picture-filled letter block and hear the ABC letter sounds pronounced. With Build Letter Blocks, kids make their own ABC picture blocks while reinforcing their newly-formed phonics skills. In Pop Letter Bubbles, letter-filled bubbles float on screen as children try to pop them. But don't be fooled by the fun - by the time children are done with this activity, they will know what letter goes with which sound! In Make Words, kids start blending phonics while putting word puzzles together.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7024_02_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/319rKUxlZbL._SL160_.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7024-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7024_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:32:49">http://www.games.com/game/cupcake-digital/wubbzys-fire-engine-adventure</link><title>Wubbzy's Fire Engine Adventure</title><description>3 READING MODES: Read &amp; Play, Read To Me, and Just A Book READ &amp; PLAY - In this mode, as you read the story to your child, they can tap and interact on each page. READ TO ME - A narrator reads the book and your child can tap and interact with the story. JUST A BOOK - This mode works like a good, old-fashioned picture book. It turns off all interaction and sound. EXCEPTIONAL LEARNING ACTIVITIES INSIDE THE STORY - Games further engage a child's imagination and to reinforce writing and counting skills. SING ALONG MUSIC VIDEOS - Your child will want to get up and dance with original music videos COLORING - Kids can tap into their creativity by painting some of their favorite characters and scenes!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7024_03_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/61zb4VKDwUL._SL160_.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7024-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7024_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:37:39">http://www.games.com/game/knowledge-adventure/madagascar-my-abcs</link><title>Madagascar: My ABCs</title><description>• “Any kid who is a fan of Madagascar should check this out!” – Playground Dad • “The activities were well thought out, entertaining and most of all had educational value.” - The iPhone Mom • “It is a fun and engaging app that keeps children learning for more than a few minutes.” - Tech Tools 4 Mom Madagascar: My ABCs app is fully interactive to keep your preschooler engaged while learning all about the alphabet! This app doesn’t just teach letters and letter sounds, but also provides writing practice and songs to sing along to for each letter! The Madagascar gang is all set to depart on their alphabet adventure! Your child will travel on a field trip with Alex, Marty, Melman and Gloria to tropical beaches, busy New York City, wild savannahs and colorful jungles! Letters can be found everywhere and your youngster will get the chance to discover letter names and sounds, practice writing upper- and lowercase letters and recognize beginning sounds of familiar words! Along the way, our Madagascar friends will help reinforce letter names and sounds in a fun and magical way! And don’t forget to make time for the Sticker Safari where special letter stickers are revealed and added to your child’s collection! This app is sure to keep your child entertained while learning all about their ABCs! Madagascar: My ABCs includes: •Use your photos as stickers or backgrounds •Upper- and lowercase letter pages that play the letter name and sound • Over 400 stickers that children can decorate their letter pages with to reinforce initial sounds • A fun game, Sticker Safari, where kids will use their trusty binoculars to reveal letter stickers • A song and poem about each letter to help emphasize rhyming • My Pictures, where kids will save their favorite letter masterpieces • Writing practice to earn coins by tracing letters that transfer to their JumpStart account to spend online at www.jumpstart.com • Player profiles allow more than one child to play and save their work and progress • Curriculum developed and reviewed by early childhood and preschool education experts If you like the game, please take time to rate it! Email us at AppComments@jumpstart.com with your suggestions and comments as we cannot respond to reviews. We love to hear your ideas and feedback! Privacy Policy: https://policy-portal.truste.com/core/privacy-policy/KA/36922980-f930-4103-ab0e-abb870eb2a56 Registration information is optional (children under 13 require parent registration). It will be used to notify of game fix updates and new features along with integration to our online educational world for kids. -Does NOT include ads -Does NOT link to social networks -Does include links and information relative to other Knowledge Adventure games and apps *** CHECK OUT OUR OTHER EXCITING GAMES! *** Madagascar Preschool Surf n' Slide, Madagascar Math Ops, Jumpstart® Pet Rescue and watch for our future apps at facebook.com/Jumpstart</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7024_04_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple4/v4/91/49/23/9149232d-8fda-00fd-bd5b-12dbb71a29c3/mzl.rpdoijbk.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7024-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7024_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:41:00">http://www.games.com/game/intellijoy/kids-abc-letters</link><title>Kids ABC Letters</title><description>Turn your Android device into an entertaining teaching tool Help your preschooler learn the ABCs with a fun set of games Choose from four different sections, teaching different aspects of the alphabet</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7024_05_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/414B3mQQIOL._SL160_.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7024-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7024_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:42:32">http://www.games.com/game/selectsoft/grammar-fun-2nd-grade-hd</link><title>Grammar Fun 2nd Grade HD</title><description>Follow a friendly robot on a language arts adventure! Kids can master the basics of grammar and have fun with over 200 exercises that teach about verbs, nouns, adjectives, tenses and more. Learn about sentence construction, reading comprehension and other language arts concepts. Features • Simple drag-and-drop interface • Over 200 exercises and games to reinforce learning • Covers concrete and abstract nouns, verbs, tenses, adjectives, articles and more Explore the universe of grammar with activities covering: • Nouns: Learn about the three main functions of nouns • Common &amp; Proper Nouns: Learn the difference between common and proper nouns • Concrete &amp; Abstract Nouns: Practice identifying the difference between concrete and abstract nouns • Action &amp; Linking Verbs: Sort action and linking verbs into categories • Verb Tenses: Identify how verbs show the past, present and future • Verb Phrases: Discover the difference between main and helping verbs • Adjectives: Identify three main uses of adjectives • Articles: Fill in the missing words to complete the sentences • Demonstrative Adjectives &amp; Pronouns: Learn the difference between demonstrative adjectives and pronouns</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7024_06_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/9d/68/20/9d6820c6-9ef2-acd5-0598-cb096cfd44ee/mzl.yttllrpc.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7024-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7024_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:46:27">http://www.games.com/game/healthteacher/awesome-upstander</link><title>Awesome Upstander!</title><description>Don’t just stand there, be an UPSTANDER! The bully is at it again. Use the power of your friends to STOP the bully before it's too late! Race through cafeterias and bathrooms to rescue a target from the bully. Collect bananas, air fresheners, and rolls of toilet paper to up your score, but hurry! Time is ticking, and you have to find and collect enough friends to stand up to the bully together. FEATURES: -Side scrolling platform adventure -TWENTY challenging levels and tons of replay value -Boy and Girl avatars -Hilarious lifelike noises! Don’t say we didn’t warn you... “This game is perfectly placed in terms of the child’s social and emotional development. It teaches kids, in a meaningful way, how to make a difference. This is the first game that reinforces pro-social behavior in an age-appropriate way.” \- Dr. Susan Lipkins, child psychologist and leading expert in the development of Awesome Upstander! HealthTeacher is the interactive leader in youth health, creating games, apps, and educational resources to make health awesome for kids. HealthTeacher's research-based products are designed to get kids moving and to develop healthy behaviors that last a lifetime. Reaching over 6 million kids through its fast-growing network of 11,000+ schools, HealthTeacher’s interactive products are used by teachers, parents, and kids to address important youth health issues, including physical activity, nutrition, and social and emotional well-being. To learn more, visit www.healthteacher.com What others are saying about Awesome Upstander!... “Hey bullies! I used to think you could push my friends and me around, but NOT ANYMORE! What can you do to eight friends sticking together? That’s what I thought. See ya never!“ \- Really Awesome Kid, PhD, Upstander University, Awesomeville.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7024_07_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/63/e0/df/63e0df74-9635-8c01-fc45-065d3857b962/mzl.rrtkyqah.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7024-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7024_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:48:00">http://www.games.com/game/selectsoft-publishing/math-fun-2nd-grade-multiplication-division-hd</link><title>Math Fun 2nd Grade: Multiplication &amp; Division HD</title><description>Simple drag-and-drop interface Over 200 exercises and games to reinforce learning Covers equations, number families, place value, vertical equations, mental arithmetic and more Includes bingo, word problems, picture questions and more for a varied challenge</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7024_08_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/51H%2Bk6nnZFL._SL160_.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7024-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7024_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:50:55">http://www.games.com/game/tearn-media/life-sciences</link><title>Life Sciences</title><description>Addictive action facilitates fast learning Holistic focus on meaning, association, and spelling concurrently Associate real images with each life science search term Speed-based learning to emulate SAT testing environments Positive reinforcement with no penalties for mistakes</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7024_09_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/71DGgmebLtL._SL160_.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7024-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7024_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:53:31">http://www.games.com/game/tearn-media/weapons-of-martial-arts</link><title>Weapons of Martial Arts</title><description>Learn lots about martial arts with numerous trivia games Guess the search terms for Google, Bing, and yahoo results Associate real images with each search term Fast-paced gameplay Positive reinforcement with no penalties for mistakes</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7024_10_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/71IHuExtr0L._SL160_.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>