<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7027">prefered or preferred</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:58:56" name="Games.com" id="FW14-e048"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e048-7027-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7027_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:58:57">http://www.games.com/game/introwizard/which-would-you-prefer</link><title>Which Would You Prefer!</title><description>★★★ DOWNLOAD FOR FREE TODAY! ★★★ A wild and crazy spin on popular games like "What Would You Choose?" and "What Would You Do?" Bizarre questions, even bizarrer answers! Great for parties! Pass it amongst your friends for a good chuckle and plenty of fun times.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7027_01_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/ee/d5/6b/mzl.takiqbhf.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7027-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7027_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:03:02">http://www.games.com/game/introwizard/whats-your-preference</link><title>What's YOUR Preference?</title><description>***FREE FOR DOWNLOAD*** What kind of person are you? What's YOUR preference? Great for parties! This inquisitive game was designed with the user in mind to find out what kind of person they are. More reliable than a fortune teller. More simple than a personality test. So ALL you have to do is select what YOU prefer and let the game do the work for you!!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7027_02_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/40/c9/18/mzl.dximlqca.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7027-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7027_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:05:39">http://www.games.com/game/oberon-media/inspector-parker</link><title>Inspector Parker</title><description>Solve a murder mystery by using your sleuthing skills to analyze the crime scene, suspects and motives.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7027_03_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/hss/storage/games/d5c1e67e73de920da2db748f92624b44</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7027-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7027_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:06:48">http://www.games.com/game/ocean-breeze-games/cube-crash-wordz</link><title>Cube Crash: Wordz</title><description>Cube Crash: Wordz, a word game with an electrifying twist! Play Arcade mode and race against rows of falling blocks, build words and clear the grid using your spelling skills or by blowing blocks up! Choose Blitz mode if you prefer to play against the clock and try and get the highest score possible.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7027_04_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/hss/storage/games/9b0728ea80330f637eb904bbbfb73a35</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7027-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7027_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:09:39">http://www.games.com/game/chris/battle-panic</link><title>Battle Panic</title><description>Those insolent orcs are getting in the way of our rightful claim to this land! Battle Panic is a brand new type of game where your mouse controls everything that happens. And we don't mean clicking - all you have to do is hover over what you want to interact with. It's so simple and slick! Mine gold, chop down trees, build buildings, train units, heal your army, and chop up bad guys directly all by just hovering over those objects! It's up to you to choose how you win - would you prefer to make a huge army to overwhelm the orcs? Or perhaps focus on a smaller, higher quality army supported by healing and buffs? Earn precious upgrade points each level that you can spend on 30 different skills that will help you further refine your favoured strategy. The better you play, the more points you earn! Complete your conquest of the orcs by destroying them in 12 action packed levels and three difficulty settings. Can you beat your panic in Battle Panic?</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7027_05_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/games.mochiads.com/c/g/battle-panic/_thumb_200x200.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7027-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7027_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:14:17">http://www.games.com/game/gamesheep/the-champions-3d</link><title>The Champions 3D</title><description>The best World Cup Soccer 2010 game! Choose your preferred team and lead your champions through the 7 matches of the World Cup Soccer 2010. Win the finals and take the trophy in the name of your favorite country!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7027_06_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/thumbs.mochiads.com/c/g/the-champions-3d/_thumb_100x100.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7027-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7027_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:18:59">http://www.games.com/game/nipponmonkey/english-pub-pool</link><title>English Pub Pool</title><description>Play 8-Ball and Straight Pool tournaments against fast thinking CPU Players to become Rank #1. Plus play Challenges and Time Attacks to set new high scores and to win trophies. There are over 60 trophies to be won by winning matches, playing challenges, making big breaks and shooting special shots. It has a nice billiards physics engine allowing you to play spin for better ball control. Human vs Human matches against your mates at home are possible too - no network play yet... Finally, you can set your preferred 8-ball pool rules in the settings options - e.g. do you play 2-shots, or no 2-shots on the black, or place the white anywhere after fouls? All can be changed to your preferred settings. This game includes the popular Random Potting challenge that has been played over 24,000,000 times and counting. Enjoy!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7027_07_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/thumbs.mochiads.com/c/g/english-pub-pool-dist/_thumb_200x200.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7027-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7027_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:24:06">http://www.games.com/game/finger-arts/solitaire</link><title>▻Solitaire</title><description>Discover the next evolution of solitaire with amazing graphics and ease of use. This is a card game like one you have never experienced before. No wonder ▻Solitaire is rated so highly! So easy to use: ▻Solitaire has been built specifically for your iPhone and iPad to bring you the best card game experience ever… for you to fall in love with it over and over again like millions of our players, which rank it the best solitaire card game and best card puzzle :) ________________________________ This is what some of our millions of players say: "Fun and Easy! (★★★★★) …Easy to use and it makes you keep wanting to beat your previous scores… I ended up playing for an hour straight without even realizing it!…" "Good Stuff ((★★★★★) Easily the best solitaire app out there. Grab it." "Addicted (★★★★★) I'm so addicted to this game!! Playing it for months now." Check out the rest of our raving reviews... and look at our ratings!!! ________________________________ ▻Solitaire makes it amazingly natural to control the cards movements and to feel in control: With tap-to-place, you simply tap the right card and it magically does the right move, or when you prefer you can also use our assisted drag-and-drop to move a card anywhere it creates a valid move. And, with our optional extra-large card symbols, squinting the eyes is a thing of the past! ________________________________ With this solitaire game you get unlimited puzzle games, all free games, all best of class games.  To the classic solitaire game we have added a Smart Point System and multiple levels of difficulty: Easy, Medium, and Hard :) • Easy games are guaranteed to be solvable and start as a card game partially solved :) • Medium games are also guaranteed to be solvable but are quite challenging :) • Hard games are… well, hard ;) ________________________________ With this solitaire card game you also get all the nice features you would expect from a first class card game, such as: • unlimited number of free games • landscape and portrait card game play • draw one card puzzles • draw three card puzzles • right and left game layout • drag destination highlight • suggested move auto hint • multiple moves hinting • automatic game save and resume • unlimited undos • cards placement hints • tap to place cards • drag and drop cards • autocomplete to finish a solved puzzle • scores, moves, and times • statistics • guaranteed winnable card games • show me how to solve a puzzle • awesome graphics and animations :) • show or hide time/battery • online games scoring • online achievements • klondike solitaire game rules • … too many more to keep listing :) ________________________________ ▻Solitaire is an iPhone game and an iPad game combined into one iOS app. Your iPhone, iPod, or iPad automatically selects for you the iPhone app and iPad app. ________________________________ ▻Solitaire is part of our family of card games and puzzle games, all created with the same mix of passion for enjoyment, midnight oil, and deep technology skills to bring you the best solitaires… try the difference: The feeling of playing ▻Solitaire is not just that of playing cards… it's the feeling of being part of a community… an enriching, shared experience that never makes you feel apart! Like us on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/fingerarts Follow us on Twitter:  @FingerArtsGames © Finger Arts www.fingerarts.com For any question, write us at support@fingerarts.com Spread the word. This free game app rocks :)</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7027_08_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r1000/069/Purple/v4/2d/b6/15/2db615ce-0ca5-94e1-2157-22900f26352c/mzm.rhosyuzw.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7027-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7027_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:27:55">http://www.games.com/game/electronic-arts/real-racing-3</link><title>Real Racing 3</title><description>APP STORE BEST OF 2013. NOW WITH REAL-TIME MULTIPLAYER! **#1 Top Free App in over 90 countries** Real Racing 3 is an award-winning franchise that sets a new standard for mobile racing games – it really must be experienced to be believed. This app offers in-app purchases. You may disable in-app purchasing using your device settings. See http://support.apple.com/kb/HT4213 for more info. Mobile Excellence Awards – WINNER: Best Mobile Game 2013 Game Connect Asia Pacific – WINNER: Game of The Year 2013, Technical Excellence, Excellence in Art Meffy Awards – FINALIST: Best Mobile Game 2013 Real Racing 3 features a continuously expanding roster of officially licensed tracks, a 22-car grid, and over 70 meticulously detailed cars from makers like Ferrari, Porsche, Lamborghini, Mercedes-Benz, Bugatti, and Audi. Plus Real-Time Multiplayer, Social Leaderboards, Time Trials, Ghost Challenges, and innovative Time Shifted Multiplayer™ (TSM) technology, allowing you to race anyone, anytime, anywhere. **This is a resource-intensive game featuring extremely high quality visuals. Please make sure you have at least 1.5GB of free space on your device.** PRAISE FOR REAL RACING 3 “Feels a full generation ahead of the competition” (IGN, 9.1/10, Editors’ Choice) “A stunning visual masterpiece on mobile” (Touch Arcade) “Sets the new standard on mobile for racing games” (Pocket Gamer, 9/10, Gold Award) REAL CARS Drive Real Racing’s largest roster of cars yet – don’t miss our new manufacturers like Ferrari, Porsche, Lamborghini, Mercedes-Benz, Bugatti, and Audi. Take the wheel of over 70 intensely detailed vehicles and test your skills on an authentic 22-car race grid – the most epic racing experience on any handheld. REAL TRACKS Burn rubber on a full lineup of 12 real tracks in multiple configurations from top locations around the world, including the latest arrivals Circuit de Catalunya and Dubai Autodrome, plus Mazda Raceway Laguna Seca, Circuit de Spa-Francorchamps, Silverstone, Hockenheimring, and many more. REAL PEOPLE Real Racing 3 brings innovative multiplayer modes for anyone, anytime, anywhere. Get bumper to bumper with friends and rivals in global Real-Time Multiplayer, powered by Game Center™. When your friends and rivals aren’t online, drop into any race to challenge AI-controlled versions of your friends in Time-Shifted Multiplayer™. If you want to hone your skills to perfection, take on Time Trial Ghost Challenges, allowing you to learn from the very best. MORE CHOICES THAN EVER Compete in over 1500 events, including Cup races, Eliminations, Endurance challenges, and Drag Races. Choose from a diverse range of upgrades to maximize your car’s performance. View the action from a variety of camera angles, tweak the HUD and fine-tune the controls to your personal preference. THE PREMIER RACING EXPERIENCE Powered by the remarkable Mint™ 3 Engine, Real Racing 3 features detailed car damage, fully functioning rear view mirrors, and dynamic reflections for truly HD racing. Enjoy a rich, next-gen game with the most advanced cross-platform social and competitive racing community ever. Real Racing 3 delivers it all and pushes the boundaries with every update. Welcome to the definitive racing experience for everyone, everywhere. __ Terms of Service : http://www.ea.com/terms-of-service Game EULA: http://tos.ea.com/legalapp/mobileeula/US/en/GM/ Visit https://help.ea.com/ for assistance or inquiries. EA may retire online features and services after 30 days’ notice posted on www.ea.com/1/service-updates Important Consumer Information: requires a persistent Internet connection (network fees may apply); requires acceptance of EA’s Privacy &amp; Cookie Policy, TOS and EULA includes in-game advertising; collects data through third party analytics technology (see Privacy &amp; Cookie Policy for details); contains direct links to the Internet and social networking sites intended for an audience over 13</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7027_09_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple4/v4/a7/45/03/a7450347-16b9-6e17-4940-ba39b52a117b/mzl.docfqrwa.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7027-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7027_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:29:54">http://www.games.com/game/oranginalplan/weaphones-firearms-simulator</link><title>Weaphones Firearms Simulator</title><description>Realistic Sound, Smoke, Flash &amp; Recoil Effects Firing and Shell Ejection Animations Full Interaction and Control Authentic Weapon Mechanics 100% Customizable to Fit User's Hand Size and Preference</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7027_10_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/91lZKgqALsL._SL160_.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>