<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7029">best buy store closings</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:03:16" name="Games.com" id="FW14-e048"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e048-7029-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7029_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:03:17">http://www.games.com/game/infinite-interactive/puzzle-quest-2</link><title>Puzzle Quest 2</title><description>*New holiday sale price for a limited time* Become a Sorcerer, Templar, Barbarian or Assassin and experience the ultimate Match-3 Puzzle-RPG! Featuring optimized touch controls, visual effects and graphics exclusively for iPhone 3GS, iPhone 4, iPad and iPod touch 3rd Gen (32 GB and above)!  WHAT THE PRESS SAYS ** Pocket Gamer - Silver Award Winner! ** IGN: 8 of 10 – ‘Impressive’ ** Slide To Play: “…the best Match-3 game on the platform, bar none.” ** touchArcade: “…superior product in every imaginable way and a great game all on its lonesome.” ** IntoMobile: “…if you enjoy match-3 puzzle games, then you absolutely, positively need to get Puzzle Quest 2. It’s just that good.” EPIC QUEST – OVER 40 HOURS OF ADVENTURE! Escape to a fantasy world filled with amazing creatures, powerful magic, and challenging mini-games! Addicting Match-3 gameplay is blended seamlessly with immersive role-playing in this sequel to the award-winning Puzzle Quest! Jump right into the action and customize your character with any one of four classes, each with different skills and abilities. Gain experience, earn treasure, earn new spells and forge new equipment! Are you brave enough to reclaim the once peaceful village of Verloren from the evil clutches of the demon Gorgon? -Simple but deep rewards and customization -New mini-games to earn treasure and experience -All new original story -Five different game modes included: Tournament, Mini-games, Quest, Quick Battle, and Endurance / Survival -Three difficulty levels – Easy, Normal, Hard MULTIPLAYER Battle head-to-head anywhere, against anyone, anytime! Play online via Game Center or via a Bluetooth or WiFi connection. Level-up your characters and put them to the ultimate test! Can you reach the top of the Game Center leaderboards? NEW TOUCH CONTROLS EXCLUSIVE TO IPHONE, IPOD TOUCH AND IPAD  Play Match-3 puzzles like you have never experienced before. Cast spells, travel the world, interact with other characters, buy new weapons and armor and level up – all with the touch of your finger. THE ULTIMATE CHARACTER PROGRESSION AND CUSTOMIZATION Puzzle Quest 2 is designed to be easy to learn, but hard to master, making it great for players of all ages. Four different character classes: Sorcerer, Templar, Barbarian and Assassin - dramatically change as you learn new skills and abilities and gather new items, armor and weapons. Purchase resources such as wood, leather, and metal to significantly upgrade your items. UNIVERSAL APP Purchase Puzzle Quest 2 once and play it across all of your Apple devices! APPLE’S GAME CENTER \- Achievements \- Leaderboards \- Multiplayer We recommend that you update your device to the latest iOS version before playing. We also recommend that you close the game before downloading the update. To do so, double-tap the home button to display the recent apps bar. Press and hold the Namco application icon until a red minus appears, then tap the minus sign to close the application. **GET MORE GREAT NAMCO GAMES!** Toss The Ball, Pool Pro Online 3, Isaac Newton’s Gravity, and more! GIFT THIS APP: Click the "Buy App" arrow on the iTunes® App Store to give to your friends Be the first to know! Get inside NAMCO info on great deals, plus the latest game updates, tips &amp; more… VISIT US: http://namcobandaigames.com/ios LIKE US: http://www.facebook.com/NamcoBandai TWEET US: http://twitter.com/Filthierich</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7029_01_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple6/v4/77/90/b1/7790b1f5-f0a4-7128-c952-030a78d93b3d/mzl.fbrutbce.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7029-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7029_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:04:42">http://www.games.com/game/loeschware/five-little-monkeys</link><title>Five Little Monkeys</title><description>-&gt; Highly recommended for Education by the App Store, as well as teachers and parents around the world! "My Kids LOVE This App" \--by Father of 3 (Under 4 yrs.) "Perfect. Great fun for a toddler. My best toddler buy yet." \--by Ro-dub _____________________________________________ "Mama Called the Doctor and the Doctor Said, "No More Monkeys Jumping on the Bed!" Designed by parents of young children for young children (pre-toddler and older), Five Little Monkeys is a fun, interactive musical counting game based on the popular rhyme everybody knows and loves. COUNTING: Children build counting and math skills as well as color recognition by adding and subtracting different colored monkeys from play, simply by touching a monkey, or shaking your iPhone. OPPOSITES: Interactive objects teach concepts like stop/go, on/off, open/close, utilizing an alarm clock that rings, a lamp, a telephone, a door, even a monkey family portrait that reacts to your child's touch! READING: Following along with the highlighted words to the rhyme fosters word recognition and sentence building skills, an important step toward a lifetime of reading and learning. SINGING: 3 original music types to play and sing to; Country, Rock, or Pop for sing-a-long. Explore, touch, and control the game with interactive options that allow creative freedom for your preschooler. This application might keep your little monkey from jumping on the bed! \- Designed for young children from 1 year and up ( pre-toddler to preschool ) \- New interactive features that your child will love, including toys that react to touch, a peekaboo dog, and a stop-n-go button that starts and stops the monkeys jumping to allow children to explore the monkeys' bedroom. \- Touch or "Shake" the Monkeys to watch them do somersaults! \- Press the highest number in the left corner to add the monkeys back to the bed. Watch them drop back into action! \- Interact with objects throughout the bedroom -&gt;Enjoy our other educational apps for children: \- Old MacDonald \- My A B C Train \- Word Wheel \- Big Top Circus \- The Bear Went Over the Mountain CONTACT US: Email us at support@loeschware.com for any questions. We will promptly respond to you. Thanks, LoeschWare LLC ***LoeschWare cares about children and respects your privacy. *** Five Little Monkeys: \- Does not collect any information \- Does not contain ads \- Does not contain in-app purchases \- Does not contain integration with social networks \- Does not use analytics / data collection tools \- Does include an indirect link to LoeschWare apps in the iTunes AppStore Please see our Privacy Policy for more details: http://www.loeschware.com</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7029_02_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/b6/86/5a/b6865ada-750d-86ba-4043-bc7e3a95f3ef/mzl.ahtnvkfr.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7029-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7029_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:08:14">http://www.games.com/game/namco-bandai-games/puzzle-quest-2-freemium</link><title>Puzzle Quest 2 Freemium</title><description>Become a Sorcerer, Templar, Barbarian or Assassin and experience the ultimate Match-3 Puzzle-RPG! Featuring optimized touch controls, visual effects and graphics exclusively for iPhone 3GS, iPhone 4, iPad and iPod touch 3rd Gen (32 GB and above)!  WHAT THE PRESS SAYS ** Pocket Gamer - Silver Award Winner! ** IGN: 8 of 10 – ‘Impressive’ ** Slide To Play: “…the best Match-3 game on the platform, bar none.” ** touchArcade: “…superior product in every imaginable way and a great game all on its lonesome.” ** IntoMobile: “…if you enjoy match-3 puzzle games, then you absolutely, positively need to get Puzzle Quest 2. It’s just that good.” FULL VERSION FEATURES: EPIC QUEST – OVER 40 HOURS OF ADVENTURE! Escape to a fantasy world filled with amazing creatures, powerful magic, and challenging mini-games! Addicting Match-3 gameplay is blended seamlessly with immersive role-playing in this sequel to the award-winning Puzzle Quest! Jump right into the action and customize your character with any one of four classes, each with different skills and abilities. Gain experience, earn treasure, earn new spells and forge new equipment! Are you brave enough to reclaim the once peaceful village of Verloren from the evil clutches of the demon Gorgon? -Simple but deep rewards and customization  -New mini-games to earn treasure and experience -All new original story  -Five different game modes included: Tournament, Mini-games, Quest, Quick Battle, and Endurance / Survival -Three difficulty levels – Easy, Normal, Hard  MULTIPLAYER Battle head-to-head anywhere, against anyone, anytime! Play online via Game Center or via a Bluetooth or WiFi connection. Level-up your characters and put them to the ultimate test! Can you reach the top of the Game Center leaderboards? NEW TOUCH CONTROLS EXCLUSIVE TO IPHONE, IPOD TOUCH AND IPAD  Play Match-3 puzzles like you have never experienced before. Cast spells, travel the world, interact with other characters, buy new weapons and armor and level up – all with the touch of your finger. THE ULTIMATE CHARACTER PROGRESSION AND CUSTOMIZATION Puzzle Quest 2 is designed to be easy to learn, but hard to master, making it great for players of all ages. Four different character classes: Sorcerer, Templar, Barbarian and Assassin - dramatically change as you learn new skills and abilities and gather new items, armor and weapons.  Purchase resources such as wood, leather, and metal to significantly upgrade your items. UNIVERSAL APP Purchase Puzzle Quest 2 once and play it across all of your Apple devices! APPLE’S GAME CENTER \- Achievements \- Leaderboards \- Multiplayer We recommend that you update your device to the latest iOS version before playing. We also recommend that you close the game before downloading the update. To do so, double-tap the home button to display the recent apps bar. Press and hold the Namco application icon until a red minus appears, then tap the minus sign to close the application. **GET MORE GREAT NAMCO GAMES!** Toss The Ball, Pool Pro Online 3, Isaac Newton’s Gravity, and more! GIFT THIS APP: Click the "Buy App" arrow on the iTunes® App Store to give to your friends Be the first to know! Get inside NAMCO info on great deals, plus the latest game updates, tips &amp; more… VISIT US: http://namcobandaigames.com/ios LIKE US: http://www.facebook.com/NamcoBandai TWEET US: http://twitter.com/Filthierich</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7029_03_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/e0/35/67/e03567b3-46d2-c84d-0d22-458855c9857a/mzl.bdnwuhfi.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7029-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7029_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:13:06">http://www.games.com/game/image-form-international-ab/anthill</link><title>Anthill</title><description>@ GAME OF THE WEEK! @ The best game on the App Store just got even better! Due to popular demand, we've added four new ant upgrades and a brand new campaign! This obviously means lots of new wonderful, terrible critters and sceneries. @@@@@ AWARDS: \- Anthill was selected as iPad Game of the Week in October, 2011! \- Anthill made the Quality Index Top 10 list in October, 2011! REVIEWS: "A must-have." - slidetoplay.com, 4/4 "Strategy done right." - 148apps.com, 4.5/5 "…the execution is amazingly fluid and perfectly suited to iOS." — iFanzine, 4.5/5 "…it’s hard to not call it one of the best, if not the best line drawing TD title available for the iOS." — the-app-shack.com, 10/10 "…a total blast!" — unboundgamer.com, 9/10 Featured on thegametrail.com! Thanks guys! @@@@@ FOR QUEEN AND COLONY! Join the ranks of Anthill, a tactical trail defense game based on the real-world behavior of ants. The award-winning user interface enables you to draw pheromone trails to direct your troops, moving streams of ants rather than individuals. Engage in the mission to protect your hill as wave upon wave of enemy bugs are thrown at you. Don't wait, join the colony today! EAT WHAT YOU KILL Take down a bug with your soldiers, then direct your workers to bring back the carcass for dinner - yum! SURGICAL STRIKES Simply tap the screen to send out bomber ants to take out those pesky ladybugs. Satisfaction guaranteed! UPGRADES! UPGRADES! UPGRADES! Buy permanent upgrades for your troops! Turn your bombers into carpet bombers, inspire courage in your workers, and make your soldiers more brutal. Boo-ya! UNIVERSAL APP Buy once, use for both your iPad and iPhone! We don't charge double for the same game. @@@@@ QUOTES FROM THE FORUMS: "…It the kind of game that grabs you and doesn't let go untill you can't stay awake anymore and the ipod touch slips out of your sweaty hands and falls on the floor." — eugekava "This is a really great TD game that feels so different from the rest. It oozes with charm and personality while having a top notch gameplay! It's frantic, fast paced but most of all fun! That's all, go for it guys you won't regret it :)" — killercow "It truly is a unique and fun change to the genre (...), and well worth the money." — paul hendricks @@@@@ With close to 40 exciting missions, beautiful surroundings, dozens of different enemies and many days of gameplay, you will love your queen and colony! Compatible with iPhone 3GS and newer, 3rd generation iPod touch devices and all iPad models. iPhone4: REQUIRES iOS 4.2 OR NEWER. VISIT US: www.anthillgame.com FOLLOW US: www.twitter.com/imageform LIKE US: www.facebook.com/imageform</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7029_04_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/9b/12/81/9b12810a-0bc9-1865-4a20-47a30acc976f/mzm.wjacqzip.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7029-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7029_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:15:05">http://www.games.com/game/loeschware/five-little-monkeys-hd</link><title>Five Little Monkeys HD</title><description>-&gt; Highly recommended for Education by the App Store, as well as teachers and parents around the world! "My Kids LOVE This App" \--by Father of 3 (Under 4 yrs.) "Perfect. Great fun for a toddler. My best toddler buy yet." \--by Ro-dub _____________________________________________ "Mama Called the Doctor and the Doctor Said, "No More Monkeys Jumping on the Bed!" Designed by parents of young children for young children (pre-toddler to preschool), Five Little Monkeys is a fun, interactive musical counting game based on the popular rhyme everybody knows and loves. -&gt; COUNTING: Children build counting and math skills as well as color recognition by adding and subtracting different colored monkeys from play, simply by touching a monkey, or shaking your iPhone. -&gt; OPPOSITES: Interactive objects teach concepts like stop/go, on/off, open/close, utilizing an alarm clock that rings, a lamp, a telephone, a door, even a monkey family portrait that reacts to your child's touch! -&gt; READING: Following along with the highlighted words to the rhyme fosters word recognition and sentence building skills, an important step toward a lifetime of reading and learning. -&gt; SINGING: 3 original music types to play and sing to; Country, Rock, or Pop for sing-a-long. Explore, touch, and control the game with interactive options that allow creative freedom for your preschooler. This application might keep your little monkey from jumping on the bed! \- Designed for young children from 1 year and up ( pre-toddler to preschool ) \- New interactive features that your child will love, including toys that react to touch, a peekaboo dog, and a stop-n-go button that starts and stops the monkeys jumping to allow children to explore the monkeys' bedroom. \- Touch or "Shake" the Monkeys to watch them do somersaults! \- Press the highest number in the left corner to add the monkeys back to the bed. Watch them drop back into action! \- Interact with objects throughout the bedroom **Enjoy our other educational apps for children: \- Old MacDonald \- My A B C Train \- Word Wheel \- Big Top Circus \- The Bear Went Over the Mountain CONTACT US: Email us at info@loeschware.com for any questions. We will promptly respond to you. Thanks, LoeschWare LLC ***LoeschWare cares about children and respects your privacy. *** Five Little Monkeys HD: \- Does not collect any information \- Does not contain ads \- Does not contain in-app purchases \- Does not contain integration with social networks \- Does not use analytics / data collection tools \- Does include an indirect link to LoeschWare apps in the iTunes AppStore Please see our Privacy Policy for more details: http://www.loeschware.com</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7029_05_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/4c/23/65/4c2365bf-94c8-2e44-e927-75f45d81593b/mzl.umdjopwd.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7029-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7029_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:18:16">http://www.games.com/game/namco-bandai-games/time-crisis-2nd-strike-hd</link><title>TIME CRISIS 2ND STRIKE HD</title><description>[Warning] Please DO NOT play this application with devices running iOS7. Otherwise your save data may disappear. We are currently looking into the cause of this issue. We apologize for any inconvenience this may cause you and appreciate for your understanding. This application does not currently support iOS7. \------------ Get it Now! FREE HD iPad-only version! IMPORTANT: About UPGRADE In this version of TIME CRISIS 2ND STRIKE, you can play the first (PROLOGUE) stage and the first Crisis Mission for free. To unlock the remaining 9 stages and 9 missions, and you'll need to purchase (upgrade to) the full version of the game. If you have already purchased the upgrade with your iTunes account, touch the “RESTORE UPGRADE” button at the Main Menu to upgrade free of charge. Critical Acclaim for non-HD version: \+ slide to Play: 4/4 (Must Have) "If you love shooters, buy this game" \+ touchArcade: "If you enjoyed the first Time Crisis Strike, then you should enjoy Time Crisis 2nd Strike as well." \+ POCKETGAMER.fr: Silver Award Winner, 8/10 TIME CRISIS, the legendary arcade cinematic rail shooting series from NAMCO, the creator of PAC-MAN, TEKKEN and ACE COMBAT, thunders back to the App Store with a vengeance! With exhilarating gameplay, next-generation graphics, and an electrifying soundtrack, TIME CRISIS SECOND STRIKE takes the touch-shooting genre to the next level! As global agent Giorgio Bruno, race against the clock on your iPad to stop multiple terror attacks from the world’s most evil forces. IMMERSIVE CONTROLS Innovative controls bring you close to the action! Tap to fire your handgun, drag a finger and unload a fury of machine gun fire as you rush to save the world! MULTIPLE WEAPONS Aside from a standard-issue handgun, your arsenal includes a machine gun, shotgun and grenade launcher. Watch out for special enemies to resupply your ammo. MULTIPLE GAME MODES \+ EPISODE MODE: clear 10 action-packed stages before the countdown timer reaches 0 and enjoy spectacular cinematic scenes. \+ COMPETITION: TIME ATTACK MODE: pick any stage from the completed episodes and try to clear it as fast as possible. \+ COMPETITION: SCORE ASSAULT MODE: similar to TIME ATTACK, this time try to score as many points as possible. \+ CRISIS MISSION: Prove your abilities in short shooting-skill scenarios. \+ LEADERBOARD CHALLENGE: Score ranking supported in all 10 stages. Blast your way to the Game Center's #1 score! Check out your predicted ranking while you fight your way through each stage: it's a thrill like never before! UNIQUE ACHIEVEMENTS (with Game Center support) \+ Beat the game? It’s not over! Try to obtain all 50 Game Center achievements! SCORE ASSAULT TIPS Activate your RAGE by shooting rapidly at enemies and scoring point multipliers. Points awarded vary: Head-shots &gt; Body-shots &gt; Limb-shots. \- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - Also from NAMCO, AVAILABLE NOW! Discover some of the best PAC-MAN games ever released for hours of entertainment on your Apple device! \- PAC-MATCH PARTY \- PAC-CHAIN</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7029_06_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/10/ca/80/mzl.iybwrouu.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7029-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7029_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:19:45">http://www.games.com/game/nine-pound-studios/xenome-episode-1</link><title>Xenome Episode 1</title><description>*** In honor of our new Verizon users, Xenome is now on sale! *** NEW! Support added for 2nd generation devices! Welcome to Silica Flats. A wasteland ripe for exploration. That is, if you manage to stay alive long enough. The land looks different from what you remember, but that's bound to happen to anyone who's been in cryo-stasis for the last 250 years. You've been reactivated during the advent of the Union-Prime war and both factions want your allegiance. More importantly, either faction would rather see you back on ice (in one way or another) than to be aligned with their enemy. Welcome to your first immersion into the Xenome Universe. A 3D Action/Adventure RPG that will have you struggling for survival as you unravel the mystery of who you are and what your purpose is.                                  ------------------------------------------------------------------- “Xenome, Episode 1 has the right stuff when it comes to role-playing” - Pocket Gamer 7/10 “With a rich storyline, about a dozen hours of gameplay, and a true feeling of freedom, there isn’t much not to like about this game. In fact, if this trend keeps up, the “iPhone’s WoW” may be coming sooner than we think. In other words, do yourself a favor and go buy Xenome now.” - SlideToPlay 4/4 “It's clear Nine Pound Studios spent a lot of time on the artwork, music, sounds and in-game graphics because they're as good as anything I've experienced in mobile gaming.” - TUAW "It begs the question of how you can manage to follow up after something this epic?" - Appspy "One of the most robust games in the App Store." - NoDPad "An excellent adventure with an engaging storyline... [that] managed to take gaming on the platform an immense step further than anyone else" - Gamezebo                                ------------------------------------------------------------------- FULLY IMMERSIVE Open 3D environment using cutting edge technology, ready to be explored. INTENSE GAMEPLAY Realtime combat and powerful abilities. Gain new skills as you level, and steal XNA (alien DNA) to take on new passive and active abilities of native creatures. ENORMOUS GAME WORLD Over 5 square miles of seamless, immersive territory teeming with mutated creatures, dangerous aberrations of nature, and other hostiles. GAIN EXPERIENCE Get powerful new items, skills and wealth while performing missions and killing monsters. CUSTOMIZE YOUR CHARACTER Choose from over 35 skills and abilities and build up your stats with over 500 items that best suit your play style. INTUITIVE INTERFACE Stylized, duel-stick control system, drop down map, quest and stats panes, tap to target, and customizable skill interface. AN ENGAGING STORYLINE Over 10 hours of deep plot lines to unravel as you make your way through the wastelands. LOADED WITH SECRETS FOR THE ADVENTUROUS Enough creatures, missions and areas to keep you playing long after the main plot has unfolded. Please note - If you are experiencing crashing, you may need to close other background apps in iOS 4.0</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7029_07_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/68/2b/f9/mzi.aulcttfk.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7029-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7029_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:20:32">http://www.games.com/game/telltale/puzzle-agent-2-hd</link><title>Puzzle Agent 2 HD</title><description>Agent Nelson Tethers just solved the biggest case of his career. So why isn't he satisfied? There’s still the case of a missing eraser factory foreman, a whispering madness is still creeping from mind to mind, and a troubling recurrence of... creatures... is lurking into the town. The FBI's Department of Puzzle Research has marked the case closed -- are they sweeping it under the rug? Or worse, do they not even care? Worried that the case will languish forever unsolved, Tethers must go rogue and venture back to the eerie town of Scoggins, Minnesota to solve the mystery of "the Hidden People" once and for all. Sequel to award-winning Puzzle Agent: * TouchArcade – Best of iPad 2010 * IGN – Best iPhone Game of E3 2010 * PC Gamer – Puzzle Game of the Year 2010 * Adventure Gamers – Game of the Year CREEPY PUZZLE ADVENTURE WITH MYSTERY &amp; DARK HUMOR! _____________________________________________ MORE GREAT ADVENTURES BY TELLTALE GAMES: Walking Dead: The Game Back to the Future Monkey Island Tales Puzzle Agent Sam &amp; Max: The Penal Zone Wallace &amp; Gromit The Last Resort Gift this App: Click the arrow next to “Buy App” on the iTunes® App Store. Never miss out on great deals, news and updates. Visit us at… TelltaleGames.com facebook.com/TelltaleGames twitter.com/TelltaleGames youtube.com/TelltaleGames</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7029_08_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/c9/89/16/mzl.jrckxzmv.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7029-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7029_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:21:36">http://www.games.com/game/punk-pie/aurifi</link><title>Aurifi</title><description>NEWS Click the 'support' link to find out about compatibility. Aurifi works with all standard installations of 3.1.3, and will not work with *non-standard* installs. Thanks! A NEW FORM OF PLAY FOR THE NEXT GENERATION Aurifi is a ground-breaking, beautiful, challenging, rewarding Audio Game. (Pronounced ‘or-if-eye’) ***** "...an enjoyable and oddly hypnotic experience." - 7/10 BRONZE AWARD PocketGamer "Aurifi marks the beginning of a completely new genre of gaming" - BornTechie "4 out of 5 : Download this app if you're ready to try a state-of-the-art audio game" - Snapcase07, Appolicious "Aurifi is unlike any game available for the iPhone, and is likely the first of its kind for any gaming device." - Appolicious "Aurifi uses a finely-woven tapestry of sound effects and music to create a gaming experience unlike anything you've experienced before." -TouchMyApps "5 New App Store Games to Watch" - TouchMyApps (writing of Aurifi) "Welcome to the advent of audio games on the iPhone and iPod Touch" - N4G "Really relaxing, great sexy female voice and just so incredibly innovative- 4 stars" - AverageApper iTunes Podcast ***** It is the first audio-only game for iPhone and iPod Touch. Aurifi combines the two things the iPhone and iPod Touch do best - music and organic interaction. What is an Audio Game? You can play Aurifi with your eyes closed, this is a 100% sonic experience. In video games, players interact with graphics, moving them, aligning them, and reacting to them. In the Aurifi Audio Game, players interact with sound in very much the same way. Sounds different? It is! Aurifi is an ever-changing sonic landscape that is breathtaking. At the same time it invites you to react, control, fine-tune, identify and dial yourself into your surroundings. The bespoke musical elements are designed to help you feel moods, emotions and progression. Aurifi was developed specifically for the iPhone and iPod Touch platforms, to make best use of the device’s methods of interaction. Shake, slide and tilt to control the sounds and complete the challenges, and also contribute to the sound. About the Audio Video Game makers pour loads of time and effort into making the visual appearance of games spectacular - we have done the same for the audio in Aurifi. Each sound element has been carefully crafted to provide you with a luscious experience that sounds incredible. You need to wear earphones or headphones to play. Once you are plugged in to Aurifi, you will realise that the ‘game environment’ is massive - you interact with sounds in a 3D audio environment with intense depth. We have designed Aurifi to ‘break outside’ of the device, and get away from the limitations of that small screen. You know that rush that you get when a big beat or bass-line come in on your favourite records? THAT is the reward in Aurifi - as you pass each micro-challenge, you hear another layer of the music, and they are designed to sound great. A staggering number of audio samples have been written to work with each other. This means we can mix-up the experience, so you very rarely hear the same music twice. No pre-defined musical path here - we’ve created an entirely new audio game engine to vary the audio experience each time you play. Like any iPhone or iPod Touch experience, the quality of audio experience can be enhanced by the use of excellent earphones or headphones. If all this sounds great, but you want to hear it before you buy, go to aurifi.com to listen to the audio demo. Make sure you come back! Allow yourself to fall in love with Aurifi. Aurifi has been created for iPhone and iPod Touch by an award-winning team of concept designers, developers, musicians, sound designers and engineers.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7029_09_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/a9/8b/29/mzi.rmejbkcl.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7029-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7029_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:25:33">http://www.games.com/game/loeschware/five-little-monkeys-christmas</link><title>Five Little Monkeys Christmas</title><description>An Apple handpicked selection for the "App Store Essentials: Apps for Toddlers" -&gt; A Toddler Favorite ! -&gt; Featured and recommended by many parents, teachers, and specialists around the world! "My Kids LOVE This App" \--by Father of 3 (Under 4 yrs.) "Perfect. Great fun for a toddler. My best toddler buy yet." \--by Ro-dub _______________________________________ Mama Called the Doctor and the Doctor Said, "CHRISTMAS Monkeys Jumping on the Bed!" Five Little Monkeys is a fun, interactive musical counting game based on the popular rhyme everybody knows and loves. Now, celebrate the Holidays with our monkey family! Christmas has come to the monkey house! **All of your favorite features from the original, with Christmas-themed surprises! COUNTING: Children build counting and math skills as well as color recognition by adding and subtracting different colored monkeys from play, simply by touching a monkey, or shaking your iPhone. READING: Following along with the highlighted words to the rhyme fosters word recognition and sentence building skills, an important step toward a lifetime of reading and learning. SINGING: 3 original music types to play and sing to; Country, Rock, or Pop for sing-a-long, now with a CHRISTMAS JINGLE. OPPOSITES &amp; MORE: Interactive objects teach concepts like stop/go, on/off, open/close, utilizing an alarm clock that rings, a lamp, a telephone, a door, even a monkey family portrait that reacts to your child's touch! **Interactive features that your child will love, including toys that react to touch, a peekaboo dog, and a stop-n-go button that starts and stops the monkeys jumping to allow children to explore the monkeys' bedroom. **New interactive Christmas surprises! ** "Shake" the iDevice for an acrobatic surprise! ** Press the highest number in the left corner to add the monkeys back to the bed. Watch them drop back into action! ** Touch the present for a blustery snowstorm! \+ Enjoy our other educational apps for children: \- Old MacDonald \- My A B C Train \- Word Wheel \- Big Top Circus \- The Bear Went Over the Mountain CONTACT US: Email us at support@loeschware.com for any questions. We will gladly respond to you promptly! Thanks, LoeschWare LLC ***LoeschWare cares about children and respects your privacy. *** Five Little Monkeys Christmas: \- Does not collect any information \- Does not contain ads \- Does not contain in-app purchases \- Does not contain integration with social networks \- Does not use analytics / data collection tools \- Does include a parent-only link to LoeschWare apps in the iTunes AppStore Please see our Privacy Policy for more details: http://www.loeschware.com</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7029_10_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple6/v4/0a/09/05/0a09050b-2f75-17d9-04ec-47b6001004c0/mzl.pejvsltp.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>