<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7051">dinosaur names</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:50:28" name="Games.com" id="FW14-e048"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e048-7051-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7051_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:50:29">http://www.games.com/game/giggleup-kids-apps-and-educational-games-pty/awesome-shape-puzzles-123-a-fun-way-of-learning-first-words-for-kids</link><title>Awesome Shape Puzzles 123 - A fun way of learning first words for kids</title><description>\- Let learning become your children's favourite pastime with this fun shape puzzle game that doubles as a picture dictionary featuring more than 150 new words! \- Multiple play modes to choose from, including a basic shape-fitting mode, an easy mode with 2-4 piece puzzles and a hard mode with 7-10 piece puzzles. \- Play Awesome Shape Puzzles 123 in more languages! Have fun learning new words in different languages including: English, French, Spanish, Japanese, German, Swedish, Russian, Dutch, Portuguese, Norwegian, Danish, Korean, Chinese and Italian. Discover an enjoyable way of learning first words with this originally illustrated shape puzzle created especially for young minds aged 1 to 6. Children will have a blast playing with dancing dolphins, flying airplanes, roaring dinosaurs and more, all the while developing problem solving and shape, pattern, and color recognition skills. Choose from 12 different categories of everyday words (including numbers and letters) and for each object, drag the scrambled puzzle pieces to their right place to complete the picture. Once completed, the object's name will be spelled onscreen and read aloud. For each successfully completed puzzle, the player will be rewarded with a new sticker to add to his/her collection! Accompanied by a friendly voice guidance, children are encouraged to play and learn at their own pace. Multiple play modes allow even the youngest mind to learn and explore with a basic shape-fitting mode, an easy puzzle mode, and a hard puzzle mode for the bigger kids. Awesome Shape Puzzles 123 is the latest all new educational app to join the much-loved Jigsaw Puzzles 123 family which has been among the best-selling kids' games all over the world and has been featured by Apple's App Store. Features: \- Child-friendly interface specifically designed for small fingers \- More than 150 puzzles to solve and new words to learn \- Multiple game modes: ‘single piece’ (whole objects), ‘easy puzzle’ (2-4 piece) and ‘hard puzzle’ (7-10 piece) \- Balloon Pop! Pop as many balloons as you can! A fun little reward for finished puzzles \- Bonus sticker book fun \- A Demo Button that enables auto-fill for optional assistance \- Helpful voice guidance \- Beautifully illustrated original cartoons \- Cheery background music track that can be easily switched on or off \- For iPhone, iPod Touch and iPad Categories featured in Awesome Shape Puzzles 123 include: \+ My First Shapes – Squares, circles, triangles, pentagons, and more. \+ Dinoland – All your child's favourite dinosaurs! \+ Fruity Fun – Apple, strawberry, pear and all their yummy friends. \+ Veggie Party – Let's not forget the veggies! Pumpkin, peas, carrots and more. \+ Toy Wonderland – All our beloved childhood friends. Teddy bear, robot, doll, and more. \+ Busy Wheels – Helicopters, motorcycles and other cool vehicles. \+ Ocean Adventure – The exciting world under the sea and all its amazing creatures. \+ Band Jam! - Learn all the musical instruments. \+ Silly Billy Farm – Old farmer and all your farm animal friends! \+ Playground Fun – Slides, merry-go-rounds, swings and more. \+ My Alphabet Book – Featuring letters A to Z. \+ Numbers and Me – Featuring numbers 1 to 20. \+ ...more categories coming in free future updates! Endless fun and learning to be enjoyed all for the price of one. Or, try our bite-sized version for FREE! Simply search for Awesome Shape Puzzles 123 FREE in the App Store. \-------------- Connect with us! Visit us: http://www.GiggleUp.com Like us: facebook.com/GiggleUpApps Follow us: twitter.com/GiggleUpApps Email us: Support@GiggleUp.com Brought to you by GiggleUp, creators of the award-winning Interactive Telling Time and other educational apps for kids. Our goal is to promote learning through play with the purpose of helping children develop useful learning skills. Our apps have been enjoyed by children and used in classrooms all around the world!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7051_01_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple4/v4/ea/8e/e8/ea8ee815-7ecf-475a-e7cd-3295d869aa76/mzl.mpoqfqev.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7051-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7051_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:51:55">http://www.games.com/game/ogangi-corporation/icallstop-free</link><title>iCallSTOP Free</title><description>Want to awaken your brain, or maybe exercise it a little? Challenge yourself, friends, or others around the globe in iCallSTOP, an exciting, fast-paced word game that will surely deliver a nail-biting, good time! You can Play Solo against the clock. Choose 1 or more Standard Categories (Animal, Color, Country…) from the list to start playing. You can buy Premium Categories from the Options menu, or you can also create your own categories when playing with others. In each round (up to 8 rounds per game), your mission is to quickly reach into the deepest recesses of your brain and extract a word that not only starts with the random letter that appears on your screen, but also matches the categories selected for the game. Don’t let the pressure render you wordless? How quickly can you come up with an animal, a celebrity, and a brand name that begins with the letter “H”? The clock is ticking! Be surprised by the categories you dominate. Can you enter your words fast enough to beat the clock and leave other players in the dust? Don’t forget to call STOP and halt the clock when all your categories are filled in. When playing with others, you can create your own categories, let your imagination run and have fun! Players are now the judge of whether answers are correct or not. Should you chose a friend’s name as the answer under a created Dinosaur category, it may result in a good joke but should not get you any points if other players Challenge your answer. Are you confident that your response is accurate? Do you believe that your opponent’s response can’t possibly be right? Don’t be shy, you can challenge any of the other players’ answers. Good luck and may your words flow swiftly to your fingertips! We’re always excited to hear from you! Please let us know if you have any feedback or questions. Email us at: icallstop@ogangi.com Like us at: http://www.facebook.com/iCallSTOPgame  Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/icallstop - @iCallSTOP</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7051_02_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple2/v4/f3/66/27/f366271e-31a2-6dbf-e211-69389a186e1c/mzl.vczvmvpz.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7051-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7051_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:55:09">http://www.games.com/game/mostafa-berg/dino-squad</link><title>Dino Squad</title><description>**iPhone 5 support !** Features: +Box2d physics +Amazing Ragdoll physics ! +HD and SD graphics. +GameCenter +OpenFeint +17 cool Achievements +Positional audio (requires headphones)! +Easy controls (no buttons, just touch the left or right side of the screen to move the vehicle) +Accelerometer goodness !! (Tilt your phone to balance the car) +25 challenging levels, with more free ones to come in future updates. +Moving Platforms, Elevators, buttons, and many other interactions in the levels +Plays iPod music. +Cute artworks. +Beautiful sounds and music +Suitable for all family members +Very, VERY challenging ! \--------------------------------------------------------------- Story: The events of this game occur in a parallel universe, where man lived at the times of dinosaurs ! Humans were dinosaurs' best friends, they lived a happily in peace till an unfortunate events were about to occur ! Thanks to human's technology at that time, they were able to detect the presence of huge meteors that were about to hit earth, endangering man's giant friends !, oh no !! This is when DinoSquad was formed, with a mission to relocate all dinosaurs on this parallel earth to a safe place in order to avoid their extinction ! Being human, they had to forget someone behind !, a baby T-Rex called "Rawr !" (As named by her dinosaur parents) Take your DinoVehicle on this amazing human/dinosaur adventure to bring "Rawr !" back to her parents before the meteors hit Earth ! P.S: Rawr loves cookies, there are 3 cookies on each level, keep your passenger happy! P.S.S: Rawr also loves speed, it makes her happy !, she'll let you know when you're driving! Good luck officer !! \--------------------------------------------------------------- For more info or help, please visit our help link or just email us directly. We love hearing from gamers like us !</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7051_03_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/ce/a6/2a/cea62a1e-9151-2b39-e4f4-b86aa4dc33f5/mzl.vujprlek.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7051-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7051_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:56:56">http://www.games.com/game/reks/caboose-express-patterns-and-sorting-for-preschool-and-kindergarten</link><title>Caboose Express: Patterns and Sorting for Preschool and Kindergarten</title><description>TWO games in one App for your kindergartener and preschooler: pattern recognition; sorting objects by size and letters/numbers by position. 1\. Complete patterns to help @Reks dinosaur travel from the East coast to the West coast of the USA: * Pattern type(s): ABAB, AABA, AABB, ABC…; * Pattern content: shapes, colors, letters (upper/lower case), numbers, mix of any previous patterns (colors and shapes, numbers and letters, shapes and numbers…); * Narration for each pattern item; * Choice of narration with names or sounds (phonics) of the letters; * Option to drag-and-drop or tap the correct item to continue the pattern; * Caboose helps your child acquire analytical and logical thinking. 2\. Sort by rearranging letters, numbers, and shapes to help @Reks dinosaur travel across Europe: * Rearrange letters in alphabetical order / inverse alphabetical order (option) * Rearrange numbers in increasing / decreasing order (option) * Rearrange shapes from largest to smallest / from smallest to largest (option) * Narration (option) Pattern recognition and completion as well as sorting represent an important developmental skill for preschool children by expanding their intelligence quotient (IQ). It is a cognitive exercise for your child’s brain. Caboose requires the child to compare concepts and recognize patterns, and to compare size / position and sort objects/letters/numbers accordingly. The process of comparing helps the child prepare for learning to recognize shapes, colors, numbers, size, etc. Although all children develop as individuals, the age ration below should provide parents as a starting point in helping their children’s performance: \- Ages 4-5: Can complete without assistance. \- Age 3: Can complete with minimal assistance after directions are given. \- Age 2: Introduction to math concepts -- can complete with adult assistance WATCH VIDEO: http://youtu.be/vlcAUj-_WxE @Reks (aka AtReks) Apps are designed in compliance with Children’s Online Privacy Protection Rule (COPPA). PRIVACY DISCLOSURE: \- Does not contain ads. \- Does contain in-app purchases. \- Does not contain integration with social networks. \- Does not use analytics / data collection tools. \- Does include links to apps by @Reks in the iTunes App Store hidden in the settings section behind child-proof settings button (press and hold). For comments and suggestions or to check our Privacy Policy go to: http://www.atreks.com/ - Thank you!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7051_04_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/b6/7a/58/b67a584b-9393-ec09-5733-c8db07fcd29c/mzl.nvluajue.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7051-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7051_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:57:30">http://www.games.com/game/wonderkind-gmbh/dino-match-dinosaur-pairs-matching-game</link><title>Dino Match - Dinosaur Pairs Matching Game</title><description>The classic memo game with colorful, hand-drawn dino cards Highlights • 3 Game modes: Classic, Dino Names, Arcade • hand-drawn graphics with the lovingly designed dino theme • single player and multiplayer modes • child-friendly navigation • 5 difficulty levels based on the sensible grading of the number of the cards used • Apple Game Center support One of the most popular memo apps is now available in the form of the dinosaur theme: Dino Match – covered picture cards are turned over until all dino pairs are found. Like in all other apps by wonderkind, the dinosaur pictures are lovingly hand-drawn on the interactive play cards. Music and sounds accompany the game and can be turned off if necessary. 3 game modes are available: Classic, Dino Names and Arcade. The app can be played by single or multiple players, both in the arcade mode and in the scorer match with other players (Apple Game Center). Dino Match is the latest app by the Berlin based developer wonderkind, who has already held the top position among children’s apps in 25 countries worldwide with its Wunderwimmelbuch. With Dino Match, wonderkind is raising the bar with another educational app featuring hand-drawn illustrations and intuitive navigation perfect for children.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7051_05_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/b6/7f/d3/b67fd37b-1682-6861-88e1-469865a358ff/mzl.imvhfylm.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7051-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7051_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:59:18">http://www.games.com/game/russpuppy/kids-dinosaurs</link><title>Kids Dinosaurs</title><description>DINOSAURS! ROAARRR!! Fun game for little kids that like big dinosaurs. Tapping a Dinosaur face button will display that Dinosaur at the top of the screen along with a fun sound effect and animation. Simple interface that any kids of any age can quickly master. It's also a fun way to learn the names of different dinosaurs. Features 16 fun big creatures, including: Tyrannasarus, Triceratops, Stegosaurs, Velociraptor, Brachiosaurus, Hypacrosaurus, Pterodactyl, Gryposaurus, Lufengosaurus, Amargasaurus, Ankylosaurus, Archaeopteryx, Elasmosaurus, Protoceratops, Woolly Mammoth, Sabertooth Tiger If you like this app, be sure to check out the other apps by Russpuppy!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7051_06_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple4/v4/0e/1d/43/0e1d43aa-5490-35e5-4127-8b54c46d5289/mzl.xggviskk.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7051-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7051_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:01:29">http://www.games.com/game/studio-sophisti/gamechanger-game-board-for-ipad</link><title>GameChanger: Game Board for iPad</title><description>This App is made for the GameChanger accessory: The Game Board for iPad! Visit www.boardgamechanger.com and learn more about this product. The app contains the board games Animal Mania and The Magic Schoolbus, and two action games named Kaboom and DuckDuck Goose. New games are coming soon and will be announced in the app and on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/boardgamechanger. AnimalMania This board game is about the animals of our world! Learn everything about them as you move around the game board. Imagine traveling from the depths of the sea to the wilds of the jungle. Meet mammals, sea creatures and even prehistoric dinosaurs as different animals challenge your young explorer along the way. With trivia questions, fun tasks and entertaining riddles, everyone one will learn about animals, their habitats and behavior in a whole new way. The Magic School Bus (content by Scholastic) This board game makes science fun! Join Ms. Frizzle and her class on this board game adventure. Explore space, imagine traveling through a human body and learn about the geology of planet earth. It's your choice. This board game comes to life with video clips of the award-winning animated series, interactive trivia and educational mini games with well known characters like Ms. Frizzle, Liz and Arnold! Join The Magic School Bus in this ever-changing game! Game rules will be explained by the iPad, so you can start playing right away!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7051_07_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/e4/0d/54/e40d5479-8f1a-0d4d-6d3e-bd870a89e35c/mzl.ukrbtmvl.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7051-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7051_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:04:49">http://www.games.com/game/22learn/puzzle-toddler-preschool</link><title>Puzzle Toddler Preschool!</title><description>Try for FREE, full version -- 66% OFF Sale -- TODAY: April 7 - 14, 2014 ***** Brought to you by 22LEARN, the creator of Abby Basic Skills Preschool – a winner of Recommended Seal by Parents‘ Choice Awards 2012. ***** A title from our extremely successful Abby series -- all EIGHT (!) RANKED #1 APP FOR KIDS on APP Store in many countries. The long-awaited new puzzle game from 22learn is coming! Do you want some fun for your child? Abby's Preschool Shape Puzzles is a must-have! Let your toddlers play with it, while developing their fine motor skills, and learning names of numerous objects! Abby's Preschool Shape Puzzles, developed by well-loved educational experts with more than two-decade old teaching experience, is a wonderful game for all toddlers. Try it and enjoy how your children make progress while being engaged! Buy this app from our extremely successful series right now! \------------------- Buying this app, you can expect to get: * one for child easy-to-use game mode * ten colorfully illustrated themes (full version only) * the entirety of more than 150 (full version ) cute individual puzzles: \- Toys for Emma \- Toys for Tom (full version only) \- Fairy Tales (full version only) \- Princess Land (full version only) \- Playground (full version only) \- Vehicles I (full version only) \- Vehicles II (full version only) \- Pets (full version only) \- Under The Sea (full version only) \- Dinosaurs (full version only) \- Farm Animals (full version only) * New scenes coming soon! \------------------- What's more, not only will your children love the art of an object assembly, but they will also be kept constanly motivated by the all funny, happily enthusiastic monkey, who is there always ready, waiting to articulate the praise children deserve for their patient efforts! Children will be wondering: how will the monkey show up this time? Will it arrive in its car, or downright jump jovially down with the parachute? And more yet -- yes... we are willing to go to a great lenghts for you -- you can rely on our updates of the various ways the monkey can appear! Your children will thus be sure to quickly fall in love with the monkey character! \------------------- Based on our twenty-year old experience in the design of fun educational tools, we made considerable effort that this app is as appropriate and easy-to-use for this very special age category as possible. We hope that your children will enjoy it the same way as our enthusiastic beta-testers did. If you have any suggestions on how we could further improve the design of our apps, please leave us a message at info@22learn.com. We always appreciate comments on how to make our apps even better! 22learn, your trusted educational apps developer</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7051_08_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/55/ba/80/55ba80a1-6479-31d2-e615-fd98c41f2334/mzl.okfexsqv.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7051-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7051_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:05:39">http://www.games.com/game/innivo/make-a-scene-christmas</link><title>Make a Scene: Christmas</title><description>The festive, animated sticker app for children with descriptive audio and fun sound effects! Join thousands of users already enjoying Make a Scene. Over 10 million scenes created! ***** This has been great for the kids this Christmas. My 5 year old loves it. ***** The best in the series so far! The kids love it. Loads of stickers! Hours of fun. \- WHY PARENTS AND TEACHERS LOVE THIS APP Make A Scene Christmas is a fun interactive game that engages children’s natural sense of creativity. It is aimed primarily at pre-school age children, but will provide hours of entertainment for children (and adults!) of all ages. Helping to develop vocabulary, fine motor skills, co-ordination and creative thinking, Make A Scene offers a great way for your child to play and learn at the same time. Make a Scene Christmas uses drag and drop interactions, descriptive audio, fun sound effects and engaging animations to create an entertaining, educational platform. Children will have endless fun using their imagination to create their very own festive scenes. \- WHY CHILDREN LOVE IT TOO! The game features typical items from the festive period such as Christmas characters, decorations, presents, toys and much more. By dragging and dropping these digital, animated ‘stickers’ onto the different backgrounds available, your child can create a large number of unique scenes. A clear voice-over reads the name of each item aloud, and is accompanied by fun animations and sound effects where possible. \- NO MORE ARGUMENTS! Are your children always arguing over who’s turn it is to use the tablet/phone? We have added multi-touch to our apps so that children can add or move multiple stickers. Great for playing along with children or allowing multiple children to play simultaneously without arguments about whose turn it is! \- SHARE WITH FAMILY AND FRIENDS As parents, we’ve all been there… your child has created a work of art and you would love to proudly display it on Facebook or simply send copies to family. This is of course difficult without getting the camera, scanner or photocopier out! With Make a Scene, once your child has created their masterpiece, at the click of a button, you can share it with friends &amp; family via Facebook, Twitter, email, or simply save a snapshot to your device. \- KEY FEATURES \- Over 90 ‘stickers’ \- 7 animated backgrounds \- 5 animated foregrounds \- Multi touch enabled \- Save scene as an image to your device \- Share your scenes with friends on Facebook, Twitter and email \- Retina graphics support \- Automatic depth of field \- Easy-to-use toolbar and menus \- Descriptive audio \- Engaging animations \- Fun sound effects \- Background sounds to bring the experience to life \- Ability to move and re-arrange ‘stickers’ \- Ability to remove individual ‘stickers’ or reset all ‘stickers’ and position them once again \- A learning experience that will keep your child engaged for hours! \-------------------------------------------------------- We’re always excited to hear from you! If you have any feedback, questions, concerns, please email us at contactus@makeasceneapp.com Or you can: \- VISIT US: makeasceneapp.com \- LIKE US: facebook.com/makeasceneapp \- FOLLOW US: twitter.com/makeasceneapp \-------------------------------------------------------- OTHER APPS IN THIS SERIES \- MAKE A SCENE: PETS \- MAKE A SCENE: FARMYARD \- MAKE A SCENE: UNDER THE SEA \- MAKE A SCENE: SAFARI \- MAKE A SCENE: OUTER SPACE \- MAKE A SCENE: JUNGLE \- MAKE A SCENE: POLAR ADVENTURE \- MAKE A SCENE: PRINCESS FAIRY TALES \- MAKE A SCENE: DINOSAURS</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7051_09_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple4/v4/22/47/9d/22479dee-f87c-6443-85b6-15b7721fb7ed/mzl.doyrbwme.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7051-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7051_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:07:10">http://www.games.com/game/apperleft/dino-quiz</link><title>Dino Quiz</title><description>You know the feeling.... you've seen this Dinosaur so many times, You have it's name is on the tip of your tongue... but you can't get it right. If only you had some letters... Try this addicting game, enjoy the clues use the bombs and don't forget to tell your friends. Features: \- Famous Dinosaur \- Compatible with all devices \- New levels keep coming!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7051_10_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/17/ed/68/17ed6830-6707-1030-cd24-83ecd07f34f6/mzl.poecxbxb.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>