<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7057">web of science</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:15:20" name="Games.com" id="FW14-e048"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e048-7057-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7057_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:15:21">http://www.games.com/game/absolutist/green-moon</link><title>Green Moon</title><description>Grab a ticket to the Moon in this breathtaking adventure!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7057_01_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/www.masque.com/materials/images/items/thumb/9813.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7057-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7057_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:16:34">http://www.games.com/game/big-fish/nightmare-adventures-the-turning-thorn</link><title>Nightmare Adventures: The Turning Thorn</title><description>Uncover A.R.C.A.N.E.'s dark secrets!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7057_02_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/cdn-games.bigfishgames.com/en_nightmare-adventures-the-turning-thorn/nightmare-adventures-the-turning-thorn_feature.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7057-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7057_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:19:36">http://www.games.com/game/halfbrick-studios/jetpack-joyride</link><title>Jetpack Joyride</title><description>You're going for a ride - from the creators of FRUIT NINJA! Now updated to support the beautiful Retina display for the new iPad! ** Winner ** \- Apple Design Award 2012! \- Pocket Gamer - Best Action/Arcade Game 2012 \- Pocket Gamer - iPhone/iPod Touch Game of the Year 2012 \- Pocket Gamer - Overall Game of the Year 2012 \- Gamasutra Mobile Game of 2011 \- TUAW Best iPhone Game of 2011 \- UGO iOS Game of the Year \- Game Revolution Best Mobile Game 2011 \- App Store Rewind, iPhone Game of the Year Runner-up! **** Suit up with a selection of the coolest jetpacks ever made and take to the skies as Barry Steakfries, the lovable hero on a one-way trip to adventure! From the creators of the worldwide phenomenon Fruit Ninja comes the action-packed Jetpack Joyride, Halfbrick's most anticipated iPhone game ever! **** "This is seriously my favorite iPhone game right now. I don't care if you have to go donate blood to afford it, do what you have to do." -- Touch Arcade "Likely the best dollar you'll spend this summer." -- MTV "Jetpack Joyride is, quite simply, an amazing game." -- IntoMobile "Like all the best mobile games, Jetpack Joyride is criminally simple." -- Kotaku "We are already blown away. Halfbrick looks like they have another hit on their hands." -- AppAdvice “A miracle, by all accounts.” - PocketGamer **** Join Barry as he breaks in to a secret laboratory to commandeer the experimental jetpacks from the clutches of science evildoers. After lift-off, simply touch the screen to ascend and release to descend, raining bullets, bubbles, rainbows and lasers downwards as you fly towards higher and higher scores! You'll start off with the legendary Machine Gun Jetpack to scatter the evil scientists, but throughout each game you'll collect coins and complete missions to earn cash and buy new gear in The Stash! Pick your favorite jetpack, snazzy outfit and stock up on items then get back out there for more action! Keen reflexes are your best weapon to avoid the obstacles in your path. These include lasers, electricity fields and even guided missiles, but thankfully this is a top secret lab - there will be even more goodies to pick up and help Barry along the way. Stay out of harm and you'll reach massive scores, unlock Achievements and beat your friends on the online leaderboards! Get a boost of speed and power using the Lil' Stomper, Profit Bird and Crazy Freaking Teleporter, just a selection of the vehicles pickups available - all playable with one touch controls. You can even splash out and upgrade the vehicles with coin magnets or shiny gold plating for that bonus style factor! Stay alive, get funky and lose yourself in Jetpack Joyride. There's so much to see and do, all the time in the world and more than enough jetpacks! As always, Barry Steakfries will provide! **** IMPORTANT NOTICE TO PARENTS This game may contain: \- The ability to purchase optional content using real money. You can disable in-app purchases in the settings menu of your device. \- Promotional material for Halfbrick products and trusted business partners. \- Links to external social networking sites intended for users over the age of 13. \- Direct links to the internet which may open the default web browser on your device. Privacy Policy: http://www.halfbrick.com/pp Terms of Service: http://www.halfbrick.com/tos</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7057_03_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/dc/8c/f1/dc8cf12a-376a-3c06-3e49-60d0dcf7913e/mzl.jhiegqzd.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7057-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7057_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:21:32">http://www.games.com/game/gamescafe/word-web-deluxe</link><title>Word Web Deluxe</title><description>Sweep away these word-smart spiders!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7057_04_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/cdn-games.bigfishgames.com/en_wordweb/wordweb_feature.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7057-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7057_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:24:26">http://www.games.com/game/enrico-de-michele/icrucipuzzle</link><title>iCruciPuzzle</title><description>► 975 top-quality puzzle games are ready to be played! You can generate innumerable puzzles! Remember: ICruciPuzzle, the ORIGINAL, the first reflecting the real game with a keyword/key-sentence. ◀ ► The aim of the crucipuzzle game (or twisted words) is to find and delete some predetermined words among a set of letters, usually shown separately. Once you find all the words in the puzzle, you should create a keyword/key-sentence with the remaining letters in reading order (from left to right, from top down). Typically, you know only the length of each keyword, for example for the key-sentence "twisted words", the length (6, 11) will be known. iCruciPuzzle brings to iPhone, iPod and iPad the classic twisted words game sticking as much as possible to the real game. The game interface is simple and intuitive. iCruciPuzzle is the first of its kind to give a chance to find a keyword/key-sentece, just like the paper game! ► What does this app provide? • English and Italian versions. • Interface for iPhone, iPod and iPad colored and optimized for display screen. • 975 puzzles between Italian and English. • Puzzles creation from the existent puzzles to play forever. • Puzzles (various sizes) using the whole screen available. • Puzzles breakdown in different categories (Miscellaneous, Education, Music, Nature, Sports, Food, Science and Technology, Time, Costume and Society). • 3 levels of difficulty: easy, medium and hard. • Fight against time and time management record. • 3 Puzzle aids, if you can not find a word. • Saving the game state if you receive a call, SMS, or close the app while you play. • Drawing line naturally and immediately. • Selection of the remaining letters in the puzzle by drawing circles, creating the keyword/key-sentence. • Possibility to restart the puzzle. • Possibility to manage and listen to the music on your iPod while you are playing. • Game Center compatibility. • Game instructions and guidance rules. ◆ Leave comments and/or send us an e-mail! Your feedback helps us to improve this app! ◆ ▶ Contact and info: email: enricodemichele@gmail.com web site: www.enricodemichele.com twitter: demicheleenrico facebook: find iCruciPuzzle page</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7057_05_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple6/v4/f6/08/8e/f6088e8d-a3db-7a18-8b6a-964b03666eeb/mzl.pvpkmzwz.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7057-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7057_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:25:43">http://www.games.com/game/involver-games/game-of-nerds</link><title>Game Of Nerds</title><description>The popular web game which was played 1,000,000+ times last year - now on the iPad! Game Of Nerds is an intense, gameshow-like quiz celebration of nerd culture that pits the nerds of the world against each other. Compete in categories that other quiz games won't even acknowledge - from internet memes and science to computer games and cult movies. \- OVER 16,000 QUESTIONS and a total of 15 diverse, nerdy categories that will keep you occupied for weeks and weeks. \- SINGLE PLAYER MODE puts you in fierce competition against friends and the nerds of the world. \- MULTIPLAYER MODE allows for intense duels between 2-6 nerds on the same iPad. \- Create CUSTOM TEAM MEMBERS that stand ready to assist you. \- Watch your WORLD RANK and your NERD LEVEL increase as you get better. \- This isn't some amateur quiz game; it's an intense, streamlined, gameshow-like experience, and every single question was made by a nerd like yourself. The categories are: Science fiction movies. The internet. Chemistry. Action and cult movies. Hardware and gadgets. Physics. Computer software. Fantasy movies. Astronomy. Computer games. Board / card / role-playing games. Biology. Math. Science fiction literature. Fantasy literature.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7057_06_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/85/77/2b/85772b88-341e-1518-6707-cf1aa7cc5e3c/mzl.scparbjp.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7057-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7057_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:29:17">http://www.games.com/game/software-mackiev/thinkin-things-1</link><title>Thinkin' Things 1</title><description>Our children will live and work in an Information Age that we can only begin to imagine. As they master the basic skills of the three R’s, they must now also develop a broader, higher-level set of thinking skills that will transfer to the workplace of the future. Edmark® Thinkin' Things was designed to offer young students experiences with a variety of just such thinking skills: memory, critical thinking, problem solving, and creativity - in short, all the twenty-first century skills that today's young learners need. Set in Toony the Loon’s Lagoon, early learners encounter colorful, fun characters as they complete challenges that are automatically adjusted to meet individual learning needs. With all instructions spoken by the characters, reading is not required so that non-readers can participate fully. FREE LEARNING GUIDE - A teacher's guide is available from the Thinkin' Things site. Click on the "Software MacKiev's Web Site" link at the bottom of this page. Designed for: Pre-K-2, ages 3-8 *** THE FIVE ACTIVITY AREAS 1\. TOONY THE LOON'S LAGOON Students build auditory and visual memory as they repeat Toony the Loon’s musical patterns. They create their own memorable melodies with Toony’s wacky xylophones: glasses, strings, hollow logs, and even squawking chickens! 2\. ORANGA BANGA® Students need to watch and listen carefully as Oranga Banga plays on his funky drum set, and then repeat what he plays. For an even greater auditory challenge, students can ask Oranga to play in the dark! 3\. FEATHERED FRIENDS Young learners will need to put on their thinking caps to create the missing bird in the series. Students will learn about attributes, differences, patterns and analogies. 4\. FRIPPLE™ GUIDES For a fun-filled lesson in Boolean logic, students visit the Fripple Shop and fill customer orders for Fripples while learning to observe, compare, contrast and recognize relationships. 5\. BLOX FLYING SHAPES Students blend music, art, science, and play as they experiment with motion and the illusion of depth, creating works of kinetic art as they control the motion of shapes and the sounds they make. *** FOR EDUCATORS - MORE ABOUT THINKIN' THINGS Thinkin’ Things celebrates intellectual diversity. A student’s musical and rhythmic intelligence may shine when working with Toony the Loon and his xylophones, or visual and spatial intelligence in creating with BLOX, or logical and mathematical intelligence with the Fripple Guides and Feathered Friends. In areas that may not come as naturally to some children, Thinkin’ Things offers warm, friendly experiences in which self-confidence is built, exploration and creativity are fostered, and persistence is rewarded with success. Thinkin’ Things also focuses attention on how students learn. Is a particular student more likely to remember what is seen or what is heard? How do they approach learning? Do they “guess and test?” Once something is “discovered,” do they use that information in another way to “see what happens?” Do they, for example, prefer to take Fripple orders at the door (both auditory and visual), on the phone (auditory only), or by mail (visual only)? Thinkin’ Things promotes learning in each student’s areas of strength while encouraging growth and building skills in other areas as well. Thinkin' Things assesses a student's capabilities as they participate in activities and automatically adjusts the difficulty level as students progress. Teachers can use the "grow slide" to see what their students are learning, to set a particular level, or select a particular exercise. LEARNING OPPORTUNITIES * Compare and contrast attributes * Improve visual and auditory memory * Hypothesize and test rules * Strengthen creativity * Create and discern patterns * Complete visual analogies * Strengthen ability to conceptualize and evaluate * Recognize visual and auditory strengths</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7057_07_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/51/8e/9f/518e9fbf-4259-0e9f-3aa1-a91c8cf2d495/mzl.mnzevofb.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7057-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7057_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:32:43">http://www.games.com/game/tangorang-labs/word-spree-thanksgiving-lite</link><title>Word Spree: Thanksgiving Lite</title><description>Happy Thanksgiving! With Word Spree Thanksgiving, random words fly out from your head and into a hilarious Thanksgiving-themed story of their own. Fill in the blanks with whatever words feel right, and behold a unique and share-worthy Word Spree Thanksgiving story creation. Share your favorite Word Spree Thanksgiving masterpieces with friends through email, Facebook or Twitter. Gobble up over 15 stories! Word Spree categories include: DINNER TIME TRADITIONS TURKEY TALES FAMILY GATHERING GIVING THANKS Use your words with Word Spree Thanksgiving! Game Features: 15 WORD SPREE THANKGIVING STORIES With story titles including “Turkey Pardon”, “Grandma’s Recipe”, “Monster Turkey” and “Embarrassing Family”, the Word Spree Thanksgiving stories that you create and share with your friends will not be holding back the funny. RANDOMIZE OPTION If you’re feeling random, or just stuck on a word, the Randomize button will insert a random word into the word blank you’re on. Feel free to keep randomizing until you’re completely satisfied. RANDOMIZE ALL OPTION If you’re really wishing to tempt fate, the Randomize All button will insert random words for each word blank in the story. If you enjoy spontaneous, unexpected fun, the Randomize All button is highly recommended. SAVE GALLERY Save your Word Spree masterpieces in the Word Spree save gallery. LIKE WORD SPREE THANKSGIVING -- EVEN MORE STORIES ARE AVAILABLE!! 30 Word Spree Classic stories and 30 Science Fiction stories are available for 99 cents each! If you liked the Word Spree Thankgiving stories, then Word Spree Classic will absolutely blow your mind. Word Spree Classic story categories include: SCHOOL SPOOKY HOLIDAYS MOVIES TRAVEL WILD WILD WEB II Word Spree Sci Fi Edition gives you a hilarious way to ponder the depths of space and the boundaries of mankind. Word Spree Sci Fi story categories include: OUTERSPACE TECHNOLOGY FUTURESCAPES SCI FI EPIC CREATURES WEIRD SCIENCE</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7057_08_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/6b/08/b6/mzi.ylzigyzo.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7057-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7057_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:34:25">http://www.games.com/game/involver-games/game-of-nerds-for-iphone</link><title>Game Of Nerds for iPhone</title><description>The popular web game which was played 1,000,000+ times last year - now on the iPhone and iPod Touch! Game Of Nerds is an intense, gameshow-like quiz celebration of nerd culture that pits the nerds of the world against each other. Compete in categories that other quiz games won't even acknowledge - from internet memes and science to computer games and cult movies. \- OVER 16,000 QUESTIONS and a total of 15 diverse, nerdy categories that will keep you occupied for weeks and weeks. \- SINGLE PLAYER MODE puts you in fierce competition against friends and the nerds of the world. \- MULTIPLAYER MODE allows for intense duels between 2-6 nerds on the same iPhone/iPod. \- Create CUSTOM TEAM MEMBERS that stand ready to assist you. \- Watch your WORLD RANK and your NERD LEVEL increase as you get better. \- This isn't some amateur quiz game; it's an intense, streamlined, gameshow-like experience, and every single question was made by a nerd like yourself. The categories are: Science fiction movies. The internet. Chemistry. Action and cult movies. Hardware and gadgets. Physics. Computer software. Fantasy movies. Astronomy. Computer games. Board / card / role-playing games. Biology. Math. Science fiction literature. Fantasy literature.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7057_09_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/a6/8d/09/a68d0950-e6ee-6721-cb00-26b0535d9361/mzl.nzfqvhqo.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7057-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7057_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:37:12">http://www.games.com/game/lightwood-consultancy/word-search-party</link><title>Word Search Party</title><description>Word Search Party is a polished and fun word puzzle game which lets you challenge your friends or find opponents online using Game Center. It's the first ever competitive multi-player word search game, and the best looking and most playable word puzzle on the App Store! Game features: ☆ The first ever competitive multi-player word search game! ☆ The best looking, most playable word puzzle game on the App Store ☆ Unlimited puzzles - it's different every time you play! ☆ Track your progress using Game Center Leaderboards and Achievements ☆ All features and game modes are available in the free app ☆ Upgrade via in-app purchase to access more word lists, or create your own ☆ Unlock "hidden words" mode for an extra challenge! ☆ Supports accented characters for non-English word lists - use it as a study aid! iPhone/iPod touch Features ☆ Play solo, head-to-head or online against up to 3 opponents in real time! ☆ Game Center integration: invite your friends or find random opponents online ☆ Stunning retina display graphics with a choice of six colour themes ☆ Three levels of difficulty ☆ Play using any word list from the Word Search Party library ☆ Quick Play option gets you into a game in seconds ☆ Brag about your victories to your Facebook friends iPad Features ☆ Designed with teachers and classroom use in mind ☆ VGA/HDMI output for connection to a monitor or projector (on all versions of iPad!) ☆ Multi-touch enabled, allowing groups to play collaboratively on one device ☆ Several users can play together without interfering with each others actions ☆ Play head-to-head against another nearby iPad, iPhone or iPod touch user ☆ A fourth "extreme" difficulty level, exclusive to iPad ☆ Game Center integration (requires iOS 4.2 or later) Our word list is constantly growing, with contributions by gamers using the iPhone app and teachers using the free WordSearchParty.com web site! At the time of writing, there are word lists covering the following topics: ☆ Vocabulary ☆ Spelling Lists ☆ Mathematics ☆ Science ☆ TV &amp; Movies ☆ Music ☆ Sports ☆ Lifestyle ☆ Geography and many more... If you have any questions or comments please send an email to support@wordsearchparty.com We cannot reply to you if you leave messages in your reviews, so please contact us first if you’re having any problems. Thanks!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7057_10_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple6/v4/92/79/4c/92794ca3-45d2-1772-c3e5-6ad8fa56287d/mzl.eluqovjq.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>