<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7079">a-team theme music</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:28:27" name="Games.com" id="FW14-e048"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e048-7079-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7079_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:28:27">http://www.games.com/game/disney/disney-sing-it</link><title>Disney Sing It</title><description>Sing to 35 favorite songs and music videos from Disney artists and programs including Camp Rock, Hannah Montana, Miley Cyrus, Jonas Brothers, Aly and AJ and “High School Musical” (favorites from 1 and 2) Compete with and against friends in numerous multiplayer modes, including Duet, Versus and Team Play With “High School Musical” star Olesya Rulin (Kelsi) as a vocal coach, practice tricky elements of singing in various vocal exercises Personalize game experiences by unlocking or downloading themed skins Download new song packs and bonus content via Xbox Live and PlayStation Network, Platforms: Nintendo Wii, ESRB Rating: Everyone</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7079_01_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/51iFa5qgTJL._SL160_.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7079-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7079_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:30:33">http://www.games.com/game/disney/hsm-3-sing-mic-required</link><title>Hsm 3 Sing - Mic Required</title><description>Sing to 25 songs &amp; music videos from all 3 High School Musical films Compete with &amp; against friends in numerous multiplayer modes, including Duet, Versus &amp; Team Play With High School Musical star Olesya Rulin (Kelsi) as a vocal coach, practice tricky elements of singing in various vocal exercises Personalize game experiences by choosing one of the three High School Musical themes, Platforms: Xbox 360, ESRB Rating: Everyone</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7079_02_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/51f6tAleBUL._SL160_.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7079-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7079_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:32:49">http://www.games.com/game/artificial-life/linkin-park-8-bit-rebellion</link><title>Linkin Park 8-Bit Rebellion!</title><description>Winning designs from the 8-Bit Heroes contest are now on display in the 8-Bit Heroes Gallery. The top two winners are featured as characters in the game now and can be found in Mike Shinoda's Gallery. Featured as “New &amp; Noteworthy” and “What's Hot” \- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - Reviews: “They were able to turn my sketches and our creative ideas into a living, breathing world that we think gamers and fans will thoroughly enjoy.” - Mike Shinoda, Linkin Park “You guys did a phenomenal job on the game.” - Jordan Berliant, The Collective, Manager Linkin Park “What really shines about this game is the online component.” - Jared Nelson, touchArcade “The interesting virtual world in the game will likely please any adventure or role-playing gamer.” - Andrew Podolsky, Slide To Play “This side-scrolling action/beat-'em-up hybrid looked, sounded and controlled surprisingly well.” - Colin Moriarty, IGN “Surprisingly interesting and endearing.” - James Isabel, The Appera “The 8-bit versions of these songs totally fit the game and are neat to hear.” - Tyler Tschida, App Advice “Listening to Linkin Park never gets old, even if it is an 8-bit version.” - Pat Dunn, TouchGen \- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - Fight the forces of evil to unlock a BRAND NEW, EXCLUSIVE song by Linkin Park! Many years ago, the world existed in 8-bit harmony…until PixxelKorp arrived. Now technological advancement dominates, and evil reigns supreme. A mass-brainwashing campaign has taken over and is turning the world into a high-res nightmare. A rebellion is rising, and Linkin Park is calling on YOU to lead the fight against PixxelKorp. From the imagination of Linkin Park comes 8-Bit Rebellion, the only game app that turns Linkin Park's world into your gaming reality. Take on action-packed missions as you fight your way through 6 Linkin Park-themed districts. Customize your own apartment and connect with friends in a massively multiplayer experience. Most importantly, recover all of the lost Linkin Park tracks to score exclusive access to an unreleased song! iPad edition is also available! Game Features: \- Enjoy 8 Linkin Park tracks in their original and 8-bit forms, including “New Divide”, “In The End,” and “Crawling” \- Explore uniquely-themed districts designed for each band member, with characters and items designed by the band themselves \- Create and customize your own avatar in 8-bit or high-res designs \- Decorate your own, personal space \- Equip yourself with an array of devastating weapons and engage in intense boss battles that will put your skills to the challenge! \- Choose the control scheme that best suits your gaming style \- Receive mission objectives straight from the band members \- Connect with Facebook to find friends, and post updates to your wall and Twitter accounts \- Compare your rebellion points with other players on the global leaderboard! Like the game? Post a review, and we'll pick our favorites to include here in the app description. \- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - We welcome you to help us improve the application by sending us feedback, please direct comments to cs@botme.com and we’ll check it out. Thank you! Try other exciting games by ALife: Adult Swim's Amateur Surgeon, Amateur Surgeon Christmas Edition, Five Minutes to Kill (Yourself) &amp; Meowcenaries, BMW Sauber F1 Team Racing 09, BMW Z4 Experience, iDroidsMania, iSink U, iSoccer Backstreet®, PANDORUM, Red Bull Air Race World Championship, Red Bull Racing Challenge, ROBBIE WILLIAMS RACING, Spartacus: Blood and Sand and VERMINATOR® Follow us on Twitter for the latest news: http://twitter.com/alifegames Join us on Facebook: http://www.botme.com/ref/alife-fb Check out our videos: http://www.youtube.com/user/alifegames</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7079_03_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple4/v4/93/d8/da/93d8da77-869c-2630-854f-eefd26d64625/mzl.njwpsnfn.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7079-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7079_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:34:25">http://www.games.com/game/viacheslav-iushchenko/zepi-music</link><title>Zepi Music</title><description>Unveil all your musical talents! Zepi Music is for you to create own musical improvisations with ‘Themes’ and ‘Instruments’ modes. With ‘Simple Sound’, you can just get relaxed. The challenge is to form the longest possible strings of same-color orbs by tapping or sliding your finger(s) onto the screen. Fantastically, it is up for you to decide which instruments as well as melodies the skins will play! Set up your own orchestra! The game features various power-ups and unique SuperBall to help you score more. Advanced players will appreciate the multitouch function and various achievements. FEATURES \- Rabbit Hole; \- Super Ball; \- bright, colorful skins: you can change them during the game; \- global leaderboard; \- accelerometer support: hold the device in a way which is comfortable for you; \- easy gameplay: your kids will love it too \- play any time, any place, it takes 5 minutes to set a new record \- Facebook and Twitter integrated Along with having fun and experiencing fresh emotions, with Zepi Music you will: 1.Develop your musical rhythms; 2\. Develop your music ear; 3.Be encouraged to take interest in cultural information, including the history of the best musical compositions of different genres and styles; 4.Practice basic math skills (addition, multiplication, progression, and functions); 5.Develop creativity of mind; 6.Practice and improve attention as well as mental reaction time. Attention! The game hides many a musical surprise! With ‘Themes’, use your accurateness and musical intuition. Those who enjoy improvisations are sure to love the game. Unleash yourself! With all our heart, we hope that you feel the joy of developing your skills as well as discovering wonderful and magical spheres like Music, Math, and you own inner world! Zepi Music developer team You can find detailed How To Play at Zepi Music Support</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7079_04_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/5c/65/99/5c6599ac-439a-837e-4e1e-2e252a03d2d5/mzl.bzwlkzfl.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7079-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7079_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:37:32">http://www.games.com/game/fun2go-trivia-more/big-80s-funblast-trivia-quiz</link><title>Big 80's FunBlast Trivia Quiz</title><description>Do you remember big hair bands, the Cabbage Patch craze, Mr. T, and Ferris Bueller’s Day Off? If so, it’s time to put on your Ray Ban sunglasses and take a walk down memory lane with the Big 80’s FunBlast Trivia challenge. FunBlast! Trivia blows away the competition covering all of your 80’s favorites like Movies, Music, TV, Politics, Pop Culture, and more, but with the FunBlast twist! Why settle for your average trivia quiz when you can now play with lively animation and over 40 sound effects in 1 player, 2 player, and team modes? Challenge your friends and family in person or on FaceBook and then compete for high scores on our global leader board. FUNBLAST! has something for everyone with FOUR distinct, easy to play game modes for the price of one: ■ MILLIONAIRE: Enjoy the excitement of a classic game show as you try to answer all 12 questions correctly and become a FunBlast! Millionaire. The questions start out easy and then get harder as you go. Employ your own strategies by using your life-lines early or save them for later in the game. ■ BET BIG: Hear the exciting sounds of a Las Vegas casino as you decide whether to bet small or BET IT ALL. Watch your winnings rack up as you double down -- or lose everything on that factoid you swore you knew! ■ GO FAST! For those who like to live in the fast lane, you're awarded more points the faster you answer a question correctly. You'll even hear the roar of the race track as the game starts and the timer counts down. ■ TRIVIA FUN: Traditionalists will enjoy the simple fun of answering both easy and challenging questions with no pressure and no time limits. See the answers you missed, or keep it a mystery -- the choice is yours. ================== FunBlast! Features ================== ■ MORE FUN with 12 Ways to Play: Get 4 game modes @ 1 player, 2 player, and Team play! ■ MORE GAME MODES: Bet Big, Go Fast, Trivia Fun, and Go Millionaire keep you hooked for hours. ■ BETTER QUESTIONS! With FunBlast!, we challenge you with only the most interesting, intriguing, and entertaining questions. Bring out your inner genius with 175 multiple choice questions (includes 50 bonus questions after free registration). Ready for more? Dozens of expansion packs are either available now or being added soon covering a wide range of traditional and pop culture topics. ■ PROFESSIONAL GRAPHICS, lively animation, and over 40 sound effects bring your trivia game to life. ■ NO MORE REPEAT QUESTIONS: By default questions are never repeated before all new questions have been used and unlike competitors, this is tracked separately for each user who plays on your device. (Unlimited users supported!) ■ CONVENIENT SHOPPING: Easily tap a button to discover the best deals and most unique merchandise related to your trivia topic of choice. ■ GREATER FLEXIBILITY let's you disable sound effects, background music, etc. You're in control! ■ PERSONALIZE YOUR GAME and make it your own by adding your favorite background image to match your style or the trivia theme. Choose your own image or one of over 20 cool built-in backgrounds. ■ CHALLENGE YOUR FRIENDS on Facebook or E-mail. You can even SHARE your best high scores and taunt your friends with your superior knowledge. ■ BETTER CUSTOMER SERVICE: We care about our customers and your total game experience. That's why we include a feedback and support button right on the main menu as well as on our website. Don't be fooled by imitators or discouraged by junkware. When you want fun and you want the best, the choice is easy: FunBlast!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7079_05_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/f8/93/e6/mzi.ueugcckq.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7079-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7079_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:41:34">http://www.games.com/game/artificial-life/linkin-park-8-bit-rebellion-lite</link><title>Linkin Park 8-Bit Rebellion! Lite</title><description>Many years ago, the world existed in 8-bit harmony…until PixxelKorp arrived. Now technological advancement dominates, and evil reigns supreme. A mass-brainwashing campaign has taken over and is turning the world into a high-res nightmare. A rebellion is rising, and Linkin Park is calling on YOU to lead the fight against PixxelKorp. From the imagination of Linkin Park comes 8-Bit Rebellion, the only iPhone game that turns Linkin Park’s world into your gaming reality. Take on action-packed missions as you fight your way through Linkin Park-themed districts! Game Features: \- Enjoy “One Step Closer” and “Faint” in their original and 8-bit forms \- Explore uniquely-themed districts designed for band members, with characters and items designed by the band themselves \- Create and customize your own avatar with special designs \- Decorate your own apartment \- Receive mission objectives straight from a band member The FULL VERSION with more missions and social networking features is now available on the iPhone and iPad! Like the game? Post a review, and we'll pick our favorites to include here in the app description. \------------------------------ We welcome you to help us improve the application by sending us feedback, please direct comments to cs@botme.com and we’ll check it out. Thank you! Try other exciting games by ALife: Adult Swim's Amateur Surgeon, Amateur Surgeon Christmas Edition, Five Minutes to Kill (Yourself) &amp; Meowcenaries, BMW Sauber F1 Team Racing 09, BMW Z4 Experience, iDroidsMania, iSink U, iSoccer Backstreet®, PANDORUM, Red Bull Air Race World Championship, Red Bull Racing Challenge, ROBBIE WILLIAMS RACING, Spartacus: Blood and Sand and VERMINATOR® Follow us on Twitter for the latest news: http://twitter.com/alifegames Join us on Facebook: http://www.botme.com/ref/alife-fb Check out our videos: http://www.youtube.com/user/alifegames</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7079_06_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple4/v4/88/29/ad/8829ad3b-ca80-df2c-1a8b-3d23bbc9896e/mzl.thheizxg.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7079-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7079_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:45:30">http://www.games.com/game/fanwide/mobileqs-trivia</link><title>MobileQs Trivia</title><description>The #1 trivia game for BlackBerry and Windows Phone now comes to iPhone and iPad! MobileQs has over 16,000 trivia questions across 38 categories! Visit MobileQs.com for more information, mobile apps, custom apps, trivia, press, support, privacy and more! Game Highlights \- Over 16,000 Trivia Questions (Qs) with 4,000 FREE questions! \- 38 different categories \- Play thousands of FREE questions \- Buy all the questions at once to unlock everything \- Buy a whole theme for thousands of questions (All Arts &amp; Leisure, All Sports, or All World &amp; Work) \- Buy an individual category \- 27 OpenFeint Achievements \- 13 OpenFeint High Score Leaderboards \- Qs written in 2010 and 2011 with a focus on current events \- 3 different types of 'Hints' \- Eliminate Answers \- Poll the People \- Replace a Question \- Dozens of difficultly levels \- 4 answer choices \- 2 lives per game \- Online instructions, support &amp; help \- All questions are in English and written by the MobileQs team Trivia Categories \- Random Questions – 2,200 Qs \- Arts &amp; Leisure – 4,200 Qs \- Arts (Fine) – 300 Qs \- Arts (Performing) – 300 Qs \- Books &amp; Literature – 300 Qs \- Celebrities &amp; Hollywood – 300 Qs \- Comics &amp; Superheroes – 300 Qs \- Games &amp; Toys – 300 Qs \- Movies – 600 Qs \- Music – 600 Qs \- Television – 600 Qs \- Video Games – 600 Qs \- Sports – 3,900 Qs \- Baseball – 300 Qs \- Basketball – 300 Qs \- Combat Sports, Boxing &amp; MMA – 300 Qs \- Cricket – 300 Qs \- Football (American) – 300 Qs \- Football (Soccer) – 600 Qs \- Golf – 300 Qs \- Hockey – 300 Qs \- Olympic – 300 Qs \- Racing – 300 Qs \- Rugby – 300 Qs \- Tennis – 300 Qs \- World &amp; Work – 5,800 Qs \- Animals – 300 Qs \- Business – 300 Qs \- Canada – 600 Qs \- Europe – 600 Qs \- Geography – 300 Qs \- Nature – 300 Qs \- Science – 300 Qs \- Stocks &amp; Markets – 1,300 Qs \- Technology – 600 Qs \- United Kingdom (UK) – 600 Qs \- United States (USA) – 600 Qs Visit MobileQs.com for more information, mobile apps, custom apps, trivia, press, support, privacy and more!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7079_07_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/72/05/30/mzl.okienopu.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7079-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7079_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:51:43">http://www.games.com/game/fun2go-trivia-more/funblast-trekkie-trivia-quiz</link><title>FunBlast Trekkie Trivia Quiz</title><description>Are you a true Trekkie or Trekker? You better know your Romulans from your Klingons if you want to rise above a Star Fleet Cadet in this part of the galaxy. Test your knowledge of the original series, the motion pictures, Next Generation, Deep Space Nine, Voyager, Enterprise, and all the way up to JJ Abrams’ 2009 Star Trek reboot. FunBlast Trivia blows away the competition and delivers with 4 unique game modes to satisfy both casual and die-hard Star Trek fans. Why settle for your average trivia quiz when you can now play with lively animation and over 40 sound effects in 1 player, 2 player, and team modes? Challenge your friends on FaceBook and then compete for high scores on our global leader board. FUNBLAST! has something for everyone with FOUR distinct, easy to play game modes for the price of one: ■ MILLIONAIRE: Enjoy the excitement of a classic game show as you try to answer all 12 questions correctly and become a FunBlast! Millionaire. The questions start out easy and then get harder as you go. Employ your own strategies by using your life-lines early or save them for later in the game. ■ BET BIG: Hear the exciting sounds of a Las Vegas casino as you decide whether to bet small or BET IT ALL. Watch your winnings rack up as you double down -- or lose everything on that factoid you swore you knew! ■ GO FAST! For those who like to live in the fast lane, you're awarded more points the faster you answer a question correctly. You'll even hear the roar of the race track as the game starts and the timer counts down. ■ TRIVIA FUN: Traditionalists will enjoy the simple fun of answering both easy and challenging questions with no pressure and no time limits. See the answers you missed, or keep it a mystery -- the choice is yours. ================== FunBlast! Features ================== ■ MORE FUN with 12 Ways to Play: Get 4 game modes @ 1 player, 2 player, and Team play! ■ MORE GAME MODES: Bet Big, Go Fast, Trivia Fun, and Go Millionaire keep you hooked for hours. ■ BETTER QUESTIONS! With FunBlast!, we challenge you with only the most interesting, intriguing, and entertaining questions. Bring out your inner genius with over 160 multiple choice questions (includes 50 bonus questions after free registration). Ready for more? Dozens of expansion packs are either available now or being added soon covering a wide range of traditional and pop culture topics. ■ PROFESSIONAL GRAPHICS, lively animation, and over 40 sound effects bring your trivia game to life. ■ NO MORE REPEAT QUESTIONS: By default questions are never repeated before all new questions have been used and unlike competitors, this is tracked separately for each user who plays on your device. (Unlimited users supported!) ■ GREATER FLEXIBILITY let's you disable sound effects, background music, etc. You're in control! ■ PERSONALIZE YOUR GAME and make it your own by adding your favorite background image to match your style or the trivia theme. Choose your own image or one of over 20 cool built-in backgrounds. ■ CHALLENGE YOUR FRIENDS on Facebook or E-mail. You can even SHARE your best high scores and taunt your friends with your superior knowledge. ■ BETTER CUSTOMER SERVICE: We care about our customers and your total game experience. That's why we include a feedback and support button right on the main menu as well as on our website. Don't be fooled by imitators or discouraged by junkware. When you want fun and you want the best, the choice is easy: FunBlast! Legal: Not affiliated with Paramount or Gene Roddenberry’s Estate. Any reference to third-party names, characters, products or other information is for convenience or educational purposes only and does not imply endorsement or sponsorship. All trademarks are the property of their respective owners.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7079_08_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple6/v4/5a/ff/d4/5affd407-fda0-967d-c325-9c1ed6383df0/mzl.wkzvxqlr.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7079-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7079_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:55:32">http://www.games.com/game/mobileart/bear-vs-penguins</link><title>Bear Vs Penguins</title><description>Bear Vs Penguins is a funny strategy game for iphone. Evil penguins rush fiercely forward to the bear’s ice house. In defense of hearth and home, what the bear can only do is to unite a large number of animals in fighting against the invasion of the penguins. You can control the bear’s alliance on five roads to defend the repeated attacks of the invading army made up of 30 kinds of penguins, thus, you can hit especially hard at the invading army. Funny characters, impressive images, flexible strategy, mysterious and inspiring music will bring you the most incredible experience. Every penguin has its own unique and funny way of walking and attacking. The attack of the defense turret will give you a big surprise. The game has 20 levels, so you can allow your imagination full play. You can combine any way of fighting you can imagine to hit the invading army. Every battle will give you different surprises. Let’s join in the fight in the defense of hearth and home. You can also visit our facebook to see the detailed account of the game and join the relevant discussion. \-------------------------------------- What's it got: \- Cute penguins are our enemies? Wanna earn your bread in the world of penguins? Well, let me tell you-it's not gonna be easy. \- It may be a game with superb graphics and brand-new experiences, but this needs your approval. \- Its theme song is produced by a famous original music team. You'll experience unimaginably unique war sound effects. Kidding? Ha, ha. \- 20 levels with amazing new game props and penguins \- 30 funny and stupid penguins+unthinkably "cruel" and "aberrant" game settings \- Where are the bullets spatting down on penguins fired from? You'll never guess. \- Turret defence is a very mixed bag. Even ordinary things from everyday life can turn into props for you to defend penguins' attack. It is like a breath of fresh air. \- As for our plan of the development of Bear VS Penguin V2.0, you can offer you ideas at our Facebook(http://www.facebook.com/pages/Bear-VS-Penguins/136214466403156) to get involved. We will specially mark your name so that you will feel very accomplished and honourable.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7079_09_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/12/19/02/mzl.sarrwfxf.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7079-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7079_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:57:24">http://www.games.com/game/fun2go-trivia-more/80s-rockband-funblast-trivia-lite</link><title>80's Rockband FunBlast! Trivia Lite</title><description>Now with more available questions and topics! Do you remember the big hair and other great rock bands of the 80’s? If so, it’s time to put on your Ray Ban sunglasses and stroll down memory lane with the 80’s Rockband FunBlast Trivia challenge. FunBlast! Trivia rocks the competition by delivering 4 unique game modes to satisfy both casual and die-hard 80’s Rock fans. Why settle for your average trivia quiz when you can now play with lively animation and over 40 sound effects in 1 player, 2 player, and team modes? Challenge your friends and family in person or on FaceBook and then compete for high scores on our global leader board. FUNBLAST! has something for everyone with FOUR distinct, easy to play game modes for the price of one: ■ MILLIONAIRE: Enjoy the excitement of a classic game show as you try to answer all 12 questions correctly and become a FunBlast! Millionaire. The questions start out easy and then get harder as you go. Employ your own strategies by using your life-lines early or save them for later in the game. ■ BET BIG: Hear the exciting sounds of a Las Vegas casino as you decide whether to bet small or BET IT ALL. Watch your winnings rack up as you double down -- or lose everything on that factoid you swore you knew! ■ GO FAST! For those who like to live in the fast lane, you're awarded more points the faster you answer a question correctly. You'll even hear the roar of the race track as the game starts and the timer counts down. ■ TRIVIA FUN: Traditionalists will enjoy the simple fun of answering both easy and challenging questions with no pressure and no time limits. See the answers you missed, or keep it a mystery -- the choice is yours. ================== FunBlast! Features ================== ■ MORE FUN with 12 Ways to Play: Get 4 game modes @ 1 player, 2 player, and Team play! ■ MORE GAME MODES: Bet Big, Go Fast, Trivia Fun, and Go Millionaire keep you hooked for hours. ■ BETTER QUESTIONS! With FunBlast!, we challenge you with only the most interesting, intriguing, and entertaining questions. Bring out your inner genius with 75 multiple choice questions (includes 25 bonus questions after free registration). Ready for more? Upgrade to the paid version for more fun! ■ PROFESSIONAL GRAPHICS, lively animation, and over 40 sound effects bring your trivia game to life. ■ NO MORE REPEAT QUESTIONS: By default questions are never repeated before all new questions have been used and unlike competitors, this is tracked separately for each user who plays on your device. (Unlimited users supported!) ■ CONVENIENT SHOPPING: Easily tap a button to discover the best deals and most unique merchandise related to your trivia topic of choice. ■ GREATER FLEXIBILITY let's you disable sound effects, background music, etc. You're in control! ■ PERSONALIZE YOUR GAME and make it your own by adding your favorite background image to match your style or the trivia theme. Choose your own image or one of over 20 cool built-in backgrounds. ■ CHALLENGE YOUR FRIENDS on Facebook or E-mail. You can even SHARE your best high scores and taunt your friends with your superior knowledge. ■ BETTER CUSTOMER SERVICE: We care about our customers and your total game experience. That's why we include a feedback and support button right on the main menu as well as on our website. Don't be fooled by imitators or discouraged by junkware. When you want fun and you want the best, the choice is easy: FunBlast!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7079_10_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple6/v4/bc/28/7a/bc287a97-1fda-670e-afad-f172821c8d90/mzl.wetgqxwj.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>