<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7119">chocolate photo</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:35:22" name="Games.com" id="FW14-e048"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e048-7119-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7119_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:35:23">http://www.games.com/game/beansprites/milkshake-yum</link><title>Milkshake Yum!</title><description>A Variety of Toppings like Wafers, Candy, Chocolates, Straws, Whipped Topping, berries, and more! Make your Milkshake from scratch starting with the ingredients like ice cream, Milk, Sugar, and extras Watch your creation blend in the Milkshake Mixer! Save your items to a photo gallery to gander at later! Endless possibilities of creation with a plethora of toppings and items to choose from!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7119_01_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/51-xIsqnq4L._SL160_.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7119-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7119_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:37:26">http://www.games.com/game/appa-apps/count-chocolates-1-20</link><title>Count Chocolates 1-20</title><description>Entertaining game to teach you to count in English from 1 to 20 20 photos of delicious chocolates, and original music by David J Bevan Multi-coloured Bubble Writing and Tracing Easy way to learn numbers for children and English language students Race Mode to check your progress and see how much you have learned Slideshow Mode to show you all the photos in sequence Easy on-screen gestures for Race Mode, Race Results, Slideshow Mode, Quiet Mode, Help and Amazon Appstore.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7119_02_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/818O8fQKevL._SL160_.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7119-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7119_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:40:00">http://www.games.com/game/maverick-software/more-popcorn</link><title>More Popcorn!</title><description>Pop up some fun on your iPad, iPhone or iPod Touch! It's the very newest virtual cooking app from Maverick Software, creators of Cupcakes!, More Cookies! and all the other food apps you love. More Popcorn gives you everything you need to pop, flavor, season and share all kinds of tasty virtual popcorn treats on your iPhone or iPad. Choose a popper from a pan or domed popper to a microwave or hot air popper. Tilt to pour in the oil &amp; kernels, shake the pan or open/close the microwave door, and watch the popcorn pop! After you've made a big bowl of hot popcorn, you can add 50+ coatings, toppings, and mix-ins. Caramel corn, kettle corn, cheese corn, wasabi, peppermint, fruit candy coatings, it's all there! Then mix in chocolate chips, nuts, gummy bears, or other kinds of fun foods. Once you've seasoned your popcorn just right (even shaking the phone to mix up the kernels to coat better), you can eat it or share it via email or save to your photos. But that's not all! You can also roll your popcorn into yummy popcorn balls, or make popcorn strings that you can use to decorate Christmas trees or wreaths, or even pick you own photo and give it the popcorn decorative touch. More Popcorn features: \- Gorgeous Retina Display graphics and full screen iPad support. No matter what you play on, from iPod Touch to iPad 2, it'll look amazing. \- 4 different poppers: pan, domed popper, microwave, and hot air popper. \- Over 80 toppings, coatings, and mix-ins. Sweet and savory, fruits and nuts, chocolate, candy, it's all in there! \- 30 achievements you can earn and brag about via Gamcenter. Find secrets, make special mixes, and earn all the points. \- Customize your popcorn bowl with 12 different colors. \- Make popcorn balls and popcorn strings, and use the strings to decorate built in Christmas themed pictures or use your own photos. \- World-wide Gamecenter leader boards to see who has popped the most and made the most strings!' \- VoiceOver support for the visually impaired. Post a review with your requests and we'll add them to our frequent free updates!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7119_03_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/df/b7/43/dfb7438b-b4a1-da1e-cb1a-c598675f3e47/mzl.ebdhjgxr.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7119-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7119_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:42:36">http://www.games.com/game/maverick-software/more-grillin</link><title>More Grillin'</title><description>More Grillin' lets you grill up your favorite foods virtually, with no mess and no chance of getting burned. From Maverick Software, creators of the most popular food games in the App Store, including Cupcakes!, More Cookies!, and More Toast! Hear the sizzle and watch the flames dance, while you flip your food to cook it, then dress it up with dozens of sauces, toppings, side dishes and desserts. All with sharpest graphics (including iPad &amp; Retina Display support) ever! Share your food with friends, save photos to your photo album, and even eat it by taking virtual bites. More Grillin' features: \- Fully universal with native resolution on iPhone/iPod Touch, iPad, Retina Display and tall iPhone 5. \- 27 kinds of food to grill (hamburgers, hot dogs, bratwurst, chicken, steak, veggie burgers, shrimp kabobs, ribs, corn on the cob, pork chops, veggie &amp; steak kabobs, salmon, pineapple, and more). Grill from rare to well done. \- 14 sauces/condiments to add to your food, everything from ketchup, mayo, mustard, and relish to hot sauce, salsa, steak sauce, and more. \- 23 toppings, like american &amp; swiss cheese slices, tomatoes, lettuce, pickles, onions, mushrooms, jalapenos, avocado, and more. \- Multiple kinds of buns and bread (plain, sesame, wheat, hot dog, bread, texas toast, rolls). \- 22 side dishes - french fries, onion rings, coleslaw, potato salad, baked beans, potato chips, watermelon, baked potatoes, cheese puffs, and more. \- 18 kinds of desserts (apple &amp; cherry pie, brownies, ice cream, chocolate cake, and more). \- 17 plates and 11 tablecloths. \- Customize your grill in 11 colors. \- Supports all iPad orientations. \- A built-in grill-o-meter to keep track of how much you've cooked, with a worldwide leaderboard to see who the best grillers are. \- Share your food via email, Facebook, or save to your photo albums. And just like our other apps, we'll be adding more! Post a review with your requests, and you never know, our next free update might have your favorite food!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7119_04_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/f8/66/ab/f866ab33-5e1e-29f6-3493-0fcaabde17e3/mzl.nauzjvoa.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7119-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7119_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:46:49">http://www.games.com/game/maverick-software/sweet-dippy-do</link><title>Sweet Dippy Do!</title><description>Dip, shake and decorate! From caramel apples to chocolate dipped pretzels, from vanilla iced cookies to chocolate covered strawberries, now you can create the sweetest treats ever on your iPod, iPhone or iPad. The newest app from Maverick Software, creators of the best food apps- with EVERYTHING unlocked, no in-app purchases. First pick what you want to dip- apples, pretzels, cookies, marshmallows, strawberries, bananas, mint or maple cremes and more! Then pick a custom stick from different colors and patterns. Once you have your dipper, choose a coating - milk chocolate, dark chocolate, caramel, peanut butter, strawberry icing, red candy, maple glaze, and more. Dip your treat in as many coatings as you want, exactly how much you want. You can even spin the dipper to dip half one coating and half another. After you've made your treats, time to shake &amp; decorate! Shake your phone or tap to add peanuts, rainbow sprinkles, toffee bits, cookie bits, cinnamon sugar, coconut, graham cracker crumbs and more. Or to decorate with more control, add any of 50 toppings, one by one. Candy corn, sprinkles, nuts, red hots, chocolate chips, gummy bears, and six kinds of drizzle! For Halloween, we've got a bunch of spooky toppings! Ghosts, bats, pumpkins and more. You've created the sweetest treat ever- so now share it via email, Facebook, or save forever to your photos album. And then eat it! Tap to take virtual bites, with no calories :) Sweet Dippy Do! features: \- Fully supports iPod Touch, iPhone &amp; iPad, including Retina Display graphics &amp; 4" iPhone 5 \- 32 dippers (apples, pretzels, bananas, shortbread cookies, fortune cookies, marshmallows, and more) \- 11 coatings (milk, dark &amp; white chocolate, red candy, caramel, peanut butter, icings, and more) \- 12 dipper sticks \- 10 shake-ons and 50 toppings, with all kinds of candies, nuts, sprinkles, and drizzles \- Fridge to save your best creations \- 20 achievements to earn by making special treats \- Game center leader board of the best treat makers \- Share your treats via email, save to your Photos album, or post on Facebook Have suggestions for other dippers, coatings, or toppings? Post a review and let us know!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7119_05_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/f3/31/57/f331571a-9e95-8ce1-54ce-0564ab85ea44/mzl.xvrgbsjl.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7119-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7119_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:47:35">http://www.games.com/game/maverick-software/more-cakes</link><title>More Cakes!</title><description>Maverick's most requested virtual baking app is finally here! Bake and decorate amazing cakes on your iPad, iPhone or iPod Touch- with no messy cleanup and no calories. Birthdays, weddings, holidays, or just for fun- mix, bake, decorate and share all kinds of cakes. First, pick a cake shape to make- sheet cakes, round, square, hearts, flowers, Christmas trees, and more. Even layered and tiered cakes! Then choose a recipe from 19 different classic flavors- white, yellow, chocolate, strawberry, red velvet, carrot cake, confetti, and more. You can mix all the ingredients from real recipes, cracking eggs, pouring milk, and sifting flour. Or if you are in a hurry, use a pre-made mix and just fill up your pans. Now it's time to pop the cake in the oven and watch it bake. Then the best part- decorating! Over 30 frostings to choose from, with different decorating tips (lines, flowers, stars, waves &amp; more). Or use smooth fondant icings in 10 flavors. Special piping tools let you put a nice line of frosting around the edges of the cake, with no mess. Besides frostings, you also get 60+ candy decorations including all colors of sprinkles &amp; sugars, and 35 toppers with candles you can light and blow out by blowing on the phone! Once your cake is done, eat it or share it with friends. Send someone a custom virtual cake for their birthday! More Cakes! features: \- Retina display graphics and tall screen iPhone 5/5th generation iPod Touch support \- Fully iPad compatible in both portrait and landscape \- Game Center achievements to discover and earn \- Share your cakes via email, save to your photo album or post on Facebook Is there a cake flavor, shape or frosting you'd like to see added? Post a review and we'll see about including it in our free updates.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7119_06_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/41/2d/ad/412dad19-ba12-c356-5b46-7c7a653f8f24/mzl.nhdwrnwa.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7119-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7119_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:50:51">http://www.games.com/game/hp-studios/a-milkshake-maker-for-ipad</link><title>A Milkshake Maker for iPad</title><description>★ A Milkshake Maker is here! MAKE YOURS! ★ Milkshakes are so good and delicious. Everyone loves them and always wants more! Includes all of your favorites like vanilla, chocolate, strawberry with ice cream, toppings, and much more! Now you can make your own milkshake creations, using your iPad! What kind do you want to make today? Choose your ice cream, shakes, toppings, blender, milk, and much more. Once you decide what you want you can be super creative and make your very own milkshakes super big or really small! You decide! You can then add the toppings to your milkshakes! SO GOOD! Then pretend to drink your delicious milkshake creations. Super easy to use and fun for both kids and adults. As an extra feature, you can even save your creations to your camera roll and email them to your friends. Even choose your own photos and add multiple milkshake images to them. SUPER FUN AND SO GOOD!! MAKE YOURS TODAY! Supports all iPads!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7119_07_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/be/1f/23/be1f23b6-7e09-cb5d-d8e3-871e05643b6e/mzl.kiatqtlx.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7119-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7119_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:53:45">http://www.games.com/game/nerbyte-gmbh/a-cookie-crafter</link><title>A Cookie Crafter</title><description>*** FREE FOR LIMITED TIME *** Cookie Crafter is finally here! Ready to mix, cut out, bake and decorate your cookies? With this App you can bake the most beautiful cookies with a realistic look. Feel free to use any shape you want. There are a lot! *** Features *** \+ Create round or shape cookies like real one \+ Enjoy beautiful animation graphics \+ Have fun with a lot of dressing objects \+ Eat your cookie and enjoy it! \+ Take a picture of your cookies and share them with your friends \+ Take a picture of your cookies and store them in your photo album \+ Have fun with the mini game - eat as much cookies as possible in only 40 seconds \+ Set the color of your kitchen to your desire \+ Buy more candy, chocolate, plate, backgrounds and slots for more fun! *** Instructions *** First, mix the cookie ingredients in the bowl. Then stir them with a wooden soon. Roll the thick dough out with a rolling pin until it is just the right thickness to cut with the cookie cutter. Now choose your cookie cutter you want to use. There are many shapes. Press it into the dough and then watch them go into the oven and bake until they are golden brown. Ready to decorate? Decorate your cookie with dozens of several candy, chocolate and icing. Choose a background and put your cookie on one plate that you can select in a huge menu. Share your cookie with your friends! *** Get it while it is FREE ***</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7119_08_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/d7/cc/83/d7cc83ca-c153-dae5-027d-6e1caed3c016/mzm.rwqbcjds.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7119-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7119_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:56:17">http://www.games.com/game/maverick-software/cupcakes-the-best-bake-decorate-app</link><title>Cupcakes! The Best Bake &amp; Decorate App</title><description>The first and still BEST cupcake making app- bake, decorate, and eat virtual cupcakes with all kinds of flavors &amp; toppings, using real recipes! \- Featured in "Our Favorite Things" - Disney FamilyFun magazine \- "The cupcakes look so good I almost licked my phone." - Robin Rhys, AppAdvice.com \- Over 6,000 five star ratings in the App Store. Cupcakes! lets you bake, decorate, eat &amp; share yummy cupcakes right from your iPod Touch or iPhone. Pick your cupcake liners, fill the pan with cake batter, pop it in the oven, and before you know it your cupcakes will come out piping hot. Shake your phone to get the cupcakes out of the pan and then choose from an amazing array of frostings and candy toppings, to build the perfect cupcake. Once you've baked and decorated your masterpieces, you can share them with your friends via email, Facebook, or save them to your photo albums. And of course you can eat them! Choose the tablecloth and plate to serve them on and you are ready for dessert. Features include: \- 27 different cupcake batters (white, yellow, chocolate, strawberry, carrot cake, red velvet, lemon, confetti, marble, apple spice, blueberry muffin, pineapple, gingerbread and more!). Mix the cupcakes from scratch or use pre-made batter. \- 32 different colors &amp; patterns of cupcake liners, plus an option to create custom liners \- 62 types of frosting, and a 'mix your own icing color' option \- 80 candy toppings from gummy bears to sprinkles, fruit to nuts \- 25 flavors of Jelly Belly gourmet jelly beans to add as toppings \- 14 kinds of plates and 9 tablecloths, to give your cupcakes the perfect presentation \- The ability to set your baking time, from lightly baked to crispy burnt cupcakes \- Candles you can blow out by blowing on your phone! (shake for older iPods) \- A "Cupcake of the Week" contest and a Hall of Fame for the best user submitted cupcakes \- Full support for VoiceOver, for the visually impaired.  \- 40 achievements to earn! Post a review with your requests, and you never know, our next free update might add your suggestion! \--- Have an iPad? Get Cupcakeroo! for all the Cupcakes fun with full iPad support.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7119_09_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple4/v4/6a/03/be/6a03be39-50f5-2b70-02d9-a40ac2cbc924/mzl.dhejlmxq.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7119-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7119_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:59:45">http://www.games.com/game/babyberry-studios/amys-froyo-lite</link><title>Amy's Froyo Lite</title><description>Follow us on Twitter via @kooapps to receive free promo codes and new game launch raffle prizes! Top 20 USA with TONS of downloads worldwide Fixed: We just fixed the crash issue mentioned in the reviews. If you're seeing this, please delete the app, re-install and re-download the valentines package. thanks! Trendy on Twitter check it out - http://twitter.com/search?q=amy froyo App Store Quotes: \--------------------------------- "I absolutely love this app it was a really good call to get it" "Love it, it’s like u doing it for real!" "My kids really love this game! its so creative and fun." Summer is sooooo hot. Want some cold delicious deserts and keep your body in shape for the beach? Decorate your own froyo to your heart's desire with tons of flavors and toppings while sharing it with your family and friends. Oh and if there's any flavors/toppings you'd like, please post us a review and we'll work on it! LITE Version Features \------------------------------ 3 cup designs, 3 flavors, 3 toppings, 3 spoons \- Eat your virtual froyo \- Save your froyo into your photo album \- Share your froyo via E-mail, Twitter, and Facebook \- Share your froyo recipe Full Version Features \------------------------------ \- 30 Unique Cup Designs \- 15 Delicious Flavors \- 41 Fun Toppings \- Eat your virtual froyo \- Save your froyo into your photo album \- Share your froyo via E-mail, Twitter, and Facebook \- Share your froyo recpie 30 Unique Cup Designs \------------------------------ Soho, Princeton, Wowa, York, Martinique, Montego, Quilt, Bermuda, Broadway, Bahama, Victoria, Mulholland, Chinchilla, Aruba, Madison, Lollipop, Roswell, Saturn, Cleveland, Poppy, St. Monica, Jodhpur, Caribbean, Macquarie, Dauphine, Manhattan, Orleans, Seattle, Comino, Malibu 15 Delicious Flavors \------------------------------ Original, Vanilla, Pomegranate, Green Tea, Soy, Tangomonium, Coconut, Chocolate, Passion Fruit, Coffee, Melon, Cherry, Banana, Mango, Blueberry 41 Fun Toppings \------------------------------ Mochi, Ricecake, Strawberry, Kiwi, Mango, Raisins, Cinnamon, Leche Flan, Cheese, Caramel candy, Chocolate syrup, Strawberry syrup, Raspberry, Blueberry, Watermelon, Melon, Pineapple, Banana, Pears, Cherries, Coconut, Almonds, Peanuts, Walnuts, Pistachio, Brownies, Oreo cookies, Mint cookies, Graham crackers, Cheesecake, White Choco chips, Chocolate chips, Strawberry chips, M&amp;M's, Marshmallows, Granola, Rice Krispies, Rainbow Sprinkles, Fruit loops, Gummy bears, Jelly beans CONTACT INFO: \--------------------------------- \- Any questions or suggestions? Email us at support@kooapps.com Become a fan of Amy's Froyo on Facebook! Our Website: http://amysfroyo.kooapps.com/ Please write us a review : ) We value your thoughts highly and appreciate all feedback. Thanks!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7119_10_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/de/38/ae/de38ae14-ac0d-e9ba-8981-ab2f7f2190b1/mzl.jvpglsse.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>