<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7131">golf games</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:13:27" name="Games.com" id="FW14-e048"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e048-7131-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7131_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:13:28">http://www.games.com/game/dmw-design-group/mini-golf-space-3d-putt-putt-golf-game</link><title>Mini Golf Space 3D: Putt Putt Golf Game</title><description>1 of a Kind Golf Game Scoring System. In App Purchase Includes Over 80 Unique Holes that Range in Difficulty. Easy to Use Slider Bar and Power Button! Gorgeous 3D Planetary Environments. New Courses Updated on the Regular!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7131_01_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/61YKbR3fHxL._SL160_.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7131-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7131_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:16:03">http://www.games.com/game/mcm-web-solutions/mcm-golf-card-game</link><title>MCM Golf Card Game</title><description>MCM Golf Card Game is an Android App version of the "Golf" card game. One player plays against two computer opponents</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7131_02_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/31LkTSHB9aL._SL160_.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7131-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7131_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:18:21">http://www.games.com/game/subhendu-behera/mini-golf-game-3d-for-ipad</link><title>Mini Golf Game 3D for iPad</title><description>Play the best casual sports game with amazing 3D graphics. Test your mini golf skills in Mini Golf Game 3D. Play 45 Pars in 5 Different gorgeous looking courses: Countryside, Ice Land, Halloween, Deserted Land and Crystal Land. 4 Different Control options, choose what you like. Swap the controls left-right for your convenience. "Oh man, is this game nice. It's nicer than a hole-in-one through a spinning windmill with six grungy kids yelling at you to hurry up. With great 3D graphics, very natural physics, an intuitive control system, some fun tunes, and a variety of courses, Mini Golf Game 3D for the iPad is my essential mini golf iPad app." \- AppAdvice.com Features: 45 Challenging Levels in 5 Courses. 2 Game Modes (Championship &amp; Timed Mode). Play in 5 unique themes. Realistic Mini Golf physics. Relaxing Soundtracks. Open Feint enabled. Achievements to unlock. Publish Score to Facebook &amp; Twitter.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7131_03_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/c6/d1/e0/mzl.spojxcux.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7131-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7131_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:20:56">http://www.games.com/game/joel-glanfield/book-of-mormon-golf-lds-scripture-mastery-game-app</link><title>Book of Mormon Golf: LDS Scripture Mastery Game App</title><description>This app is the Full (non-Lite) version of "Book of Mormon Golf" and includes the following features: * use Game Center to track your lowest scores and compare with others * complete game redesign * play from any of the 4 standard works, including Scripture Mastery * use Twitter and Facebook to post your best scores * complete interface redesign * completely ad-free</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7131_04_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple4/v4/e1/23/09/e12309dc-6aa2-0519-d2ff-ef26b296c325/mzl.gbwaqduy.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7131-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7131_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:24:30">http://www.games.com/game/scott-hotaling/golf-card-game</link><title>Golf Card Game</title><description>Golf is a card game for two or more players, in which the object is to score as little as possible, as in the sport of Golf. In front of each player is a layout of cards arranged in a square or rectangle, 2 x 2, and players improve their scores by drawing new cards to replace unwanted cards, which they discard. Each deal is seen as the equivalent of a hole of Golf, and in many versions a complete game consists of 9 or 18 deals, corresponding to the length of a Golf course. Multiplayer = Human vs Computer and Human vs Human</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7131_05_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/8c/9d/ae/mzi.giknayqt.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7131-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7131_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:27:52">http://www.games.com/game/david-olea/golf-card-game-hd</link><title>Golf Card Game HD</title><description>Golf Card Game ** I have been waiting for someone to make this game for the iPad and iPhone. Great game everyone should download it. ** Great app. This golf game has just the right amount of strategy and luck to keep me interested. A full game takes about 10 minutes so it's a great way to pass the time. You will like this one! ** This games really fun!!! ** This is pretty fun to play! ** Fun game! I have zero issues and very happy with my purchase! ** An excellent, fun and original game. A card game for all ages. Whether you're a 4 year old girl or a 80 year old man, this game is easy to learn. Yet it involves some decisions to challenge the most competitive of players. You can play against the computer or up to 3 other friends over wifi or bluetooth. The game of golf is a simple but fun 4 card game where the lowest score wins the hole. Score as few points as possible on each hole. The lowest score of each hole wins the hole and gets a point. The player with the most points after 9 holes wins the game. * View scorecard with both Match play and Stroke play totals * Tap hole flag to view scorecard at any time * "Play again" option after round is over Please send feedback or requests to admin@spiralinnovations.com. Enjoy!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7131_06_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/a6/a2/22/a6a22214-92c8-7bf4-a008-9ed6fba31e0e/mzl.gfkympyk.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7131-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7131_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:30:48">http://www.games.com/game/fun-apps/golf-quiz-golfer-faces-game</link><title>Golf Quiz - Golfer Faces Game</title><description>THINK YOU KNOW YOUR GOLF? Prove it in this easy to use fun game. * Over 180 Players * Players from 4 decades * Auto complete feature Download today and see what everyone is talking about. All rights, content and trademarks are owned by their respective owners and not associated to fun-apps.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7131_07_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/9f/96/40/9f9640a2-9452-47b4-1342-3504313b78b4/mzl.hoqrejip.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7131-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7131_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:34:22">http://www.games.com/game/keitgames/crescent-ridge-mini-golf-the-best-miniature-golf-game-ever</link><title>Crescent Ridge Mini Golf - The Best Miniature Golf Game Ever</title><description>The perfect miniature golf game for the iPhone and iPod Touch. Ever. What does Crescent Ridge Mini Golf have that makes it so amazing? Well, it features things like: * An intuitive flick-motion for a true golf-like feel. * Ramps, Obstacles, Out-Of-Bounds, and more. * 45 hand-crafted Holes spread over 5 courses. * Each course is even individually themed!. * You can play ANY course at ANY time. * A simple, easy-to-navigate menu system. * Even iPhone 5 Support. (And coming soon: Multiplayer!! Where you can play with up to 4 people on the same device!) Making use of the Cocos2d and Box2d engines, Crescent Ridge Mini Golf offers mini golf on iOS like you've never played before. With all of the listed features above, it is certain that anyone who plays this game will enjoy every aspect. And hey! It's even free! So go ahead, try the first few levels. Maybe you'll find out you actually DO love mini golf on the phone (even if you're not a fan of playing it in person). Enjoy! :) *** DISCOVER KEITGAMES *** Facebook: www.facebook.com/KeitGames Website: www.keitgames.com Email: contact@keitgames.com</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7131_08_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/dd/49/30/dd493093-8ad2-6bc2-38ce-1e8967420470/mzl.pnghuczz.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7131-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7131_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:37:46">http://www.games.com/game/bright-gaming/paper-golf-the-golf-game-free</link><title>Paper Golf - The Golf Game - Free</title><description>*** Paper Golf - The Golf Game - for the iPhone and iTouch - and now iPad *** *** Now available to try for FREE *** In a world made out of paper, play an addictive game of golf. Realistic physics and one-finger control make this easy to play for anyone, yet hard to master. Completing the course is only one goal as there are Star Challenges to complete also. Retina graphics and a unique art style. This game will continue to grow with free updates and extra courses.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7131_09_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/df/dd/e1/dfdde1d6-8875-4aca-7c8c-5ddb53ac85ba/CoHbItThpAwfRfMtsbXF9g-temp-upload.ncfvyjgj.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7131-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7131_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:39:26">http://www.games.com/game/masque-publishing/solitaire-tripeaks</link><title>Solitaire: TriPeaks</title><description>Create a long chain to conquer the connected card pyramids and reach the high-scoring peaks.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7131_10_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/hss/storage/games/c4c1de4d7f702926e76bcbe1d4d84bdc</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>