<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7136">Soccer trick</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:45:12" name="Games.com" id="FW14-e048"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e048-7136-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7136_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:45:13">http://www.games.com/game/flashgamedistributioncom/goooaaaalll-2012</link><title>Goooaaaalll 2012</title><description>"He rushes, dribbles past 3 opponents, tricks the goalie, shoots and..... GOAAALLLLLLLLLL!!!!!" Are you a soccer star? Win all your matches, reach the final and win the cup!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7136_01_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/hss/storage/games/7761d94fa5c9415cf512955dc2d8afbc</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7136-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7136_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:49:09">http://www.games.com/game/novel-games/freestyle-soccer</link><title>Freestyle Soccer</title><description>Showcase the gorgeous trick of Around the World!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7136_02_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/hss/storage/games/19f96644303b9d83e387d284eef3fc69</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7136-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7136_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:50:16">http://www.games.com/game/flashgamedistributioncom/goooaaal</link><title>Goooaaal!</title><description>Are you a football star? Win all your matches, reach the final and win the cup!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7136_03_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/hss/storage/games/2cf849d8ff4d41f42dc9b614cd2e0fc</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7136-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7136_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:52:29">http://www.games.com/game/electronic-arts/fifa-street</link><title>FIFA Street</title><description>All-New Skill Moves - Over 50 never-before-experienced skill moves - double the amount found in FIFA 12 - that will enable you to beat your opponents and look good doing it. FIFA Gameplay Engine - Powered by the critically acclaimed FIFA 12 gameplay engine and the revolutionary Player Impact Engine, FIFA Street delivers an arsenal of groundbreaking street dribbling styles and trick moves that ignite the one-on-one battles. Complete Authenticity - The most authentic street football game ever created replicates the way the game is played by street football players all over the world. Play with and against the stars of the most popular clubs in the world - or real-life street players - and compete at more than 35 locations around the globe. Own the Street - From parking lots and parks to gyms and rooftop arenas, FIFA Street will feature cool and unique environments where the world plays street football. More than 35 different environments, including iconic locales like Rio de Janeiro, London, and Amsterdam. Street Ball Control - Enjoy a superior fidelity of ball control and responsiveness than anything ever experienced. Street Ball Control replicates the touch, creativity and flair street stars bring to the streets. Take on the challenge of beating - and embarrassing! - your opponent, Platforms: PlayStation 3, ESRB Rating: Everyone</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7136_04_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/61F9hTvJYbL._SL160_.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7136-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7136_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:56:51">http://www.games.com/game/electronic-arts/fifa-street-3</link><title>FIFA Street 3</title><description>Hit the streets with some of the best pro players and experience all the style and attitude of street soccer Choose from over 250 of the world's best players representing 18 of the top international teams Ultra-responsive controls and an easy-to-use trick system give you instant control over your idols Authentic training kits and street wear; distinctive style of play with unique abilities to match Set in exotic locales around the world with an eclectic selection of seamlessly infused music, Platforms: PlayStation 3, ESRB Rating: Everyone</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7136_05_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/513Ieo-6m3L._SL160_.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7136-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7136_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:58:32">http://www.games.com/game/electronic-arts/fifa-soccer-06</link><title>FIFA Soccer 06</title><description>Passion Real life abilities Realistic and Playable As you win against tougher and tougher teams, you'll earn points you can spend on improved skills, special tricks and more Challenging team chemistry keeps teams in the game, pulling together when the game gets rough, Platforms: Nintendo DS, ESRB Rating: Everyone</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7136_06_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/511yv8FJXlL._SL160_.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7136-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7136_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:03:26">http://www.games.com/game/nintendo/excitebots-trick-racing</link><title>ExciteBots: Trick Racing</title><description>Online multiplayer support for up to six player via a Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection in both Excite Race and Poker Race modes, and 2-player multiplayer versus mode in local play. Special ExciteBots: Trick Racing bundle features included Nintendo Wii Wheel. Insect and animal inspired off-road bot racers able to walk, fly and drive that via pick-up-and-play controls catch big-air and provide thrills at blinding speed like no other game in the Excitebike series. Having your vehicles drive, walk or fly around the track quickly is one thing, but it's more important to go around in style. Players earn stars for huge jumps, cool tricks and daring feats at high speed. A wide variety on mini-games, including soccer, poker, bowling, darts and clowns among others, that occur during races., Platforms: Nintendo Wii, ESRB Rating: Everyone</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7136_07_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/61OGawGJ01L._SL160_.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7136-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7136_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:07:52">http://www.games.com/game/electronic-arts/fifa-street-2</link><title>FIFA Street 2</title><description>Battle rivals with the ultimate display of soccer skills in this exciting game Trick-stick weapon with full arsenal of tricks including new juggling moves 320+ pro stars representing 20 national teams; 24 stars with signature moves Customize unique player and teams; build home turf with Pitch Creator Team up with friends in 3-player Co-op mode, Platforms: Sony PSP, ESRB Rating: Everyone</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7136_08_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/417ATY1T75L._SL160_.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7136-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7136_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:12:42">http://www.games.com/game/digital-artists-entertainment/cristiano-ronaldo-freestyle-soccer-hd</link><title>Cristiano Ronaldo FreeStyle Soccer HD</title><description>Think you’ve got what it take to freestyle with the best? Experience the rush of pulling off amazing tricks, moves and combos as one of the world’s greatest footballers in the officially licensed Cristiano RonaldoTM Freestyle game. For the first time ever, Cristiano Ronaldo Freestyle brings all of Ronaldo’s unique soccer skills and style into one amazing game. Packed with hundreds of tricks and challenges, multiple gameplay modes and set in different real-world locations, Cristiano Ronaldo Freestyle is the ultimate game to test your soccer skills to the max! •Earn achievements and unlock new items to fully customize your Cristiano Ronaldo character including shorts, T-shirts, shoes,sunglasses and even hairstyles •Choose from 5 gameplay modes including: ◦ Hype Endurance: Perform hype tricks whilst juggling the ball to get the crowd's attention as quickly as possible ◦Time Attack: Get as many points as possible in the duration of the whole song ◦Freestyle Battle: Compete against an opponent for the camera’s attention ◦Don’t Drop the Ball: How long can you last without dropping the ball? ◦Freestyle Showdown: 15 seconds competition to prove that your better than your opponent •Shuffle Mode launches a level at random. Want a different level? just reshuffle again to find one you like •Play soccer samba-style: make Cristiano Ronaldo move and dance to the beat while controlling the ball •25 challenges in 8 unique world locations. Battle opponents with their own personality and style from England, France, USA, Japan, Spain and Portugal</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7136_09_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/cc/2c/db/mzl.rromekii.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7136-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7136_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:16:27">http://www.games.com/game/gameloft/skater-nation</link><title>Skater Nation</title><description>" The best skateboarding game on the App Store." - IGN, Levi Buchanan Rule your board in Skater Nation and experience skateboarding in a way no other iPhone or iPod touch game can offer! \---------------------------------------------------------------------------- A WORLD OF POSSIBILITES Ride freely through an enormous 3D city and just have fun in the 10 different environments including beaches, residential areas and a skate park! BE YOUR OWN SKATER Pick from 8 different skaters, each with their own unique animations and style. Then make the board your own at the Skate Shop where you can purchase a selection of 10 different decks, trucks and wheels. ALL THE RIGHT MOVES Every location is jam packed with ramps, pipes and posts for you to perform your arsenal of tricks on. Show off your ollies, 360 flips, nose grabs and more! More than 30 tricks are available! SHOW OFF YOUR GREATNESS Ever perform the most amazing trick and wish somebody was there to see? Save your replay and upload it to YouTube and discuss them on skaternationgame.com, then dare your friends to do better. Connect to Gameloft LIVE! and chat with your friends or show off your unlocked trophies. LIVE BY THE BOARD Enter the Career mode to discover challenges waiting for you throughout the city. Become part of a story that puts you in the middle of the skateboarding world. \---------------------------------------------------------------------------- Become a fan of Gameloft on Facebook: gameloft.com/facebook Follow Gameloft on Twitter: twitter.com/gameloft www.skaternationgame.com Other Gameloft games you may like: Let’s Golf!, Real Tennis 2009, Gangstar, NFL 2010, Asphalt 5, Real Soccer 2010. Coming soon: James Cameron's Avatar, N.O.V.A. - Near Orbit Vanguard Alliance, Driver, Tom Clancy's H.A.W.X. Published and distributed by Gameloft. Certain apps allow you to purchase virtual items within the app and may contain third party advertisements that may redirect you to a third party site.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7136_10_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/78/76/a6/mzl.spanhdcb.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>