<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7348">map of the united states</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:09:50" name="Games.com" id="FW14-e048"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e048-7348-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7348_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:09:51">http://www.games.com/game/learning-gems/flash-cards-united-states</link><title>Flash Cards - United States</title><description>Colorful map of the United States Learn State names, capitals and abbreviations in a variety of formats of flashcards Clear graphic call outs and instructions on how to play and navigate through the cards Total of 430 different flash card variations</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7348_01_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/51KwSWhRXOL._SL160_.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7348-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7348_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:11:22">http://www.games.com/game/sillysoft/american-history-lux</link><title>American History Lux</title><description>Do you know history well?</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7348_02_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/cdn-games.bigfishgames.com/en_americanhistorylux/americanhistorylux_feature.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7348-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7348_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:13:56">http://www.games.com/game/gameloft/tom-clancys-rainbow-six-shadow-vanguard</link><title>Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six®: Shadow Vanguard</title><description>** 148Apps: “Rainbow Six: Shadow Vanguard is just all round great if you hadn’t already guessed.” ** SlideToPlay “Must have”: “If you want a tactical shooter in your pocket, you've come to the right place.” For the first time on iPhone and iPod touch, enjoy a new FPS experience that allows you to lead a team of elite soldiers! A global terrorist organization threatens the world balance. Only one team can prevent this: The Rainbow Unit! These colors never run. AN ICONIC BRAND FINALLY AVAILABLE ON THE APP STORE One of the most popular video game brands finally lands on your iPhone and iPod touch. AN ORIGINAL TITLE WITH EPIC MISSIONS Play 11 thrilling missions to defeat a dangerous and well-organized terrorist group. Play recreated and enriched levels based on the original Rainbow Six game like the Embassy Hostage Crisis, an oil platform assault or the infiltration of a rebel camp in Africa. Join a new Rainbow Unit complete with 3 new members, each with their own unique abilities like recon, demolition or stealth. EXPERIENCE CO-OP AND A RICH MULTIPLAYER MODE Join up to 2 friends and challenge the entire game together in Local and Online Co-op modes. You can also go head-to-head with the best unit leaders in the world on 5 exclusive and thrilling maps in Multiplayer mode - up to 10 players. THEY’LL NEVER SEE IT COMING Infiltrate enemy compounds without them ever knowing you’re there thanks to a wide range of state-of-the-art gadgets. Use snake cameras to spy around corners, silencers to keep your kills discreet and many more covert tools and weapon upgrades. BE THE LEADER OF AN ELITE UNIT An exclusive real-time tactical system for iPhone that lets you lead your teammates through each level. Order them to cover, shoot or use grenades to clear rooms before an assault! Warning: This game is not compatible with iPod touch 3G 8GB and older devices Certain apps allow you to purchase virtual items within the app and may contain third party advertisements that may redirect you to a third party site.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7348_03_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/fc/2a/9d/mzl.txkmzzfv.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7348-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7348_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:14:33">http://www.games.com/game/rocketpop-games/jetpack-junkie</link><title>Jetpack Junkie</title><description>RocketPop Games celebrates our fans- Jetpack Junkie full version is now free! Rock and Roll! #1 in Italy, Germany, Austria, Panama, Ecuador, Iceland and the Bahamas! Top 5 in Japan, Chile, Peru, Mexico, Columbia, Guatemala,Venezuela and France!Top 25 in over 30 Countries! Top 15 in the United States! Can you become a legend? “Jetpack Junkie is a great way to kill some time….If you want a serious challenge in your 3D runner, this is the game to get” CNET.com ”you can experience amazing jetpack flight and fun with games like Jetpack Junkie for all iOS devices”- APP Chronicles ”addictive experience constant of continuous action” - iPhones.co.il ”A 3D endless runner with a futuristic setting, Jetpack Junkie is more entertaining than you'd expect - largely due to the jetpack on the back of the main character.” - PocketGamer TIME TO TAKE BACK YOUR CITY! It’s the year 2035 – Metropolis has been taken over by an alien force! The Human Resistance must locate the enemy weapons to take back their beloved city. Alien tech jams all sensors, so they created Recon Runners to map the city. A few became legends and they were known as Jetpack Junkies. Do you have what it takes to move up the command chain and become a Jetpack Junkie? Features \- Addicting “play just one more time” endless gameplay \- Upgrade crazy powerups by collecting coins \- Unlock all 5 characters \- Game Center Leaderboards to compete with your friends \- Simple smooth tilt and touch controls \- Gorgeous full 3D environment \- Customize game play \- Level up to become a legend! * Not recommended for iPhone 3GS or below.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7348_04_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple2/v4/12/0e/9c/120e9cdb-a715-df22-f230-8db66ec8ab03/mzl.srycttxj.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7348-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7348_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:18:07">http://www.games.com/game/exedria/the-50-states-states-capitals-flags-of-the-united-states</link><title>The 50 States - States, capitals &amp; flags of the United States</title><description>* Entered Top 20 Games/Trivia in USA * Entered Top 50 Games/Educational in USA * Entered Top 5 Games/Trivia in France * Entered Top 20 Games/Trivia in Italy, Germany, Russia, Spain, Switzerland, Norway &amp; Denmark * Entered Top 10 Games/Trivia in Japan * Universal App, runs on iPhone, iPod Touch &amp; iPad! * Features: \- 6 games in one with states, capitals and flags \- 3 match games to improve memory, concentration and reaction time \- 3 quiz-style games \- Learn while playing with your iPhone, iPod Touch &amp; iPad \- Detailed information for each State \- Zoomable map of the USA divided by States \- Professional statistics to keep track of your scores \- Links to Wikipedia to learn more \- Optimized for retina display Play and learn: \- While you move from place to place \- During your commute, get the most out of your time! \- At the aiport waiting for your flight \- On the bus, on the train when going to work \- On the beach and during your vacations \- While waiting in line at the store \- On your sofa! Empower: \- Memory and concentration \- Visual perception \- Spatial reasoning and problem solving \- Speed and reaction time \- Fluid intelligence \- Brain health Get the most out of your time, use it wisely learning something useful for your life and your career. Twitter http://twitter.com/exedria</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7348_05_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/92/e8/8a/92e88afa-592b-887a-3916-ed8165d6b661/mzm.vvodfehz.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7348-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7348_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:21:52">http://www.games.com/game/digital-press-publishing/united-states-quizzle</link><title>United States Quizzle™</title><description>Do you know the capital of Idaho? Who was the 9th President? Can you identify New Hampshire on a map? If you want to test your knowledge of the United States, you'll want to try the new United States Quizzle™ app! Test your knowledge and learn fun facts. Plus be part of the community and let us know what new categories and questions you want us to add. Plus the more 5-star ratings we receive the more questions we will add to this Quizzle! Also check out Famous Faces Quizzle!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7348_06_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple2/v4/f7/7b/6f/f77b6f4e-8d75-0a92-f40d-9d150bbc23bd/mzl.qxayoydm.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7348-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7348_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:25:28">http://www.games.com/game/lakoo/demonsouls</link><title>DemonSouls</title><description>■ Oh MY God! $1.99 -&gt; FREE for limited time! Ask friends to download DemonSouls now! ■ Get the daily reward and play the game every day! (Internet connection needed) ■ This game supports English/Japanese/Chinese. You may change the language setting by the option "Language“ from the main menu of the title scene. ★★★★★"the game is brilliant. The beautiful graphics, fun Rpg gameplay, and a unique and beautiful story of two lovers. NO RPG these days have love story's as romantic and beautiful as this game."-Hambo12, TouchArcade ★★★★★"Awesome, Lakoo is making the best rpg games so far"-DarkMedow, United States ★★★★★"I've played them all in this genre and I can honestly say this is one of the best for a long time, interesting pet/skill/forge system with gotta catch em all vibe and charming graphics."-Comeplaydie, United Kingdom ★★★★★"Great graphics and gameplay I love the storyline and works Awesome on IPhone 4-4S and 5"-zxhero, Canada ★★★★★"Nice graphics and design. I kinda like the demon soul skills, I thought that was quite unique."-ArcFate, Singapore App Store A stunning epic classic styled ARPG for today’s digital devices! In this dynamic fantasy action game, your heroic adventure will see you battle with demons, mastering their demonic powers through their souls! Guide Thunder, who turns from a simple young fisherman to a legendary hero, through this epic journey, as he discovers secrets in this immersing fantasy world, which will help him save the realms of humans and demons! GAME FEATURES: \- Classic styled ARPG with stunning visuals and animation! \- Quests filled with adventure, mysteries and real-time epic battles! \- Unleash demonic attacks through casting and summoning spells! \- Level up and customize your character’s attributes! \- Dialogue choices that will unlock one of the multiple endings! \- Demon horde mode arena! \- Demonic Elemental System! \- Customize 60 weapons and armor with demonic powers! \- Over 40 Achievements that earn rewards! \- Over 50 maps to explore! \- Daily rewards! \- Demon Field Journal! \- Intuitive controls for easy to understand game play! Real-time Battles There’s no time to blink with demons attacking you from every corner! Move and fight off hordes of demons with your normal attack, or charge up your ultimate combo and lay waste to the foul creatures! Cast demonic auras, attack and summoning spells too! Demon souls Demon souls can be taken from those you defeated. Cast demonic auras, attack and summoning spells, imbue equipment with demonic abilities, as well as create new breeds of demons by merging various demon souls! Multiple Endings Many hours of replay value through item hunts, side quests, demon soul hunts and unlocking the multiple endings! Demon Horde Mode Unlock this demon battling arena, where you will have timed battles with various levels of demons! What better way to test your mantle while leveling up your character? Demonic Elemental System There’re three demonic elements: fire, wood and water that counteract each other. This makes forging your equipment and demonic spells strategically dynamic and vital to succeed in battles. Daily Rewards Log in every day to get daily rewards including: gold coins, soulstones and epic items! (*** requires 3G/WIFI connection) Demon Field Journal As you capture demon souls, your demon field journal will be updated with information about them. Use it to find out the best way to smite your enemies! After you finish the game and can play again and capture the demon souls you’re missing to help unlock the multiple endings! If you like DemonSouls by Nova Studio from Lakoo, check out their other game Dawn of Magic, a classic styled JRPG on iTunes now! Lakoo Official Website http://lakoo.com DemonSouls Fan Page http://www.facebook.com/demonsouls.en Our Fan Page http://www.facebook.com/lakoogames http://twitter.com/lakoogames Help &amp; Support: http://cs.lakoo.com/home</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7348_07_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple6/v4/d5/d1/a3/d5d1a3a3-833d-d269-8262-e74e22212c3f/mzl.afpsalcb.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7348-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7348_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:28:52">http://www.games.com/game/inmotion-software/i-dig-it-expeditions</link><title>I Dig It Expeditions</title><description>ON SALE FOR THE HOLIDAYS! "This game surpasses many titles on both DS and PSP" - Go! Go! Mob, "Without hesitation, we say buy this game." - Slide To Play, "I Dig It Expeditions takes the same popular formula of the original and improves upon it in nearly every way imaginable" - Touch Arcade, "Graphics and sound are downright excellent. If you played the original, this game bests it." - Phoneblog.com "It’s a fun throw back to old school gaming with enough modern wrinkles to keep it on my iPhone..." - Games Plus Blog Touch Arcade 4.5/5 Best Games Nov. '09 Slide To Play 4/4 Score Go!Go! Mob Award Pocket Gamer 9/10 Gold Award \-------------------------------- Embark on an epic adventure with the fantastic digging machine. Travel the world in search of ancient artifacts, lost civilizations, and unimaginable treasure. Manage fuel, temperature, damage, cargo space, oxygen, etc while searching for underground diggins. Sell your rare collection of artifacts to earn cash. Use cash to upgrade your digging machine, make repairs, or purchase additional supplies. Discover new hazards, such as ocean currents, methane gas pockets, geo-thermal vents, and a new species unknown to man... Featuring 4 unique locations around the world: * Mid-West United States * Antarctic tundra * South American Amazon * South Asian Ocean * 6-10 hours of game-play in the campaign * Plus hours of additional challenges * Freeplay mode * Save checkpoints along the way * New full screen map to chart your underground tunnels * Dozens of new supplies available to help along the way * New inventory screen to manage your diggins and supplies</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7348_08_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/3a/b6/b3/mzl.mltrwxfu.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7348-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7348_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:31:49">http://www.games.com/game/big-wood-games-limited/magic-craft-the-hero-of-fantasy-kingdom-free</link><title>Magic Craft: The Hero of Fantasy Kingdom Free</title><description>As the legend says, a long, long time ago there was a kingdom ruled by a wise king, a queen, and their beautiful daughter, in a place they called Fantasy Land. All was well until the darkness attacked this magical place and took away the princess. The king gathered to all the brave men in the kingdom stating that anyone who can defeat the darkness army and got her daughter back could get married to her daughter. It's your time now, hero. The beautiful princess is waiting for you! * Game Features* 3 DIFFERENT WORLDS Fight on forests, ice worlds and fiery valleys, defend your kingdom and princesses against darkness! 27 FUN-DEAD MAPS Epic defense battles that will hook you for hours! EPIC CHALLENG MODE Extra game modes that will challenge your tactical skills! FANTASY RPG CLASSES Recruit wizards, warriors and archers, customizing your defensive strategy with different unit upgrades and talents! OVER 20 DIFFERENT ENEMIES Fight against hordes of goblins, orcs, skeletons, giants and other darkness armies! OVER 24 HERO TALENTS Customize different talent builds to defeat darkness armies and bosses! \--------------------- MORE GAMES \--------------------- \- Magic Craft \- Hungry Piggy Spy Edition \- Tommy &amp; cheese \- Ice Pengy \- Doodle Cubes \- Coco Birds \--------------------- Tips and Updates \--------------------- bigwoodgames.com</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7348_09_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/8c/c4/d7/8cc4d7e8-525e-7e00-c911-09acde4f7cd2/mzl.vzsfoxcs.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7348-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7348_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:33:55">http://www.games.com/game/joy-preschool-game/animal-shape-puzzle-free-educational-preschool-learning-games-for-kids-toddlers</link><title>Animal Shape Puzzle Free- Educational Preschool Learning Games for Kids &amp; Toddlers</title><description>※※※"Restore" your purchase if any game or scenes was locked after your updates, and it is FREE if you have already purchase it before.※※※ &gt; 409 cute individual puzzles with funny sounds and Word Learning! &gt; 57 SCENES--40 Noun Scenes(12Animal+4Food+8Life+9Map+4Festival+3Others), 9 Verb Scenes and 8 Adj. Scenes.(Only 12 scenes in free version) &gt; Pure &amp; Native English, Spanish, German and French pronunciation! "This is a super puzzle for beginning skills. Recent update with added puzzles really makes this app worth the $$$"--Autism father. "He is learning spacial logic, vocabulary and working his fine motor skills all at once."--Grouperone "Awesome game! Love the fact that you can set the language! Have it set to German and my daughter loves it!!!"--by Tampamom74. Looking for something entertain but also educational for your kids? Animal Jigsaw Puzzle is a must-have! It will keep your kids educationally entertained, all the while developing their concentration, memory, and cognitive skills, and teaching them what sounds objects make. It will also keep your kids quit while they play it again, again, and again…right when you need that much-needed break in a restaurant, on a plane, or in a car. And, costing less than a bottle of water, it will be the best money you’ve ever spent. Animal Jigsaw Puzzle was designed to be kid-friendly! There are no complicated menus for kids to get confused by, or multiple options to get lost in. It was tested by several toddlers and we took their suggestions seriously to create a funny but educational app for them. Such as: we added (+) button to help kids finish difficult puzzles automatically according to their advice. What’s more, not only will your children love the art of a puzzle, but they will also be kept constantly motivated by the all funny, happily enthusiastic hippo, who is there always ready, waiting to articulate the praise children deserve for their patient efforts Scenes: 1 Dinosaur scene 2 Sea scene 3 Farm scene 4 Forest scene 5 Africa scene 6 Insect scene 7 Polar Region scene 8 Desert scene 9 Bird scene 10 Bakery scene 11 Fruit scene 12 Beverage scene 13 Vegetable scene 14 Toy scene 15 Vehicle scene 16 Playground scene 17 Living room scene 18 Bedroom scene 19 Music scene 20 Continent scene 21 United States scene 22 Australia scene 23 Canada scene 24 Germany scene 25 Spain scene 26 France scene 27 United Kingdom scene 28 China scene 29 Halloween scene 30 Thanksgiving scene 31 Christmas scene 32 Solar System scene 33 Number Scene 34 Color Scene 35 Flower Scene 36 Clothing Store Scene 37 Circus 1 Scene 38 Circus 2 Scene 39 Circus 3 Scene 40 Christmas 2 Scene 41-49 Verb 1-9 Scene 50-57 Adj. 1-8 Scene New scenes coming soon! Contact Us: Email:joy-preschool@hotmail.com Like:facebook.com/JoyPreschoolGame Follow:twitter.com/JoyPreschool</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7348_10_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/77/a8/1c/77a81c73-a19a-109e-f4ae-439d102b7507/mzl.cjjksqpf.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>