<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7425">coloring picture cars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:01:02" name="Games.com" id="FW14-e048"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e048-7425-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7425_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:01:02">http://www.games.com/game/planarsoft/tootooni-for-toddlers-kids</link><title>TooTooNi! for Toddlers &amp; Kids</title><description>Draw the tracks: Drag your finger on the screen to create a train track, road or airway over the on-screen scenery, then watch as the cartoon trains, cars and airplanes travel along the paths while making their distinctive sounds. Building blocks: Pick up and place different shapes and colors of blocks and form houses, trains, etc with or without gravity. Match the pairs: Tap the screen to reveal pictures of the cartoon vehicle characters and excercise your memory by matching the pairs of identical pictures. Water paint: Brush your finger over the black-and-white sketches to reveal the colors that complete the picture. Finger paint: Choose colors from the palette and brush your finger over the canvas to color-in the black-and-white sketches using your own imagination. Picture puzzle: Reassemble the scrambled pictures by dragging the tiles to their correct place on the canvas. Music room : Tap on the cartoon characters and hear the sounds they make. Connect the dots : Tap on the numbered dots in sequence to reveal the hidden image. Scratch the cards : Scratch with your finger the card to unveil the picture. Blackboard: Write your name, letters, numbers, outlines, do additions using your finger as chalk on the blackboard.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7425_01_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/71HIpL-SCaL._SL160_.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7425-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7425_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:01:55">http://www.games.com/game/sulaba/race-rally-3d-racing-car-arcade-fun</link><title>Race Rally 3D - Racing Car Arcade Fun</title><description>Key features; ? Beautiful 3D graphics of unique race track &amp; cars ? Challenge AI opponents ? Drizzling rain or day mode ? Turn into night racing with lights on or off ? Custom choice of Steering, Stick, or Motion control for wheel and throttle ? Picture-in-Picture(PIP) 2D overview track map ? Continuous feed - car back camera view mirror ? Choose from 3 fun game modes Race &amp; Chase, Countdown &amp; Timer ? 6 diff.camera views including front facing car view (Inside/Outside &amp; Sky views) ? Collision fire sparks ? Choice of race car color ? Unique and absorbing music tracks plus SFX/sound controls ? Amazingly small footprint of binary size for a quality 3D racing game.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7425_02_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/81NomOBoyML._SL160_.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7425-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7425_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:03:37">http://www.games.com/game/sulaba/race-n-chase-3d-car-racing-game</link><title>Race N Chase - 3D Car Racing Game</title><description>Play a racing game with 3D graphics of a beautiful racing track &amp; cars Challenge the AI opponents Drizzling rain or shine mode Turn into night racing with lights on. Collision fire sparks Custom choice of Steering, Stick, or Motion control for wheel and throttle Picture-in-Picture(PIP) 2D overview track map Continuous car back view camera mirror Choose from 3 fun game modes - Lap Race &amp; Chase, Countdown &amp; Timer Toggle between 6 camera views including front facing car view (Inside, Outside &amp; Sky views) Choose your race car color Unique and absorbing music tracks plus SFX/sound controls Amazingly small footprint of binary size for this level of 3D racing game and no need of in-app purchase.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7425_03_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/81OmQDY%2B0bL._SL160_.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7425-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7425_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:04:29">http://www.games.com/game/sulaba/race-n-chase-3d-car-racing-action-arcade</link><title>Race N Chase - 3D Car Racing Action Arcade</title><description>Play a racing game with 3D graphics of a beautiful racing track &amp; cars Challenge the AI opponents in drizzling rain or shine mode Turn into night racing with lights on. Collision fire sparks Custom choice of Steering, Stick, or Motion control for wheel and throttle with SFX sound Picture-in-Picture(PIP) 2D overview track map Continuous car back view camera mirror Choose from 3 fun game modes - Lap Race &amp; Chase, Countdown &amp; Timer Toggle between 6 camera views including front facing car view (Inside, Outside &amp; Sky views) Choose your race car color &amp; custom controls</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7425_04_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/51CuiPkvvDL._SL160_.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7425-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7425_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:07:36">http://www.games.com/game/sulaba/race-n-chase-3d-action-arcade-cars-racing</link><title>Race N Chase - 3D Action Arcade Cars Racing</title><description>Play a racing game with 3D graphics of a beautiful racing track &amp; cars Challenge the AI opponents in drizzling rain or shine mode Turn into night racing with lights on. Collision fire sparks Custom choice of Steering, Stick, or Motion control for wheel and throttle with SFX sound Picture-in-Picture(PIP) 2D overview track map Continuous car back view camera mirror Choose from 3 fun game modes - Lap Race &amp; Chase, Countdown &amp; Timer Toggle between 6 camera views including front facing car view (Inside, Outside &amp; Sky views) Choose your race car color &amp; custom controls</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7425_05_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/81OmQDY%2B0bL._SL160_.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7425-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7425_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:11:23">http://www.games.com/game/sulaba/street-circuit-racing-3d</link><title>Street Circuit Racing 3D</title><description>Beautiful 3D graphics of modern city roads,bridges &amp; riverbed. Switch between day &amp; night city mode during game play. Totally pleasing and racer will like it. Challenge AI opponents Choose between 2 different unique car models and 6 different colors for each. Custom choice of Steering, Stick, or Motion control for wheel and throttle Picture-in-Picture(PIP) 2D overview track map Continuous feed - car back camera view mirror &amp; collision fire sparks Choose from 3 fun game modes Race &amp; Chase, Countdown &amp; Timer 6 diff.camera views including front facing car view (Inside/Outside &amp; Sky views) Unique and absorbing music tracks plus SFX/sound controls</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7425_06_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/91V2ffbf6IL._SL160_.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7425-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7425_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:14:01">http://www.games.com/game/aijun-she/ghosts-revenge</link><title>Ghost's Revenge</title><description>Ghost's Revenge! [ The story ] A little girl was knocked down by a flying car in the village, and the driver escaped with the car. The girl was very serious and finally was gone. Her ghost wake up, and decie to follow that bay guy.She followed the guy to their party. They were not aware of the Revenge.  The ghost gathered many fellows, dicussing the revenge……The ghost ask for Dryad’s help. Those bad guys were terribly frightened by  the dryads,running away. And finally got arrested by the police. Ghost's Revenge finished, they fly away and the village return peaceful. [ How to play ? ] Looking difference between the 2 pictures! The differences between the pictures are very slight in every points of the game. You should find a difference and click the different point in any picture. You can chose ‘play with hints’ firstly. [The features] The pictures are extremely fine,each pair of pictures are almost identical and perfect. There are only slight differences between two pictures,such as the socks of the characters,color of the hairs, watchband of the hands,points of the trees,color of house even far away. Including the feet,shoes, the grass direction even the hair direction. update: 1.3.5 fix the bug of save game</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7425_07_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/f5/5b/8d/f55b8d7a-6505-66d9-a4b5-5bbc0e73e899/EMTB46EVLbbSAButDD939M-temp-upload.yzyeiefx.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7425-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7425_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:16:24">http://www.games.com/game/22learn/abby-basic-skills-preschool-puzzles-and-patterns-hd-free</link><title>Abby - Basic Skills Preschool: Puzzles and Patterns HD Free</title><description>Try for FREE, full version 66% OFF SALE - TODAY: April 7 - 14, 2014 ***** A title from our extremely successful series -- all EIGHT (!) RANKED #1 APP FOR KIDS on APP Store in many countries: ABBY BASIC SKILLS PRESCHOOL, ABBY – PAINTER STAR, ANIMAL PRESCHOOL SHAPE PUZZLES - FIRST WORD; ABBY'S MAGIC LAPTOP FOR PRESCHOOL AND TODDLERS, ABBY MONKEY – ANIMAL GAMES FOR KIDS HD, ANIMAL TRAIN - FIRST WORD HD, ANIMAL PRESCHOOL WORD PUZZLES HD, and ABBY MONKEY – First Words for Preschool: Animals HD). All five other products ranked in TOP 10 in EDUCATIONAL category. Letters, Counting, Puzzles, Sizes, Shadows, Matching, Colors, Shapes, Differences, Patterns and more -- you are on the right address! Abby's Basic Skills application is a new application from a series developed by a team of educational experts from 22learn designed to best prepare your children for success in the kindergarten curriculum. Its simple child-friendly interface offers children an engaging way to master the essential skills in the total of 12 (full version only) DIFFERENT EXCITING EDUCATIONAL ACTIVITIES (ten educational activities + two creative activities). We sincerely hope your children will enjoy them all! \----- "I really appreciate the incredible amount of activities. The option to select only those activities you want your child to practise is great! What a helpful toy both for parents and their toddlers!" Anita, a mother of three. "One, two, three cars! Bye-bye train!" Nathan, a three-year-old beta-tester. \----- The ENTHUSIASTIC MONKEY CHARACTER is going to guide children through the whole game. As a reward after each round, children receive the opportunity to become creative artists and CHANGE THE DESIGN OF THE TRAIN, or obtain STICKERS TO SHOW OFF ON THEIR BOARD! 1) LETTERS Tap on the word that starts with the letter that was pronounced! Great for teaching children to realize the connection of letters to words, understand the position of the first letter, and practise matching the names of letters to their symbolic notation! 2) COUNTING Count the toys! Hearing the counting pronounced helps children to better remember the order of the numerals as well as get used to the counting procedure. Way to learn how to count! 3) SIZES Train the skills of understanding the comparative nature of concepts of big, small and the same! 4) PUZZLES Fix the broken toy! Puzzles mode enables your children to train fine motor skills and improve their logical thinking skills when they need to realize the correct position of each puzzle and understand how they together make a whole. 5) SHADOWS Drag the object to its silhouette! 6) MATCHING Match the toys! Matching game serves to train children's memory and understanding of the concept of the same. Children need to match in total four pairs of toys. 7) COLORS The task is to tap on the toy that is painted in a certain color. The task is made slightly easier by the fact that the name of the color is always written on the top of the screen, making the activity great for children only beginning with colors learning. 8) SHAPES Shapes is an activity designed to teach children recognition of names of common shapes (such as a square, rectangle, or triangle). The task is to tap on the shape whose name was pronounced. 9) PATTERNS This activity gives children practice in the area of common patterns recognition. Task is to drag the object that completes the toy pattern into its correct place. 10) SAME AND DIFFERENT This game tests the ability of comparing pictures and finding differences. Task is either to select the different toy among several others, or to find the same toy as the displayed one. We hope that your children will enjoy the application the same way our little beta-testers did. Thank you for your purchase!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7425_08_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/7f/91/30/mzl.rofxtwjv.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7425-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7425_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:19:08">http://www.games.com/game/out-of-the-blue-digital/colorforms-revolution-free</link><title>Colorforms® Revolution™ Free</title><description>It’s More Fun To Play the Colorforms Way!™ And now you and the entire family can play on your iPad with the Colorforms® Revolution™ Free app. Combine shapes, colors, patterns and backgrounds in endless combinations to create an infinite number of exciting designs. A rectangle and two circles becomes a car, a square and a triangle becomes a house. Put them together and a story is born. Or fling a shape across the screen to see it come to life! The only limit is your imagination! Colorforms® Revolution™ is Color and Shape \- Play with 19 shapes and 64 unique colors and patterns! Colorforms® Revolution™ is Visual, Creative and Expressive \- Choose from 26 colored and patterned backgrounds or import your own photo! Colorforms® Revolution™ is Original and Interactive \- Drag or tap as many shapes into your picture as you like! You can interact with a single shape or create an intricate work of art! Colorforms® Revolution™ is Reusable, Repositionable and Forgiving \- You can always change a shape’s color, pattern, size, rotation and position or discard it, save your picture to your gallery to edit later or start over! Colorforms® Revolution™ is Contemporary \- Swipe through your saved creations in your Gallery. You can also share them with your friends and family on Facebook or save them to your device! Colorforms® Revolution™ is Approachable and Universal -With simple controls you’ll figure out as you go, Colorforms® is good wholesome fun for everyone! Just pick it up, start playing and join the revolution! The FULL Colorforms® Revolution™ app is now available for the iPad, iPhone and iPod Touch with new shape colors &amp; patterns, backgrounds and three exciting new modes: Play Sets, Puzzle Boards and Go Wild!! Get it now on iTunes and join the revolution! About Colorforms® Colorforms®, the classic toy brand that has inspired young kids to follow their own imaginations for over 60 years, develops important skills in visual creativity and emotional expression. Unlike many newer toy brands on the market, Colorforms® encourages kids to learn by using their imagination in an open-ended environment they create themselves. See our entire line of Colorforms® toys at www.colorforms.com. About Out of the Blue Digital Out of the Blue Digital is a division of Out of the Blue Enterprises, a leader in children's educational entertainment. We are the creators and producers of Super Why, the Emmy-nominated literacy series on PBS Kids, Daniel Tiger's Neighborhood, the upcoming animated series inspired by Mister Rogers' Neighborhood &amp; Nickelodeon's Blue's Room. As specialists in children's media, we aim to engage kids and families with age-appropriate, interactive, &amp; meaningful learning experiences. Check out our other apps on iTunes: -Super Why! -Super Why Paint! -Super Why Alpha Boost! -Chuggington: Terrific Trainee! -Colorforms® Revolution™ HD About University Games Founded on April 1, 1985, University Games’ philosophy has always been to offer games that encourage social interaction &amp; imagination through game play with learning sprinkled in to season the game! Our foundation is built upon a quarter century of successful game play around titles including Murder Mystery Party®, 20 Questions®, Colorforms® and Sort It Out!, which was named Game of the Year in the 2010 Toy Of The Year Awards. The new Sort It Out! app is now on iTunes. Colorforms® Revolution™ is Open Feint enabled and works with Game Center!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7425_09_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/8d/10/a1/8d10a156-1088-ca62-3e8b-54ed8f852940/mzl.lobtpaoi.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7425-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7425_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:20:14">http://www.games.com/game/nodeflexion-com/tozzle-toddlers-favorite-puzzle</link><title>Tozzle - Toddler's favorite puzzle</title><description>\-- comment by 2 year old Madeleine: "again!" ******* NOW 44 PUZZLES AND FUNNY ANIMATIONS! ******* *** SUPPORTS IPHONE 5 AND IPHONE 4 &amp; 4S RETINA DISPLAY! *** Tozzle supports english, german, french and spanish! Try before you buy! Search for Tozzle Lite on the AppStore. Looking for something entertaining but also educational for your kid? Then Tozzle is the perfect App for you! This puzzle app is built for children from age 2 - 99. It keeps your toddler entertained and he/she learns to improve shape recognition and motor activity. Choose from 44 different puzzle pictures, all including funny sound effects. It's really easy to use. Just let your toddler pick one out of 44 colorful, child orientated puzzles and let him / her solve it by drag&amp;drop. Once a puzzle is solved your kid can play around with the sound effects by tapping on the figures. An exit button on the bottom left brings you back to the selection menu. This program was tested by several toddlers and we took their suggestions seriously to create a funny but educational app for them. If a child can't find the right place for a piece, a helping arrow appears after the third try so every child can solve every puzzle. Look forward to relaxed car rides, you´ll never again have to drive AND entertain your kid, you can concentrate on driving while your child is having fun with Tozzle! If you want to see Tozzle in action, just search for "Tozzle" on Youtube. To change the language, select "Settings -&gt; Tozzle -&gt; Language" follow us on twitter: twitter.com/nodeflexion \---- It's always a good idea to restart your iPhone after installing a new App. \----</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7425_10_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/24/bd/d0/24bdd0ba-2407-4c7b-9f18-b9c2b9c30dbc/mzl.cafjpszd.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>