<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7438">facebook privacy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:33:51" name="Games.com" id="FW14-e048"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e048-7438-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7438_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:33:52">http://www.games.com/game/electronic-arts/monopoly</link><title>MONOPOLY</title><description>**YOU VOTED &amp; THE CAT’S OUT OF THE BAG** Thanks to the votes from YOU and thousands of loyal MONOPOLY Facebook fans from 185 different countries, the CAT mover is now available to play with in this latest update as well as in the classic board game version of MONOPOLY! BUY, SELL &amp; TRADE FAMOUS PROPERTIES From Marvin Gardens to Water Works to Park Place, own and manage the famous holdings of the MONOPOLY board. EMPLOY HANDS ON MANAGEMENT Shake your device to “roll” the 3D dice. Tap the screen to manage your properties. Building hotels or taking a “Chance” is easy and intuitive. CHOOSE YOUR LEVEL AND LOOK Play through 3 levels of difficulty and save games in progress. Also customize the number of players, the “game rules,” and even the game environment. FEELING MORE COMPETITIVE? Challenge up to 3 friends via local WiFi and Pass ‘N Play Multiplayer, and up to 2 friends with Bluetooth Multiplayer. PLAY WITH OTHER iOS FRIENDS You can even play multiplayer games with friends who have MONOPOLY for iPad (just note that you’ll be playing the iPhone/iPod touch version). So buy Boardwalk! Go directly to jail! Are you ready? It’s “GO” time! Terms of Service : http://www.ea.com/terms-of-service Privacy and Cookie Policy: http://www.ea.com/privacy-policy Game EULA: http://tos.ea.com/legalapp/mobileeula/US/en/GM/ Visit https://help.ea.com/ for assistance or inquiries.EA may retire online features and services after 30 days’ notice posted on www.ea.com/1/service-updates.Important Consumer Information. This app: Contains direct links to the Internet; Collects data through third party analytics technology (see Privacy &amp; Cookie Policy for details).</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7438_01_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple6/v4/bf/6c/02/bf6c02d0-9650-d6ae-d19e-1e6eddf55bce/mzl.ogvlqywp.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7438-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7438_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:36:11">http://www.games.com/game/electronic-arts/the-sims-3</link><title>The Sims 3</title><description>This app offers in-app purchases. You may disable in-app purchasing using your device settings. See http://support.apple.com/kb/HT4213 for more info YOU’VE NEVER SEEN THE SIMS LIKE THIS BEFORE! This #1 bestselling award-winner* is better than ever on iPhone and iPod touch. Enjoy visual quality made to maximize the Retina Display plus Fast App Switching to get you in and out of game sessions faster than ever. Long live The Sims! CREATE YOUR OWN SIM Make your Sims neurotic, funny or shy. Choose appearances, clothing, and accessories, and bring your Sims to life! Make your Sims flirtatious or total jerks! Or, if your Sims are the solitary kinds, head to the lake and go fishing (make sure to bring a pole, though). SEE AND EXPLORE NEW LOCATIONS Lose yourself in the amazing open-world environment designed to take advantage of Retina Display. Discover what kinds of characters your Sims will turn out to be! Will they stay home and take care of the house, or will they be Sims about town? KEEP ‘EM SATISFIED Fulfill your Sims' essential needs like eating and sleeping to increase the amount of activities your Sims can do. Take good care of your Sims so you can enjoy more exciting interactions and activities. DREAM BIG! Stay in tune with your Sims’ mercurial desires like growing corn, staying well-rested, or buying stuff. Unlock and achieve 73 Goals and Wishes to help your Sims reach their full potentials. SIMOLEON CHEAT! (WARNING! REPEATABLE AND ADDICTIVE) To get unlimited Simoleons, follow these steps during gameplay: Press the Pause Button with the 3 dots that’s in the lower-left corner…press “Help &amp; About”…select “Gardening Tips”…then shake the device for Simoleons! * Apple iTunes Rewind 2009 “#1 BESTSELLING GAME,” Mobile Excellence Awards “BEST MOBILE GAME FOR 2009” ________________________________________ *** DON'T MISS OUR OTHER EXCITING GAMES! ** TETRIS®, MONOPOLY, Madden NFL 11 by EA Sports™, Pogo Games FREE, Liqua Pop, ROCK BAND® Reloaded, Need for Speed™ Hot Pursuit &amp; Surviving High School FREE GIFT THIS APP: Click the “Buy App” arrow on the iTunes® App Store Be the first to know! Get inside EA info on great deals, plus the latest game updates, tips &amp; more… VISIT US: ea.com/iphone FOLLOW US: twitter.com/eamobile LIKE US: facebook.com/eamobile WATCH US: youtube.com/eamobilegames Terms of Service : http://www.ea.com/terms-of-service Privacy and Cookie Policy: http://www.ea.com/privacy-policy Game EULA: http://tos.ea.com/legalapp/mobileeula/US/en/GM/ Visit https://help.ea.com/ for assistance or inquiries. EA may retire online features and services after 30 days’ notice posted on www.ea.com/1/service-updates. Important Consumer Information. This app: Contains direct links to the Internet; Collects data though third party ad serving and analytics technology (See Privacy &amp; Cookie Policy for details).</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7438_02_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/26/76/6e/26766e07-9ff2-3e14-f701-497825026c8f/mzl.scjtgmyo.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7438-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7438_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:37:40">http://www.games.com/game/electronic-arts/the-sims-3-ambitions</link><title>The Sims 3 Ambitions</title><description>THE MOST AMBITIOUS EXPERIENCE OF THE SIMS™ ON THE APP STORE! Now your Sims can turn passions into professions…Build dream homes or businesses…Even have BABIES! Get everything you love about The Sims and more from this all-new member of The Sims™ family of games for iPhone® &amp; iPod touch®. CAREER MODE! MAKE A DREAM A DESTINY For the first time ever on iPhone &amp; iPod touch, turn your Sims’ hobbies into fulfilling jobs. Will your Sim become a Firefighter? Rock Star? Artist? Teacher? Chef? Sports Star? Get down to business with new career-oriented goals, mini-games, outfits, and locations. Follow your Sims to work and see them get happier as they make their dreams come true. BUILD MODE! CREATE A DREAM HOME OR BUILD UP A BUSINESS Think big with the improved and expanded Build Mode feature. Resize, add, or delete rooms, floors, walls, doors, and windows as you make a new home for your success-driven Sim. Buy and sell furniture and objects. And now you can also build workplaces like a Bistro, a Preschool, or a Night Club for your musical Sim to rock. BABIES! WHAT YOU’VE BEEN WISHING FOR! Your most requested feature is here! For the first time on iPhone &amp; iPod touch, your Sims can have babies! Feed them, play with them, and put them to bed! Watch Sims babies become Sims toddlers. Take them to the park, play hide-and-seek, or give them a little cuddle. Having Sims children changes everything! IMPORT &amp; EXPORT BETWEEN OTHER SIMS GAMES FOR iPHONE &amp; iPOD TOUCH Bring in your favorite Sims from The Sims™ 3 and The Sims™ 3 World Adventures for iPhone &amp; iPod touch. Give them the chance to pursue their dreams, too! A COMPLETE EXPERIENCE! THE BIGGEST, BOLDEST YET With all-new features, plus more of the Sims gameplay you know and love, this really is the fullest experience of The Sims ever made for iPhone &amp; iPod touch! _______________________________________ ** DON'T MISS OUR OTHER EXCITING GAMES! ** SCRABBLE, The Sims™ 3, TETRIS®, MONOPOLY, Madden NFL 11 by EA Sports™, Pogo Games FREE, Liqua Pop, ROCK BAND® Reloaded, Need for Speed™ Hot Pursuit &amp; Surviving High School FREE GIFT THIS APP: Click the “Buy App” arrow on the iTunes® App Store Be the first to know! Get inside EA info on great deals, plus the latest game updates, tips &amp; more… VISIT US: ea.com/iphone FOLLOW US: twitter.com/eamobile LIKE US: facebook.com/eamobile WATCH US: youtube.com/eamobilegames Terms of Service : http://www.ea.com/terms-of-service Privacy and Cookie Policy: http://www.ea.com/privacy-policy Game EULA: http://tos.ea.com/legalapp/mobileeula/US/en/GM/ Visit https://help.ea.com/ for assistance or inquiries. EA may retire online features and services after 30 days’ notice posted on www.ea.com/1/service-updates. Important Consumer Information. This app: Contains direct links to the Internet; Collects data through third party analytics technology (see Privacy &amp; Cookie Policy for details).</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7438_03_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/12/93/a7/1293a703-0dc0-d840-b58b-404aabcb446f/mzl.xnylbegh.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7438-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7438_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:38:51">http://www.games.com/game/electronic-arts/the-sims-medieval</link><title>The Sims™ Medieval</title><description>GET MEDIEVAL WITH THE SIMS™! Your favorite lighthearted Sims universe is going old-school – back to the times of castles, kings, jesters and knights! DELVE INTO A MAGIC STORY-DRIVEN WORLD Create your hero and determine your Sim’s destiny in this new fantasy. From serf and squire to Lady and Lord, role-play even as a Vampire! Immerse yourself in a dramatic adventure where the possibilities are endless. QUEST YOUR WAY TO DESTINY Complete quests to propel your Sims onward. Master skills and make wizardly potions like a death potion – or a love potion. Join parties across a richly detailed medieval realm, or test your skills with features like combat and fishing. LONG LIVE THE SIMS MEDIEVAL™ ON iPHONE &amp; iPOD TOUCH View all the feuding, feasting and frivolity with the visual glory of the Retina Display. _______________________________________ ** DON'T MISS OUR OTHER EXCITING GAMES! ** SCRABBLE, The Sims™ 3, TETRIS®, MONOPOLY, Madden NFL 12 by EA Sports™, Pogo Games FREE, Liqua Pop, Ghost Harvest, ROCK BAND® Reloaded, Need for Speed™ Hot Pursuit &amp; Surviving High School FREE GIFT THIS APP: Click the “Buy App” arrow on the iTunes® App Store Be the first to know! Get inside EA info on great deals, plus the latest game updates, tips &amp; more… VISIT US: ea.com/iphone FOLLOW US: twitter.com/eamobile LIKE US: facebook.com/eamobile WATCH US: youtube.com/eamobilegames Terms of Service : http://www.ea.com/terms-of-service Privacy and Cookie Policy: http://www.ea.com/privacy-policy Game EULA: http://tos.ea.com/legalapp/mobileeula/US/en/GM/ Visit https://help.ea.com/ for assistance or inquiries. EA may retire online features and services after 30 days’ notice posted on www.ea.com/1/service-updates. Important Consumer Information. This app: Contains direct links to the Internet; Collects data through third party analytics technology (see Privacy &amp; Cookie Policy for details); Contains direct links to social networking sites intended for an audience over 13.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7438_04_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/98/fd/bd/mzm.abmmjxqe.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7438-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7438_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:40:23">http://www.games.com/game/rovio-entertainment/angry-birds-space-hd</link><title>Angry Birds Space HD</title><description>#1 in 116 countries! Big thanks to all our fans! “Intergalactic phenomenon worth every penny” – AppCraver “Takes the fundamental physics-based flinging of the original and turns it on its head... It's satisfying, yet completely familiar, and is heaps of pig-smashing fun.” – Gamespot “Anyone burnt out on vanilla bird flinging will enjoy the game's out-of-this-world adventure.” -- IGN ALL NEW ANGRY BIRDS GAME FROM ROVIO -- the #1 mobile game of all time blasts off into space! After a giant claw kidnaps their eggs, the Angry Birds chase it into a wormhole and find themselves floating in a strange new galaxy – surrounded by space pigs! Luckily the Angry Birds have super powers of their own... Angry Birds Space features over 230 interstellar levels on planets and in zero gravity, resulting in spectacular gameplay ranging from slow-motion puzzles to lightspeed destruction. With new in-app purchases, brand new birds, brand new superpowers, and a whole galaxy to explore, the sky is no longer the limit! FEATURES • Over 230 interstellar levels! • Brand new birds! • Brand new superpowers! • Zero-gravity space adventures! • Trick shots using planets’ gravity! • New in-app purchases! • Hidden bonus levels! • Beautifully detailed backgrounds! DANGER ZONE • In-app-purchase for the ultimate Angry Birds fan! • 30 of the most difficult levels EVER! • Can you master the DANGER ZONE? SPACE EAGLES • Open a wormhole of destruction with Space Eagles! • Aim carefully to wreak havoc on the pigs! • Earn through gameplay or buy in-app • New goals and achievements! Join the global phenomenon as it goes galactic! Become a fan of Angry Birds on Facebook: http://facebook.angrybirds.com Follow us on Twitter: http://twitter.angrybirds.com Terms of Use: http://www.rovio.com/eula Privacy Policy: http://www.rovio.com/privacy This application may require internet connectivity and subsequent data transfer charges may apply. Important Message for Parents This game may include: \- Direct links to social networking websites that are intended for an audience over the age of 13. \- Direct links to the internet that can take players away from the game with the potential to browse any web page. \- Advertising of Rovio products and also products from select partners. \- The option to make in-app purchases. The bill payer should always be consulted beforehand.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7438_05_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple4/v4/29/1a/5e/291a5e27-5948-1263-0b4a-79d3d746c5a0/mzl.bgoqudcg.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7438-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7438_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:42:10">http://www.games.com/game/games2win/fab-tattoo-artist</link><title>Fab Tattoo Artist</title><description>Welcome to the ultimate tattoo studio! Here you can make your own never-seen-before masterpieces with our awesome freestyle mode! What’s more, we have also included a special mode where you can paint the faces of the cutest babies from around the world. Of course, there are 15 demanding customers who want to get inked with unique tattoo designs that suit their personalities! From college cheerleaders to party animals – they refuse to get anything but the coolest designs! Draw out these wicked tattoo designs from scratch and get inking with your tattoo gun as you experience the step-by-step process of making a tattoo. What’s more, you can even save your creation and share it with your friends on Facebook! So what are you waiting for? Unleash you inner tattoo artist with Fab Tattoo Artist. Fab Tattoo Artist Features: • 15 Demanding Customers • 30+ Unique Tattoos • 20+ Colors • Exclusive Freestyle Mode • Awesome New Face Paint Mode • Simple Gameplay You can also play Fab Tattoo Artist on your Mac or PC! Try the free web version on our website: http://www.games2win.com/en/arcade-games/fab-tattoo-artist-game.asp VISIT US: http://games2win.com LIKE US: http://facebook.com/Games2win FOLLOW US: http://twitter.com/Games2win Contact us at mobile@games2win.com for any problems you may have with Fab Tattoo Artist. Privacy Policy: http://www.games2win.com/corporate/privacy_policy.asp</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7438_06_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple4/v4/08/2f/cf/082fcfa4-9387-2a34-f215-f67d18f61dee/mzl.dhlohfep.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7438-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7438_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:44:53">http://www.games.com/game/rovio-entertainment/angry-birds-seasons</link><title>Angry Birds Seasons</title><description>Angry Birds Seasons takes the captivating gameplay of the original to a whole new level! From Halloween to Chinese New Year, the birds are celebrating different festive seasons around the world! With more than 300 levels and regular free updates, these special episodes offer more challenging levels of pig-popping action and golden eggs to discover. "All the fun of Angry Birds, but more challenging, and with pumpkins and presents." – Slide to Play "More of the great Angry Birds gameplay you’ve come to know. Well designed and incredibly challenging levels." -- Gamezebo "A hauntingly good extension of the original, Angry Birds Halloween delivers more of the same entertaining physics puzzle play." -- Pocket Gamer "So, if you’re an avid bird-slinger, this purchase just makes too much sense to put off. It’s the best, most season-appropriate way to stay on top of all the action, and the price is oh-so-low." -- App Chronicles With more than 1 billion downloads, Angry Birds is the most popular mobile game of all time. Join the global phenomenon! Become a fan of Angry Birds on Facebook: http://facebook.angrybirds.com Follow us on Twitter: http://twitter.angrybirds.com Terms of Use: http://www.rovio.com/eula Privacy Policy: http://www.rovio.com/privacy This application may require internet connectivity and subsequent data transfer charges may apply. Important Message for Parents This game may include: \- Direct links to social networking websites that are intended for an audience over the age of 13. \- Direct links to the internet that can take players away from the game with the potential to browse any web page. \- Advertising of Rovio products and also products from select partners. \- The option to make in-app purchases. The bill payer should always be consulted beforehand.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7438_07_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/c0/98/41/c098410f-5e34-f559-6805-c4d7c5da8050/mzl.chhbixmv.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7438-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7438_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:48:12">http://www.games.com/game/halfbrick-studios/fruit-ninja</link><title>Fruit Ninja</title><description>For the hundreds of millions of fans around the world with trillions of fruit sliced - thank you for your amazing continued support! You have made Fruit Ninja one of the most popular games of all-time! Fruit Ninja is a juicy action game with squishy, splatty and satisfying fruit slicing carnage! Become the ultimate bringer of sweet, tasty destruction with every slash. **** "It's simple, fun and best of all challenging." - Touch Arcade Review "Fruit Ninja is fun, fun, fun. It’s an instant pleasure." IGN Review "The low price makes the game more than worth it." - TUAW Review "Fruit Ninja is the sort of game that has come to typify the rising dominance of quick, simple and most of all additively fun gameplay." - AppSpy Review "You'll know it's fun, and you'll know you want to keep playing." - Slide to Play Review "Fruit Ninja epitomizes all things a great iPhone game needs." - Resumeplay Review "The game oozes style and polish." - AppAdvice Review "My God this game is great. Best iPhone game in a while." - User Review "Just spent 15 minutes on the crapper in my office complex playing this little gem of a game. Productivity -1" - Touch Arcade Comment **** Swipe your finger across the screen to deliciously slash and splatter fruit like a true ninja warrior. Be careful of bombs – they are explosive to touch and will put a swift end to your juicy adventure! Fruit Ninja features Classic, Zen and the amazing Arcade mode. We’ve even added an all-new challenge system to keep you on your toes! Sharpen your skills, climb your way to the top of our global Game Center leaderboards and unlock epic achievements on your path to glory. Your success will also please the wise ninja Sensei, who will accompany your journey with words of wisdom and fun fruit facts. Fruit Ninja is the messiest and most satisfying fruit game ever! To view Halfbrick's privacy policy please go to: www.halfbrick.com/pp **** IMPORTANT NOTICE TO PARENTS This game may contain: \- The ability to purchase optional content using real money. You can disable in-app purchases in the settings menu of your device. \- Promotional material for Halfbrick products and trusted business partners. \- Links to external social networking sites intended for users over the age of 13. \- Direct links to the internet which may open the default web browser on your device. Privacy Policy: http://www.halfbrick.com/pp Terms of Service: http://www.halfbrick.com/tos LIKE FRUIT NINJA ON FACEBOOK! http://www.facebook.com/fruitninja FOLLOW HALFBRICK ON TWITTER! http://www.twitter.com/halfbrick</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7438_08_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/db/05/ec/db05ec9c-5389-c49e-18c3-a570c54c3173/mzl.aphoftta.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7438-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7438_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:49:35">http://www.games.com/game/supercell/hay-day</link><title>Hay Day</title><description>Hay Day is a totally new farming experience with smooth gestural controls lovingly handcrafted for your iPad or iPhone. PLEASE NOTE! Hay Day is completely free to play, however some game items can also be purchased for real money. If you don't want to use this optional feature, please disable in-app purchases in your device's settings. Also, under our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy, you must be at least 13 years of age to play or download Hay Day. Get back to nature and experience the peaceful, simple life of working the land and rearing chickens, pigs, cows and sheep. Make a name for yourself by harvesting crops and building bakeries, sugar mills and dairies that turn your fresh produce into wholesome goods you can trade with your friends at your very own Farmer's Market. REVIEWS 5/5 "This game is so awesome and unique! Coolest game I had ever played. Thank you Hay Day!!!!! :)" 5/5 “Both calming and addictive. My husband and I both love this game.” 5/5 "Really fun game to play with the family" 5/5 "Such a fun and addicting game! The animals and all they do is super cute - never a dull moment!!! Love it" 5/5 “I love this game, great players!! Always something to do and always something new!!!” FEATURES • FREE TO PLAY! • Produce delicious food using natural ingredients from your very own farm • Buy and sell your healthy, farm-fresh produce at the Farmer’s Market • Play and trade with your friends on Game Center and Facebook • Easy, fun touch gestures that mimic real farming activities • Raise and care for funny farm animals with quirky personalities! • Catch dozens of fish between harvests with just the swipe of a finger • Your farm is fully customizable -- make it your very own • Beautiful animations and sounds. Your farm really feels alive! • Retina optimized for the new iPad Having problems? Any suggestions? We would love to hear from you! You can reach us at hayday.feedback@supercell.net or find us on Facebook at http://facebook.com/haydayofficial</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7438_09_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/cc/37/7a/cc377ab5-35d3-3de4-cc42-6e1f072b602e/mzl.orizxxxo.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7438-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7438_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:50:35">http://www.games.com/game/rovio-entertainment/angry-birds-space</link><title>Angry Birds Space</title><description>#1 in 116 countries! Big thanks to all our fans! “Intergalactic phenomenon worth every penny” – AppCraver “Takes the fundamental physics-based flinging of the original and turns it on its head... It's satisfying, yet completely familiar, and is heaps of pig-smashing fun.” – Gamespot “Anyone burnt out on vanilla bird flinging will enjoy the game's out-of-this-world adventure.” -- IGN ALL NEW ANGRY BIRDS GAME FROM ROVIO -- the #1 mobile game of all time blasts off into space! After a giant claw kidnaps their eggs, the Angry Birds chase it into a wormhole and find themselves floating in a strange new galaxy – surrounded by space pigs! Luckily the Angry Birds have super powers of their own... Angry Birds Space features over 230 interstellar levels on planets and in zero gravity, resulting in spectacular gameplay ranging from slow-motion puzzles to lightspeed destruction. With new in-app purchases, brand new birds, brand new superpowers, and a whole galaxy to explore, the sky is no longer the limit! FEATURES • Over 230 interstellar levels! • Brand new birds! • Brand new superpowers! • Zero-gravity space adventures! • Trick shots using planets’ gravity! • New in-app purchases! • Hidden bonus levels! • Beautifully detailed backgrounds! DANGER ZONE • In-app-purchase for the ultimate Angry Birds fan! • 30 of the most difficult levels EVER! • Can you master the DANGER ZONE? SPACE EAGLES • Open a wormhole of destruction with Space Eagles! • Aim carefully to wreak havoc on the pigs! • Earn through gameplay or buy in-app • New goals and achievements! Join the global phenomenon as it goes galactic! Become a fan of Angry Birds on Facebook: http://facebook.angrybirds.com Follow us on Twitter: http://twitter.angrybirds.com Terms of Use: http://www.rovio.com/eula Privacy Policy: http://www.rovio.com/privacy This application may require internet connectivity and subsequent data transfer charges may apply. Important Message for Parents This game may include: \- Direct links to social networking websites that are intended for an audience over the age of 13. \- Direct links to the internet that can take players away from the game with the potential to browse any web page. \- Advertising of Rovio products and also products from select partners. \- The option to make in-app purchases. The bill payer should always be consulted beforehand.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7438_10_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/ee/a5/4e/eea54e7b-43f4-8056-b8ab-9cb91160c85c/mzl.xrnzhymx.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>