<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7439">make crown</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:53:53" name="Games.com" id="FW14-e048"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e048-7439-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7439_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:53:53">http://www.games.com/game/bradido/squiggle-squid</link><title>Squiggle Squid</title><description>Squiggle Squid is a mouse-controlled action puzzle game where you control the son of the Kraken as he seeks the legendary Coral Crown. Use Squiggle Squid's ink dash to collect plankton and avoid ocean obstacles such as spiny sea urchins but it won't be easy. As the level goals increase, you must master the ink dash to make huge chains, collect power-ups and avoid dangerous sea life. There are 50 levels in quest mode and a high score mode.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7439_01_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/cdn.mochiads.com/c/g/squiggle-squid_v2/_thumb_100x100.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7439-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7439_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:55:47">http://www.games.com/game/hipsoft/build-a-lot-fairy-tales</link><title>Build-a-lot: Fairy Tales</title><description>Protect the town from fire-breathing dragons!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7439_02_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/cdn-games.bigfishgames.com/en_buildalot-fairy-tales/buildalot-fairy-tales_feature.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7439-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7439_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:56:41">http://www.games.com/game/gamevil-usa/baseball-superstars-ii</link><title>Baseball Superstars® II</title><description>THE BEST VERSION OF THE HIT BASEBALL SUPERSTARS SERIES YET! Baseball Superstars II is a full featured baseball game with 7 different modes to satisfy everyone's needs. ───────────────────── NEW FEATURES IMPROVED MY LEAGUE &amp; SEASON MODE Diverse scenarios with vastly improved storyline and engage in various events at the same time. USER-CREATED SUPER SKILLS Customizable super skills include unlimited number of pitching styles and dozens of batting effects. ENHANCED CONTROL &amp; GRAPHICS SIMULATION Simplified user interface and enhanced player's point-of-view system. ADVANCED BASEBALL EXPERIENCE Six new super players, various weather types, and improved AI makes the game even more challenging. ───────────────────── IMPROVED FEATURES OVER 12M COPIES SOLD WORLDWIDE Since 2002, the Baseball Superstars series has been loved by worldwide gamers. FULL FEATURED BASEBALL GAME 7 different modes include Exhibition, My League, Season, Homerun Race, Tournament, Mission and Match Mode to guarantee endless play time. TOTAL MANAGEMENT Engage in various events, win tournaments, and achieve success by purchasing the right equipment and performing the necessary training. ADDITIONAL CUSTOMIZATION Customize game settings to select specific scenarios or players that you wish to play with, and now decorate the stadium to earn more money for your ball club. BECOME CROWNED AS CHAMPIONS Form the best line up by acquiring hall of famers, trading players, and hiring super players, and dominate other users in Match Play mode. ───────────────────── OTHER GAMEVIL GAMES Baseball Superstars® 2012 ZENONIA® 4 AREL WARS™ Toy Shot™ ADVENA LAST WAR™ DESTINIA Air Penguin Colosseum Heroes ILLUSIA KAMI RETRO Chalk n' Talk HYBRID 2: Saga of Nostalgia HYBRID: Eternal Whisper Soccer Superstars® 2011 NOM 5 VANQUISH: The Oath of Brothers ───────────────────── NEWS &amp; EVENTS Website http://www.gamevil.com Facebook http://facebook.com/gamevil Twitter http://twitter.com/gamevil YouTube http://youtube.com/gamevil</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7439_03_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/10/ab/5d/mzm.aocegbnw.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7439-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7439_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:00:14">http://www.games.com/game/300-ad/be-a-king</link><title>Be a King</title><description>Be a King and create your empire!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7439_04_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/cdn-games.bigfishgames.com/en_be-a-king/be-a-king_feature.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7439-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7439_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:02:32">http://www.games.com/game/kairosoft-co-ltd/dungeon-village</link><title>Dungeon Village</title><description>Welcome to an epic RPG world in which the town you build can grow from humble hamlet into a mecca for the land's most ambitious adventurers! The enterprising warriors that stop by your blossoming burg will defeat monsters and earn you money. Conquering dungeons and clearing out hordes of monsters will bag you loot to stock your shops. And if your hamlet flourishes, adventurers will want to set up house and settle down! Build training facilities like Combat Schools and Magic Labs to hone your heroic denizens' skills and boost your village's Popularity. The more faces that flock to your cause, the bigger the baddies you can beat! An all-new "Cauldron" feature also allows you to test your alchemic expertise. Toss items obtained from quests or shops into the Cauldron and your armory might receive a rare addition. No dungeon is too deep! Make your village the crown estate of this bold RPG narrative! \---- The game now lets you switch between English and Japanese.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7439_05_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/d2/73/1c/d2731cf7-a472-9b74-af56-fc2bde217ad7/mzl.kwnwoyti.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7439-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7439_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:03:32">http://www.games.com/game/appsnminded/fairytale-princess</link><title>Fairytale Princess!</title><description>She is a beautiful princess looking for her prince! To find her prince and gain entry to the castle, she must first kiss a few frogs - yuck! Yes, but you never know which frog will turn into a prince. Once inside the castle, choose from endless dress, shoe, crown, accessory and hairstyle choices. Now the princess is ready to meet her prince! Will he make her his queen? Find out - It's lot's of royal fun! Features: \--Fun Kiss-The-Prince game \--Endless dress and shoe choices \--Oodles of accessories and hairstyles to choose from \--Fairytale backgrounds galore \--Magic un-color to reveal your favorite princess look! \--A royal closet to save all of your princess looks \--A dashing prince Like our apps? Find us on facebook for free apps and contests: http://www.facebook.com/appsnminded</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7439_06_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/be/4b/77/be4b7788-bf28-aff9-ee71-270c110332f3/mzm.wwmmyaeb.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7439-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7439_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:05:13">http://www.games.com/game/app-street-software-private-limited/roulette-mobile</link><title>Roulette Mobile</title><description>Bring Vegas and Monaco to your iPhone and iPad with Roulette Mobile, a complete Roulette app. Impeccably designed and intuitive, this one is sure to make you go "wow". Play solo, using Bluetooth or with others around the world. Compete with your friends for various interesting titles and achievements. Play, compete, show off and make friends! A complete Roulette ****************************** Play as many as 20 different types of bets. Master the inside and outside bets and then, graduate to call and full bets. We got everything covered! Fun for free ****************************** Get thousands of free chips by simply sharing on Facebook and Twitter. Play and feel like a high roller without dropping a penny! Play your way ****************************** You can play solo or with a friend over Bluetooth or with the whole world through the game centre. There is always a table waiting for you! Five different tables ****************************** Choose the table you want to play on and compete with like-minded people. Start with the learning table and move up to become a Billionaire! Join the league ****************************** Spin your way into the leader boards and pick up hilarious achievements on your way. Crowning glory ****************************** As you play and gain expertise in the game, conquer various crowns and show them off to the world. Flaunt what you got ****************************** With a single tap, share your scores and titles with the world through Facebook and Twitter.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7439_07_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple4/v4/ec/19/09/ec1909a6-abda-675e-7ed3-f2252ac1dda7/mzl.zudwbjrl.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7439-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7439_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:06:38">http://www.games.com/game/ae-mobile/ae-coin-mania</link><title>AE Coin Mania</title><description>AE Coin Mania coming! Win Gold Coins and Prizes! You won’t be able to stop yourself! *This game requires an iPhone4 or newer or an iPad2 or newer device to run. Thanks. Any feedback please emails us, because we can’t reply on comments. Thanks very much for all your support in our games! Try to push off as many as shiny coins and exciting prizes as you can, make sure to push them towards you because if they fall off the left or right side they are gone and don’t count. Numerous prizes will appear in the game, crowns, diamonds, chests... each type of them have different bonus, and you should at least gather one tier for each type of prizes to unlock the bonus. Also, you can sell the prizes for coins. It’s ok if your coins run out; more will be filling up your pockets very soon. When you are online, the system will add on a gold coin every 30 seconds, even if you are offline the system will also add on a gold coin every 9 minutes. Beyond of that, you can use Slot to win coins. Also, if your gold coins quantity is low, visit the Coin Shop to Top-Up for more gold coins. If you like Coin Push-LasVegas, Slot Machine, Solitaire, Spider, Roulette, Baccarat, UNO, Texas Poker, Card Ace: Casino, Blackjack, dice and other card and casino games, you should not miss this game! Game includes: -Impressive 3D graphics -Amazingly realistic physics -Lots of Daily Mission -Over 20 Special Coins and Prizes! -Lots of special effects More updates coming soon!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7439_08_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/49/4d/ff/494dff26-be43-ea58-e875-2d1c65b08c94/mzl.sarczfyl.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7439-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7439_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:08:21">http://www.games.com/game/usm/wars-of-the-roses-rosenk-nig</link><title>Wars of the Roses - Rosenkönig</title><description>The Wars of the Roses for the crown of England have started again: The strategy game classic is available for iPhone and iPad! England, in the 15th century: The house of York, bearing the white rose in their coat of arms, and the house of Lancaster with the red rose struggle for the kingship. Only the best strategists will emerge victorious from the Wars of the Roses… Play your might cards deliberately to gain control over large, connected areas. The cunning use of your heroes will foil your opponent’s plans and bring the crown within your reach! Wars of the Roses’ rules are simple; a comprehensive guide will get both beginners and board game veterans into the game quickly. The game is exciting at any time, because even the last moves of the game can make the difference between victory and defeat. Wars of the Roses can be played against computer-controlled opponents, or with friends via hot seat multiplayer, or via Bluetooth or on the internet via Game Center. Compete with other players through online leaderboards and achievements via Game Center, or replay historic battles in the challenging campaign mode for one player! Features: • The classic strategy game with high resolution graphics in an atmospheric presentation • Universal app for both iPhone and iPad • Challenging AI opponents in 3 difficulty settings; campaign with a variety of scenarios • Various multiplayer modes: hot seat, Bluetooth, or online via Game Center • Comprehensive introduction to the rules • Leaderboards and achievements accessible via Game Center (Online multiplayer, leaderboards and achievements require to access the Apple Game Center and therefore will not be available on older devices. If you would like to use these features, please make sure your device and iOS version support Game Center. However, the game is also playable without them, of course.) ***** Questions or suggestions for improvements: Mail to ios@usm.de We are looking forward to your feedback! Please do not ask your questions in the reviews as we do not have the possibility to respond to you there. For more information on news and updates: www.usmgames.com or visit us on www.facebook.com/UnitedSoftMedia and twitter.com/USM_News *****</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7439_09_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/72/99/12/729912cc-9d00-cc6a-6bdf-f09d3414eec3/mzl.xgmrpdba.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7439-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7439_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:10:11">http://www.games.com/game/konsole-kingz/kandi-koated-spades</link><title>Kandi Koated Spades</title><description>FREE Download! Kandi Koated Spades is now FREE for a limited time only. \---------------------------------------------------------| Play Spades with your friends! 5 star rated! Play with your rules - Reneg, Jokers, Deuces. Profile Photos and more! \---------------------------------------------------------| Version 1.3 A number of new features. \- Added Private Rooms - invite your friends to play in your room \- Game Invites - Invite someone online to play with you \- Custom Rules - set point totals, game timer, and set Spades or Diamonds high on Deuces \- Fixed Reneg bug \- Fixed bidding bug at start of game Version 1.2.1 \- Fixed scoring bug \- Fixed bidding bug Version 1.2 \- Fixed iOS5 crash \- Fixed multiplayer connecting problem \- Added in-game and lobby chats \- Added Twitter messaging (from Menu button, end of hands and at end of games) \- Sped up single player mode \- Compatible with iPad \---------------------------------------------------------| What's up. It's your girl, Kandi, and this is my new spades game - Kandi Koated Spades. It's the best spades game available, and I'm not just saying that because it's my game. I'm a spades pro. I've played every spades game in the app store. Are you wondering what makes Kandi Koated Spades special? Take a look at the features below and you will see why this is the last spades game you will ever need on your iPhone, iPad or iPod Touch. Don't forget to tell your friends, family, classmates and co-workers that Kandi Koated Spades is the truth! \---------------------------------------------------------| Kandi Koated Spades Key Features \- Online Multiplayer (play against 3 real people) \- Custom avatars (use the camera to put yourself in the game) \- In-game profiles (let everyone know where you're from, post your Twitter and Facebook, and earn awards (crowns) for playing) \- Practice mode (for those of you that need to step your game up) \- Reneg (Call reneg on someone playing out of suit and get those 3 books!) \- Tweet your scores and wins to all your Twitter followers \----------------------------------------------------------| Kandi Koated Spades House Rules \- 250 point game \- Card Ranking Joker (HI) Joker (LO) Deuce of Diamonds Deuce of Spades Spades Suit \- Spades can lead (play a spade whenever you feel like it, but don't reneg) For the complete list of rules and features visit www.KandiKoatedSpades.com. Make sure to follow on twitter @KandiSpades, join in the twitter conversation hashtag #spades, and "Like Us" on Facebook (www.facebook.com/kandikoatedspades) \------------------------------------------------------------| Coming soon to Kandi Koated Spades \- Facebook \- Custom Decks \- Friends List \- More Rule Customization \----------------------------------------------------------| About Kandi Kandi Burruss is a Grammy winner and history-making songwriter. She is the newest addition to Bravo’s rating sensation "Real Housewives of Atlanta". At the age of 17, she was apart of Jermaine Dupri's platinum-selling R&amp;B quartet, Xscape. Since then, Kandi has become an established songwriter, penning hits for TLC "No Scrubs", Destiny’s Child "Bills, Bills, Bills" and Pink "There You Go". Follow Kandi on Twitter (@kandi) and learn more about her at Kandionline.com</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7439_10_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/d7/2b/5c/d72b5c1e-7af3-41dd-01b3-1ec6d2c17d0e/mza_7975664258316056287.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>