<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7445">marathon training</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:36:03" name="Games.com" id="FW14-e048"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e048-7445-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7445_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:36:04">http://www.games.com/game/braintonik-games/vocabulum</link><title>Vocabulum</title><description>Single-player (Marathon, Classic and Training) Multi-Player (Championship, War of the Word) Skill Test Customize almost everything!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7445_01_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/616t9giCjaL._SL160_.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7445-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7445_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:39:26">http://www.games.com/game/soli-deo-gloria-productions/marathon-infinity</link><title>Marathon Infinity</title><description>Rage hard.. Marathon Infinity is the climactic conclusion to Bungie's groundbreaking Marathon Trilogy. Learn the the truth about the events of Marathon and Marathon: Durandal first hand in "Blood Tides of Lh’owon", the single player portion of Infinity. FEATURES \- 25 levels divided into four chapters \- 5 hidden levels \- missions include exploration, puzzles and extermination \- "Carnage is as easy as point and shoot." ~Marathon Manual \- introducing a new weapon: KKV-7 10mm SMG Flechette submachine gun ===== to.be.a.vidmaster ==== What does it mean to be a Vidmaster? It is being balanced in the calm center of a whirling and untouchable tornado of destruction, while showers of grenades patter harmlessly around you and bullets crawl toward you in slow-mo. It is when your brain develops a new bundle of nerves whose only function is to re-route impulses directly from your eyes to your finger muscles, so that you can twist and snap off a rocket long before you’re conscious of the yellow blip in your motion detector. It is when the difference between a roomful of alien warriors and a carpet of them is a matter of seconds. The word "vid" entered the Marathon lexicon during development of the first game, to distinguish the excellent players (particularly in net games) from the fodder. The Oath of the Vidmaster was inscribed into the skip-levels dialog (Command-Option-Begin New Game), to remind players of the highest level of excellence they could aspire to: "I pledge to punch all switches, to never shoot where I could use grenades, to admit the existence of no level except Total Carnage, to never use Caps Lock as my 'run' key, and to never, ever, leave a single Bob alive." To do these things is to invite maximum peril, and requires one to play the game as hard and unrelentingly as possible, at the highest level of skill; to play as a Vidmaster. These three games, the Marathon saga, are the best training and testing ground for Vidmasters. You can play against aliens alone or in a networked group through more than 80 levels. But the true challenge is surviving in one of the 50 included netgame arenas against other people. It is in such trials by fire that mighty Vidmasters are forged. Rage hard.. ===== ~Marathon Infinity Manual Visit us at http://www.marathon4ios.com Follow us on twitter http://www.twitter.com/blezek Source code for this app is licensed under the GNU General Public License v2 (http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.html) and is available upon request (see http://www.marathon4ios.com for details).</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7445_02_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple2/v4/6a/b2/b5/6ab2b5d0-e45c-3225-373f-913c2bfb3989/mzl.ralrckgf.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7445-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7445_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:42:53">http://www.games.com/game/douzedix/wordbreaker-lite-lingo-trainer</link><title>WordBreaker Lite - Lingo Trainer</title><description>WordBreaker is the Mastermind of words! How fast can you find the secret word? With every try, WordBreaker tells you which letters are correct or misplaced. Think that's easy ? Think again... Keep in mind that only well formed english words of the right length will give you the feedback you need! Any mistake and you lose that try... Currently, Word Breaker dictionary contains more than 220,000 entries ranging from 5 to 12 letters and 4 increasing difficulty levels. Upgrade to the full featured Word Breaker app through a single in-app purchase ! WordBreaker is also available on the AppStore in Spanish, Dutch, German and French for iPhone and iPad. ✦✦ NEW IN VERSION 2.0 ✦✦ ✓ Better VoiceOver support ✓ Game Center (iOS 4.2) ✓ Performance enhancements ✦✦ ALL EXTRA FEATURES ✦✦ ✓ Ad free ✓ Play with your friends over Wifi, Bluetooth or GameCenter Customize your favorite gameplay : ✓ Choose your word length, ranging from 5 to 12 letters. ✓ Choose the average level of difficulty for secret words: "Easy", "Medium", "Hard" or "Expert". ✓ Choose the number of attempts available to find the secret word. ✓ The higher the speed, the less time you get for each try. Choose your favorite game mode : ✓ Training : Just practice, and score ! ✓ Marathon : Find as many words as you can, with an increasing difficulty, and reach the best score in one go without failing. ✓ Time trial : Find a predefined number of words in a limited amount of time. And much more : ✓ Include/exclude specific British English words. ✓ Choose one of the available skins or switch on/off sound effects. ✓ Landscape mode ✓ 5 to 12 letter-words (or choose random) ✓ 9 graphic themes with customizable background ✓ two wildcard letters for hard and harder difficulty levels ✓ Challenge your friends with your best scores (also works with Word Breaker HD for iPad) ! ✓ Multi-user (each family member can have its own profile and scores) ✓ Improved input mode (disable the option to go back to the original mode) ✓ Bonus points for speed Need a little help? Just shake your iPhone or iPod to trigger the "wildcard letter". Be aware however that this trick works only once per word and reduces your score... ✦✦ Discover Word Breaker HD (universal app for iPad+iPhone), also available on the AppStore ✦✦</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7445_03_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/7b/78/f9/7b78f9b2-1d3f-dbb2-6224-d6d803fb489b/mzm.sdsnufnn.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7445-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7445_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:46:05">http://www.games.com/game/thinkcube/block-buster-free</link><title>Block Buster Free</title><description>You will love Block Buster! The new simple yet UNBELIEVABLY ADDICTIVE puzzle game. Click on 3 or more connected blocks of the same color to bust them. Clear all blocks to solve a puzzle! Sounds simple? Give it a try and let the game speak for itself! ~~~~~What Players has been Saying~~~~ ★★★★★ by Osundood - I'm basically out of control. Can't stop busting. This app is rocking my face off! ★★★★★ by KGspecial - Never grow tired of playing. Quite addictive!! And tons of fun! ★★★★★ by SusieCatLady - Amazingly addictive! It seems slow at first, but watch out! It gets harder as it goes along. By then, you'll be hooked! ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ Play for free through hundreds of puzzles, test your reaction and agility in Time Rush Mode, or train your analytic and endurance skills in Marathon Mode. Puzzles range from relaxed to head-scratching, it is for you to decide your playing style. Try Block Buster for free, and let your brain tingling begin! ~~~~~~ BLock Buster Features ~~~~~~~ \- 500 free puzzles from simple to challenging. \- 8 board sizes each with up to 8 block color. \- Made a wrong move? Don't Worry! Roll back moves with "UNDO"! \- Stuck? No Problem! In-game solution will guide you step by step! \- TimeRush Mode : Solve as many puzzles as you can before time runs out! \- Marathon Mode : Solve puzzles without fail. Keep in mind, there is no "UNDO" for Marathon! \- Want more? over 2000 puzzles available for purchase! ~~~~~~~~~ Note Worthy ~~~~~~~~~~ \- Track progress of every puzzle (incl. best-time, moves). \- Puzzle difficulty increases gradually for TimeRush and Marathon. \- Compete with Friends! GameCenter achievements and leader-board updates as you play. \- Colourful UI, Smooth interactions, &amp; Crispy graphics and animations \- Block Symbols available for color impaired players \- We say NO to pop-up ads! ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ We hope you will enjoy Block Buster! Your acknowledgement is our biggest motivation! Think Cube Games Version - 1.2</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7445_04_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple6/v4/64/24/72/6424724f-e8f0-2aaa-473a-58ec3042b6d6/mzl.kvmmusyj.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7445-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7445_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:48:04">http://www.games.com/game/apps-r-us/trump-tight</link><title>Trump Tight</title><description>Are you Trump Tight? Game recognize Game, play your cards right. Trump Tight is the latest and most comprehensive App on the market for card players. Featuring five different card games: Bid Whist, Whist, Minnesota Whist, Dirty Hearts, and Spades. • Play on Playa • FEATURES: • Trump Tight features some very unique graphics and animations, including: shuffling, cutting, and dealing your cards. • Have you ever ran a Boston? Not the marathon...Trump Tight recognizes your Boston's, other wins, and losses in some very interesting ways. If you've got game, take the train or hop the next flight to Boston. If you win, You're The Bomb (literally). And let's just say losing will get you laughed at. • Three Levels of expertise to choose from: Rookie, Skilled, or Expert. • Five different rooms themes to choose from as the backdrop for game play such as: the Kitchen, Garage, Game Room, Blue Lights in the Basement, or Vegas. • Create your profile with an avatar or upload your own photo. • Detailed game instructions as well as a show hints feature to get players acclimated to unfamiliar games. • Challenging and fun Artificial Intelligence making game play exciting for seasoned card players or those new to a particular game. • Five levels of achievement with scoring breakdowns and detailed statistics for each game. • Unique features such as Sporting the Kitty. _____________________________________________________________ Who's Mr. Boston? They call me Mr. Boston because you guessed it, I run Boston's. That's just what I do. Up late nights playing cards, talking trash, and slamming cards is indicative of my typical Friday night. I'm not just some character in a game, I'm the ultimate card player. I take pleasure in setting my opponents and amassing numerous wins. Trump Tight is your peek into my world. My private plane and tight train are just a few of the amenities I enjoy for keeping my game tight...Trump Tight. And if you don't know, you better ask somebody. Trump Tight will have you reaching for your phone every chance you get. With five of my favorite card games, you can't go wrong. And if you've never played Bid Whist, Whist, Minnesota Whist, Dirty Hearts, or Spades, now is your time to learn. MAYBE one day you'll get on my level and know just what to do, when you get that perfect hand and find yourself "Trump Tight." • Play on Playa •</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7445_05_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/29/8c/67/298c67d8-25d7-1ef1-b775-226abf0fd40b/mzl.grkypwqa.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7445-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7445_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:48:55">http://www.games.com/game/lowell-list/red-revolution-3d</link><title>Red Revolution 3D</title><description>Like Tetris®? Step up to 3D with this dizzying puzzle-stumper where proprioception, intellect, and cheeky Soviet nostalgia meet. FEATURES • Unique, intuitive controls for 3D gameplay Three amazing game modes: • MARATHON – train and develop your cerebral abilities! • HAVOC – the ultimate challenge against the forces of chaos • PUZZLE – solve the puzzles and rack up the coins! • Bombs and 7 AWESOME unlockable power-ups, including Earthquake, Freeze, Pulse, Rainbow Blocks, etc.! • 7 challenging block types, including moving blocks, morphing blocks, invisible blocks, color cipher blocks, Tank blocks, etc.! • Over 200 Puzzle Levels in 5 Unique Sectors • 9 tracks of Original and Remixed Dubstepping Music! • Beautiful Original Artwork, with over 65 backgrounds! • Engaging Voice Commentary • Full Level Editor! Create and Share Levels with your Friends! • The People's Levels - Play, Rate, and Comment on Levels created by other players! • Smooth 60 FPS 3D graphics! • Support for all Retina resolutions (iPhone, iPad) including iPhone 5 NOTE: Game is free to download and preview. Unlock all game modes for $1.99 USD. Game coins may also be purchased in-game but are not necessary for completing the game. www.redrevolution3d.com support@redrevolution3d.com</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7445_06_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple4/v4/e9/37/8e/e9378ec5-4c41-71e0-757f-f27f3ca3e2c9/mzl.netdertr.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7445-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7445_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:52:16">http://www.games.com/game/thinkcube/blockbuster-4-of-a-kind</link><title>BlockBuster 4-of-a-Kind</title><description>Get Ready for a new twist on Classic Block Buster - The simple yet UNBELIEVABLY ADDICTIVE puzzle game. Prepare for even more brain twisting! Now you have to find &amp; click on 4 or more connected blocks of the same color to bust them! Clear all blocks to solve a puzzle. Are you up for the challenge? Let your brain tingling begin! ~~~~~What Players said about Block Buster~~~~ ★★★★★ by Osundood - I'm basically out of control. Can't stop busting. This app is rocking my face off! ★★★★★ by KGspecial - Never grow tired of playing. Quite addictive!! And tons of fun! ★★★★★ by SusieCatLady - Amazingly addictive! It seems slow at first, but watch out! It gets harder as it goes along. By then, you'll be hooked! ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ Play for free through hundreds of puzzles, test your agility in Time Rush Mode, or train your endurance in Marathon Mode. Puzzles range from relaxed to head-scratching, it is for you to decide your playing style. ~~~~~~ Features ~~~~~~~ \- 500 free levels keep your brain spinning for hours. \- Made a wrong move? Don't Worry! Roll back moves with "UNDO"! \- Stuck? No Problem! In-game solution will guide you step by step! \- TimeRush Mode : Solve as many puzzles as you can before time runs out! \- Marathon Mode : Solve puzzles without fail. Keep in mind, there is no "UNDO" for Marathon! \- Want more? 14 Puzzle Chests with over 2500 puzzles in total waiting for you! ~~~~~~~~~ Note Worthy ~~~~~~~~~~ \- Daily Bonus Solution Give-Aways! \- Track progress of every puzzle (incl. best-time, moves). \- Compete with Friends! GameCenter leader-board updates as you play. \- Puzzle difficulty increases gradually for TimeRush and Marathon. \- Colourful UI, Smooth interactions, &amp; Crispy graphics and animations \- Block Symbols available for color impaired players \- Works perfectly for iPhones, iPods, iPads &amp; iPad Minis ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ We hope you will enjoy Block Buster 4-of-a-kind! Your acknowledgement is our biggest motivation! Think Cube Games</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7445_07_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/d1/ec/92/d1ec9251-5385-a262-04e1-acb9889c439b/mzl.prmtwudo.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7445-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7445_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:55:49">http://www.games.com/game/douzedix/wordbreaker-hd-the-lingo-trainer</link><title>WordBreaker HD - The Lingo Trainer!</title><description>WordBreaker is the Mastermind of words! Can you find the secret word in less than 7 chances? With every try, WordBreaker will tell you which letters are correct or misplaced. Think that's easy? Think again... Only well formed english words of the right length are accepted! Any mistake and you lose one chance... Need a little help? Just tap the "Wildcard" button (iPad) or shake your device (iPhone/iPod) to reveal a new letter. But if you think you're the best at Lingo game, then challenge your friend over wifi, bluetooth or GameCenter! WordBreaker is also available in Spanich, Dutch, German, Italian or French (Smotus). If you like WordBreaker HD please rate it ! If you have any problem or question, please tell us how we can help at support@douzedix.com. Thank you. ✦✦ NEW IN VERSION 3 ✦✦ ✓ Optimized graphics for the new iPad "Retina Display" ✓ Play with your friends over Wifi or Bluetooth ✓ Challenge your friends on GameCenter ✓ New "Mineral" skin ✓ New options to switch on/off landscape mode and bonus letters (as requested) ✓ Screen does not enter sleep mode anymore after a few seconds of inactivity (as requested) ✓ Minor bug fixes ✦✦ NEW IN VERSION 2 ✦✦ ✓ Universal application (now works on iPhone/iPod) ✓ Landscape mode and new graphic themes with customizable background ✓ VoiceOver support ✓ One more wildcard letters for hard and harder difficulty levels ✓ Challenge your friends with your best scores (compatible with WordBreaker for iPhone) ! ✓ Multi-user (each family member can have its own profile and scores) ✓ Game Center compatibility ✓ and much more... ✦✦ FEATURES ✦✦ Customize your favorite gameplay : ✓ Choose your word length, ranging from 5 to 12 letters. ✓ Choose the average level of difficulty for secret words: "Easy", "Medium", "Hard" or "Expert". ✓ Choose the number of attempts available to find the secret word. ✓ The higher the speed, the less time you get for each try. Choose your favorite game mode : ✓ Training : Just practice, and score ! ✓ Marathon : Find as many words as you can with an increasing difficulty, and reach the best score in one go without failing. ✓ Time trial : Find a predefined number of words in a limited amount of time. Other options : ✓ Allow/Disallow specific British English words. ✓ Choose one of the 10 available skins, customize the background image and switch on/off sound effects. WordBreaker for iPhone is also available on the App Store !</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7445_08_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/81/58/80/81588037-4aaa-7f1d-07e7-7c6b4c9015af/mzm.hnplcked.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7445-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7445_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:58:59">http://www.games.com/game/douzedix/wordbreaker-lingo-trainer</link><title>WordBreaker - Lingo Trainer</title><description>★★ The Mastermind of italian words ★★ WordBreaker is the Mastermind of words! How fast can you find the secret word? With every try, WordBreaker tells you which letters are correct or misplaced. ➤ WordBreaker and WordBreaker HD are also available in English, Dutch, German, Spanish and French (Smotus) on the AppStore. Think that's easy ? Think again... Don't forget that only well formed italian words of the right length will give you the feedback you need! Any mistake and you loose that try... Currently, WordBreaker's dictionary contains more than 300,000 entries ranging from 5 to 10 letters and 4 increasing difficulty levels. ✓ Challenge your friends with your best scores! ✓ Game Center compatibility to share/compare scores and achievements online ✓ Play online with your friends through GameCenter or Wifi/Bluetooth Need a little help? Just shake your iPhone or iPod to trigger the "wildcard letter". Be aware however that this trick works only once per word and reduces your score... Each time you find the secret word, you get between 100 and 220 points depending on the difficulty level. Double your score by finding the secret word in 3 tries only, make it fivefold by finding it in 2 tries only, and tenfold if you find it at the very first guess !!! Check your scores or the found word history in the "Score" view. Customize your favorite gameplay : ✓ Choose your word length, ranging from 5 to 10 letters. ✓ Choose the average level of difficulty for secret words: "Easy", "Medium", "Hard" or "Expert". ✓ Choose the number of attempts available to find the secret word. Choose your favorite game mode : ✓ Training : Just practice, and score ! ✓ Marathon : Find as many words as you can, with an increasing difficulty, and reach the best score in one go without failing. ✓ Time trial : Find a predefined number of words in a limited amount of time.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7445_09_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/ab/76/ad/ab76adef-de46-e399-d7ac-d8ef4a308453/mzm.gpbwrjyc.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7445-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7445_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:01:38">http://www.games.com/game/e4c-solutions/zanshin-lite</link><title>ZANSHIN LITE</title><description>Welcome to ZANSHIN LITE- a new martial arts strategic combat app for the iPhone and iPod Touch!! This is the lite version of ZANSHIN. In the game, players must train and compete to prove their skill, knowledge and mastery of the martial arts. Fight in the dojo or around the countryside settings to see who the best is. Are you ready? Features: \- Colorful Graphics and Deep Gameplay Mechanics \- 11 Unique Directional and Combat Moves to MOVE, EVADE, ATTACK and BLOCK \- Play against the AI in Single Player Mode!!! \- Two (2) gameplay modes: Tournament and Free Play \- 4 Different Control Configurations (Beginner to Intermediate) for gradually learning gameplay and strategy \- Three (3) levels of A.I. difficulty - Easy, Medium, Hard \- Use strategy to defeat your opponent. There is a counter to any favorite move. \- Included in-app QUICKPLAY instructions \- Detailed instructions are at: www.e4csolutions.com/zanshin Important Info: \- Four (4) different controller configurations can be used to play the game. Beginning and intermediate players can use the EZ and LT versions of the D-Pad Buttons or Swipes controls to fight with a small but highly effective set of 8 directional and attack moves. WHEN FIRST INSTALLED, THE CONTROLS ARE SET TO THE BUTTONS EZ CONTROLLER!! Decide on your controller of choice!! Buy the FULL VERSION - ZANSHIN 1.1!! The full version adds: \- Access to all 27 fight moves (version 1.1). The lite version has only 11 fight moves (7 attack/defend and 4 directional). \- Fight head to head with a friend using two (2) iPhone/iPod Touch devices with 2 player fighting over bluetooth (tournament and free play modes). \- Access to mini games "Dodge" and "Marathon" (version 1.1). Test your skill in these martial arts survival games. \- Personalize Full Controller move-to-gesture mappings for more ease of use. \- Personalize taunts and fighting sounds in the game. \- Access to a Practice Mode to perfect your timing.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7445_10_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/8a/90/c1/mzl.kfmdxcdu.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>