<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7447">running shoes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:05:05" name="Games.com" id="FW14-e048"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e048-7447-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7447_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:05:05">http://www.games.com/game/mattel/barbie-fashionistas</link><title>Barbie® Fashionistas®</title><description>****WORKS ONLY ON iPAD2 and iPOD TOUCH 3rd GENERATION AND ABOVE**** ****FOR BEST PERFORMANCE, PLEASE CLOSE ALL APPS RUNNING IN BACKGROUND**** Welcome to the Barbie® Fashionistas® Endless Closet™ - your place for endless fashion fun! Mix and match trendy looks on your favorite Fashionistas® dolls in the Dressing Room and create your own custom designs in the Design Studio! Step into the Design Studio and create endless looks with the patterns, colors, and graphics you like best. Not enough fashion play for you? We’ve put together some amazing collections that you can purchase separately or buy them all! Best of all, once you’re finished creating, you can try on all your designs in the Dressing Room! Inside the DRESSING ROOM The Dressing Room still offers the fabulous, fun, free play of putting together trendy looks with the swipe of your finger. Mix and match tops, bottoms, shoes, accessories, and hairstyles. Try adding glitter to her top! What about giving her a pet?! You can even try on designs you created in the Design Studio! We can’t wait to see what you dream up! Don’t forget with a Fashionistas® ring you can transform some of your fashions even further — change hemlines, sleeve length, and more! Don't have a ring? Try using your fingers! When you’ve finally put together that perfect look, take a picture! It’s automatically saved in the Photo app on your device. In Barbie® doll’s Endless Closet™, the fashion fun really is endless! Please note: Barbie Fashionistas is free to play, but you can purchase in-app items with real money. You can disable in-app purchases by adjusting your device’s settings. Fashionistas® rings are sold with select Fashionistas® products at select retailers. Please rate and review us! We love your comments! *** Please rate and review us! We love your comments!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7447_01_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/ef/a3/45/efa345d2-15bc-2eca-e013-02b946c8ba34/mzl.oelgykrb.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7447-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7447_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:08:04">http://www.games.com/game/hothead-games/big-win-football</link><title>BIG WIN Football</title><description>Get Big Win Football for FREE now and for a limited time Unlimited FREE Energy! (Save $9.99) "This strategic &amp; competitive gameplay has got us HOOKED!" - Appoday Get ready to go for the end zone with BIG WIN Football! From the opening kickoff to the game winning touchdown, BIG WIN Football is the gridiron game for everyone! Step into the shoes of both GM and coach and train your players to be a pro team. Shuffle your offense and defense to find the ultimate roster and take on other teams on the field in multiplayer battles. FRIENDS MODE Connect to Facebook and challenge your friends to action packed football games EVENTS MODE Players can compete in limited time Big Bowl events for a chance to win HUGE prizes TROPHY MODE Choose the number of games you want to play, rally your players and battle it out in Pro and Amateur Big Bowls to reach the top of the standings QUICK MATCH MODE Practice your offensive and defensive skills and test your team’s abilities in this fast, casual game mode CREATE your own unique dream team, COMPETE against opponents from around the world, WATCH your team battle it out, BOOST your player’s throwing, running, tackling and other skills and get ready for the ultimate BIG WIN! HIGHLIGHTS * Full team and player customization allowing you to create your own fantasy team! * Open Bronze, Silver and Gold card packs to find new players and skill boosts to improve your team * Play game changing Big Impact cards and watch them affect the outcome when they come to life on the field! BIG IMPACT CARDS \+ Iron Curtain \+ The Big Boot \+ Strip it! \+ Solid Grip \+ Hold The Line \+ Can't Catch Me \+ Break It Up \+ Field Goal Focus \+ and many more… Other games in Hothead Games' BIG WIN Sports Series include: BIG WIN MLB BIG WIN Baseball BIG WIN Basketball BIG WIN Hockey BIG WIN Soccer Play your favorite sport with BIG WIN Sports! Go for the BIG WIN! © 2013 Hothead Games Inc., Hothead, Big Win and Big Win Sports are registered trademarks of Hothead Games Inc., all rights reserved.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7447_02_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple4/v4/b6/6b/f7/b66bf711-399b-e637-f060-145c35db3c53/mzl.cjbzctlk.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7447-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7447_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:10:31">http://www.games.com/game/kitmaker-entertainment-sa/football-championship</link><title>Football Championship</title><description>Get ready to play with the best teams in the world, FOOTBALL CHAMPIONSHIP is the game for football lovers. With FOOTBALL CHAMPIONSHIP you can step in the shoes of a professional player, you will have to have a team strategy and score as much as you can. Now you can measure up with the most important players in the world with this game designed for you to practice your sports skills. Run with the ball in your power and have a team play, only that way will you be able to score as much as you can. Kick, pass, hit and score! FOOTBALL CHAMPIONSHIP is the game you were wainting for!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7447_03_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/71ys%2B9E8DFL._SL160_.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7447-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7447_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:11:26">http://www.games.com/game/aijun-she/ghosts-revenge</link><title>Ghost's Revenge</title><description>Ghost's Revenge! [ The story ] A little girl was knocked down by a flying car in the village, and the driver escaped with the car. The girl was very serious and finally was gone. Her ghost wake up, and decie to follow that bay guy.She followed the guy to their party. They were not aware of the Revenge.  The ghost gathered many fellows, dicussing the revenge……The ghost ask for Dryad’s help. Those bad guys were terribly frightened by  the dryads,running away. And finally got arrested by the police. Ghost's Revenge finished, they fly away and the village return peaceful. [ How to play ? ] Looking difference between the 2 pictures! The differences between the pictures are very slight in every points of the game. You should find a difference and click the different point in any picture. You can chose ‘play with hints’ firstly. [The features] The pictures are extremely fine,each pair of pictures are almost identical and perfect. There are only slight differences between two pictures,such as the socks of the characters,color of the hairs, watchband of the hands,points of the trees,color of house even far away. Including the feet,shoes, the grass direction even the hair direction. update: 1.3.5 fix the bug of save game</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7447_04_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/f5/5b/8d/f55b8d7a-6505-66d9-a4b5-5bbc0e73e899/EMTB46EVLbbSAButDD939M-temp-upload.yzyeiefx.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7447-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7447_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:12:14">http://www.games.com/game/crazysoft-limited/the-odyssey-hd</link><title>The Odyssey HD</title><description>(Caution: This game does not run on iPad 1. Only from iPad 2 and newer models!) ▶ www.crackberry.com review: "Fancy a challenge? Guide Ulysses home with The Odyssey HD. If you are looking for a mystical adventure game then The Odyssey HD may well be just what you are after... If you fancy taking on the challenge of getting Ulysses home, you won't want to miss this game." ▶ www.pdasnews.com review: "Being a Lucas/Sierra addicted fan, I loved this game. It kept me playing for several hours each day and when I finished it (with tips of course) I wanted more. I totally recommend it to all the genre fans and all the other guys who are just bored playing 'hidden object' games." ▶ www.blackberryos.com review: "If you were born before the 90's, then you most likely are familiar with some old classic point and click adventure games. My all time favorite was the King's Quest series. This game will keep you entertained for hours on end. Beware, highly addicting!" This is the free / lite version. Its fully playable until its 3rd chapter completely free. Many hours of free adventure game playing guaranteed! No ads, try it for free! This game contains in-App ability to buy a full license. FEATURES: ▶ Huge and classic point-and-click adventure game. ▶ Be part of Homer's epic story and educate yourself while playing. ▶ Face ancient Gods, Sirens, Cyclops and other monsters. ▶ Beautifully hand drawn cartoons (Full HD), humorous dialogs and challenging puzzles. ▶ Short animation synopsis for educational purposes. ▶ Fully translated into English, German, French, Spanish, Russian and Greek. ▶ iPad with Retina display is fully supported. Step into this epic point-and-click mythical adventure game. See what it takes to be the Greek hero Odysseus (Ulysses)! Get ready to embark on a journey filled with danger, mythical creatures and ancient Gods. Thrilling moments and unexpected twists as well as the evil presence of legendary creatures dominate this mythical game throughout. You will have to step into the shoes of Odysseus (Ulysses) and his journey home after the fall of Troy. It took him ten years to reach Ithaca after the ten- year Trojan War. Become a part of Homer's original myth, live the adventure, and educate yourself during the process. Beware; this is not a simple task. You will have to escape from Goddess Calypso's island, blind Cyclops Polyphemus, face the witch-Goddess Circe, go to the land of the death in search of an oracle, avoid the Siren mermaids, pass between the six-headed monster Scylla and the whirlpool Charybdis, and visit the Sun God's island. Finally, you will have to murder the suitors and get together with your beloved wife, Penelope and your fearless son Telemachus.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7447_05_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple6/v4/d3/fd/e6/d3fde6ef-18e0-8a93-17ad-1194850e22d3/mzl.dqchawlg.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7447-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7447_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:13:58">http://www.games.com/game/viwid-webdesign-software-development-inhaber-nils-fischer/blackjack-card-counting</link><title>Blackjack Card Counting</title><description>Practice your card counting skills wherever you want! Draw cards with a swipe over the screen and count as fast as you can! Choose from a selection of the most popular and successful card counting strategies and check the count anytime. Toggle easily between single and dual card display by using your device’s portrait or landscape mode and optionally shake your device to shuffle the cards! Blackjack Card Counting simulates a shoe of cards with the gorgeously designed, Retina-Display-optimized original „Altenburger Spielkarten“ with English or German artwork. Because the App uses realistic graphics, you can train counting cards for the actual Blackjack table in casinos, where you have to take care of so much more than just recognize the cards dealt. Blackjack Card Counting helps you learn to instantly spot and recognize the cards and assign the their value. Blackjack Card Counting utilizes the Hi-Lo strategy by default to display the game’s current count. This method is the easiest to learn and even the most lucrative one, as many experts suggest, because it simplifies counting cards itself, so that the player can rather concentrate on his surroundings. Furthermore, there are 22 additional strategies (see "Features" for the complete list) to unlock via In-App Purchase. An explanation is integrated to support beginners. Contrary to what popular movies like „21“ suggest, counting cards is not difficult and only requires the ability to count +/-1! To be able to effectively count cards in a Casino Blackjack game, you just need some practice in recognizing cards and assign them their correct value quickly. This is what you can easily learn with this App. ### FEATURES ### +++ English and German card artwork with the original „Altenburger Spielkarten“ +++ Intuitive, Retina display optimized User Interface +++ Display either one (Portrait mode) or two (Landscape mode) cards by just rotating your device +++ Universal App for both iPhone/iPodTouch and iPad! +++ Shake to Shuffle! +++ Current Running Count and True Count always available +++ Possibility to choose the number of packs used in the stack of cards +++ Automatic calculation of the Initial Running Count for unbalanced strategies, depending on the number of pack and the strategy's net unbalance. If you use a custom IRC, you can disable this option. +++ Free! You can support us by removing the iAd banners via In-App Purchase +++ Strategies available: Hi-Lo, REKO, Zen Count, Canfield Expert, Canfield Master, Hi-Opt I, Hi-Opt II, KISS 2, KISS 3, K-O, Mentor, Omega II, Red Seven, Revere Plus-Minus, Revere Point Count, Revere RAPC, Revere 14 Count, Silver Fox, Unbalanced Zen 2, Uston Adv. Plus-Minus, Uston APC, Uston SS, Wong Halves If you miss a method, please just contact us!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7447_06_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple4/v4/f1/b4/3a/f1b43a7e-ff5a-28d2-2f06-851da0481de0/mzl.tihzqnxg.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7447-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7447_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:15:27">http://www.games.com/game/2k-games/2k-sports-combo-pack</link><title>2K Sports Combo Pack</title><description>NBA 2K13 - A JAY Z Production including MyCAREER Mode, NBA 2K "MyTEAM," the Shoe Creator and Classic Teams. NBA 2K13 - Improved Gameplay features, including such innovations as the Control Stick, Dynamic Shot Generator, Signature Skills, and Revamped Passing System. MLB 2K13 - Now with Total Control Pitching &amp; Hitting, My Player, MLB Today, MLB Today Season, Dynamic Tendencies, Inside Edge &amp; Stats Inc., Franchise, Postseason and Home Run Derby., Platforms: Xbox 360, ESRB Rating: Everyone</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7447_07_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/51gh0RVdVaL._SL160_.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7447-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7447_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:18:37">http://www.games.com/game/paramount-digital-entertainment/the-dictator-wadiyan-games</link><title>The Dictator: Wadiyan Games</title><description>Own the outrageous and hilarious film NOW on iTunes in US and Canada. Also available August 21 on Blu-ray &amp; DVD.* *Available in UK and Ireland starting September 24, New Zealand starting October 3, and Australia starting October 4. The Wadiyan Games continues with SOCCER! Help the Dictator, General Aladeen, score another medal for Wadiya! The Wadiyan Games lets you step into the shoes of the General Aladeen and compete in his four favorite events – running, swimming, fencing and boxing. You can also upload a headshot and pose alongside the General Aladeen and share the picture on Facebook, Twitter and email! The game also features the ultimate finishing moves for each event. Additional sporting events and backdrops can be unlocked with in-app purchase. Due to the size of the app, it is recommended that you download over a WiFi connection, if your country allows internet access! Requirements: Compatible with iOS devices iPhone 4, iPhone 4S, iPad 2, iPad 3 and iPod Touch 4th Generation. Not compatible with iPhone 3GS and iPad 1. This app is designed for both iPhone and iPad Now available in German, Italian, Spanish, Portuguese, French, and Russian</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7447_08_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/b5/ae/2d/b5ae2d4a-6ac4-a12c-bdd7-b68ed54ec463/mzl.inwluvas.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7447-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7447_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:21:48">http://www.games.com/game/bulkypix/aby-escape</link><title>Aby Escape</title><description>Run Aby, Ruuuuuuuuuuuuuun !!! Help poor Aby, the unluckiest and clumsiest raccoon, escape from his assailants. Whether being pursued by the hunters in his native forest, by the police in town or by the bikers on Route 66.5, Aby never stops running to escape from all these dangers. UNLIMITED MODE Slide, jump and accelerate to dodge all the obstacles in your path. Collect coins and unlock loads of power-ups. Achieve the best score you can and complete 50 exclusive challenges. STORY MODE Progress through 30 levels split across 3 different universes, and take on every kind of obstacle and unique situation: a catapult, an American football stadium, elephants, and trucks, just to name a few. Get an overview of the next update by completing Story mode. WINTER RUSH MODE Aby's back! He's supposed to be on vacation in the mountains, but some bogus Santas have decided to spoil his fun. Quick as a flash, he jumps on his sled and hurtles down the slopes to escape. Check out the three game phases for even more fun: 1 - Progress by dodging the obstacles. 2 - Take your enemies out by throwing snowballs at them. 3 - Survive a terrifying avalanche. Features: - 50 challenge to take on in Unlimited mode - 30 levels in Story mode - Lots of enemies to shake off or avoid (hunters, policemen, bikers, footballers, elephants, etc.) - Lots of power-ups available (Ghost, Magnet, Extra life, Shield...) - Objects to unlock (characters, shoes, etc.) - Universal iPhone/iPad version - Game center \------------------------------- CURIOUS? More info on: \------------------------------- bulkypix.com facebook.com/Bulkypix twitter.com/Bulkypix youtube.com/Bulkypix pixelratio.es/ twitter.com/Pixel_Ratio www.facebook.com/pages/Pixel-Ratio-SC/186041741443088?ref=ts</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7447_09_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/de/58/b1/de58b1e0-c742-3851-584d-090e6fb46ed5/mzl.ibaleosn.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7447-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7447_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:23:20">http://www.games.com/game/temple-of-fun-run-and-jump-games/zombie-smuggler-business</link><title>Zombie Smuggler Business</title><description>You have entered the zombie smuggling business. Yes, you smuggle tiny zombies to all parts of the world. As a smuggler, you need to keep things efficient. The goal is to create nice neat rows of zombie crates, so that they fill up a whole row and will be shipped off. But is the game good? Here is what was just reentry said: "With its Tetris styled game play, this one is addictive and fun. It really comes alive on the iPad, but plays well on the iPhone." - Monster Free Apps Zombie Smuggler Business puts you in the shoes of a dirty Zombie Smuggler, trying to make as much money as possible. You will need to run and jump over and around crates so you can push them around. Stack as many tiny zombie crates side by side to fill up the whole row so that you can ship them to your customers. Easier said than done, Zombie Smuggler is a fun and addictive game of reflexes and strategy. It will puzzle even the best minds. If you want a top of the line game that is addicting and will keep you coming back for more, then try Zombie Smuggler Business. This is a game for the whole family, boys and girls included. Get the kids involved and let them stack those tiny zombie crates up high!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7447_10_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/5e/61/f3/5e61f3c6-de0e-f111-a3e7-eb22185205fe/mzl.wumilvtv.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>