<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7453">pc 2 games reviews</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:51:13" name="Games.com" id="FW14-e048"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e048-7453-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7453_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:51:13">http://www.games.com/game/mumbojumbo/midnight-mysteries-salem-witch-trials</link><title>Midnight Mysteries: Salem Witch Trials</title><description>Try for free, then unlock the full experience with in-game purchase! REVIEWS "Midnight Mysteries: Salem Witch Trials is a gorgeous and clever point-and-click hybrid that asks you to use your brain more than most games.” – Jayisgames.com* “… Dark, beautiful graphics, a compelling story, and a solid mixture of HOG and point and click adventure elements… ” – Gamezebo.com* DESCRIPTION A storm is brewing in Salem!!! Can you solve this Midnight Mystery? Explore 10 adventurous missions in stunning HD in the full version of this intriguing hidden-object adventure game. The famed writer Nathaniel Hawthorne has died during a freak snow storm, and his ghost has come to you, asking for help. There’s more to this case than first appears, and only you can help free his spirit. Optimized for the iPad, Salem Witch Trials features a cool zoom element that allows you to get up close with each setting. Travel back and forth in time from the scene of the author’s demise to the 17th century, where a town is going mad with rumors of witchcraft and a woman is facing accusations and the gallows. Explore the spooky terrain and structures of Salem village inside and out, interview ghosts, solve brain-teasing puzzles and collect hidden objects. Search for collectible clovers in each scene to unlock unlimited hidden object mode! Scour scenes for ravens to use as hints along the way. Or, use your lantern to figure out the shape of the object you’re searching for. Unravel the secrets of Salem’s accused witches and solve the mysterious death of Hawthorne in this Midnight Mystery! MORE GREAT GAMES FROM MUMBOJUMBO!!! Search for MumboJumbo on the App Store and the Mac App Store, or visit www.mumbojumbo.com to find more great games from MumboJumbo!!! 7 Wonders 7 Wonders 2 7 Wonders Magical Mystery Tour Chainz Galaxy Glowfish Luxor Luxor: Amun Rising Luxor 2 Luxor Evolved Midnight Mysteries: Devil on the Mississippi Midnight Mysteries: Haunted Houdini Pickers Samantha Swift and the Fountains of Fate Unlikely Suspects *Note: Jayisgames.com’s and Gamezebo.com’s reviews refer to PC version of Midnight Mysteries: Salem Witch Trials.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7453_01_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/0f/31/f1/0f31f180-5efd-9375-0d01-e641b0228f71/mzm.wfqtevaa.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7453-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7453_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:53:26">http://www.games.com/game/mastersoft-mobile-solutions/chess</link><title>Chess ⋆</title><description>Mastersoft Chess has one of the World's best Desktop PC chess engines crammed inside! This engine finished 4th in the World Microcomputer Chess Championships and is not available in any other iPhone chess game. Designed by chess champions to play like a human opponent, Mastersoft Chess will take you from Novice to Grandmaster level! Features stunning high resolution sets by renowned Chess designers. ✮✮✮ Easy to play but difficult to beat, this is pick up and play chess at its best! ✮✮✮ As previously supplied by the World's biggest OEMs, and now available for a fraction of the original price thanks to the power of the App Store! ✮✮✮ The #1 Best Selling Chess App for iOS* ✮✮✮ PROFESSIONAL REVIEWS: ★"I bought all chess applications for iPhone and this one is probably better than many $7-9 applications. Check TEST ALL. 66 chess applications at only ONE page in the World ..." \- www.chess-iphone.blogspot.com ★"It truly is close to flawless and is by far the best mobile Chess game I have played on any platform." \- PDA 247. ✮✮✮ AWARDS ✮✮✮ ★HP Choice Strategy Game of the Year ★Smartphone Magazine runner up. Various levels, board styles and breathtaking Retina Display chess sets combine with an outstanding World beating chess engine to offer you a great playing experience and an ever increasing challenge. Whether you're just starting out or else a seasoned pro, Mastersoft Chess has something for you! BEGINNERS ★Hint facility. ★Built in coach to monitor your progress ★Training levels that dumb down your iPhone / iPod Touch. ★Take back a move if you change your mind! ★Your iPhone/iPod Touch checks that your moves are allowed. ★Simple intuitive uncluttered interface that lets you concentrate on your game. NB If you are new to Chess then please ensure that the coach is turned on in options and that the lowest difficulty level is selected. GRANDMASTERS ★A unique engine unlike any other - plays interesting and sometimes quite aggressive chess. ★Designed to play like a human opponent - right up to Grandmaster level! ★Opening Book of over 23000 moves! ★100% Full Chess rules including enpassant, castling etc. ★Thought analysis (main line, depth and score). ★Setup position (including castling rights, enpassant and side to move) ★Move forward / backward to any point in the current game. ★Includes Standard Chess Book Sets in addition to the realistic ones. OTHER FEATURES ★Huge collection of stunning high resolution chess sets in both 2D and 3D. Makes the most of Retina Display! ★Boards constructed from the real thing - Oak, Ash, Marble, Slate and more! ★Save and load games. ★Realistic sound effects. ★Adjustable piece movement animation. ★Autosaving of your current game. ★Great for novices but will grow with you and still offer a challenge at Championship level. ★Universal App. Play on your iPod, iPhone and iPad. No additional purchase necessary. ★Great value! *Source: US App Store 2011.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7453_02_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1965.phobos.apple.com/us/r1000/086/Purple/v4/f5/64/8e/f5648edf-f20d-50d4-e6d3-15cae23dd425/mzl.oxkwerqt.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7453-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7453_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:55:09">http://www.games.com/game/pokercruncher/pokercruncher-advanced-poker-odds-calculator</link><title>PokerCruncher - Advanced - Poker Odds Calculator</title><description>The App Store's top Texas Hold'em odds calculator. "... incredibly powerful tool ... must-have application." -- PokerSoftware.com "... essentially functions as an advanced version of the PC’s PokerStove application." -- Bluff Magazine Take your game to the next level with PokerCruncher, an advanced professional-level **hand ranges** odds calculator that goes beyond even PokerStove. \--&gt; Super fast and easy to use for basic hand matchups. \--&gt; Advanced features like hand ranges and Deal-To-Flop and flop texture analysis for serious strategy analysis. Most odds apps are nowhere as powerful as PokerCruncher. Some don't even support random hands (let alone hand ranges), some don't let you enter cards for multiple players, some make an incomplete attempt at hand ranges, … PokerCruncher is the full real deal, more powerful than even the PC's PokerStove application, and has a clean and easy-to-use interface. Start using PokerCruncher today to improve your game and your results! *** iPhone, iPad, and Mac(Expert) versions available *** ===== Recent Notable Updates: * Some new Deal-To-Flop stats, e.g. TopPair, MiddlePair, BottomPair. Many more great reviews on our TwoPlusTwo forum thread (400+ posts). (See our website for links.) ===== ***** Note: Tutorial on our website. Our Tutorial gives thorough explanations of this app's features, which may help you get the most out of this advanced odds app. ***** \--- Completely General --- Up to 10 players, with specific cards, random/unknown cards, or hand ranges for each player. Dead cards, %age's or n:1 odds, … \--- Fully General Hand Ranges --- Poker is a game of incomplete information; we need to put our opponents on **ranges of hands**. PokerCruncher surpasses even PokerStove's features, e.g. range equity breakdown heat maps and hand combo stats. Full grid of all 169 starting hands, top x% of hands slider, extensive built-in hand ranges, save/load and export/import hand ranges, … \--- Deal-To-Flop and Flop Texture Analysis --- \--- Many Stats --- Hand type stats (odds for making OnePair, TwoPair, etc.), flop hit stats, odds for flopping draws and combination draws, OnePair breakdown stats, … \--- Tutorial --- If thinking in terms of hand ranges and flop texture analysis (techniques advanced players and pros use) are new to you, no problem, we've written a **Tutorial** to get you started. ***** Continual improvement for 5+ years: 40+ iOS version updates. Follow us on Facebook and Twitter. ***** GENERAL FEATURES: \+ Runs locally on device, internet connection not needed \+ Fast Monte Carlo simulation, complete enumeration for some common cases \+ Completely general tool, e.g. up to 10 players \+ Specific cards, random/unknown cards, fully general hand ranges, for each player \+ Generate random player and board cards to set up what-if and test scenarios \+ Dead cards \+ Fold/Un-Fold players \+ Save/load and export/import scenarios (hands) and hand ranges \+ %age's or n:1 odds \+ Clean and crisp retina card graphics Please see the Tutorial for a full description of all of the features. App Store reviews are greatly appreciated, thank you. ***** Also please check out our companion app "Tournament Cruncher" (ICM). ***** ===== Regarding a few (incorrect) "odds are wrong" reviews on a few countries' App Stores: The odds are correct, and have always been correct. It looks like some people don't understand the advanced Deal-To-Flop feature (which even PokerStove doesn't have), or have other basic confusions on poker stats. We wish they'd write to us instead of just leaving an incorrect review. Examples: 1) liljoe81 (USA App Store): You probably set Deal-To = Flop instead of the intended (default) Deal-To = River. 2) chrishpa (Germany App Store): The TwoPair: 38% stat in the app's 1st screenshot is correct. Totally incorrect reviews like these hurt this app unfairly. If you like this app it would be great if you could write a review. Many thanks, -RJ =====</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7453_03_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/ca/27/fe/ca27fe94-7c2a-4035-eb07-976c2ae6b601/mzl.bdpushlb.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7453-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7453_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:56:16">http://www.games.com/game/big-fish-games/drawn-dark-flight-hd</link><title>Drawn: Dark Flight HD</title><description>Introducing Drawn: Dark Flight, the sequel to the number one hit game, Drawn: The Painted Tower! Iris has escaped from the Tower but she still needs your help! Explore the Kingdom of Stonebriar and solve the mysteries of the shadows that prowl its streets in this cinematic adventure game. Enter magical worlds through colorful paintings and meet a host of fantastic characters that will help you on your quest. Only someone with the power of imagination can unravel the mysteries of the three beacons, and save a future queen that will bring hope back to a people! ☆☆☆ Features ☆☆☆ ✓ Explore 100+ screens on your magical journey through the town of Stonebriar ✓ Original music score composed specifically for each area of the adventure ✓ Overcome dozens of elaborate environmental puzzles that block your way ✓ Enter lush paintings and meet fantastic characters in magical worlds ✓ Integrated Game Center Achievements ✓ Gestural navigation ✓ Localized in Spanish, French, German, and Japanese ☆ Reviews ☆ “What I like most of all about Dark Flight, however, is its message. Here’s a game about helping people in need, for no other reason than that they are in need. And it’s about helping those people not through violence – with swords or guns or big veiny fists – but instead with art, and music, and craftsmanship. It’s an absolute celebration of creativity, and all the magic that comes with it. That the game is so unequivocally and consistently creative itself just seals the deal.” - Lewis Denby, Beefjack.com “Gorgeous, whimsical scenery will draw you into Dark Flight’s living world of art and imagination…” - 4/5 Adventure Gamers “It’s perfectly sculpted from beginning to end, crafting a story that’s intriguing, gameplay that never ceases to be interesting, and an overall experience that will leave you satisfied but ready for more. Easily one of the best casual adventure games ever released.” - Jayis Games ☆☆☆ Discover more from Big Fish Games! ☆☆☆ We’re big believers that everyone is a gamer at heart and that games are a great source of joy and relaxation. Founded in 2002, Big Fish Games is a developer, publisher and distributor of casual games. We offer a virtually endless selection of interactive games that you can enjoy anytime, anywhere — on your PC, Mac, mobile phone, or tablet. Renowned for offering A New Game Every Day!® on www.bigfishgames.com, Big Fish Games distributes more than two million games per day worldwide. We have many other great iPad games including: ➠ Mahjong Towers Touch HD ➠ Doors of the Mind: Inner Mysteries HD ➠ Time Builders: Pyramid Rising HD ➠ Antique Road Trip: USA HD ➠ Flux Family Secrets: The Ripple Effect HD ➠ The Serpent of Isis HD ➠ A Witch’s Curse: Princess Isabella HD ➠ Empress of the Deep: The Darkest Secret HD ➠ Haunted Manor: Lord of Mirrors HD ➠ PuppetShow: Mystery in Joyville HD ➠ Drawn: The Painted Tower HD ➠ Awakening: The Dreamless Castle HD ➠ Awakening 2: Moonfell Wood HD ➠ Ancient Spirits: Columbus' Legacy HD ➠ Amazon: Hidden Expedition You can always find an updated list at www.bigfishgames.com! Try out Big Fish Games' iSplash! newsletter and never miss a sale or new game again! Sign up at: http://bigfi.sh/isplash Follow us on Twitter: http://bigfi.sh/BigFishTwitter Become a fan on Facebook: http://bigfi.sh/Mfacebook</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7453_04_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/2d/cc/6b/2dcc6b41-9553-1afc-5171-9bfeed07268a/mzl.vpjlrtrt.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7453-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7453_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:57:49">http://www.games.com/game/owlchemy-labs/snuggle-truck</link><title>Snuggle Truck</title><description>Now with over 30,000 free community levels included! Create your own and race, now optimized for Retina! * The premiere snuggling game :) * Featured by PC World, TouchArcade, Kotaku, Joystiq, Penny Arcade, George Lopez Tonight and countless others! Reviews: ***** PocketGamer - Game of the Week "It's bonkers, hilarious, and utterly addictive... A perfect addition to your home screen." ***** SlideToPlay - Must Have 4/4 "Whether you call it Snuggle Truck or Smuggle Truck, this game is an absolute blast." ***** Kotaku Gaming App of the Day ***** Penny Arcade PAX East Boston Indie Showcase Snuggle Truck is an over-the-top physics-based driving game where you must save your cargo full of animals by delivering them to the zoo quickly. Tilt your truck, catch flying animals, avoid TNT, rocket off of cliffs, and blast through hills, caverns, deserts, and forests while trying to keep those animals in the truck! Features: \- New recording feature for saving the funniest and most amazing replays. Upload straight to Youtube! (iPhone 4 / iPad 2 and up!) \- Bumpy physics gameplay makes for hilarious results -- keep those animals in the truck while bouncing over obstacles and down cliffs. \- Optimized for the iPhone 5 with crisp hi-res graphics! \- Access to tons new content thanks to community-created levels. \- Beautifully hand-painted backgrounds and high resolution graphics crafted by the genius artist of 'Curse of Monkey Island' fame. \- Built-in Level Editor - showcase your creative side! Make crazy-fun levels and share them with others. \- Rocket boosters, flying animals, backflips, loops, roadkill, moose, TNT, and more! \- Game Center leaderboards and achievements - race for the fastest time! \- Dynamic medal system rewards multiple gameplay styles. Try to save every passenger or go for the Speed Run and ditch the passengers! Read about the story behind the game at Snuggletruck.com</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7453_05_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple4/v4/66/cf/79/66cf795c-eab4-4b3c-7285-9e10c13c165d/mzl.rxjjlosn.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7453-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7453_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:00:02">http://www.games.com/game/stainless-games/carma-free</link><title>Carma Free</title><description>Carmageddon is the original freeform driving sensation, where pedestrians (and cows!) equal points, and your opponents are a bunch of crazies in a twisted mix of automotive killing machines. The game features anarchic drive-wherever-you-like gameplay and over-the-top surreal comedy violence. It’s the racing game where racing is for wimps. Now the same Mac &amp; PC classic that was BANNED AROUND THE WORLD is back and available on iPhone, iPad and iPod touch! Carmageddon features real-world environments that have been turned into killing fields, where the locals stay out on the streets at their peril. As well as using your car as a weapon, every level is sprinkled generously with power-ups that have a vast variety of mad effects, adding a whole extra level of craziness to the proceedings. In every event you have the option to “play it your way”… Waste all your opponents, kill every pedestrian, or (perish the thought) complete all the laps. THE FREE VERSION FEATURES: • 5 dangerously deranged Opponents • One event and Environment: Maim Street, in Bleak City • The Eagle (Driver Max Damage) • Universal App • Multiple control methods: digital, analogue (mix ‘n’ match), tilt • Edit your control layout in game to your preferences • Comprehensive Action Replay System • Movie editing; Save your movies straight from the game to YouTube; Share links using iOS 6 • Retina display and iPhone 5 support • Environment maps and other special effects • Enhanced pre-lit environment • Buckets of gibs • Tons of laughs UPGRADE TO THE FULL VERSION FOR: • Career Mode featuring 36 satisfyingly violent Levels • 28 dangerously deranged Opponents • 11 wildly exhilarating Environments • Race and Wreck opponents to unlock 30 playable cars! • iCloud Support • Game Center integration • 27 Cunning Stuntworthy Achievements • Leaderboards Plus the opportunity to make in app purchases to unlock ALL the cars (apart from the secret one) and ALL the races! Carmageddon requires iOS 5.1 or later. AWARDS AND RECOGNITION FOR THE ORIGINAL GAME Carmageddon won the “Game of the Year” trophy in the 1997 PC Zone Reader awards. Carmageddon 1 &amp; 2 were “Driving Game of the Year” 1997/1998. SELECTED REVIEWS OF THE ORIGINAL GAME Originally released for the PC in 1997, Carmageddon was an instant hit and the titles went on to sell over 2 million copies worldwide. Here’s what a sample of the gaming press thought at the time: “Carmageddon is visceral, violent, vehicular fun...” - GameSpot 8.8 out of 10 “Carmageddon, to get straight to the point, is one of the best computer games I've ever played… Carmageddon is God!” - Duncan McDonald 95% Classic Award PC Zone Magazine “Carmageddon is one of those games that only come along once in a blue moon. An essential purchase.” - Escape Magazine 6 out of 6 “The gameplay is spot on and anyone with a dark enough sense of humour should give it a go.” - Computer Gaming World 4 out of 5 “So next time you gun down coppers on GTA VI, just remember, Carmageddon’s controversy was there first, and you have a lot to thank it for.” - RetroGarden ABOUT STAINLESS GAMES Stainless was founded in 1994 by Patrick Buckland, a veteran of the games industry going back to the Jurassic period of 1982, and Neil Barnden, who used to have hair like a mammoth. A team of 8 worked on the original Carmageddon at Stainless, and 5 are still with the company today, although a couple of them are now kept manacled in a small padded room in the cellar. Stainless Games now employs well over fifty mad, dedicated people of assorted gender, height and width. They can all be found dangling precariously from a small chalky rock just off the South Coast of England.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7453_06_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/ac/c9/f4/acc9f44e-5895-1e9a-598b-4e5fcbe8cd90/mzl.sntzmesw.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7453-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7453_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:00:52">http://www.games.com/game/pixel-mine/underworlds</link><title>Underworlds</title><description>Underworlds featured by Apple in the following categories: -Best RPG Game (August 2010) -What's Hot! (August 2009) -New and Noteworthy (May 2009) The Underworlds Icon was also featured in the nationwide 'Best of' iPhone apps advertisement! Named by Touch Arcade as a MUST HAVE game of 2009! Over 3,200 five star App Store reviews! Underworlds is the best action RPG for the iPhone and iPod Touch! Game of the Month - AppGamer.net "it occupied almost all my free time from the minute I downloaded it." - MacWorld, 4 of 5 star review. "Underworlds is a game that will loot your heart and have you coming back for more...Underworlds is an absolute blast!" - thatvideogameblog.com review "I give Underworlds a strong recommendation to any hack and slash fan. I’ve had a great time playing through it, and I’m still having fun on my second time around." - TouchArcade.com "The game is dark, atmospheric, intense, and it’s a fine debut" - 9 out of 10 review, AppGamer.net "I’ve been waiting for an action RPG in the same vein as Diablo on this platform for months and now it’s finally here." - iphones.com "This is the first Authentic iPhone Role Playing Game!!" - appBank.net Touch Arcade's YouTube Preview - http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-wzJjty4OLI -~^-~^-~^-~^-~^ About the Game Underworlds is the premiere role-playing adventure game on the iPhone/iPod Touch! Chapter 1: Into the Abyss You are the guard of McTavish's traveling caravan, carving out a comfortable existence by taking odd jobs and protecting against the occasional Orc raider when a mysterious attack on the nearby town of Albrect compels you to lend your blade to the good townspeople. It's not just rats that plague the Happy Cadaver Inn. Denizens of hell are seeping through to the world of mortals! During your journey you'll face a horde of gruesome enemies...and their wicked overlords! Chapter 2: The Giant Fortress Discover the hidden secrets of the sprawling town of Termon. Face new and fierce enemies in your quest to lift the curse that plaques the 'old town' residents. The fortunes of many are in your hands! More about Gameplay The experience you gain during your adventure lets you learn powerful offensive feats like Slash, Shield Bash and Berserk or advance in the healing arts to gain Health and Vitality Boosts. As you increase in level, you can upgrade your existing Feats or add new ones. The active combat feats feature graphically stunning on-screen special effects to help make your battles even more heart-pounding and exhilarating. As you progress you can choose exactly how to improve your character's abilities. Hone your strength to become a real bruiser, become nimble and accurate by focusing on dexterity, increase intelligence to unlock more feats, or work on your constitution to better withstand the onslaught of the undead. Features: • An iPhone/iPod Touch exclusive release! The game was designed around the powerful Touch controls of the iPhone/iPod Touch • Fully configurable controls for right or left hand play, use a virtual direction pad or just touch where you want to go • Customize your character's attributes and feats to suit your play-style • Advance your character's abilities while you explore mysterious graveyards, dark chambers and dangerous crypts • Test your skill on 4 difficulty settings, including the extreme difficulty challenge • Find thousands of unique armor and weapons to use or trade for gold • Discover hidden traps and treasures • Choose from two simple, smooth control schemes to make play easy at home or on the go • Save your progress at any time or restart with your current experience and items • Enjoy Underworlds again and again - play through multiple times, on different skills levels -~^-~^-~^-~^-~^ ENJOY UNDERWORLDS AND WANT A NEW CHALLENGE? Try our FREE MMORPG, Ashen Empires on your PC. Download the game launcher at www.pixelminegames.com to get started!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7453_07_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/6b/13/a0/mzi.txayubxx.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7453-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7453_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:03:33">http://www.games.com/game/gamescafe/sallys-spa-hd</link><title>Sally's Spa HD</title><description>★★★★★ Sally's Spa HD™ 30% OFF! Limited Time ★★★★★ ♥♥♥♥♥ Why wait? Relax &amp; Refresh in Sally's Spa HD! ♥♥♥♥♥ Now with Multiplayer and Smart Shopper modes!  ☆☆☆☆☆ CRITIC REVIEWS! ☆☆☆☆☆ "Sally's Spa HD is a fast paced, addictive game that's loads of fun to play!" – PadGadget.com "Better than any time management game out there”,”Great fun on the iPhone, even better on the iPad”" – AppAdvice.com “This time management based beauty spa sim is among the most addicting titles available in the App Store.” – 148apps.com “Whether it’s haircuts or hot stone massages, Sally’s dream of beauty and wellness domination has resonated among casual gamers all over.” – TouchMyApps.com "Sally’s Spa HD for the iPad is a wonderful game that will provide you hours of enjoyment and fun" - TouchReviews.net A P P L I C A T I O N - D E S C R I P T I O N: Sally's Spa HD™ now available on iPad with better graphics, multiplayer and GameCenter! Treat yourself to some relaxation and fast paced fun in Sally's Spa and see why millions of players have made Sally’s Spa the best selling casual game for iPhone, PC/Mac and now it’s available for your iPad! Sally's back and ready for a relaxing rush in luxury spa locations around the world. Refresh your customers with saunas, manicures, bath bombs, massages, hot stones and more. Enhance the experience of your clients with upgrades for your rapidly growing business. Melt away the stress from a wide variety of customers and personalities including blushing brides, demanding fashionistas, calm couples, and many others! As you build your Spas, earn money to shop for over 65 items including employees to help your Spa business grow! Sally's Spa features all of the fun of Sally's Salon, plus loads of new surprises! A wonderful escape for gamers of all ages, join Sally on her latest adventure today! F E A T U R E S: • Minigames are now iPad designed with swipes, touches, and drags to perform fun spa services like Mud Masks, Hot Stones, Bath Bombs, Massages, Manicures &amp; much more! • New “Best Friends” mode where you play a co-operative multiplayer game on one iPad. • Sally Spa’s HD has GameCenter! Earn up to 30 Achievements for meeting Sally's challenges and compete on 2 different Online Leaderboards. Add friends and show off your scores! • Use your finger to touch and drag your customers to your Spa stations such as Saunas, Massage Tables, Mani-Pedi stations and serve them Tea to help them relax and refresh. • It’s not just about massaging your customers, they need extra products like Body Butter and Calming Bath salts too! Maximize your product sales buy getting more soothing products for your shelf. • Buy powerups to keep those clients happy! After all, how do you calm down a Fashionista? With a patience candle of course! • As you travel from New York, Paris, Rome, Japan, Fiji and many more places you will meet many character personalities like Rock Stars, Heiresses, Male Models, Athletes and more! At GamesCafe we worked really hard to make Sally’s Spa HD the best game possible for the iPad. We really hope that you enjoy this game and tell your friends and family! Post your ★★★★★ Reviews! Follow us on twitter for Sally's Spa HD updates and more! @SallysGames (http://twitter.com/SallysGames) Become a Sally Fan on Facebook! (http://bit.ly/cPtUDM) Or just search for "Sally's Games" on Facebook and you'll find her!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7453_08_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/39/f0/6f/mzl.qasgawqw.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7453-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7453_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:07:20">http://www.games.com/game/amanita-design/machinarium</link><title>Machinarium</title><description>iPad version of the award-winning adventure game from the makers of Samorost and Botanicula. WHAT'S NEW IN VERSION 2.0: * Pinch-to-zoom * Supports iPad1 * Retina Graphics * Universal App (you can play it also on your iPhone), * Achievements, Game Center, iCloud. ! Please note that your old saves from 1.X version will not work, but you can use the "Lost Save" functionality within the game to partially recover your position (there are 6 pre-saved positions from various parts of the game). REVIEWS: "Absolutely Fantastic" - TouchArcade "It's Phenomenal" - AppAdvice 4/4 - USA TODAY 4/4 - SlideToPlay 9/10 - Pocket Gamer You can play Machinarium also on your Mac or PC.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7453_09_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple4/v4/b9/b4/57/b9b457fb-e24c-5591-5b37-4a309d27062e/mzl.pwgirzgm.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7453-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7453_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:08:09">http://www.games.com/game/big-fish-games/dark-tales-edgar-allan-poes-murder-in-the-rue-morgue-collectors-edition-hd</link><title>Dark Tales: Edgar Allan Poes Murder in the Rue Morgue Collector's Edition HD</title><description>A dreadful murder and kidnapping has occurred in the Rue Morgue and only you can solve the dark crime! Follow the clues to find the killer and the missing family. Become the apprentice of the famed C. Auguste Dupin and solve the devious puzzles to find the hidden clues that will lead you to the monstrous murderer. Based on Edgar Allan Poe’s most acclaimed murder mystery, Dark Tales: Edgar Allan Poe’s Murder in the Rue Morgue is a fantastic Hidden Object Adventure game full of suspense and excitement. TRY IT FREE, THEN UNLOCK THE FULL ADVENTURE FROM WITHIN THE GAME! ☆☆☆☆☆ Features ☆☆☆☆☆ ✓ Mysterious atmosphere &amp; gorgeous, crisp graphics ✓ Intriguing hidden object and adventure game play ✓ Explore Paris in this great story! ✓ Unlock the Collector’s Edition to get amazing extra content, including: \--Exclusive adventure scenes and inventory items \--Bonus hidden object puzzles &amp; minigames \--Includes the strategy guide, concept art &amp; wallpapers \--A sneak preview of the next game in the story For the best experience, we recommend setting your device to display in English or another supported language while playing this game. 本ゲームを最大限にお楽しみいただくために、お使いのデバイスの言語設定を英語またはその他のサポートされている言語に変更されることをお勧めいたします。 ☆☆☆ Discover more from Big Fish Games! ☆☆☆ We’re big believers that everyone is a gamer at heart and that games are a great source of joy and relaxation. Founded in 2002, Big Fish Games is a developer, publisher and distributor of casual games. We offer a virtually endless selection of interactive games that you can enjoy anytime, anywhere — on your PC, Mac, mobile phone, or tablet. Renowned for offering A New Game Every Day!® on www.bigfishgames.com, Big Fish Games distributes more than two million games per day worldwide. We have many other great iPad games including: ➠ Mahjong Towers Touch HD ➠ Doors of the Mind: Inner Mysteries HD ➠ Time Builders: Pyramid Rising HD ➠ Antique Road Trip: USA HD ➠ Flux Family Secrets: The Ripple Effect HD ➠ The Serpent of Isis HD ➠ A Witch’s Curse: Princess Isabella HD ➠ Empress of the Deep: The Darkest Secret HD ➠ Haunted Manor: Lord of Mirrors HD ➠ PuppetShow: Mystery in Joyville HD ➠ Drawn: The Painted Tower HD ➠ Awakening: The Dreamless Castle HD ➠ Awakening 2: Moonfell Wood HD ➠ Ancient Spirits: Columbus' Legacy HD ➠ Amazon: Hidden Expedition You can always find an updated list at www.bigfishgames.com! Try out Big Fish Games' iSplash! newsletter and never miss a sale or new game again! Sign up at: http://bigfi.sh/isplash Follow us on Twitter: http://bigfi.sh/BigFishTwitter Become a fan on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/BigFishGamesMobile</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7453_10_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/be/4b/9b/mzl.duvzjoao.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>