<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7463">hollywood actress</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:18:28" name="Games.com" id="FW14-e048"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e048-7463-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7463_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:18:29">http://www.games.com/game/sandlot-games/fashion-forward</link><title>Fashion Forward</title><description>Help Risha launch her line!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7463_01_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/cdn-games.bigfishgames.com/en_fashion-forward/fashion-forward_feature.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7463-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7463_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:20:53">http://www.games.com/game/game-factory-interactive/detective-stories-hollywood</link><title>Detective Stories: Hollywood</title><description>Hollywood is in a tizzy!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7463_02_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/www.masque.com/materials/images/items/thumb/9828.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7463-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7463_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:22:01">http://www.games.com/game/redwind-software/movie-challenge-oscars-special</link><title>Movie Challenge: Oscars® Special</title><description>The best iPhone Trivia game for the Oscars®. This trivia game celebrates Oscar® winners from Academy Awards® history to the present day, offering everything you need to brush up on your all important awards trivia during Oscar® season. *Academy Award(s)®, Oscar(s)®, Oscar Night® and Oscar® statuette design mark are the registered trademarks and service marks, and the Oscar® statuette the copyrighted property, of the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences. **Redwind Software &amp; "Movie Challenge: Oscars® Special" is in no way associated to or endorsed by The Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences. "Movie Challenge: Oscars Special" features: ★ Over 2000 original questions ★ Best in class Anti-Repetition Question technology ★ Three game modes: Regular, Pass 'n' Play &amp; Blindfold ★ Eight distinct question categories ★ Eight Power-Up options ★ Six games types or 'mini-games' ★ Gorgeous graphics &amp; stunning sound effects ★ Automatic Games Save feature ★ Detailed statistics viewer ★ Option to submit your own questions ★ All powered by the unique "Inquizitor" game engine ★ In App downloads for the most up to date content "Movie Challenge: Oscars® Special" builds on the growing success of "Movie Challenge", yet offers an amazing opportunity to test your knowledge of Hollywood's most celebrated night. "Movie Challenge: Oscars® Special" features categories like Best Picture, Directors, Actors, Actresses and more. The game types include general Trivia, True or False, Guess the Year and Quotes. All bundled into this comprehensive entertainment package. Become the ultimate Oscars® expert by topping our online global leaderboard or test your knowledge against the best to be crowned Trivia Master by virtue of having the highest score across all our games, with the "Inquizitor" Global Leaderboard. ★ Be sure to check the "Latest Fixes" In App download for the most up to date questions.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7463_03_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/56/b7/df/mzl.ezhdehbi.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7463-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7463_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:22:47">http://www.games.com/game/glu-games/stardom-hollywood</link><title>Stardom: Hollywood</title><description>Start a new life as an aspiring actor in Stardom: Hollywood, and go from nobody to A-list celebrity! ◆ YOU’RE THE STAR in a huge interactive adventure: sleazy agents, self-centered celebs, parasitic paparazzi... what you do is up to you! ◆ Create your own actor or actress: make your own look from hundreds of style options! ◆ Star in hit TV shows and blockbuster movies: land roles, earn reviews, and win awards! ◆ Crash the best parties and hottest clubs: flirt and make the next power-couple, or network with Hollywood elite to land the best roles! Stardom: Hollywood is a huge new adventure in a huge new city. Hollywood is bigger and better than ever: visit all-new restaurants, clubs and movie studios, flirt and network with other famous actors to get the best roles, customize your home with cool designer furniture, avoid the paparazzi, and get famous in new movies and TV shows. Your favorite characters are back with new quests, along with a bunch of new people and stories. FOLLOW US: facebook.com/StardomHollywood facebook.com/GluMobile Twitter @GluMobile *** Stardom: Hollywood requires an iPhone 3GS, iPod Third Generation, iPad or later device to run *** *** Stardom: Hollywood is free to play. Players can purchase additional Cash and Stars (the in-game currencies) for real money, or earn currency through special offers. Please adjust your device settings if you wish to lock out the ability to purchase in-game content ***</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7463_04_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/fc/cf/27/fccf272b-cd66-a46b-cfb4-8f9360b00b7d/mzl.ovlgzexv.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7463-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7463_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:25:01">http://www.games.com/game/fugazo/film-fatale-lights-camera-madness-deluxe</link><title>Film Fatale - Lights, Camera, Madness Deluxe</title><description>Save a Hollywood starlet from a lunatic in Film Fatale - Lights, Camera, Madness Deluxe.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7463_05_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/cdn.media.zylom.com/images/deluxe/200x240/2988.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7463-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7463_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:27:53">http://www.games.com/game/toy-maker/movie-girl</link><title>Movie Girl</title><description>☆☆ Live the Hollywood dream and become a MOVIE GIRL! ☆☆ Be a true international superstar! Movie Girl now supports Italian, French, Spanish, German, Korean, Japanese and Chinese! ☆ Ever wanted to be an actress, living it up, wearing pretty clothes and starring in movies? Now you can! ☆ ☆ Dress up in the most beautiful movie costumes! ☆ Film many movies in several different genres! ☆ Do jobs, earn fame and work your way to becoming a movie superstar! ☆ Attend exclusive red carpet movie premieres in gorgeous designer gowns! ☆ Support iPhone 5 resolution ☆ Universal app! ☆ And much more!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7463_06_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/d0/5d/73/d05d730f-fa09-734c-2ea3-279ac9615cbb/mzl.ydufckjx.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7463-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7463_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:30:12">http://www.games.com/game/devada/quiz-apps-hollywood</link><title>Quiz Apps: Hollywood</title><description>How well do you know movies? How about famous actors? Do you know Oscars®? Hollywood Quiz is a fun and fast game that will test your Hollywood knowledge. 3 different game modes will challenge you whether you are relaxing at home or just need a short fun break on-the-go. The rich content will provide you with months worth of entertainment. Look out for other Quiz Apps for more fun and innovative quiz shows. Features; \- 3 different and unique game modes; "20 Questions" provides you 20 continuous questions with 10 seconds for each, "Time Attack" gives you 80 seconds to give as many correct answers as you can, "Perfect Wave" is the mode for perfectionists where you need to provide all correct answers. \- Over 100,000 unique questions that can provide you months worth of fun. \- Keep your high scores for each mode and compete with other players on Game Center. \- Contains all Oscars® data for Best Movie, Best Director, Best Animated Feature, Best Actor, Best Actress, Best Supporting Actor and Best Supporting Actress as well as Ceremony Hosts. \- Free updates for upcoming ceremonies and additional categories. About Quiz Apps: Quiz Apps is a series of fun and fast quiz shows apps that will test your knowledge on various themes in innovative and rich modes.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7463_07_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple6/v4/36/b0/81/36b081aa-b39b-cb45-03bd-9b3508ab8374/mzl.bpebqgbf.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7463-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7463_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:32:39">http://www.games.com/game/dress-up-media/dress-up-hollywood</link><title>Dress Up! Hollywood</title><description>Dress like the most beautiful actresses in Hollywood from iconic stars like Marilyn Monroe and Audrey Hepburn to today’s most popular and glamorous! With Dress Up! Hollywood, you can dress up like any Hollywood stars! ❤Totally glamorous ❤ Lots of outfits, hairstyles and accessories to get you ready for that red carpet look ❤ Hundreds of combinations! Mix and match!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7463_08_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/2a/fa/89/2afa89ba-b4ec-5ddc-1c9f-fe1e7bd86e3b/mzm.vlbbvgno.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7463-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7463_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:35:19">http://www.games.com/game/rotor-games/final-run</link><title>Final Run</title><description>Final Run is a massive 3D driving-action game, combining vehicle combat, exploration, zombie-blasting and landmined road challenges, all set to a compelling story. With an immense 3D world, Final Run boasts 19 levels in diverse environments like the open desert, military compounds and industrial zones. Come fight the Infection! THE CRITICS SAY: 4.5/5 "Final Run makes the zombie genre feel fresh again! A masterful blend of compelling plot, well-drawn characters, and incredibly intense and perfectly paced gameplay adds up to one of the most impressive indie debuts yet this year." - iFanZine Good! "Looks like someone has finally followed the Hollywood dream, a storyline so perfect that all it lacks only is a well renowned actor and actress." - AppCroc.com 4.5/5 "The gameplay is awesome with great graphics &amp; story. Go pick up Final Run!" - PhoneGamerUK.co.uk 82% "Cool, Smooth Indie Car Shooter, lovely graphics." - LittleAppReview "Those who love action packed driving games should definitely check out this alltogether great indie game." - IPlayApps.de STORY: A catastrophic global epidemic has wiped out millions. Now the highly contagious infected have been contained. Bordering the containment area lies the Grey Zone. In this derelict no-man's-land, only the desperate survive... In Final Run, renegade scavenger Kurt Boltares finds himself protecting Doctor Shizu Lee as they are forced to flee the containment area. Having betrayed their former leader, a ruthless mercenary they call the Chief, they know that if they can’t escape, he’ll have them killed. Or, if they’re really unlucky... the Virus will get them first. FEATURES: \+ An epic story in 19 spectacular 3D levels! \+ Kill zombies, destroy vehicles in combat, and dash across mined roads \+ An immersive original soundtrack supported by a dynamic music system \+ Achieve extra in-mission goals to unlock all 6 weapons and all 6 vehicles \+ Intense boss fights with special mechanics and enemies \+ No in-app purchases – all unlockables are accessible for everyone \+ Customizable controls – play as you want! \+ Support for iCade, iControlPad, 60beat GamePad and GameDock! Like the game? Please rate us 5 stars! ROTOR GAMES: Rotor Games is a Dutch indie developer. Final Run's development spans 15 months. The game was made by a talented group of individuals: one full-time developer, one part-time developer, and three freelancers. Final Run is Rotor Games' debut title. FOLLOW US: twitter.com/rotorgames facebook.com/rotorgames youtube.com/rotorgamesvideo</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7463_09_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/8f/9d/ac/8f9dac5b-1846-768e-9b69-ea06a69af91d/mzm.kditwjxx.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7463-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7463_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:38:43">http://www.games.com/game/fourfig-applications-s-l/celebrities-quiz-famous-stars-caricatures</link><title>Celebrities Quiz: Famous Stars Caricatures</title><description>How many celebrities do you know? This fun quiz consists on guessing the names of hundreds of celebrities. You are presented with a caricature of the celebrity and have to select the correct name. There are more than 300 celebrities with great drawings (more coming soon), consisting of: ► Famous movie stars shared between actors and actresses from Hollywood. ► Sportsmen/sportswomen from tennis, soccer, Basketball players, Hockey superstars, Football players and Baseball stars! ► Famous singers and musicians from the best known music groups Not only an actor quiz, neither a sportsmen quiz or a musicians quiz, it’s all in one, with a free trial of 50 caricatures of actors and actresses from Hollywood movies. How many can you guess? ⋯⋯⋯⋯ FEATURES ⋯⋯⋯⋯ ► Compete with your friends using GameCenter Leaderboards and Achievements ► Great exclusive caricatures drawn by Carlos León. ► Contains caricatures of actors, caricatures of sportsmen, and caricatures of musicians. ► Casual game, easy to use ► Polished design ► Retina Support ► Universal App This enjoyable trivia game will be updated with new caricatures. If you want you can ask for your favourite famous people. Let us know your favourite actor or actress, your preferred sportman or sportwoman, a musician or a singer who is your idol. We will do our best to include them in future updates. If you like this addictive game let us know! We will appreciate it!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7463_10_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/d3/92/4c/d3924c58-3b22-142d-5d55-7fb3729bdea8/mzl.byxwsqbb.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>