<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7482">popular twitter stars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:22:17" name="Games.com" id="FW14-e048"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e048-7482-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7482_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:22:18">http://www.games.com/game/ndemic-creations/plague-inc</link><title>Plague Inc.</title><description>Can you infect the world? Plague Inc. is a unique mix of high strategy and terrifyingly realistic simulation. Your pathogen has just infected 'Patient Zero'. Now you must bring about the end of human history by evolving a deadly, global Plague whilst adapting against everything humanity can do to defend itself. Brilliantly executed with innovative gameplay and built from the ground up for iPhone &amp; iPad, Plague Inc. evolves the strategy genre and pushes mobile gaming (and you) to new levels. It’s You vs. the world - only the strongest can survive! ◈◈◈ #1 top game globally with 200 million+ games played ◈◈◈ Plague Inc. is a global hit with over half a million 5 star ratings and features in newspapers such as The Economist, New York Post, Boston Herald, The Guardian and London Metro! The developer of Plague Inc. was invited to speak at the CDC in Atlanta about the disease models inside the game! ▶ “The game creates a compelling world that engages the public on serious public health topics” – The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention ▶ “Best Tablet Game of 2012” - New York Daily News ▶ “Plague Inc. will snag your attention in all the right ways and keep it there” - Touch Arcade ▶ “No denying Plague Inc.'s high-level of quality” - Modojo ▶ “Plague Inc. should not be as much fun as it is” – London Metro ▶ “Will leave you hoping to destroy the world, all in the name of a bit of fun” – Pocket Lint ▶ “Plague Inc.'s gameplay is infectious” - Slide to Play ▶ Winner – “Overall Game of the Year” – Pocket Gamer ▶ “Killing billions has never been so fun” – IGN ◈◈◈ Features: ● Stunning retina graphics with a highly polished interface (Contagion guaranteed) ● Highly detailed, hyper-realistic world with advanced AI (Outbreak management) ● Comprehensive in-game help and tutorial system (I am Legendarily helpful) ● 12 different disease types with radically different strategies to master (12 Monkeys?) ● Full Save/Load functionality (28 Saves Later!) ● 50+ countries to infect, hundreds of traits to evolve and thousands of world events to adapt to (Pandemic evolved) ● Full game support for scoreboards and achievements ● Expansion updates add the mind controlling Neurax Worm, the zombie producing Necroa Virus, Speed Runs and real life Scenarios! Localised in English, German, Spanish, Brazilian Portuguese, Italian, French, Japanese, Korean and Russian. (more coming soon) P.S. Give yourself a pat on the back if you got all the themed literature references! Special sale price to celebrate being the 15th most popular iPhone game of 2012! ◈◈◈ Like Plague Inc. on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/PlagueInc Follow me on Twitter: www.twitter.com/NdemicCreations</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7482_01_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple4/v4/c6/84/df/c684dff6-848a-0976-120b-566b67dbd5bc/mzl.fqjfaebw.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7482-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7482_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:25:49">http://www.games.com/game/popcap/bejeweled-hd</link><title>Bejeweled HD</title><description>This app offers in-app purchases. You may disable in-app purchasing using your device settings. See http://support.apple.com/kb/HT4213 for more info. It’s the biggest, brightest Bejeweled ever! Discover all-new ways to play the world’s #1 puzzle game! Find your perfect match with 6 breathtaking game modes. Ease into Classic Bejeweled for cascades of fun, test your gem-swapping ability with Lightning, save Butterflies from a hungry spider, dig into Diamond Mine for a gem-blasting challenge, slip into Zen for a revolutionary way to relax, or make Pairs, Flushes, Full Houses and more in the new Poker mode. And collect flashy Bejeweled badges and achievements as you soar to dazzling new heights in the Game Center leaderboards! “Bejeweled — perhaps the most insanely addictive puzzle game ever.” —Games Magazine Game Features: ARE YOU FAST AS LIGHTNING? Test your gem-swapping ability in a race against time. CLASSIC GEM-MATCHING FUN Play the most popular puzzle game of the century with powerful new gems. DIG INTO DIAMOND MINE Blast gems to collect gold, diamonds and buried artifacts before the clock runs out. RELAX IN ZEN MODE Customize sights and sounds to create your own relaxing retreat. SAVE THE BUTTERFLIES! Match gems to free the butterflies before they move up the board where a hungry spider awaits! GO ALL-IN WITH POKER Make poker hands with gem matches, including Pairs, 3 of a Kind, Full House, 4 of a Kind, Flushes and more! CREATE FOUR SPECIAL GEMS Create electrifying special gems like Flame gems, Star gems, Hypercubes and Supernova gems! PROVE YOUR GEM-MATCHING PROWESS Earn flashy Bejeweled badges and Game Center achievements to prove your multifaceted skills! CLIMB THE WORLD RANKS Compete against the world and your friends in Game Center leaderboards for the top score! MORE COOL FEATURES Fantastic retina display graphics — Bejeweled is more sparkling than ever before! Ultra-Smooth Action — Make multiple matches while new gems fall into place. Hints on Demand — Can't quite spot the next match? Use the "Hint" button for a quick tip. Stats Galore — Gloat over your scores for total matched gems, all-time best moves and top 10 personal bests in Classic and Diamond Mine! Support for More Languages — You can now enjoy Bejeweled in French, Italian, German and Spanish! PLEASE NOTE: Bejeweled has ultra-awesome graphics, so you’ll need a 3rd generation (16GB or more) or later iPod touch, iPhone 3GS, iPhone 4/4S to play or iPad 3 or above. Please make sure your device is compatible prior to download. Blitz mode will open a separate, free Bejeweled Blitz App. This app contains direct links to the Internet that can take players away from the game with the ability to browse any Web page. More Apps from PopCap: PLANTS VS. ZOMBIES™ 2 — The sequel is here: meet, greet and defeat legions of zombies from the dawn of time to the end of days! PLANTS VS. ZOMBIES™ — Soil your plants in the award-winning action-strategy game ZUMA’S REVENGE!™ — Take on the tikis in this ball-blasting challenge! PEGGLE® — Clear the orange pegs in this epic blend of luck and skill. BOOKWORM® — Feed your appetite for fun in THE brain-tickling word puzzle game. POPCAP MAKES LIFE FUN! Visit us at PopCap.com Follow us at twitter.com/PopCap Like us at facebook.com/PopCap Bejeweled Support Application License Agreement EA may retire online features and services after 30 days’ notice posted on www.ea.com/1/service-updates Important Consumer Information: This App: Contains advertisements for EA and its partners; collects data through third party analytics technology (see Privacy &amp; Cookie Policy for details); EA may retire online features and services after 30 days’ notice posted on www.ea.com/1/service-updates; contains direct links to social networking sites intended for an audience over 13; contains direct links to the Internet. ©2014 Electronic Arts Inc. Bejeweled and PopCap are trademarks of Electronic Arts Inc.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7482_02_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/cd/89/2f/cd892fc2-957f-5ce7-0715-9256e26bd62a/mzl.abrqamuo.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7482-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7482_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:26:28">http://www.games.com/game/warner-bros/scribblenauts-remix</link><title>Scribblenauts Remix</title><description>►►Scribblenauts Remix now has over 4 million players! Get it now!.◄◄ ►►If you purchased the World Pass or Avatars and can't find them after the update, just use the “Restore DLC” button in Options to get them back - you will NOT be charged for them again! ◄◄ THINK IT! CREATE IT! SOLVE IT! The award-winning, best-selling video game is now available for the iPhone, iPod touch and iPad. Help Maxwell acquire the Starite by creating any object, bringing it to life and using it to solve each challenge. Let your imagination run wild in this groundbreaking puzzle game. Summon to life a ‘colossal, winged car’ or a ‘shy, frost-breathing, robotic hippopotamus’! If you can think it, you can create it. It’s the perfect game for the casual player looking for fun and extensive replay with unlimited solutions and different outcomes. Or, the Scribblenauts fan wanting the complete Maxwell experience. Whether you’re 9 or 90, the only limit is your imagination! ============================================================================ And, the critics love it! &gt; “Editors’ Choice Award” – IGN.com &gt; “A work of utter genius.” – Touch Arcade &gt; “A brilliant game.” – Wired.com &gt; “Fits splendidly into the iOS catalog.” – The Daily &gt; “4/4 Stars. A highly recommended puzzle game for all ages.” – USA Today ============================================================================ FEATURES: CLASSIC GAMEPLAY 50 levels to play! Includes 40 of the most popular levels from Scribblenauts and Super Scribblenauts plus 10 original levels exclusive to Remix. WORLD PASS Purchase a World Pass and receive all current and future world expansions - 90 extra levels and counting! If you previously purchased a world expansion, you’re automatically upgraded to a World Pass and all future worlds will now automatically appear in your game for free. PLAYABLE AVATARS Re-live Scribblenauts by playing as a different character from in the game. Try out the feature with the free Lifeguard and God avatars! SCRIBBLE PICS Post images of your playground creations and puzzle solutions to Facebook and Twitter and share them with your friends! SCRIBBLE SPEAK – EXCLUSIVELY FOR SIRI ENABLED DEVICES Use the keyboard microphone icon to create objects using only your voice! UNLIMITED FUN Enter the Playground to create objects to your heart’s content, playing and interacting in a true sandbox! GOLD CROWNING LEVELS Engage in endless replayability (and earn a Gold Crown for your troubles!) by solving a puzzle multiple times using different words. PLAY ON MULTIPLE DEVICES Use iCloud to seamlessly switch between the iPad, iPhone and iPod touch without ever having to restart your game. INNOVATIVE USER INTERFACE Use the “shake to undo” function to remove created objects simply by shaking your Apple device. CREATE AND SHARE Use Game Center to check out the leaderboard to see how your score ranks and to compare game achievements with friends. You can also post game statistics to your Facebook and Twitter profiles. GIFT THE APP Give the gift of Maxwell to your friends and family! Create what you want and see what happens! Hang out with Maxwell! &gt; VISIT Maxwell: www.scribblenauts.com &gt; LIKE Maxwell: www.facebook.com/ScribblenautsVideoGame &gt; FOLLOW Maxwell: http://twitter.com/ScribbleMaxwell Requirements for Scribblenauts: \- iPhone 3GS, iPhone 4, iPhone 4S, iPhone 5 \- iPod touch 3rd generation (32GB and 64GB models only), \- iPod touch 4th generation \- iPod touch 5th generation \- All iPads</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7482_03_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple6/v4/f4/42/be/f442be41-1e2c-b389-e4a4-b16ea47909e7/mzl.vvlbbuke.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7482-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7482_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:28:23">http://www.games.com/game/app-minis/design-this-home</link><title>Design This Home</title><description>The most popular home design game in the world with 7,000,000 players! Over 200,000 five star reviews and #1 around the globe! **DESIGN YOUR DREAM HOME!** Have you ever wanted to build, design and decorate your perfect dream home? Now you can in App Minis’ latest game, Design This Home™! Become a superstar designer as you decorate and expand your house! Customize every element of your home: arrange furniture, put up cabinets, paint the walls, renovate the floors and more - anything is possible in Design This Home™! Increase your home's value and collect income from your residents - the nicer the home, the more cash and XP you'll earn! **YOUR HOME - YOUR STYLE** Incredible variety! Choose from different styles ranging from modern, traditional, country, Southwestern, European, Asian, Victorian and many more! Over 700 items to customize your house with! No other game in the App Store has this much variety! **DREAM IT, BUILD IT** Your creativity shouldn't be constrained to a single space - you have an entire house to decorate to your heart's content. Customize your residents, share your house with your friends, clean and fix up your home, and earn rewards by completing tasks. In Design This Home™, there really is no place like home! FEATURES: \- Over 700 items - the largest home design game in the App Store \- Expertly crafted high-quality retina art and animation \- Customize every aspect of your home, from the floors to the walls and everything else! \- Nine full-sized rooms to construct and decorate \- Choose from six beautiful floor plans! \- Own multiple homes! \- Add your friends as your house residents \- Frequent updates, new items, seasonal decorations, tasks, and more \- Intuitive and easy to play for all ages \- Universal app - play on either your iPhone, iPod Touch or iPad! \- Share your home with your friends over Facebook, Twitter and email *NOTE: DTH has a minimum requirement of iOS 4.0 and an iPhone 3GS, iPod touch 3G (16gb/32gb), or iPad* _______________________________________ Design This Home is an ever-expanding game with new content planned regularly. FUTURE FREE UPDATES: New items, new residents, new floor plans, gardens and landscaping, neighbors, monthly contests and more! We want to hear from you! What would like to see in Design This Home? Let us know by reviewing the game or visiting our website! Design This Home™ is free to play and also offers in-game currency that can be purchased. If you would like to prevent yourself or others from making purchases, please turn off In-App purchasing in your device settings. __________________________</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7482_04_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/c6/78/8b/c6788b62-5341-d3b3-a720-c46eb3440669/mzl.gosolwdh.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7482-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7482_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:29:10">http://www.games.com/game/sporcle/word-ladder</link><title>Word Ladder</title><description>NEW FREE GAME EVERYDAY! iPhone, iPod Touch and iPad! Climb to new heights of word play with the Word Ladder app from the wildly popular and addictive trivia quiz website Sporcle.com. First popularized by Lewis Carroll, a word ladder is solved by altering a single letter in a chain of clues. With a new puzzle every day, Word Ladder from Sporcle is a word lover's dream come true. __________________________ FEATURES NEW FUN EVERY DAY FOR FREE! Play a new word ladder quiz that is pushed to your device every day. The fun never stops! PLAY ANYWHERE, ON ANY DEVICE Network access is not required to play, so have fun while on the train or in the middle of the woods. Word Ladder is optimized for iPhone, iPod Touch, and iPad, so play with any device! SHOW OFF YOUR SMARTS Log in to share your scores on Facebook and Sporcle.com. Earn Knowledge Stars and compete with your friends and the world through GameCenter. PLAY AGAIN AND AGAIN TO IMPROVE YOUR SCORE Track your improvement with your saved play history. See which games you’ve played and your best scores. BUY A GAME PACK TO INCREASE THE FUN Don’t want to wait until tomorrow for a new quiz? Buy a game pack and have fun for hours! __________________________ CHECK OUT OTHER SPORCLE GAMES Sporcle Missing Word Mixed Word Minute Morsel ___________________________ MORE GAMES ON THE WEB AT http://www.sporcle.com Be the first to know about new games, updates, contests, and more… LIKE US on Facebook: http://facebook.com/sporcle FOLLOW US on Twitter: http://twitter.com/sporcle VISIT our Blog: http://sporcle.com/blog</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7482_05_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple6/v4/9c/e7/f9/9ce7f9ab-e31d-13ac-e4e6-0293ae1bf958/mzl.ozbfdkhn.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7482-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7482_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:30:27">http://www.games.com/game/kwiqapps/balloony-word</link><title>Balloony Word</title><description>✭ Everybody likes to play Hangman but you may feel a little uncomfortable with the idea of 'hanging' a man to guess a few words. Then Balloony Word is for you! ✭ Balloony Word is a family-friendly educational game that helps anyone practice and broaden their vocabulary skills. You will discover Dolch sight words, animal and fruit names, grade appropriate common words, elementary science terms and much more, while having fun popping a few balloons along the way! NOTE: access to word list is only available in Balloony Word Pro. ✭ By popular demand, this game is changed to FREE supported by Ads. For ads-free version, check out "Balloony Word Pro". ✭ ✭✭✭✭✭ What Our Users Are Saying "Cute and endless fun" - User Review. "This is a cute game that will keep your spelling skills sharp" - CrystalsMom "I had fun playing it along with kids" - mecinply Download the only word guessing game that is radically new and fun! After playing Balloony Word Pro, you won't want to touch any other Hangman games out there. ✭ The Game is suited for adults of all ages and kids with keen spelling interests. You can play this game alone or with your loved ones. Whether it is a quick five minutes game time after dinner or half hour play time with your kids cuddled on the sofa, you will surely have fun together and learn something new. When you need a little bit of challenge, change the word list dictionary. THE STORY Gordon the Gorilla and Kendra the Kangaroo Need Your Help! Gordon the Gorilla and Kendra the Kangaroo are happily floated in the air by twenty six balloons, with one letter on each balloon. For each word presented, you will have only seven chances to make the correct guess by tapping on the balloons. If you make a wrong tap, the balloon will pop. So be very careful, you don't want to send the cute Kangaroo or Gorilla crashing onto the ground! THE FEATURES • Pickup and Play - you will launch straight into the play mode without any game menu to get in the way. • Themes - two themes featuring the lovely Kendra and Gordon. • Original Music - created specifically for the game. • Settings - of course you can change the kind of words that will be presented to you to guess. [only available in Balloony Word Pro] • Secret Feature - well this is a 'secret' but we will give you a hint. It's a life saver when you are stuck! But be careful because it will pop your balloons too. ✭✭✭✭✭✭✭✭✭✭✭✭ Your 5-star iTunes rating and reviews help us develop more great Apps. * Connect with other word game fans: http://facebook.com/ipadwordgames * Checkout More Apps By us: http://www.kwiqapps.com * Follow us on Twitter @kwiqapps for updates and time-sensitive promotions. Send us your feedback!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7482_06_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/ef/32/fe/ef32fe67-fda0-3e39-05c2-688b1f643dd7/mzl.hydgwtgd.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7482-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7482_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:31:27">http://www.games.com/game/lomah-studios-pty/rip-curl-surfing-game</link><title>Rip Curl Surfing Game</title><description>There is no other surfing game like this on the iPhone! Created by international surfing company Rip Curl and creative agency LOMAH Studios. ★★★★★ "The graphics on this game are surprisingly good for a mobile app." \- Editor, Surfline Reviews. ★★★★★ "After just a few minutes playing with Rip Curl’s iPhone game I can wholeheartedly say it… Rip Curl’s got game." http://www.livethesearchgame.com/ \-------------------------------- Rip Curl's "Live The Search: The Ultimate Surfing Game" THE GAME "Live The Search" is the first high-end 3D surfing game to hit the iPhone and combines high-action arcade game-play with a realistic surfing experience. Travel the world searching out secret waves and surfing as ASP World Champions Mick Fanning or put yourself in the game by creating a unique surfer. Progress your way through the game by completing goals, unlocking trips and taking on other objectives. THE STAR Mick Fanning: Two-time ASP World Champion and Australian sporting icon Mick Fanning is one of the most famous and popular surfers on the planet. Mick has been on “The Search” with Rip Curl since he was a young teenager and loves to escape the gruel of competitive surfing every chance he gets. Mick is sponsored by: Rip Curl, Red Bull, Reef, Dragon, DHD, Creatures Of Leisure, Vertra, Skullcandy, FCS fins. www.mickfanning.com.au www.twitter.com/mick_fanning "I’m a big iPhone and iPad geek so it’s great having a surfing app. It's the perfect game to kill down time." - Mick Fanning (2 x ASP World Champion) "The Search concept is such a big part of Rip Curl's culture and I'm glad we decided to focus on this for the game - traveling the world in search of perfect waves is what surfing is all about..." - Mick Fanning (2 x ASP World Champion) THE SEARCH Surfing is a lifestyle. For many it’s a way of life. It’s the chance to explore the world and chase adventure. The opportunity to experience the unknown, seek something new, discover the undiscovered and search for fun most only dream of… THE GAMEPLAY Tilt Movement: Live The Search utilizes the iPhone's "Tilt Movement" accelerometer technology, allowing the player to control the movement of your surfer by tilting the iPhone left or right. Tilting to the right will make your surfer turn right and tilting left will turn them left - both on the face of the wave and above the lip when performing airs. Swipe Controller: While many iPhone games use up-down-left-right controller pads, Live The Search features a high-tech swipe controller, which holds the key to performing airs and making turns on a wave. Use your finger to make directed swipes on screen to perform maneuvers, such as cutbacks on the wave and grabs and flips in the air. Stall &amp; Floater Buttons: On the left of the screen are the stall and floater buttons, which help position you in the right spot on the wave when you're lining up for a big maneuver. The Stall button will slow you down on the wave and help positioning. The Floater button will help you float the lip of the wave with your board when you're riding high and close to the barrel. ★★★★★ "5 Stars" "The graphics are smooth with very few glitches. Stoked!!!" \- Editor, Surfline Reviews. ★★★★★ "If you’re looking for an i-device surfing game that’s fun and has high replay value, Rip Curl’s Live The Search is best in class and worth every penny." \- Editor, Daily Stoke Reviews.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7482_07_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/81/c4/e0/mzi.uztlhtkf.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7482-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7482_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:32:48">http://www.games.com/game/owlchemy-labs/jack-lumber</link><title>Jack Lumber</title><description>Use the supernatural powers of Jack Lumber to massacre the forest and make Granny proud in this time-warping line-drawing log-slicing pun-filled lumberjacking mashup from Owlchemy Labs! Jack Lumber is ‘Poplar’ With the Press! 4 out of 4, A Must Have! "Between the excellent art style, goofy humor, and enjoyable gameplay, Jack Lumber is as lovable as its rugged hero. It's the stuff of App Store legends." \- Andrew Podolsky | Slide to Play G4 GAME OF THE WEEK! "...A funny (and solid!) story, hilarious power-ups, and non-intrusive IAP. Jack Lumber is an easy shoe-in for one of this year’s best iOS games." \- Ashley Esqueda | G4 'Knuckle Up' 148Apps EDITOR'S CHOICE! "Jack Lumber is completely ridiculous and I love it. It’s easy to pick up and play, has plenty of laughs, and actually has a great number of levels to go along with it. Put on some flannel, grow out that beard, and chop some wood." \- Carter Dotson | 148Apps "The addition of super-hard four-star scores and difficulty-upping beards keep the replay value high. Jack Lumber injects a welcome layer of depth and strategy into the casual touch-slicing genre. The title is a great combination of frantic finger action and smart combo scoring." \- Justin Davis | IGN "Axe-identally in love; funny and addictive, and has tremendous respect for the player. Jack Lumber is quirky, stylized, and unlike anything on iOS." \- Chris Plante | The Verge A LUMBERJACK WITH AN AXE TO GRIND A tree killed his granny and now he is out for revenge. Meet Jack Lumber, the superhuman lumberjack who hates trees, loves animals, and hates trees. Did we say that twice? The guy really hates trees. Hike the trails of Flapjack Forest, trudge through The Loggers Bog, and ascend Widowmaker’s Peak chopping down every pine, oak, and maple that stands between you and the tree that killed your sweet old granny. SHOW 'EM WHO'S BOSS With one mighty swing of his axe, Jack Lumber sends logs, syrup bottles, explosives, and forest critters flying into the air. Use magic powers to enter LumberTime. With the logs suspended in slow motion, draw a smooth path for Jack’s axe following the grain of every treacherous log. Poke at the adorable forest animals living rent-free in your cabin after you’ve destroyed their homes Raid Granny’s Cupboard! \- Drink Granny’s magical syrups to enhance your powers. \- Intensify the gameplay by equipping challenging new beards \- Spruce up the old cabin with tasteful lumber-decor! \- Turn the forest into sawdust with the finesse and grace that only a burly lumberjack can possess. But be careful not to harm your furry friends. Every level requires timing, skill, logic, and flannel to solve. (Flannel wear not actually required) Unlockable missions, player driven challenges, and inventive power-up combos make it exciting to play this game again and again. OTHER FEATURES: \- Universal support \- GameCenter Leaderboards and Achievements \- Optimized for retina displays on the New iPad, iPhone 4/4S and iPhone 5 \- Social features (seamless Twitter/Facebook integration) Fight the forest and MAKE GRANNY PROUD! ______________________ Check out other games from Owlchemy Labs: Snuggle Truck AaaaaAAaaaAAAaaAAAAaAAAAA!!! (Force = Mass x Acceleration)</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7482_08_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/5c/7b/e6/5c7be6d2-8f41-4958-31af-e4dbab577fdd/mzl.dnkteuon.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7482-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7482_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:34:28">http://www.games.com/game/sporcle/minute-morsel</link><title>Minute Morsel</title><description>NEW FREE GAME EVERYDAY! iPhone, iPod touch and iPad! Only got a minute? Kill your boredom with a quick trivia challenge guaranteed to take a minute or less. Minute Morsel, from the wildly popular and addictive trivia quiz website Sporcle.com, will exercise those trivia muscles with a quick game every day. __________________________ FEATURES NEW FUN EVERY DAY FOR FREE! Play a new morsel that is pushed to your device every day. The fun never stops! PLAY ANYWHERE, ON ANY DEVICE Network access is not required to play, so have fun while on the train or in the middle of the woods. Minute Morsel is optimized for iPhone, iPod Touch, and iPad, so play with any device! SHOW OFF YOUR SMARTS Log in to share your scores on Facebook and Sporcle.com. Earn Knowledge Stars and compete with your friends and the world through GameCenter. PLAY AGAIN AND AGAIN TO IMPROVE YOUR SCORE Track your improvement with your saved play history. See which games you’ve played and your best scores. BUY A GAME PACK TO INCREASE THE FUN Don’t want to wait until tomorrow for a new quiz? Buy a game pack have fun for hours! __________________________ CHECK OUT OTHER SPORCLE GAMES Sporcle Word Ladder Missing Word Mixed Word ___________________________ MORE GAMES ON THE WEB AT http://www.sporcle.com Be the first to know about new games, updates, contests, and more… LIKE US on Facebook: http://facebook.com/sporcle FOLLOW US on Twitter: http://twitter.com/sporcle VISIT our Blog: http://sporcle.com/blog</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7482_09_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/b9/ff/08/b9ff0849-3f07-7d98-6b3d-c140f0cf0852/mzl.nahqfdpi.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7482-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7482_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:36:09">http://www.games.com/game/giggleup-kids-apps-and-educational-games-pty/farm-jigsaw-puzzles-123-free-for-ipad-fun-learning-puzzle-game-for-kids</link><title>Farm Jigsaw Puzzles 123 Free for iPad - Fun Learning Puzzle Game for Kids</title><description>\-- Featured in Apple's New &amp; Noteworthy and What's Hot. \- BRILLIANTLY HAND-DRAWN INTERACTIVE JIGSAW PUZZLES FOR YOUNG LEARNERS! \+ Perfect for helping young children to develop logical thinking and learn simple words. \+ Includes 52 jigsaw puzzles in 8 different beautiful farm scenes and comes with 5 difficulty levels to choose from. \+ Animation and encouraging feedback makes solving puzzles an enjoyable and rewarding experience. \+ Play Farm Jigsaw Puzzles 123 in more languages! Have fun learning new words in different languages including: English, French, Spanish, Japanese, German, Swedish, Russian, Dutch, Portuguese, Norwegian, Danish, Korean, Chinese and Italian. \----- “It’s definitely nice to have one puzzle app that works for my toddler and my six year old!” - The iPhone Mom “[The creators] raise the bar with elements such as encouraging feedback with adorable animations to help encourage your child in solving their puzzles.” - The iPhone App Review, rated 5/5 stars “Very content-rich...kids can be kept busy with this delightful app for quite some time.” - GiggleApps \----- This fun and education app was developed to suit the tastes and learning abilities of young children from ages 1 to 6. Start with simple 2-piece puzzles (great for infants and toddlers) and gradually move up the levels to master the 16-piece puzzles. When one puzzle is completed, the name of the animal will be spelled on the screen and read aloud. Watch the farm come to life with color when all the puzzles are completed. Cute animals and playful animations are sure to make this puzzle game a favourite pastime for kids. This app will help your child excel in the following areas: \- Problem Solving \- Logical and cognitive skills \- Concentration \- Memory \- Linguistic skills Farm Jigsaw Puzzles 123 Featuring: \- 8 beautiful farm scenes including: \+ Happy Farm \+ The Veggie Patch \+ Piggy’s Mud Playground \+ Rainbow Creek \+ Farm Babies \+ Old Farmer Joe and Friends \+ The Barn and \+ Goodnight Farm! \- 52 puzzles to be solved \- 5 difficulty levels, ranging from 2-piece puzzles to 16-piece puzzles \- Easy to use interface specifically designed for young children \- Light and cheerful music \- Interactive animation for even more fun \- A hint on/off feature to give optional assistance \- ...more scenes and puzzles coming soon to new versions. For more fun titles from our popular jigsaw series, just search for ‘Jigsaw Puzzles 123’ in the App Store. \-------------- Connect with us! Visit us: http://www.GiggleUp.com Like us: facebook.com/GiggleUpApps Follow us: twitter.com/GiggleUpApps Email us: Support@GiggleUp.com Brought to you by GiggleUp, creators of the award-winning Interactive Telling Time and other educational apps for kids. Our goal is to promote learning through play with the purpose of helping children develop useful learning skills. Our apps have been enjoyed by children and used in classrooms all around the world!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7482_10_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/b8/f2/8b/b8f28b75-f853-c0c0-bcca-ad48a5c13234/mzl.xfdjhutx.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>