<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7483">facebook paying?</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:39:37" name="Games.com" id="FW14-e048"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e048-7483-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7483_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:39:38">http://www.games.com/game/com2us-usa/9-innings-2013-pro-baseball</link><title>9 Innings: 2013 Pro Baseball</title><description>Get ready for the No. 1 baseball game on mobile! It’s back and better than ever- 9 Innings: 2013 Pro Baseball! Officially licensed with the Major League Baseball Players Association (MLBPA)! 9 Innings: 2013 Pro Baseball is the hottest, most realistic baseball simulation game that uses the names, photos, data, and league schedules of real baseball players! Com2uS’s very own player card system uses the photos and stats of over 1,400 baseball players across 30 teams! Enjoy dynamic graphics that will blow you away, and amazingly optimized controls that make it easy for everyone to play! Batter up for the greatest baseball simulation game ever created TODAY! This game is free to play, but you can choose to pay real money for extra items. You can play 9 innings 2013 in English, 한국어, 日本語, 中文简体, 中文繁體. USER REVIEWS: 5/5- “This is probably the best baseball game I’ve played on a phone.” –Ji 5/5- “Real life players, easy controls and lots of fun. Baseball fans, what are you waiting for? Download it now!” –Karan 5/5- “This game has just the right amount of interaction and a lot of options for more control. It is very addicting. I love it!” -Tim FEATURES: Official licensing contract with Major League Baseball Players Association (MLBPA)! \- Uses real data, photos, and stats of 1,400 players on different 30 teams \- Provides latest player data and constant roster updates! \- Standard player and Monster Season players! Unique card development system! \- More varieties in player/cheerleader/equipment cards and a new draw/combination system! \- Trade baseball cards with players from all over the world to complete your card collection! \- Exchange cards and points with friends through the in-game inbox. Easy, fast, and realistic! \- Real graphics, smooth motions and an outstanding game engine! \- Quick gameplay through autoplay (Supports offense and defense only) \- Play against 16 teams through Friendly, League, Home Run Derby and Special modes! \- Carry out over 100 challenges and go for card and point rewards! \- Rookie players can learn the game in a cinch with the easy-to-follow tutorial! This game is the FREE version. To batter up with no ads, download 9 Innings: 2013 Pro Baseball PLUS from the App Store and receive 500 bonus Stars (approximately $4.99 value)! Please note that you need a Hub ID to receive your 500 Stars. Users playing on an unauthorized OS cannot access the Card Market or the Store. More from Com2uS! • Golf Star™ • The World of Magic • Wizcraft • Divine Girls Connect with Com2uS! Follow us on Twitter twitter.com/Com2uS Like us on Facebook! facebook.com/Com2uS For information on new games and special events, check out global.com2us.com!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7483_01_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple4/v4/a9/a8/63/a9a86375-50a8-5f62-2c3f-17e5ad944a75/mzl.oergimpx.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7483-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7483_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:40:29">http://www.games.com/game/gameloft/six-guns</link><title>Six-Guns</title><description>For the first time ever on iPhone and iPad, you can explore a truly enormous and open frontier in a Wild West full of mystery, bandits and more…unnatural enemies. Play it for free: Make your enemies pay! Buck Crosshaw never shot a man who didn’t deserve it, but now he’s an outlaw who had to fake his own death and escape to Arizona. But in escaping one evil, Buck is about to face another, for an ancient and wicked force stirs in the hills of this mysterious region. A WILD FRONTIER Freely explore an open world set in Arizona and Oregon full of events, mystery and challenges for you to discover as you become completely immersed in the story and the action. But don’t be fooled by this land’s beauty - outlaws, vampires &amp; many other unnatural foes lurk in every shadow. ACCEPT THE CHALLENGE Take on 40 missions with a great variety of tasks for you to overcome. You’ll race horses, take out robbers, fend off waves of enemies and more along the way! SADDLE UP In this kill-or-be-killed land, you’ll need to unlock all 8 different horses, 19 weapons and a wide selection of clothes, ammo and other items to help you on your journey. PLAY FOR FREE It costs you nothing to download and play the game to the end! \---- Visit our official site at http://www.gameloft.com Follow us on Twitter at http://glft.co/GameloftonTwitter or like us on Facebook at http://facebook.com/Gameloft to get more info about all our upcoming titles. Check out our videos and game trailers on http://www.youtube.com/Gameloft Discover our blog at http://glft.co/Gameloft_Official_Blog for the inside scoop on everything Gameloft. Certain apps allow you to purchase virtual items within the app and may contain third party advertisements that may redirect you to a third party site.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7483_02_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/cc/3a/92/cc3a92bc-1cb3-2758-9f0b-0a3174c17abe/mzl.tkxnizzb.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7483-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7483_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:43:36">http://www.games.com/game/gameday/doors-rooms</link><title>Doors&amp;Rooms</title><description>※ Delve into the All New Escape Game ※ Don't question why. Just open the doors and escape! Simple yet fatally addictive See through the tricks and find hints for your escape! Never-ending battle of wits against the developers Be careful, though: one mistake can cost you everything. ※※ Features ※※ \- Various themed backgrounds \- Evolving difficulty levels \- Stage expansion through constant updates \- Superior graphic quality never before seen in the Escape genre \- Free Game Coins are given away at certain intervals \- Intuitive UI and inventory \- Absolutely free to play! ※※※ Tips ※※※ \- Don't miss even the slightest detail! Even a scrap of paper can be a hint. \- Obtained items can be examined, dismantled, and compounded for new hints. \- Think outside the box. Sometimes, it pays to follow your gut instinct. \- Use common sense. \- Stay alert and listen. Sometimes, sounds can help you successfully escape. Join Us................................................................. Facebook – www.facebook.com/GamedayGlobal Website – www.mgameday.com Twitter – twitter.com/Gameday_Global .........................................................................</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7483_03_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple6/v4/87/7d/f4/877df4d5-8af6-112b-db45-85fbdb17655e/mzl.fnnbcmyc.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7483-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7483_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:44:17">http://www.games.com/game/glu-games/deer-hunter-challenge</link><title>Deer Hunter Challenge</title><description>NOW WITH MORE WEAPONS, NEW CLOTHES AND NEW STORE ITEMS!! ARE YOU UP TO THE CHALLENGE? The ultimate DEER HUNTER experience has arrived, and it's ALWAYS open season! DEER HUNTER CHALLENGE takes the most popular and realistic hunting franchise to extreme wilderness environments in search of the biggest, most prized game around the world. Go from rookie to master sportsman as your experience level increases, and upgrade to greater weapons, equipment and clothing. The more successful hunt trips you take, the more you'll be able to enhance your hunter's skills. Use the GPS map to track and train your sights on black bear, reindeer, cougars, axis deer, moose and more. Animals' behaviors have never been more true-to-life, so exercise extreme caution as these wilderness inhabitants will sometimes charge right at you! Relive your greatest kills in the interactive trophy room- animals' vitals are recorded as well as bullet trajectory and kill locations. Think you've got what it takes to become a master huntsman? The challenge has been issued... become a hunt legend in DEER HUNTER CHALLENGE. RETINA DISPLAY 3D GRAPHICS Deer Hunter Challenge now has the highest resolution graphics possible on both the iPhone 4 and iPod Touch 4th Gen, along with HD Graphics on the iPad! GAME CENTER Compete against your friends in the global Leaderboards and brag by unlocking all the Achievements! NEW CAREER MODE Earn experience points and become a more skillful hunter PERSONALIZE YOUR HUNTER Earn coins after successful hunts and get clothing and weapon enhancements EXTREME HUNTING LOCATIONS Experience far-flung hunting locations in extreme wilderness environments REALISTIC GUNS Choose from a variety of customizable weapons such as the Bolt Rifle, Shotgun, Crossbow and more! TROPHIES Earn trophies for bagging the biggest game and relive your proudest moments in the Trophy room MINI GAMES Play additional mini-games and bonus rounds FOLLOW US at Twitter - @deerhchallenge facebook.com/deerhunterchallenge Deer Hunter Challenge is free to play, but you can choose to pay real money for some extra items, which will charge your iTunes account. You can disable in-app purchasing by adjusting your device settings.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7483_04_thumb.jpg">http://o1.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/02/39/d5/mzl.parnmntb.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7483-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7483_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:45:50">http://www.games.com/game/gamesys/slots-by-jackpotjoy</link><title>Slots by Jackpotjoy</title><description>***Download the #1 slots experience for FREE today!*** With millions of players and over 35,000 five star reviews worldwide, Slots by Jackpotjoy is the place to enjoy slots on your iPhone or iPad. Spin the reels of our exclusive and original slots and you will feel the thrill of Las Vegas wherever you are for FREE! ► EASY to play, you can start winning in SECONDS! ► Over 35 different slot games and a new slot released every 2 weeks. ► Daily spins and bonus coins means you always have coins to win those JACKPOTS! ► Unique and varied slot features - Cascades, All Pays, 10, 20, 25, 50 &amp; 100 line games, Free Spins, Expanding Wilds, Stacked Symbols and many other innovative features. ► Connect with Facebook to save your progress and share free coins with friends DOWNLOAD NOW IF YOU LOVE SLOTS! WHAT PEOPLE ARE SAYING ABOUT SLOTS BY JACKPOTJOY "Definitely the best slots game I’ve ever played" "Fun, challenging and lot of slots to choose from." "Love it! Bonus games are awesome!" Like us on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/JackpotJoySlots Slots by Jackpotjoy is a slot simulator for entertainment use only. It is free to play, and you can choose to purchase additional coins with in-app transactions.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7483_05_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/ed/be/e3/edbee3ff-2b73-9d29-a967-18e81dd1cd0d/mzl.nxvslcdu.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7483-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7483_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:48:10">http://www.games.com/game/glu-games/contract-killer</link><title>Contract Killer</title><description>NOW WITH NEW DAILY CO-OP CHALLENGES, NEW WEAPONS: DUAL WIELD &amp; THE MACHINE GUN, NEW GEAR: CYBERNETIC SCOPE &amp; ULTRASOUND EMITTER, NEW MISSION TYPE: TEST OUT THE BEST WEAPONS, DAILY DEALS AND NEW ACHIEVEMENTS!! They might call you an enforcer, or an assassin. Call it what you like - you're a CONTRACT KILLER. Pulled into a world of bounty hunters, mobsters and criminals, you must check in with your contacts and accept SECRET MISSIONS that only you can handle. Select your WEAPON OF CHOICE from an inventory of sniper rifles, assault rifles and machine guns. Locate your target, zoom in, take aim and GO FOR THE HEADSHOT to earn cold hard cash. You might eliminate a crime boss and escape without being spotted, or you might walk straight into an AMBUSH... WELCOME TO CENTRAL CITY Prepare for your mission and then jump into one of many vantage points within 5 gritty 3D locations UNLIMITED MISSIONS 17 Story Missions and unlimited Random Missions provide cash, XP and lots of action DEADLY WEAPONS 20 distinct weapons including handguns, sniper rifles, machine guns and assault rifles ALIVE OR DEAD Use the Tranquilizer Gun to capture your target or put them down... permanently FOLLOW US at Twitter @glumobile facebook.com/ContractKillerGlu The Glu Assassins are always shooting to make sure we keep Contract Killer locked-&amp;-loaded full of free content and new features. Previous updates include: New weapons New Game Center Achievements Easy weapon swap and reload Contract Killer is free to play, but you can choose to pay real money for some extra items, which will charge your iTunes account. You can disable in-app purchasing by adjusting your device settings.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7483_06_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/37/1b/0f/371b0fe2-d94f-3225-f1ca-82c4cabcfd23/mzm.vbpvpnud.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7483-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7483_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:51:19">http://www.games.com/game/fluik/office-jerk</link><title>Office Jerk</title><description>There's a Jerk in every office. A know-it-all, overachiever who comes in early, stays late and kisses up to the boss. Exact revenge on “that guy” with Office Jerk: grab whatever you can find, and hurl it at him! The Office Jerk can only take so much - find out how much by throwing: * Laptop (NEW ITEM) * Fire Extinguisher (NEW ITEM) * Cheesy Button * Snappy Mouse Trap * “Joe” the boss from Kick The Boss 2 * Leather Racing Glove * Garden Gnome (cameo appearance from Streaker Run) * Nice, Blue Water balloon * Suction Cup Dart - Always Classic, Always Funny * Stick O' Dynamite * Agitated, Honey-Filled Bee Hive * Shiny Red Stapler * Crumpled Piece of Paper ...and a whole bunch more, plus mystery items! And we're adding new items all the time. Don't just sit back and take it: pay it back. Grab whatever feels right, and fling it at his head or shoulder - or go right for the face! Tap the desk organizer and see what other items you can rain down on that office meanie. Finally wipe that smirk off his face, in this feel-good app from Fluik Entertainment. &gt; Hit the Jerk with 45+ items &gt; Unlock hilarious reactions for each item &gt; Discover tons of environment interactions &gt; Master the Office Jerk checklist &gt; Earn Daily Rewards &gt; Complete Daily Challenges &gt; Achievements Galore! “Way funny, I love to wipe the smile off that jerks face!” “Makes you want to throw things at people you work with and compare reactions!” “Who can resist blowing off some steam by picking on the office jerk!??? Very enjoyable.” Play Office Jerk today! “Like” Office Jerk on Facebook - https://www.facebook.com/OfficeJerk Get FREE in-game Coins when Office Jerk gets 100,000 “Likes” on Facebook! ___________________________ Office Jerk is brought to you by Fluik Entertainment, makers of wicked-fun mobile games such as Grumpy Bears, Plumber Crack and Streaker Run. Search the App Store for “Fluik” to browse all our games. Follow @FluikGames on Twitter for awesome game announcements and other updates. NOTE: To help keep Office Jerk awesome, please send any bug reports or suggestions directly to us, instead of posting them in your app reviews. We can't respond directly to app reviews, so it's hard for us to help you with your problem or issue. You can post all your bugs or suggestions on the Facebook fan page, https://www.facebook.com/OfficeJerk, or email them to us at support@fluik.com</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7483_07_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/23/4c/40/234c40ed-2538-4d4e-d35c-9b70891ec289/mzl.rnqqlqie.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7483-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7483_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:52:12">http://www.games.com/game/glu-games/contract-killer-zombies</link><title>Contract Killer: Zombies</title><description>MAJOR UPDATE: New Helicopter missions, new guns and new zombies!!! You have killed more criminals than you can count. Now it’s time to face the apocalypse and blow the crap out of thousands of zombies! From the team that brought you Contract Killer comes CONTRACT KILLER: ZOMBIES. “Today is just another day. Since the horde came we’ve been lucky to see tomorrow. Came up fast, out of nowhere. Zombies! Walking dead meat. I just kill ‘em… and keep on killin’ em. I’m not a hero… just trying to survive. They call me “Shooter”, because that’s what I do. Shooting zombies is the only thing I’m good at… and I’m good. DAMN good.” Save the remnants of humanity by infiltrating the zombie-infested city, stocking up on supplies, rescuing civilians and ushering them to safety while slaughtering every zombie in your path! EXPLODING ZOMBIE BRAINS is just about the best fun you can have these days! HELP THE SURVIVORS and assist Evelyn as she goes on supply runs and special missions. Build up an arsenal of AWESOME ZOMBIE KILLING WEAPONS and gear including sniper rifles, assault guns and grenade launchers! Take aim and collect bonuses for HEADSHOTS and MULTI-KILLS! FOLLOW US at Twitter @glumobile facebook.com/glumobile Contract Killer: Zombies is free to play, but you can choose to pay real money for some extra items, which will charge your iTunes account. You can disable in-app purchasing by adjusting your device settings.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7483_08_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/83/0b/b5/830bb5a0-7844-6efd-74c9-d1166fcd0b47/mzm.uylmqwxj.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7483-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7483_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:54:02">http://www.games.com/game/drop-d-studios/tap-studio-3</link><title>Tap Studio 3</title><description>Create, Play and Share song taps for all of the popular artists with your own music! Taps for Beyonce, Lady Gaga, Justin Beiber, Katy Perry, Coldplay, Bruno Mars, LMFAO, FUN., Metallica, Eminem, Owl City, Drake, Nicki Minaj, PSY and many many more! With over 5 million downloads, Tap Studio is the most popular series of games for creating and sharing song taps on iOS! Do you love Tap games? What if you could tap ANY song you own? What if you could make your own taps and share them with all your friends? What if you could access a Tap Vault of over 400,000 song taps for an amazing variety of songs, from todays hottest artists to some of the strangest music you can imagine, with more added every day? And all for free! "I was a huge fan of tap tap revenge 2, the only bad part is the fact that they didn't have a wide selection of any music, let alone my genre (metal). I've had my iPhone for about 3 months now, and this is without a doubt my favorite app out of all of them. It must be otherwise I wouldn't have took the time to write this review. It's free, take advantage of it, I would GLADLY pay 2.99 up to 5.99 for this game &lt;3" - Josh Tap Studio 3 features: ■ Create and play and share taps for all the music on your iPod touch, iPhone or iPad ■ Edit your taps until they are perfect ■ Powerups! ■ Take high scores to a new level with powerups that save you from missed taps, increase your multiplier up to 16x and more! ■ Access the Tap Vault containing user submitted taps for nearly any song imaginable! See details such as high scores and ratings with comments! ■ Tap Vault Library tab will automatically find highly rated song taps in the Tap Vault that match the music in your library ■ Browse the Tap Vault by Featured, Most Popular, Highest Rated, Most Recent or perform an easy Search with suggestions as you type ■ Game Center integration with achievements and global leader boards! ■ Play with up to 3 of your friends with Multiplayer through Game Center! ■ Full retina and iPhone 5 / 4" iPod touch support ■ Choose from a variety of play skins with different graphics in portrait or landscape orientations ■ 3 and 4 rail recording and playback in all game play skins ■ Album artwork is part of the game play background in some play skins ■ Share your best taps with your friends and all the world ■ Send and receive Tap Challenges. Beat your friends high scores ■ Adjustable difficulty level setting that controls the playback speed ■ Facebook and Twitter integration so you can share your high scores Tap Studio 3 users rock! Keep the good reviews coming and we'll keep the updates coming! Thank you for your support. Visit us on Facebook: http://facebook.com/dropdstudios Follow us on Twitter: http://twitter.com/dropdstudios ■ PLEASE NOTE that we do not store songs on our database, nor do we facilitate the sharing of songs. Tap Studio PRO simply uploads and downloads the tap data. Each user is required to have their own copy of the matching song on their device. ■ Tap Studio 3 matches song taps to songs by an exact match of song name, album name, and album artist name. If there is not an exact match found on your device, you will be given the option to purchase the song from iTunes (if available), or to browse your library to manually match the song. Be sure to choose the correct song or your taps may not line up properly!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7483_09_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple6/v4/36/80/23/368023e7-fd5b-ee13-f8c5-9ac93d2e2e19/mzl.uyxgylep.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7483-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7483_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:57:46">http://www.games.com/game/istom-games-kft/nyan-cat-lost-in-space</link><title>Nyan Cat: Lost In Space</title><description>** The most popular and most appreciated Nyan Cat game on iPhone/iPad! "Awesome!" - prguitarman, author of the original Nyan Cat character WARNING! The Nyan Cat game and music are seriously addictive! Play with Nyan Cat only at your own risk! iTunes reviews (US and UK): "Best, game, EVAR!" - Jamiejdjdjdjdj "This is the beat of the nyan cat games" - Crazyboy4826 "This game is pro!" - Oseycyhycyg "I can't stop playing this Nyantastic game" - Rossw123 "cute game thats fun to play! love the art style &amp; glad it's universal! dont like cats, but i DO love this game!" - Starscream1017 In Lost In Space, you can do all these pure awesomeness: Play with the most celebrated flying cat in human history. Drink milk, eat ice-cream, collect coins, buy gorgeous boosts, fly like a superhero (sorry... supercat), jump onto platforms made of cake, avoid angry dogs, and discover the infinite space. And that's not all, you can choose from multiple game modes, where you can play with Nyan Cat's evil foe Tac Nayn, learn to fly on different planets with Nyan Wings or visit parallel universes. If you're tired, you can even train and feed your own Nyanagotchi. Oh, and last but not least: you can enjoy the wonderful Nyan-song as many times as you want! All this funky stuff can't be missed. Or... Wait! Did I mentioned that we pay for you to play? Features for Humans: \- tasty COLLECTABLES (energy drinks, donuts and more) \- crazy POWERUPS (rockets, bubbles and more) \- freaky POWERDOWNS (dynamites, flashlights and more) \- evil ENEMIES (dogs, UFOs and more) \- leaderboards &amp; ACHIEVEMENTS (Game Center) \- stunning boost ITEMS (score miltiplier, shield and more) \- 5 GAME MODES, including Nyan Wings \- NYANAGOTCHI room: keep your Nyan happy to earn gifts! The happier he is the quicker you get your prize. \- Game Days - an opportunity to get a lot of coins for FREE - we pay for you to play! \- different background THEMES (Halloween, Xmas and more) \- different forms of NYAN CAT (Supernyan, Zombienyan, and more) \- TAC NAYN \- universal app (supports iPad/iPhone/iPhone4/iPod) \- twitter and facebook integration \- iCloud backup \- unlocked themes and skin packs are synchronised between your devices via iCloud \- child mode \- nyan nyan nyan nyan NYAN nyan (nyan, nyan and more) Features for Nyans: nyan nyan nyan nyan POWERUPS nyan nyan nyan ACHIEVEMENTS nyan nyan SUPERNYAN nyan ONLINE HIGH SCORES nyan nyan RETINA DISPLAY nyan nyan nyan UNIVERSAL APP nyan BEAUTIFUL PIXEL ART nyan nyan nyan Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/IstomGames Official Nyan Cat fan page: http://www.facebook.com/NyanCatWorld</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7483_10_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/04/ac/e3/04ace35d-17f4-d1f5-b696-fcb23161e727/mzl.sbuyzuiv.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>