<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7499">gold price</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:34:14" name="Games.com" id="FW14-e048"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e048-7499-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7499_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:34:15">http://www.games.com/game/great-world-games/jokers-crown-video-slot-game</link><title>Jokers Crown Video Slot Game</title><description>"Jokers Crown" is a Joker themed, 5x3 Video Slot Game featuring bet-able reels that allow up to 243 ways to pay. Each reel allows a maximum bet of 5 credits, which yields a maximum total bet of 150 credits when all reels are live. The Joker is featured throughout the base and bonus game. She multiplies any win by 2, 3, or 5X! Consecutive Jokers multiply the action! The bonus is a "complete the hand" card game with Jokers "Wild". Try to hit the Royal Flush or 5 of a Kind! All of our games use real math and true industry standard random number generation for maximum Las Vegas excitement. Priced at less than one "max bet spin" at your local casino slot machine, you will truly enjoy the exciting experience offered by this game. This is a follow on to our wildly successful slot game "Buffalo Gold" which is sold separately. This game is a "for fun" multi-denomination game with 1 cent, 2 cent, 5 cent, 25 cent, $1, and $5 play. This game has been optimized for iPad/iPad 2 and Retina displays.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7499_01_thumb.jpg">http://o4.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/f6/54/af/f654aff9-c601-1f7e-1dc8-f2d759548a92/mzl.jpcwgpit.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7499-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7499_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:35:45">http://www.games.com/game/gameloft/n-o-v-a-2-near-orbit-vanguard-alliance</link><title>N.O.V.A. 2 - Near Orbit Vanguard Alliance</title><description>The ultimate sci-fi FPS is back! Get ready to step into a whole new level of gaming on your Apple device! Pocket Gamer - 9/10 + Gold Award: "Without question, it's the finest first-person shooter on iPhone and iPod touch to date, replacing its predecessor with sharper action, killer graphics, and the best multiplayer experience around." IGN - 8.5/10 + Editor's Choice: "The controls are smooth, which helps so much when the action gets furious." The AppEra: "N.O.V.A. 2 is simply the BEST FPS on the App Store right now. Go get it, now." TouchGen: "Intense and highly addictive." iLounge: "It’s hard to find a game with this much content and intensity at any price." 148apps: "N.O.V.A. 2 really does feel almost console worthy." App Advice: "The best online multiplayer around with quick connection, and ten player battles." \--------------------------------------------- BETTER, FASTER, STRONGER! \- Meet new enemies with improved AI! Volterites’ new tactics make the gyroscope controls ideal \- Master a larger range of weapons &amp; powers \- Much more diversified gameplay: run, shoot, fall, drive a motorbike, pilot a giant mech, and blast a laser \- The more, the merrier, now with up to 10 players in 10 multiplayer maps \- Build a career and rise through the multiplayer leaderboard \- Explore new locations, offering amazing graphics, fully optimized for the Retina display \- Enjoyed the first N.O.V.A. – Near Orbit Vanguard Alliance? Be rewarded with extra bonuses. 6 years have passed since the events depicted in the first episode. Humanity is now thrown into a bloody civil war fought on one side by the central government of the Terran Orbitals and the self-appointed Human-Alien Alliance; a new organization with a mysterious origin and agenda. Kal Wardin left active service in N.O.V.A. years ago and now lives among the colonists of the desert planet Scorpius. But war never spares even the most peaceful places... AN UNPARALLELED SINGLE-PLAYER CAMPAIGN: \- 12 chapters taking you through hostile, yet amazing environments of various Orbitals \- Over a dozen weapons including the Dual Hand Guns, Assault Rifle, Shotgun, Automatic Shotgun, Sniper Rifle, Rocket Launcher, Grenade Launcher, Alien Plasma Gun, Alien Lightning Gun, Alien Laser Gun, Turrets, Frag Grenades and Mines \- 3 special powers: Freeze, Slow Time and Disc for melee combat \- A wide range of enemies with improved AI, for even more intense combats INTENSE MULTIPLAYER MODES: \- 1~10 players online or locally \- 5 modes: Free for All, Team Deathmatch, Capture the Flag, Freeze Tag, and InstaGib \- Ranking &amp; Perk systems \- 10 maps on which to battle it out \- Play against your friends or the entire world through Gameloft LIVE! \- Worldwide leaderboards in the game &amp; on the official website, www.near-orbit-vanguard-alliance.com EXCLUSIVE REWARDS FOR VETERAN PLAYERS If you played the first episode: \- Jump into multiplayer with bonus XP, allowing you access to advanced weaponry \- Unlock a special achievement on Gameloft LIVE! \--------------------------------------------- JOIN THE FIGHT WITH MANY OTHER FANS! Enlist on Twitter @NOVA_fps Visit www.near-orbit-vanguard-alliance.com for more information. Certain apps allow you to purchase virtual items within the app and may contain third party advertisements that may redirect you to a third party site.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7499_02_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a4.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/fe/ad/e2/mzl.sibztklm.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7499-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7499_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:37:10">http://www.games.com/game/tin-man-games/fighting-fantasy-blood-of-the-zombies</link><title>Fighting Fantasy: Blood of the Zombies</title><description>SALE - over 60% OFF! Steve Jackson's STARSHIP TRAVELLER docking SOON! Fighting Fantasy, the world famous interactive gamebook series returns for its 30th Anniversary! Ian Livingstone and Tin Man Games present Blood of the Zombies on iOS!! "Insane megalomaniac Gingrich Yurr is preparing to unleash an army of monstrous zombies upon the world. He must be stopped and his undead horde defeated. In this life-or-death adventure the decisions YOU make will decide the fate of the world. Can YOU survive or will YOU become a zombie too?" ** REVIEWS ** “Blood of the Zombies is a hugely enjoyable, brilliantly presented, hilariously violent romp. If this is your first gamebook or your 30th, you’re going to have a whale of a time.” – POCKET GAMER - 9/10 - GOLD AWARD! “…its speedy combat and inbuilt adversity make it a great candidate for the app treatment. A skilled app designer and an experienced author have collaborated and managed the rare feat of creating something greater than the sum of their individual talents.” - GAMEZEBO - 4.5/5 “Ultimately, fans of the old stories should enjoy Blood of the Zombies. It delivers an authentic Fighting Fantasy experience while updating the gameplay and style in its own way. ” – STARBURST - 8/10 “…for those looking for an interesting storyline and a delightful walk down memory lane, it’s a sterling effort and one that very much deserves its asking price. I’m already looking forward to other Fighting Fantasy/Tin Man Games collaborations.” – 148 APPS - 4.5/5 – EDITOR’S CHOICE! “Beautifully presented, a little campy but oh-so-worth that walk down memory lane, Blood of the Zombies will not go amiss in your library of interactive iOS-based tales.” – TOUCH ARCADE - 4/5 ** FEATURES ** Blood of the Zombies is a digital Fighting Fantasy gamebook, an interactive adventure in which YOU are the hero! You can only win through by choosing the correct path, finding equipment, avoiding traps and surviving combat. Exclusive new features in the app: • All new death endings, written by Ian Livingstone. Not available in the print book! • Kevin Crossley’s amazing illustrations colorised for the app, making full use of the high-resolution retina displays. • Alternate artwork to unlock by Fighting Fantasy favourite, Martin McKenna. • Achievements to find throughout the gamebook with full Game Center connectivity. • Make the gamebook as easy or hard as you like and even turn on a special cheat mode to read it old-school! • An animated Greg Staples cover – the zombie comes to life! Blood of the Zombies has been brought to iOS using Tin Man Games’ critically acclaimed Gamebook Adventures Engine featuring: • Universal iOS support. Buy the app once and it works on all your devices! • Read the book horizontally or vertically on your iPad. • An automated Adventure Sheet to keep track of stats and inventory. • Realistic physics based dice rolling. Shake your iOS device! • Artwork gallery. Find an illustration in the gamebook and be able to access it full-screen forever. • Bookmarking system which saves your position in the gamebook, much like putting your fingers between the pages to remember your previous page when reading the paperback! • Specially composed soundtrack and sound effects. Tin Man Games have signed a licensing deal to release the Fighting Fantasy series on iOS, so expect to see more of your favourite adventure gamebooks appearing on the App Store! Coming Soon... The Warlock of Firetop Mountain, Forest of Doom, Deathtrap Dungeon, Appointment with F.E.A.R. and more!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7499_03_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a1.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/f2/79/fe/f279fe9b-54c8-608e-53a0-e78dbc2d594e/mzl.njbemlqs.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7499-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7499_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:38:39">http://www.games.com/game/24kt-studios/storage-warfare-gold-edition</link><title>Storage Warfare: Gold Edition</title><description>Outbid, Outsmart and Defeat your opponents in Storage Warfare! Storage Warfare: Gold Edition combines all versions of Storage Warfare into one big package of Storage Auction fun! The Gold Edition includes the original version of Storage Warfare, along with Storage Warfare: Jersey Beach and Storage Warfare: Holiday Rush. The Gold Edition features over 200 units to bid on, and over 90 items to discover! Have you ever heard of a Storage Auction? Well Storage Auctions are modern day treasure hunts. In Storage Warfare, you attend storage auctions and your goal is to locate the treasures buried within the storage units, and then turn a profit! The only weapon you have in Storage Warfare is your cash. The more cash you have, the more deadly you become. In Storage Warfare, you have 4 main competitors who will do whatever it takes for them to get to the treasure and leave you with the trash. They will outbid you every chance they get, or they may just run the price up on you to make sure you won't be able to turn a profit. You have you use a close eye on what is in each unit, to make sure that you can outsmart your opponents and only bid on units that will be profitable. In Storage Warfare, the auction season is 24 months long. Once you have attended the last auction, the total cash you have left in your bank account is your final score. That score is submitted to the leader boards. That is where you can see how good of a storage unit buyer you really are.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7499_04_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple4/v4/1b/dc/b9/1bdcb934-d00a-36e3-17e9-d0976b80064d/mzl.jvyuwtym.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7499-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7499_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:39:34">http://www.games.com/game/fireflame-games/dungeon-raid-lite</link><title>Dungeon Raid Lite</title><description>Play the awesomely addictive Puzzle/RPG Dungeon Raid for FREE! "Dungeon Raid is an effortless recommendation... download this game now." \- TouchArcade "Pick this one up. For its price, they definitely made me feel like it was well worth the money in so many ways" \- appSafari "If you’re looking for a different type of match 3 game or you’re an RPG nut that wants to get a quick fix every now and again, Dungeon Raid is just the game for you" \- TouchMyApps "Dungeon Raid manages to capture the essence of both rogue like dungeon crawling, and addictive match 3 in a easily accessible formula" \- TouchGen "It’s a fun mix of match-three puzzling and role-playing" \- Pocket Gamer Dungeon Raid is a puzzle RPG, a blend of puzzle game with roleplaying mechanics. Your mission is to trace a path through a set of matching tiles, but watch out – you may be attacked by enemies who improve as fast as you do. As you go, the object is to collect as many resources as you can, like gold and experience. Get enough points and you can buy or upgrade equipment and level up. All the while, remember to avoid those nasty enemy skull tiles and fight them off for as long as you possibly can. And don't get too greedy, or you risk being overwhelmed! The higher you go in a Dungeon Raid game, the more strategy you’re going to need to match a greater number of tiles, grab bonuses and stay ahead of those evil adversaries. Never forget that they improve as the game continues. Keep your wits about you as you play Dungeon Raid. As you level up, there are many trade offs to consider and complimentary combinations of skills to be chosen. If you’re not used to the tense pace of the higher levels, go ahead and start on easy difficulty. That gives you the chance to play the game in a more relaxed way, and watch how powerful your avatar can become. Regardless of your skill level, you’ll never get bored with Dungeon Raid because there’s so much going on! There are hundreds of items to collect, a growing list of character skills and many different strategies for you to use. You’ll be itching to play just one more turn, just one more game for hours and days on end. Features: ★ 4 difficulty levels: select a relaxing easy game or go for a challenging and strategic experience ★ 400+ unique items to buy and upgrade ★ 30 diverse abilities to help you and hinder your enemies ★ 30 special monsters to defeat ★ 20 powerful upgrades to apply to your items ★ Level up and improve your avatar as you kill enemies and collect experience points ★ Global leaderboards using Game Center &amp; OpenFeint ★ Play your own music during the game ★ Constant save system: quit the game and return to it at any time If you want the thrill of playing a truly exciting game, you’ve come to the perfect place. Download Dungeon Raid now and prepare to be impressed! See this exciting game in action here: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eumnCTG0AE8</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7499_05_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/e6/7e/1c/mzl.toylbumu.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7499-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7499_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:41:41">http://www.games.com/game/gold-lion-apps/free-gold</link><title>FREE Gold</title><description>The most fun you can have checking the spot prices of gold and silver daily. Live prices are updated every 30 seconds while the worldwide markets are open. Play a quick round or two of the slots each day to add to your virtual gold and silver holdings. A thousand ounces of real gold is worth over $1,760,000 today. Download it now for FREE.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7499_06_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/51/91/af/5191af46-eec6-4720-e35f-21919bcc632e/mzl.fjzsvxvv.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7499-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7499_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:44:01">http://www.games.com/game/mobivention-gmbh/backgammon-gold-free</link><title>Backgammon Gold FREE</title><description>Backgammon Gold - for beginners and professional players. Play against the computer or online with chat! Test the popular BGBlitz software, 100% fair dice rolls. *** NEW *** Elo-based matchmaking (premium feature) | Block list | Random opponents can be rejected Backgammon Gold - lots of exciting and extendable features such as tournaments, help functions, difficulty levels and game variations will take you into the world of one of the oldest and best-known board games. Guaranteed no rigged dice due to absolute random dice rolls from random.org (online connection is required). Login with your social network account (Facebook, Twitter &amp; more) or use our mobivention Game Service. Create a friends list and send and receive game invites. THE FEATURES: \- 1 and 2 players + Online \- Elo rating \- Play against other users \- Friends list for game invites (no Game Center account needed) \- Single game &amp; tournament \- Classic &amp; Nackgammon \- 100% fair dice rolls with random.org or Live Rolls function \- 4 board designs \- 3 difficulty levels \- Automatic moves for fast gaming \- Double deactivating \- Save games \- Confirm move function \- Redo function BUY ADDITIONALLY: \- No ads \- Search for online opponents with a similar skills than yours (elo-based matchmaking) \- 4 additional board designs \- Bluetooth support for 2 player mode \- The BGBlitz Tutor to learn The perfect move \- BGBlitz - The international rewarded Backgammon Software from The maker of BGBlitz (difficulty level IIII) \- Full version at a reduced price Get Backgammon Gold now for your smartphone and show your opponents how to play properly! Our gamers say: ***** "Finally a challenging KI in an appealing design." ***** "The best Backgammon of all!" ***** "A game everybody knows and which makes lots of fun." ***** "I'm very happy and play it often with my girlfriend. Great!" If you like our Backgammon Gold we're looking forward to your rating in the App Store. For questions or other feedback visit us on Facebook: www.facebook.com/mobivention</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7499_07_thumb.jpg">http://o3.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple6/v4/5f/0f/7b/5f0f7be7-94d5-33f7-6ad3-9ad84afa0542/mzl.pqaliums.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7499-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7499_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:45:27">http://www.games.com/game/gold-lion-apps/free-gold-fortune</link><title>FREE Gold Fortune</title><description>The most fun way to check the price of gold every day! Play the only slot game that uses real gold prices to calculate your winnings. See if you can win 1000 ounces of virtual gold and put them into your personal bullion vault. They would be worth over $1,761,000 at today's prices for real gold. Fortune of the Day - "Champions keep playing until they get it right." ^Tap the 47 buttons that can lead you to a fortune in real gold. You don’t have become a gold miner in Alaska to strike it rich. You don’t have to find the next King Tut tomb. Or, find a sunken treasure ship. Or, discover a secret pirate’s cave with hidden loot. Or, climb the Peruvian Andes mountains to locate the entrance to an abandoned mine full of gold. Imagine what you will do with your own personal fortune in gold – island vacations, flights to space…you dream it, you get it. Exploring for gold is now as easy as downloading the Gold Fortune app now and tap every button. Your gold is waiting for you now.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7499_08_thumb.jpg">http://o2.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a5.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/96/a7/e9/96a7e9ec-9ba0-81dd-261f-d74a334cc83f/mza_7958488062766147945.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7499-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7499_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:46:56">http://www.games.com/game/ryan-furio/year-of-the-dragon-2-slot-machine</link><title>Year Of The Dragon 2 Slot Machine</title><description>Year Of The Dragon II is a brand new 5 reel Vegas Style Slot Machine. It offers multiple ways to wager, whilst at the same time providing various interactive features. The game is designed around a Chinese New Year Dragon Theme. We have created a visually appealing slot, with various animations that don't over-complicate or interfere with game play. Features: -Vegas Style 5 Reel Slot Machine -4 Bonus Rounds (Card Gambling + Shake the Dragon + Card matching + Scratch Off Card) -9 Paylines with WILD and BONUS Icons -On Demand Card Gambling -Free spins -3D Icons with 3D Animations -Gold Reels pay triple -3D Rendered Coin Shower on Big Win -Multiple spin,Bonus,Win sounds -Game remembers credits; so you can play where you left off. -Smooth Play -Great Graphics -Chinese New Year Dragon Theme Getting started: The paytable is located on the upper right hand side and should be referred to before playing, all buttons and game options are located at the bottom and sides of the slot. You can select from 1 to 9 lines by pressing the numbers on the sides of the screen. Each line has a wager that is user selectable and ranges from $1 to $10 allowing the user to wager from $1 to $90 on a single spin. Pressing the "BET MAX" button plays all 9 lines at the maximum wager for a total wager of $90. Get at least 3 BONUS ICONS on a payline to enter one of the 4 BONUS Rounds. If your spin uses the "Golden Reels" win triple. All our games use real math and near industry standard random number generation for maximum Las Vegas excitement. Priced at less than one "max bet spin" at your local casino slot machine, you will truly enjoy the exciting experience offered by this game. NOTE: Reset credits by touching "Credit" on the bottom left of the slot. NOTE: This slot machine is not associated with any real casino and was made ONLY for fun. All money amounts shown are FUN money. Good Luck and Have Fun!</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7499_09_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a3.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/28/f4/39/28f43963-900c-a42c-c6d9-0212b6f41214/mzm.lrungxde.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e048-7499-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7499_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:48:44">http://www.games.com/game/mumbojumbo/pickers-hd</link><title>Pickers HD</title><description>Get ready for the ultimate treasure hunt! Your shop, Rusted Gold, has shelves to fill, auctions to run, and money to make—and you can only do that with the best finds. Check out the dozens of locations from run-down farms to back road antique shops to abandoned storage units to see if you can stumble upon your next great treasure. What do you do once you’ve found something? Shine it up or sell it as is to see if you can turn a profit, or if you hit bust. Haggle with crazy characters as you try to build your reputation for having the best picks around and learn more about what makes each person tick. Consult with an expert to avoid being hoodwinked! Combine items to increase their values and learn how to increase your odds along the way. Price your picks to sell them in your shop, or take your chances on the auction block to see if you can make an even bigger profit! FEATURES Fill the shelves of Rusted Gold to try to turn a profit Check out 12 cool locations and the nooks and crannies of each one to find your next great pick! Meet America’s quirkiest characters and try to haggle them down Build up your reputation for being the best Picker around Combine items you find to turn an even bigger profit! Don’t be fooled—consult an expert to appraise your items Unique combination of Adventure, Resource Management, and Hidden Object game play …………………………………………………………………………………… Visit us on the App Store at http://itunes.apple.com/us/artist/mumbojumbo/id312416866 to find more amazing casual games from MumboJumbo including: the Luxor Series, Midnight Mysteries Series, 7 Wonders Series and more! Find us on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/MumboJumboGames Follow us on Twitter: @MumboJumboGames ……………………………………………………………………………………</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e048/7499_10_thumb.jpg">http://o5.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/79/86/1/o.aolcdn.com/games-scaler/proxy/172/188/1/a2.mzstatic.com/us/r30/Purple/v4/05/e8/68/05e8684b-d68e-b803-835c-333783056b23/mzm.towwtwfi.100x100-75.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>