<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7027">prefered or preferred</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:33:16" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7027-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7027_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:34:02">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=7443116</link><title>Ask HN: Common or Preferred Stock (joining a startup for 25% equity)?</title><description>Ask HN: Common or Preferred Stock (joining a startup for 25% equity)?

2 points

by mangeletti

about a month ago

4 comments Follow

If I was going to join a company for 25% equity, what would be the benefits of going with preferred stock over common stock, or vice versa? Are there legal advantages or disadvantages to either, tax advantages, ability to be screwed over in the future, etc.?

*[about a month ago]: 2014-03-21T16:15:56.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7027_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/7443116.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7027-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7027_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:35:04">http://venturefizz.com/blog/atsa-should-i-raise-my-seed-round-using-convertible-note-or-preferred-stock</link><title>Should I raise my seed round using a convertible note or preferred stock?</title><description>Should I raise my seed round using a convertible note or preferred stock? (http://venturefizz.com/blog/atsa-should-i-raise-my-seed-round-using-convertible-note-or-preferred-stock)

1 point

by venturefizz

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

*[3 years ago]: 2010-12-13T17:47:06.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7027_02_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2001290.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7027-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7027_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:35:44">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=4746538</link><title>Web development lead</title><description>Web development lead

1 point

by pkress

about a year ago

0 comment Follow

Seeking a talented back-end web developer that can lead a project team and write clean, fast, maintainable code. Our weapons of choice are PHP5 and MySQL but willing to work with developers who have deep understanding of any other object oriented web development languages. -Ability to work in a team environment with both technical and non-technical people. -Strong leadership skills and the ability to work with non-tech people to understand their needs and propose technical solutions. -Deep understanding of an object oriented web language such as PHP5. -XHTML/CSS/JavaScript/AJAX - Expert level JavaScript/XHTML/CSS development will be necessary, jQuery experience preferred. -MySQL Modern database development expertise, words like 'trigger' and 'view' should be part of your vocabulary -Object Oriented Development/CS Background - You should be intimately familiar with object oriented development, and apply OO concepts to everything they do. Formal CS background or experience preferred -Self-Starter: Looking for candidates who can jump in quickly without a lot of direction We are located in Oakland, CA and are open to developers who work remotely.

*[about a year ago]: 2012-11-06T00:06:21.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7027_03_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/4746538.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7027-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7027_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:36:18">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=3401691</link><title>Hiring: Research Assistant in the Financial Services Industry</title><description>Hiring: Research Assistant in the Financial Services Industry

1 point

by MDCFinancial

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

This entry-level position will provide you with a great opportunity to break into the Finance Industry with a paid position. MDC Financial Research, LLC provides equity research for Institutional Investors (Hedge Funds, Mutual Funds, etc.). We focus on finding areas of market inefficiency, and we help our Clients exploit them. Our first research service, "Event-Driven Legal," follows significant legal disputes of public companies to provide both long and short-term investment ideas. We are a small but rapidly growing company. We are three years old, and we nearly doubled our client-base in 2011.

We are looking for a bright and hardworking individual that wishes to grow with our Company. We expect to train you on all of your assigned duties, but we also expect you to seek new areas to add value to our business. The right candidate will use this opportunity to launch a fruitful career in the Financial Services industry.

We are a recent startup; so please expect to wear several hats. You will assist in Research, Accounting, and Clerical Duties in this position.

Position: -Assisting with many aspects of a Registered Investment Advisor (RIA) that distributes subscription research services to institutional investors. -We are currently based in Fremont, California. (This position will also provide you with an opportunity to do some of your work from home.) -The position begins with a three-month probationary period that will be 10-to-30 hours per week. (We are flexible and can adjust to your school schedule if you have one). -A successful candidate that is offered full-time employment would then be eligible for Medical/Dental benefits.

Requirements: -Bachelors Student or Recent Graduate with 3.3+ GPA (Business, Economics, Finance, Math, Statistics, or Legal majors preferred). -Knowledgeable and skilled in the use of Microsoft Office and the internet. -Self-Motivated and able to work with minimal direction. -Excellent oral and written communication skills. -An attention to detail; we value high-quality work over speed. -An unquenchable thirst for knowledge; our company supports life-long learners. -Ability to type at least 40 words per minute. -Strong analytical skills.

Preferred (any one item below): -Graduate Student or Recent Graduate with 3.3+ GPA. -Skills or Training in one or more of the following areas: Finance, Law, Accounting, Editing, Programming, and/or Statistics. -CFA Candidate or CFA Charterholder.

Please contact Dan at MDCFinancial dot com.

*[2 years ago]: 2011-12-28T22:29:10.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7027_04_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3401691.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7027-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7027_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:36:58">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=2971211</link><title>Ask HN: YCombinator Term Sheet - Protective Provisions</title><description>Ask HN: YCombinator Term Sheet - Protective Provisions

1 point

by jwomers

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

I want to learn more about Angel and VC Terms Sheets and general investing legal documents and thought that the YCombinator Term Sheet (found here http://ycombinator.com/seriesaa.html) would be a great place to start. Everything in there I understand and seems to make sense. But, I have one question: In the Protective provisions section, it states:

"So long as any of the Preferred is outstanding, consent of the holders of at least 50% of the Preferred will be required for any action that:"... "(iii) approves any merger, sale of assets or other corporate reorganization or acquisition"

Because Preferred stock can be converted to common stock at any time surely this means that the owners of Preferred stock can convert 99.9% of their Preferred stock to common stock, and keep the 0.1% of Preferred stock through all rounds of funding and have final say on all matters mentioned in (iii) above?

Is this done in practice, what am I missing? (and thanks in advanced)

*[3 years ago]: 2011-09-07T20:13:55.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7027_05_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2971211.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7027-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7027_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:37:35">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=2166590</link><title>Kontagent (SF/SOMA) is HIRING for multiple positions</title><description>Kontagent (SF/SOMA) is HIRING for multiple positions

1 point

by sarahmascardo

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

Kontagent (San Francisco/SOMA) (Working remotely is an option for the right person!)&lt;p&gt;Kontagent is HIRING for multiple positions!&lt;p&gt;1\. Sr. Software Engineer&lt;p&gt;Role:&lt;p&gt;Your core responsibility here will be to develop cutting-edge technologies to solve big data problems. More specifically, this will include designing and implementing robust, scalable systems for efficiently processing, storing and querying large data sets and the data derived from them. You will build frameworks that others can leverage as well to rapidly add functionality to our products. For success in this role, you will draw upon the following skills and experiences acquired to date.&lt;p&gt;Qualifications: -BS or MS in Computer Science or equivalent degree (PhDs or PhD dropouts are a bonus) -Senior level experience with back-end services and data processing (5-7 + years) -Interest in and ability to work on tough scalability/performance challenges for systems that handle terabytes of data -Extensive experience with data stores (MySQL, Cassandra, MongoDB, etc.) -C, Python experience (preferred, but not required) -Solid understanding of Linux systems -Background in distributed systems, information retrieval, data storage, data processing, and infrastructure scaling a bonus&lt;p&gt;2\. Software Engineer&lt;p&gt;Role&lt;p&gt;Your core responsibility here will be to develop cutting-edge technologies to solve big data problems. More specifically, this will include designing and implementing robust, scalable systems for efficiently processing, storing and querying large data sets and the data derived from them. You will build frameworks that others can leverage as well to rapidly add functionality to our products. For success in this role, you will draw upon the following skills and experiences acquired to date. They include:&lt;p&gt;-BS or MS in Computer Science or equivalent degree Senior level experience with back-end services and data processing (2-4 years) -Interest in and ability to work on tough scalability/performance challenges for systems that handle terabytes of data -Extensive experience with data stores (MySQL, Cassandra, MongoDB, etc.) -C, Python experience (preferred, but not required) -Solid understanding of Linux systems -Background in distributed systems, information retrieval, data storage, data processing, and infrastructure scaling a bonus&lt;p&gt;3\. Front End Python Engineer&lt;p&gt;The Role&lt;p&gt;You will play a lead role in the development of the Python-based user interface framework for Kontagents analytics platform, with a very strong emphasis on the server-side component. The key challenge is to build a highly scalable and flexible front-end framework that will enable rapid deployment of new features in the dashboard. You'll develop, maintain, and optimize the performance of our customer facing dashboard in this highly visible role based in our downtown San Francisco (SOMA) office.&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities -Develop server-side framework and production code using Python -Develop and integrate with front-end production code using JavaScript and jQuery -Evaluation and integration of relevant open-source technologies -Use coding methodologies and architectures that facilitate continuous integration testing -Heavy interaction with front end designers and developers, and server development team Iterate using two week development and product release cycles&lt;p&gt;4\. Front End Software Engineer&lt;p&gt;Role&lt;p&gt;You will take the lead developing our user interface by turning basic wireframes into production code. The key challenge you will be facing is building an easy-to-use, fast, flexible, front end interface that is able to draw out key insights from visualized data. You'll develop, maintain, and optimize the performance of our customer facing dashboard in this highly visible role. For success, you'll draw on the following skills and experiences acquired to date. We are open to highly talented and motivated individuals that have recently graduated, or may have just a few years' experience working with UI's.&lt;p&gt;-Experience with Javascript and major framework such as jQuery -HTML and CSS knowledge -Understanding of web standards and best practices -Eye for great design and information architecture&lt;p&gt;Although not required, the following qualifications would add to your candidacy: -Experience with data visualization -Mathematical inclination and a familiarity with statistics -Python &amp; Django coding experience -Flash and AS3 experience a plus&lt;p&gt;5\. API Web Engineer&lt;p&gt;Role&lt;p&gt;You will design a REST API and write a set of associated client libraries to interface with it in a number of languages such as PHP, Ruby and Python. In addition, you will be tasked with creating a framework to do automated online client-side user tracking through means such as image pixels, cookies through JavaScript, or server side code. The key challenge is to create a set of tracking methods that is powerful, yet easy for customers to implement. Our Web Tracking Engineer will also assist customers with set up and implementation of these tracking systems. For success in this role, youll draw on the following skills and experiences acquired to date.&lt;p&gt;Qualifications: -BS or MS in Computer Science or equivalent degree preferred but not required (PhDs or PhD dropouts are a bonus) -Extremely deep understanding of web servers, protocols and client side web technologies -Experience in Javascript, PHP, Ruby, Java, Python -Ability to write very clean and well-documented publicly-visible open source code -Ability to pick up new programming languages very quickly&lt;p&gt;Interested?&lt;p&gt;Please submit your resume directly on our Careers page: www.kontagent.com/jobs or send it directly to Sarah Mascardo, Recruiting Manager at sarah.mascardo@kontagent.com&lt;p&gt;About Kontagent:&lt;p&gt;Kontagent measures people, not pages, and is a leading analytics platform for social application developers. The platform has been built to provide deep social behavior analysis and visualization that provides actionable insights via a hosted, on-demand service. It works with many of the worlds largest developers and brands, tracking thousands of social applications and games with over 70 million monthly active users. Kontagent works with developers to gain insights, drive higher revenue through better tools and testing, and lower time-to-market. Kontagent is a Facebook Fund winner backed with financing from Altos Ventures, Maverick Capital, and a large number of angel investors including James Hong (cofounder of Hot Or Not), Larry Braitman (co-founder of FlyCast and Adify) Jameson Hsu (co-founder/CEO of MochiMedia), Mike Sego (CEO of Gaia).

*[3 years ago]: 2011-02-01T18:27:46.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7027_06_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2166590.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7027-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7027_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:38:37">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=3321201</link><title>Tell HN: Recruiters and Bizarre Skillsets</title><description>Tell HN: Recruiters and Bizarre Skillsets

2 points

by watmough

2 years ago

8 comments Follow

HN'ers, this is from a real email I was sent by a recruiter. What you you think if you received such a set of potential positions?

Position: .NET Developer
Must Have Skills: .NET, C#, SQL Server 2005 (2005 or better), OOP/OOD.
Preferred: WCF, workflow, messaging
Wish List: Mono or MonoTouch , Erlang, Scala, F#, RabbitMQ, ZeroMQ, Redis, Couchbase, Raven DB
Years experience: 5

Position: Web Developer
Must Have Skills: .NET, C#, Javascript, HTML5, Jquery, SQL Server 2005 (2005 or better), OOP/OOD.
Preferred: WCF, workflow, messaging, MVC, Mono or MonoTouch.
Wish List: Erlang, Scala, F#, Rabbit MQ, Zebra MQ, REtis, Couch Base, Raven DB
Years experience: 5

Position: Mobile Developer (Android)
Must Have Skills: .NET, C#, SQL Server (2005 or better), Java, OOP/OOD.
Preferred: Mono for Android
Wishlist: Erlang, Scala, F#, Rabbit MQ, Zebra MQ, REtis, Couch Base, Raven DB
Years experience: 5

Position: Mobile Developer (iOS)
Must Have Skills: .NET, C#, SQL Server (2005 or better), OOP/OOD, Objective C
Preferred: C++, Mono or MonoTouch, SQL Light, IOS 4 (or better), Core Data, Smalltalk
Wishlist: Erlang, Scala, F#, Rabbit MQ, Zebra MQ, REtis, Couch Base, Raven DB

What are your thoughts?

*[2 years ago]: 2011-12-06T21:41:09.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7027_07_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3321201.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7027-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7027_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:39:01">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=6065790</link><title>Application Security Risk Specialist</title><description>Application Security Risk Specialist

1 point

by GTNjw

9 months ago

0 comment Follow

Location: Irving, TX 75039 Position Type: Direct-Hire Hourly / Salary: BOE!, RELOCATION PACKAGES FOR OUT OF TOWN CANDIDATES. Educational Requirements: BS Computer Science, strongly preferred but not required

ABOUT THE POSITION GTN Technical Staffing is currently seeking an Application Security Risk Specialist. The Application Security Risk Specialist will specifically examine application code and conduct penetration testing to flush out any vulnerabilities. The Application Security Risk Specialist should have experience with design reviews and threat modeling, and would typically need to have familiarity with multiple programming languages ( C# .NET and Java / J2EE preferred, C++ or Smalltalk a big plus ). Preference will be given to those with a background working for firms / vendors that specialize in these services, as most organizations hire a third party to conduct this type of testing. Not only are your talents in penetration testing and vulnerability testing key, but our client is also keenly interested in someone with lots of upward potential you will be expected to demonstrate your potential in the interview, and follow through if hired. Candidates with a greater probability of having the right background might come from Gotham Security, ISEC Partners, Fortify, Vericode, Raytheon, Fidelity, Cigital, and/or McAfee, etc.

The keys to this opportunity are strong skills in penetration testing and vulnerability testing.

TECHNICAL REQUIREMENTS 2+ years of experience in the following skill sets Penetration Testing / Vulnerability Application Testing Design Reviews Threat Modeling Familiarity with Multiple Programming Languages C#.NET or Java / J2EE Familiarity Analyze / Interpret / Anticipate / Resole Risks

PREFERRED (but not required) C++ / SmallTalk Familiarity, strongly preferred

*[9 months ago]: 2013-07-18T19:13:54.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7027_08_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/6065790.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7027-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7027_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:40:04">http://venturehacks.com/articles/understand-protective-provisions</link><title>Why investors want protective provisions</title><description>Why investors want protective provisions (http://www.venturehacks.com/articles/understand-protective-provisions)

9 points

by nivi

7 years ago

0 comment Follow

Protective provisions let preferred shareholders veto certain actions, such as selling the company or raising capital. They protect the preferred, who are minority shareholders, from unfair actions by the common majority. However, the preferred shouldn't use protective provisions to serve their other interests.

*[7 years ago]: 2007-08-02T23:40:18.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7027_09_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/38861.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7027-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7027_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:40:54">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=1943216</link><title>GREAT OPPORTUNITY SR. FRONT END LEADER JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER, 145 K | New York |</title><description>GREAT OPPORTUNITY SR. FRONT END LEADER JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER, 145 K | New York |

1 point

by volorawha

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

EVELOPER, 145 K Address:New York, NY 10022 (map) Job Type:Full-time Description&lt;p&gt;My client seeks a Sr. FRONT END JavaScript Developer.&lt;p&gt;Salary: 145 K&lt;p&gt;Skills: HTML templating and design integration of Backend code (not coding Backend but integrating FrontEnd code with BackEnd code) experience using source code/version control systems Nice to have: Linux/Unix environment knowledge PHP and Symfony knowledge Experience with ant Skills required: - 5+ years experience with front end web development \- Expert level CSS, including best practices, standards and optimization techniques - Expert with cross-browser compatibility - Expert level html, xhtml - Knowledgeable in page load time optimization - Experience with OO JavaScript, AJAX, JSON, jQuery - Experience with developing applications using Model View Controller design patterns - Experience with source control and version control tools (preferably Subversion) - Experience with linux command line - Understanding of Social Networking and Web 2.0 technologies - Experience using 3rd party development API's (Facebook, Google, etc.) \- Ability to work in a small team and build consensus with colleagues Not required, but preferred: - Experience with PHP, MySQL, and/or other backend technologies - Experience with Flash&lt;p&gt;Job Description: My client is seeking a Java script Developer this position which pays 145K FRONT END JAVA SCRIPT DEVELOPER for New York City We seek a JavaScript Developer Industry Interactive Responsibilities and Requirements Skill Summary Primary JAVA SCRIPT Other Ajax ANT CSS Flash Html Linux Mysql PHP Unix&lt;p&gt;About the Senior Front End Developer role: We are looking for a detail oriented, senior-level developer with extensive experience writing for large-scale, front-end applications. You will play a key role in helping lead our development efforts and building our application portfolio. Only senior level developers should apply. Our ideal candidate will have a track record of delivering high quality work on time and on budget. You must be flexible and able to thrive within a dynamic, fast-paced environment while adhering to our processes and policies.&lt;p&gt;About you: You are known by all of your current and past colleagues as the ?go to? person for anything and everything related to styling a webpage. CSS layout, microformat, clear-div and IE double margin issue are standard vocabulary for you. You are familiar with conditional comments, "* html" and other oddities, even you if you choose not use them. In your career, you have come across very few people who are better than you at html and CSS. You know the good and bad sides of using @import. You are confident enough to set, document, and share your knowledge with the team, yet humble enough to listen to a backend developer's point of view and value it. To summarize, you are a professional front-end developer with awesome CSS and html skills. If you are still reading, please check the required skills and consider contacting us! Extremely knowledgeable with native Javascript (not with libraries)&lt;p&gt;Must understand and have working knowledge of: CSS, CSS frameworks, CSS Resets Javascript Libraries (any but jQuery is preferred), Javascript APIs (FB, twitter, etc.) Javascript patterns, techniques, debugging and testing ross-domain scripting for widget development, JSON, AJAX, JSONP&lt;p&gt;Read more: http://newyork.ebayclassifieds.com/it-software-development/new-york/great-opportunity-sr-front-end-leader-javascript-developer-145-k/?ad=7516344#ixzz16QFi0E2A

*[3 years ago]: 2010-11-26T20:33:19.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7027_10_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/1943216.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>