<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7047">Dewar flask</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:28:42" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7047-01"><link>http://stacksmashing.net/2012/08/10/dear-flask-please-fix-your-secure-cookies/</link><title>Dear Flask, Please Fix Your Secure Cookies</title><description>Dear Flask, Please Fix Your Secure Cookies (http://stacksmashing.net/2012/08/10/dear-flask-please-fix-your-secure-cookies/)

38 points

by mxey

2 years ago

47 comments Follow

*[2 years ago]: 2012-08-11T00:00:48.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7047_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/4368903.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7047-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7047_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:30:01">http://codesketch.com/2010/01/dear-flash-plugin-love-osx/</link><title>Dear Flash plugin, love OSX</title><description>Dear Flash plugin, love OSX (http://codesketch.com/2010/01/16/dear-flash-plugin-love-osx/)

98 points

by g0atbutt

4 years ago

65 comments Follow

*[4 years ago]: 2010-01-16T19:56:33.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7047_02_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/1057378.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7047-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7047_03.jpg" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:30:51">http://fc01.deviantart.net/fs19/f/2007/284/0/b/Extra_Value_Combo_Alpha_by_Lysol_Jones.jpg</link><title>Dear HN: Please make this a simple Flash game</title><description>Dear HN: Please make this a simple Flash game (http://fc04.deviantart.com/fs19/f/2007/284/0/b/Extra_Value_Combo_Alpha_by_Lysol_Jones.jpg)

3 points

by jasonlbaptiste

4 years ago

1 comment Follow

*[4 years ago]: 2010-05-10T03:21:23.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7047_03_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/1333448.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7047-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7047_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:31:51">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=1774769</link><title>Ask HN: Why there is so much advertising crap around?</title><description>Ask HN: Why there is so much advertising crap around?

13 points

by TeMPOraL

4 years ago

10 comments Follow

Dear HN'ers, please help me, because I can't comprehend this. Why is there so much advertisement crap around? Is it even working for advertisers? I don't see any proof for that when I look at people. On the contrary, it is now common knowledge, that one shouldn't start using the Web without AdBlock or NoScript (http://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=1772025). In Poland, people using the most popular Instant Messenger there install 3rd party plugins or escape to open source clients just to avoid flash ads. We have Commercial skipping technology for TV (http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Commercial_skipping) and other projects (like recently mentioned on HN http://unlogo.org/) designed to avoid or remove advertising content. Hell, there is even a psychological phenomenon of "banner blindness" (http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Banner_blindness)! And there are bloggers, entrepreneurs, etc. writing and talking (http://www.ted.com/talks/richard_st_john_s_8_secrets_of_success.html) about honesty, user experience, and about how providing something valuable is the best way to get money in the long run. So please, tell me, why are we doing it to each other? What value is in producing those boatloads of crap that no one wants to see?

*[4 years ago]: 2010-10-09T09:51:09.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7047_04_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/1774769.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7047-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7047_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:32:17">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=1786901</link><title>Hire me: The Rails Frontend Guy</title><description>Hire me: The Rails Frontend Guy

2 points

by flacon

4 years ago

0 comment Follow

Howdy! I am looking for a job that will harness my skills of Ruby and Frontend development to build great products and actuating great ideas.

Maybe you are an Entrepreneur or Tech lead that needs an extra hand to build your great product. Or maybe you are part of a Rails consulting company looking to subcontract some projects. I want to speak with you!

A little about me: 6 years Web Software Development 3 Years of Ruby on Rails Development BA degree from UC Berkeley

Acronyms dear to my heart: Git, HTML5, CSS, SASS, JS, JSON, SEO, MYSQL, CS3-CS4, *nix, Ack Acronyms I can tolerate: SVN, PHP, XML Misc: Selenium IDE, Linux server hacking, Facebook Integration, Wordpress Hacking, Sphinx search

What I have done: Been part of several startup tech teams Helped scale a major Rails Ecommerce site from 0 to 1.5 Million uniques a month. Built custom storefront applications using Sinatra for Fortune 500 Companies. Built an email templating and tracking system and integrated it with a major ESP API Built interactive financial tools with Ajax, Flash, HTML and Ruby Coded integrations with a bunch of different API's

Why Rails Frontend? I have built Rails apps from end to end and been part of a number of teams building Rails or ruby apps. Whereas hardcore backend programmers seem to be in abundance, I think that there is a real lack of quality developers who can really build quality UI's on top of Rails while being able to dive into the Controllers and Models to make magic happen there also. I think I fill that niche really well.

I am seeking: A remote web job. I live 2 hours outside of Chicago, so I could potentially travel to Chicago once a week or once every other week if you are located in Chicagoland somewhere.

If you want to fly me out to CA or NY occasionally, if that's where you are head-quartered than that could work also.

I could do a fulltime salaried position or a contract position with a minimum of 6 months, prefer a 1 year though. My salary needs are pretty reasonable for a great Rails front-end dev with good communication skills and startup experience.

I am not interested in working for solely equity. Been there, done that. I need to eat.

Anybody have any thoughts, suggestions, or job offers regarding this?

Drop me a line to learn more and see examples of my work: rubyfrontendguy@gmail.com

*[4 years ago]: 2010-10-13T12:51:23.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7047_05_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/1786901.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>