<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7057">web of science</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:49:28" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7057-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7057_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:50:18">http://www.jordanm.co.uk/post/50417122608/the-science-of-web-design</link><title>The Science of Web Design</title><description>The Science of Web Design (http://www.jordanm.co.uk/post/50417122608/the-science-of-web-design)

1 point

by nvk

11 months ago

0 comment Follow

*[11 months ago]: 2013-05-15T13:13:29.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7057_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/5711692.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7057-02"><link>http://thedailyglobalpost.com/</link><title>Thedaily Globalpost is the World web portal of Tech science Entertainment news</title><description>Thedaily Globalpost is the World web portal of Tech science Entertainment news (http://thedailyglobalpost.com/)

1 point

by abdulseo

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

Thedaily Globalpost is the World web portal. The blog is started with the aim to cover latest Tech,Science,Politics,business,lifestyle and Entertainment News. we are also Focused on the Pictures, Funny,cute and Humor.

*[2 years ago]: 2012-02-20T10:29:59.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7057_02_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3611973.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7057-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7057_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:51:21">http://www.fastcompany.com/1593583/tim-berners-lee-head-institute-web-science-uk-britain-goes-broke-web</link><title>UK to Create Institute of Web Science, Headed by Tim Berners-Lee</title><description>UK to Create Institute of Web Science, Headed by Tim Berners-Lee (http://www.fastcompany.com/1593583/tim-berners-lee-to-head-up-institute-of-web-science-in-uk-as-britain-goes-for-broke-on-the-w)

1 point

by inmygarage

4 years ago

0 comment Follow

*[4 years ago]: 2010-03-23T01:50:53.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7057_03_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/1211920.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7057-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7057_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:52:16">http://www.economist.com/node/18618025</link><title>Organising the web: The science of science</title><description>Organising the web: The science of science (http://www.economist.com/node/18618025)

4 points

by pama

3 years ago

1 comment Follow

*[3 years ago]: 2011-05-12T16:31:04.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7057_04_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2541162.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7057-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7057_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:53:15">http://www.nature.com/news/2011/110404/full/471566a.html</link><title>Social science: Web of war</title><description>Social science: Web of war (http://www.nature.com/news/2011/110404/full/471566a.html)

2 points

by harkain

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

*[3 years ago]: 2011-05-09T13:51:50.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7057_05_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2528680.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7057-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7057_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:54:08">http://blogs.scientificamerican.com/guest-blog/2011/08/29/hacking-science-the-intersection-of-web-geeks-and-science-geeks/</link><title>The intersection of web geeks and science geeks</title><description>The intersection of web geeks and science geeks (http://blogs.scientificamerican.com/guest-blog/2011/08/29/hacking-science-the-intersection-of-web-geeks-and-science-geeks/)

2 points

by ColinWright

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

*[3 years ago]: 2011-08-29T20:30:27.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7057_06_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2938793.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7057-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7057_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:54:47">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i8t53Ak_yrQ&amp;feature=youtu.be</link><title>The best of science around the web</title><description>The best of science around the web (http://youtu.be/i8t53Ak_yrQ)

1 point

by shawndumas

about a year ago

0 comment Follow

*[about a year ago]: 2013-02-08T00:19:51.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7057_07_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/5185426.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7057-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7057_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:55:25">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=4295302</link><title>Ask HN: Will I ever feel like I know "everything" about web programming?</title><description>Ask HN: Will I ever feel like I know "everything" about web programming?

1 point

by marcamillion

2 years ago

2 comments Follow

I am a fairly technical person. Bachelor's degree in Computer Science and have a solid understanding of the building blocks of computer science and the web.

I "learned" programming in college, but when I graduated I felt like all I could do is just build random projects - which is what I did - in languages I considered 'archaic' and uninteresting to me (largely C, C++, Java, Assembly, etc.). I am not starting a flame war, but those languages are just not interesting to me - or rather, they weren't until I stumbled upon Ruby.

I learned OOP via Java and hated it.

Over the last 3 - 4 years I have been teaching myself Ruby &amp; Rails dev. I am loving every minute of it - but I am a bit self-conscious about my development skills because I know how much I don't know.

I am not one of those guys that has a huge Github repo and actively participates in lots of OSS projects. But if I want to build something, no matter how long it takes me - I figure it out. I can't say it's always "very elegant" the first time, but there is always a desire for me to make it so.

Is it normal that 3 years into Ruby &amp; Rails development I feel like I still have A LOT to learn? Will I ever feel like I know "everything" there is to know about Ruby, Rails, OOP, etc.?

The more I learn Ruby is the more I find myself looking at other languages to see how things are handled in those languages, which also leads me to start thinking about languages (both programming and natural/spoken) and the way they are constructed and other things outside of web programming. But then I just stop because I already feel a bit overwhelmed with the amount I have to learn about the web.

I know this may be a bit subjective, but I feel torn.

I don't know if the way I am feeling is a good thing (i.e. because I know what I don't know, I am always trying to improve my craft) or a bad thing (that I am learning too slowly - I do tend to take the long route because I want to make sure I thoroughly understand what I am learning).

*[2 years ago]: 2012-07-26T10:24:31.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7057_08_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/4295302.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7057-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7057_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:56:01">http://kk.org/thetechnium/2008/06/the-google-way/</link><title>The Google Way of Science. Google's translation of Chinese web pages invalidates Searle's Chinese Room riddle</title><description>The Google Way of Science. Google's translation of Chinese web pages invalidates Searle's Chinese Room riddle (http://www.kk.org/thetechnium/archives/2008/06/the_google_way.php)

4 points

by ivankirigin

6 years ago

3 comments Follow

*[6 years ago]: 2008-06-30T04:15:03.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7057_09_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/231698.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7057-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7057_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:56:46">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=2474215</link><title>Is having a good grasp of computer science basics required for web programming?</title><description>Is having a good grasp of computer science basics required for web programming?

2 points

by jackbean

3 years ago

5 comments Follow

There's lot of talk about computer science basis in hackernews, but in most job descriptions I see only mention of web frameworks and other stuff like javascript, dbs and what not.

Though I do see computer science degree as requirement in most of them and fully understand that with Rails and other frameworks its easy to create a web app thanks to numerous open source libraries and tutorials online.

The reason I'm asking is I was wondering if I should spend at least the next 3 months learning about the computer science basics or spend that time getting better at Ruby and learning new technologies that I'll directly use.

Sure learning both is better, but I'm more interested in web programming than writing a compiler or other intensive tasks. (True the experience and critical thinking would be helpful.)

Thanks.

*[3 years ago]: 2011-04-22T14:50:53.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7057_10_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2474215.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>