<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7063">Spanish unemployment</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:02:13" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7063-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7063_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:02:56">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=4378338</link><title>Ask HN: How do you land the first online clients?</title><description>Ask HN: How do you land the first online clients?

2 points

by victorin

2 years ago

9 comments Follow

Long story short, my girlfriend and me have been living in the US for the last year, but in a couple of months we'll move back to Spain.

I'll continue working on my current project, but my girlfriend will need to enter the labour market. Right now the unemployment rate in Spain is at 24.8% (53% for under 25), so I think our best bet is to set up her own company (like somebody said "when jobs are scarce, create your own" ).

She is a graphic designer so we have set up a website with two landing pages offering Logo and Business Card design services.

It is a crowded space, but I think it's not totally impossible to make a full spanish salary (around $1200/month) in the long term.

BEING SAID THAT, I'd like to ask for some methods to land the first clients that may worked for you in the past.

Although our budget is tiny, our initial approach is to start some adwords campaigns and keep optimizing landing pages and ad copies to see if we're able to reach a profitable cost-per-conversion.

The website for the new graphic design studio is http://mylidias.com

So, How do you land the first clients for your recently launched online service?

*[2 years ago]: 2012-08-13T21:48:46.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7063_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/4378338.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7063-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7063_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:03:40">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=4341664</link><title>Remote contract opportunities for a globetrotter who knows seven languages?</title><description>Remote contract opportunities for a globetrotter who knows seven languages?

1 point

by buu700

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

A well-travelled, brilliant, personable friend of mine is fluent in Russian, French, English, Italian, and Spanish with intermediate proficiency in Arabic and Danish. She's considering taking a gap year from university to travel the world one year from now, but she's worried about being able to find stable income during her travels. What kinds of opportunities should she be looking at, and what sorts of temp/contract offers (or full-time offers) should she expect to receive during this time?

She does have dual US citizenship, so government employment is one option. Aside from that, I was thinking she could look into representing tech startups at international events on contract, recruiting, hosting events, teaching for short periods of time, or possibly other things.

I'm pretty convinced that someone like her would be in high demand, but we don't quite have a concrete idea of where exactly to find that demand. Any tips?

*[2 years ago]: 2012-08-05T15:27:11.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7063_02_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/4341664.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>