<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7078">count in korean</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:40:30" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7078-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7078_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:40:59">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=6245874</link><title>The "Filter this crap" button on Hulu</title><description>The "Filter this crap" button on Hulu

1 point

by nineninenine

8 months ago

0 comment Follow

Dear Hulu, It is quite simple... \- I don't want to see any Korean dramas. Ever, never. Where is the negative filter??? AKA the "Don't show this crap" button. In a google search you can do that with a minus sign. \- Your staffs "top picks" suck. Fire the staff. \- An episode should only show up once in the "most popular this week" stream. Here is what you need to do: 1) sort the episodes by view count 2) display the results. Each episode should have one entry, period. \- Hulu should be a huge time sink for millions of people, but Hulu plus is the dumbest thing ever. Who wants to pay to see advertisers. The first time I saw Alec Baldwin and those Capital one barbarian morons I cringed and it was over. But every 4 minutes the same crap!! The best thing about your ads is the option to watch a long trailer. I can read a different tab while it plays and then I have a blissful uninterrupted viewing. \- No GOT. Unacceptable. Call HBO and hammer out a deal. Seriously, do this before the next season. \- Comcast and Time Warner are harming your business. their computer-fu is weak and the throttling speeds is slowing your s@#t down. The only solution is to click the little gear on the bottom right and make set quality (AKA user experience) to "medium". It is like setting the amplifier to 6 when it goes up to 11. \- Over the last year I have cut down the time I spend on Hulu from 4-5 hours a day (8 at my worst) to 1-2 a week. There are just too many quasi-legal alternatives out there to deal with your weak ass stuff. Make life easier dammit!

*[8 months ago]: 2013-08-20T19:08:34.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7078_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/6245874.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7078-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7078_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:41:23">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=1960714</link><title>Tell HN: My job struggle</title><description>Tell HN: My job struggle

10 points

by thecluttering

3 years ago

6 comments Follow

I can code. In a world of pre-maddona engineers I still count on my fingers. If I cube the largest number that's on the high side of your monthly page views, but I still want to work for you. Sometimes during the interview it's hard to explain why, to put yourself fully out there.

In some words, I feel like an interview refugee. The recruiters who are your friends until you are cut. After that even a friendly e-mail won't receive a reply. I have had interviews only to be told at the end that a paid internship is no longer being offered. I'm not sure if that's a lie, half truth, or just poor planning. I have had interviews that were interrupted by phone calls to the founders "other" business no less than five times. I have spent time on an assigned functional product to get garbage feedback and an interviewer who when I followed up hadn't even read my documentation. I had two interviews, sent in code samples, and completed a code test and asked if I was open to a trial period or apprenticeship of sorts. A week later that opportunity was nixed because they thought about it and said I don't have enough experience. False hope.

I had some great feedback from some companies. One setup a chat on the phone and said I would need to live in California and then perhaps something could happen in the near future. I had another company who wasn't looking for junior engineers but liked my style and the e-mail I wrote. There are nice people out there. Those people usually know what they want.

But I can code...

Not only can I code, but I'm a genuinely good person. I spent a year overseas teaching English to children in Korea. On a trip to the DMZ I met a young Argentinean who lives in Germany and works for company in Palo Alto. He said if you can code, you can get a job. I have an IT internship on my resume now so I thought that I could at least get another django internship.

I can code.

I'm not cynical, just feeling a bit worn from this experience. Part of it is my fault, that much I would admit. I decided to take a different path in college and graduated with an Anthropology degree. I couldn't handle the math portion of a computer science degree and didn't want to go to a technical school. So now I'm thinking about applying to a university for computer science. Of course this brings a whole new set of challenges and being a student changes a lot of things.

Just some soul searching, hope you don't mind. Throwaway account.

*[3 years ago]: 2010-12-02T02:14:46.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7078_02_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/1960714.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7078-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7078_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:42:04">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=5959992</link><title>Ask HN: Can you help me speak on the People's Stage at the Web Summit please?</title><description>Ask HN: Can you help me speak on the People's Stage at the Web Summit please?

1 point

by kieranoleary

10 months ago

0 comment Follow

Hi guys,

I've been nominated to speak at the Web Summit in Dublin in October but I need votes to secure my place.

You can vote for me here: http://www.websummit.net/competitions/peoples-stage/entries.html#1-226

You need a Facebook account but its straightforward to vote. You just like the link on the page above. Remember to confirm your vote. Otherwise your vote wont count.

The details of my talk are below. I'm an electronic engineer. My talk is based on my experiences of working in Korea. I think that Ireland can learn a lot from South Korea about developing a tech based economy. This is my little bit to help Ireland get back on its feet after a difficult couple of years economically.

Title: 'An upbeat chat on what post Celtic Tiger Ireland can learn from the "Irish of the Orient"'.

Description: I'm Irish, an engineer and an optimist. I believe that rumours of Ireland's demise are greatly exaggerated. Koreans are often known as the "Irish of the Orient". True to form, Ireland had its "Celtic Tiger", South Korea had its "Miracle on the Han". Both ended in economic woe. Let's take an upbeat, sometimes even humorous, look at what lessons Ireland can now learn from our Asian friends about creating a high-tech economic Phoenix from the ashes. We have more in common than you think!

The Web Summit is a great event and the People's Stage is a fantastic idea. If my talk doesn't float your boat, there are lots of other topics that you might like to vote for. Even if you don't vote for me, please think about supporting the talks that you would be interested in hearing if you were to attend.

Finally, if you're going to the Web Summit, I'd love to meet up and have a chat about my talk or anything else. It would be great to meet some other hackers.

Thanks very much. I appreciate it.

Kieran O' Leary

*[10 months ago]: 2013-06-28T19:49:15.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7078_03_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/5959992.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7078-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7078_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:43:11">http://www.eweek.com/c/a/Midmarket/Internet-as-Important-as-Food-Air-Cisco-Report-364137/</link><title>Internet as Important as Food, Air: Cisco Report</title><description>Internet as Important as Food, Air: Cisco Report (http://www.eweek.com/c/a/Midmarket/Internet-as-Important-as-Food-Air-Cisco-Report-364137/)

1 point

by jpietersma

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

Is the Internet as important as the air we breathe? According to a Cisco survey, many feel exactly that way. Rate This Article: Poor Best E-mail

Print

PDF Version

The results of a revealing survey from Cisco suggest the Internet has become such an integral part of our functionality that it is deemed as important to our lives as water, food or air. The "2011 Cisco Connected World Technology Report" found that more than half the study's respondents said they could not live without the Internet and cite it as an "integral part of their lives"in some cases more crucial than cars, dating, andhorror of horrorspartying.

One of every three college students and employees surveyed globally (33 percent) believes the Internet is a fundamental resource for the human raceas important as air, water, food and shelter. Nearly half (49 percent of college students and 47 percent of employees) believe it is "pretty close" to that level of importance. Combined, four of every five college students and young employees believe the Internet is vitally important as part of their daily lives' sustenance.

Two-thirds of students (66 percent) and more than half of employees (58 percent) cite a mobile device (laptop, smartphone or tablet) as "the most important technology in their lives." In addition, smartphones are poised to surpass desktops as the most prevalent tool from a global perspective, as 19 percent of college students consider smartphones their "most important" device used on a daily basis, compared with 20 percent for desktopsan indication of the growing trend of smartphone prominence and the expected rise in usage by the next generation of college graduates upon entering the workforce.

The finding also suggests the increasing prevalenceand sometimes intrusionof social networking in daily life. About nine out of 10 (91 percent) college students and employees (88 percent) globally said they have a Facebook account; of those, 81 percent of college students and 73 percent of employees check their Facebook pages at least once a day. A third said they check them at least five times a day.

College students reported constant online interruptions while doing projects or homework, such as instant messaging, social media updates and phone calls. In a given hour, more than four out of five (84 percent) college students said they are interrupted at least once. About one in five students (19 percent) said they are interrupted six times or morean average of at least once every 10 minutes. Additionally, 12 percent said they lose count how many times they are interrupted while they are trying to focus on a project.

In a sign that the boundary between work and personal lives is becoming thinner, seven of 10 employees "friended" their managers and/or co-workers on Facebook. Culturally, the United States featured lower percentages of employees friending managers and co-workersonly about 23 percentalthough 40 percent friended their co-workers.

The global study consists of two surveysone involving college students, the other on young professionals in their 20s. Each survey includes 100 respondents from each of 14 countries, resulting in a pool of 2,800 respondents. "The lifestyles of prosumers'the blending of professionals and consumers in the workplacetheir technology expectations and their behavior toward information access is changing the nature of communications on a global basis, noted Dave Evans, Ciscos chief futurist.

The second annual "Cisco Connected World Technology Report" examines the relationship between human behavior, the Internet and networking's pervasiveness. It uses this relationship to provoke thoughts around how companies will remain competitive amid the influence of technology lifestyle trends. The global report, based on surveys of college students and professionals 30 years old and younger in 14 countries, provides insight into present-day challenges that companies face as they strive to balance current and future employee and business needs amid increasing mobility capabilities, security risks, and technologiesfrom virtualized data centers and cloud computing to traditional wired and wireless networks that can deliver information ubiquitously.

*[3 years ago]: 2011-09-25T16:36:16.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7078_04_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3036090.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>