<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7083">I'm on the road again</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:03:19" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7083-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7083_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:04:38">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=1221670</link><title>Ask HN: Running a contest/competition</title><description>Ask HN: Running a contest/competition

4 points

by megamark16

4 years ago

2 comments Follow

So I'm working on my little side project, a webapp builder called AppRabbit (http://apprabbit.com) that is similar to Zoho Creator or DabbleDB. It's still missing some key features but I'd love to get people using it and giving me ideas for the direction I should take it. So I decided it might be fun to have a contest to see who can build the coolest or most useful app with it, and I'd give away something small like a gift card or a something as a reward to the winner.

So my question is, has anyone done something like this before? Do I need to worry about laws and regulations with regards to doing a little contest like this, or should I just wing it and try to keep it simple? I figured I'd just judge this round myself, and maybe down the road if I do something like this again have some sort of judging committee or something.

So what do you folks think?

*[4 years ago]: 2010-03-26T18:19:49.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7083_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/1221670.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7083-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7083_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:05:30">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=1791735</link><title>Ask HN: Considering quitting my day job to work on my startups</title><description>Ask HN: Considering quitting my day job to work on my startups

18 points

by podman

4 years ago

37 comments Follow

I launched two start ups about three months ago while still working a full time job. I honestly hoped that things would progress slowly with them and I wouldn't be overwhelmed or burn out. That turned out to not be the case. After launching, I no longer control the pace of things that go on and I find myself constantly focusing on them instead of my day job. My productivity over the past couple of weeks has dropped to almost nothing because I'm coding all day and all night. I'm not really even interested in the projects I'm working on at my day job anymore either. There are really two things that are holding me back right now:

1) The combined net incomes from both ventures is not enough to fully support my financially right now (not to mention I have partners for both companies so it's not like I can take all of the profit for myself anyway). I've got enough savings to support myself for about a year with zero income, so I've got a bit of a runway to see if things will work out and find a job if I need to, but it's still a large gamble.

2) My employer is already trying to hire another developer and has been trying to do so for a few months. Considering how hard of a time they're having finding one developer, I'm concerned that my leaving would put them in a very bad situation. I'm really good friends with everyone at the company and I'm worried that there might be some resentment towards me if I do leave. Then again, I'm not giving them 100% and that isn't fair to them anyway. If I don't quit it's possible that I might be fired down the road anyway.

Have any of you gone through this before? Anyone have any advice? Is there anything I'm probably not thinking about that might blindside me down the road?

Thanks!

*[4 years ago]: 2010-10-14T17:29:34.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7083_02_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/1791735.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7083-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7083_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:06:18">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=2129924</link><title>Ask HN: Work 15 hours/month Earn 100K USD/Year...now what?</title><description>Ask HN: Work 15 hours/month Earn 100K USD/Year...now what?

7 points

by dablue

3 years ago

12 comments Follow

DEAR HACKER NEWS:

5 years ago, I was lucky enough to start a non-public SAAS for a large global company. Before I showed up, they were doing things manually, spending &gt; hundreds of man hours per month and outsourcing totaling 200K USD/year.

After working like crazy the first two years, pulling all-nighters and automating everything as much as possible, I've shrunk their entire workforce down to 1 person (myself) and after a lot of optimizations now I only work ~15 hours a month earning 100K USD/year.

What they get is better quality than before, 10 times faster turnaround, and their budget slashed in half. Not to mention all their internal staff and facilities are free to work on other things.

I tried approaching potential clients in their same niche market. But it seems like the other players don't specialize in this area as much as the biggest player.

So I've concluded this is a deadend road for me, this task is at 100% optimization, effiency, and quality. But I find no use for this core technology in any other area except for this one company.

So I'm sitting on my ass and earning a good yearly pay while doing nearly basically nothing. What worries me is what should I be doing now?

P.S. No vacations to pat myself on the back, cuz basically it's a vacation at home for me everyday... and it's been like this for quite a while so I'm getting bored. I'm eager to work like the first two years and getting excited again... it's a rush for me to encounter a complex problem but to find a simple elegant solution. I find the process of writing code and learning new technologies enjoyable also. Especially when you're not sure and testing things out and suddenly IT WORKS!

Sincerely, 
DOING NOTHING AT HOME (for now)

*[3 years ago]: 2011-01-22T04:39:07.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7083_03_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2129924.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7083-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7083_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:07:20">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=1496597</link><title>I may have Carpal Tunnel Syndrome and I'd appreciate some advice. (Long Post)</title><description>I may have Carpal Tunnel Syndrome and I'd appreciate some advice. (Long Post)

6 points

by AgentConundrum

4 years ago

10 comments Follow

Even though I'm looking for general advice, I'd like to go over my situation in detail to minimize the chances of being offered advice that could further injure me. I therefore apologize for the length of this post. I understand that you folks aren't doctors, and nothing you say is medical advice. I'm here because this community is probably at a higher risk than average for this sort of injury, and so there's a better chance of hearing from people who have lived through this here than elsewhere.

Anyway, a couple weeks ago I started getting pain in my wrist while I was typing. I managed to get an appointment with my family doctor for a week later, but because of the pain and my fear of doing more damage, I opted to go to a walk-in clinic I've been to a number of times previously.

The doctor at the clinic seemed to assume it was most likely Carpal Tunnel Syndrome just based on the fact that the pain was in my wrist. He had me flex my wrists (Phalen's Maneuver) and tapped on the underside of my wrist (Tinel's Sign) but neither of these tests really did anything to me - there was no pain or tingling present in either case (NB: When I try Phalen's now, I feel a bit of pressure in the underside of my wrist, but that's it).

The doctor told me to get a wrist brace, and specifically told me to get one made for CTS. He told me that a lot of people flex their wrists into odd positions in the middle of the night, so I should wear the brace when sleeping and when typing. I looked this up later, and there are mentions online about CTS sufferers mangling their wrists like the doctor said, and that this can present as waking up with your hands numb/asleep. I had noticed this a few times recently, so things seem to line up there.

After looking at various models in the drug store and discussing the situation with a girl who worked there, I eventually purchased a relatively expensive model (http://www.amazon.com/M-Brace-Wrist-Splint-Size-Regular/dp/B000X9SUKA). I wore this brace home that day, and have generally worn it when typing since then and always while sleeping.

Things seemed to be improving until I went to my doctor the following week. At my appointment, my doctor did hardly anything to check on my condition, except trying Tinel's again (no symptoms presented during this test this time either). He examined the brace and had me put it on, and he said it was good. The point, he said, was just to limit the range of movement for my wrist, and that the brace did its job just fine. He asked me why I wasn't wearing it when I came in, and I told him that I only really wore it to bed and while on the computer. He told me I should be wearing it all the time, but that I could take it off to sleep (which struck me as horrible advice, given what I had researched). He told me I should wear it all day, and through the night if I wanted, for maybe the next week or 10 days, which I've mostly done. I asked him if that was a bad idea since I had read that leaving the brace on all the time could weaken the muscles, but he said that that only occurred over the long term, and a week wouldn't do any damage.

After wearing the brace all day for several days, I started noticing that the base of my thumb was stiff/sore and the area around my pinky was sort of the same. Everything else felt more or less ok, so I started not wearing the brace through the day, thinking that maybe the brace was constricting my thumb too much. Things have been pretty good for the last couple of days, but there's still lingering... awareness, I guess. I'm aware of a bit of a strain in my wrist/forearm (and there's a tingle in my elbow sometimes) from time to time, but it's mostly alright. In fact, I've typed this entire post without the brace mostly without pain. There is some noticeable strain, but by taking a lot of mini-breaks it's very manageable. I'm also aware that I shouldn't be pushing this hard, but I wasn't really expecting to write quite this much.

Another factor seems to be that I'm typing sitting upright on my smaller couch, with ample room for my right arm (the pained one). Normally, I type lying down on my other couch while watching TV or just relaxing, and my right arm can sometimes get pinned a bit. Another factor I think is probably relevant is that not terribly long before I started getting the wrist pain, my elbow/shoulder would feel a bit cramped while lying down and typing. I moved the pillow beside me out of the way and that seemed to help the issue. For this reason I'm wondering if I might have pinched a nerve or something which is helping cause these issues.

Before it's mentioned, I know that my "laying on the couch" arrangement isn't good for me, but it's a habit that formed out of convenience. I don't have a good desk chair (and even my cheap piece of crap chair is broken to the point that my posture would suffer), so I don't really use my desk anymore (I really never have since I got this laptop three years ago).

I'm currently unemployed (one year today!), so money is extremely tight right now. This means that I consider a lot of typical fixes (better desk, better chair, laptop dock with ergo-keyboard and trackball mouse) are hard for me to considr out of financial concerns.

The one expenditure I am considering is massage therapy. There is a school across the road from my apartment that only charges $27 per session, so I think I could talk myself into paying for a single session to see if it'll work out any pinched nerves I might have.

I have a few questions regarding the "free" fixes I can try:

* I've been taking a lot of Ibuprofin as an anti-inflammatory on the advice of my doctor. For the last couple of days, I've been taking two pills right before bed on the assumption that if my body does most of its healing while asleep, then the anti-inflammatories would do the most good if they reduced inflammation during periods of increased healing. Is this an accurate assessment, or is this more likely to be a placebo?

* Regarding icing, I've read a number of different options for this (rubbing ice directly on the wrist until the skin is pink to promote bloodflow, icy dips followed immediately by hot dips and repeated several times, gel packs, etc.). Is there a "best way" to go about icing? How often should I be icing the arm?

* Regarding stretching, am I risking damage by stretching (see http://lifehacker.com/5195481/exercises-that-protect-against-carpal-tunnel-syndrome) while the condition persists, or should I wait until the pain has dissipated via rest before beginning a stretching regimen?

* I lead a pretty sedentary lifestyle at the moment, but I've been thinking that cardio is likely a great idea since increased bloodflow would likely promote healing in the wrist. I'm told that the wrist, being a smaller tunnel, doesn't always have the best bloodflow, which is partly why wrist injuries like this can take so long to heal. Does this seem like a good idea? I'm thinking of walking all the way up the stairwell in my building (it's 9 stories to the top from my apartment) and back down.

* I've heard that the electrical nerve tests (or whatever they're called) are extremely painful, but would they be worth it to determine if this really is carpal tunnel? If the problem is carpal tunnel, I've heard that the surgery is pretty much batting 1000 in terms of permanently ending the pain. If the nerve conduction tests show carpal tunnel, should I get the surgery as a preventative measure? What's recovery like?

Sorry for the extremely long post, but I'm extremely worried about my present condition. I'm only 25 years old and I'm terrified that I'm going to end up unable to work or go back to school because of this issue. Just writing this post has been incredibly theraputic to me, especially since it hasn't been particularly painful to write (though there are pre-cursor signs in my wrist, so I should really rest a bit after this).

Thank you so very much for any advice or anecdotes or support you can provide!

*[4 years ago]: 2010-07-08T05:43:29.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7083_04_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/1496597.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7083-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7083_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:08:48">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=2765794</link><title>Ask HN: Established developer with no CS experience looking to catch up</title><description>Ask HN: Established developer with no CS experience looking to catch up

2 points

by inceptor

3 years ago

3 comments Follow

Hi HN!

I've been an avid spectator here for about a year now and wanted to start by thanking everyone here for keeping me up to date on the latest and providing a source for me to read intelligent discussion on the things I care about.

As a bit of backstory, I got into computing when I was about 12 years old and programming shortly thereafter. I never accomplished much, but I learned the fundamentals as I bounced from VB6 to C++ to C# to Java to PHP and eventually found Ruby whilst serving a tour of duty in Iraq a couple years ago. I was going to attend school after I returned and get a CS degree, but something much more wonderful happened that prevented me from doing so.

One day while I was in Iraq, I read a blog post written by someone who would become one of the most influential figures in my life that had a profound impact on the way I went about doing my hobby projects. I emailed him directly to express my gratitude, and to my surprise he responded! We continued to correspond during the remainder of my time overseas, and I worked on a small Rails project that he had the idea for but never the time to do.

Shortly after I returned home, he proposed one day that instead of going back to stocking shelves at Wal-Mart as I had originally intended to do when I got back, that I come work for his consulting company as an intern, with the potential for a salary offer sometime down the road. Midway through the year and I was a full salaried employee working for a respected consulting firm, which was more than I could have come to expect in my wildest dreams. Our firm was acquired by a hot startup earlier this year, and I'm now still doing my dream job in the company of some of the most amazing people I've ever met.

One thing has been itching at the back of my mind ever since last year though, and that's my tremendous lack of knowledge when it comes to CS fundamentals. Algorithms. Data structures. Math. These are things that I see most people in my field around me excel at, and I often find myself stumped at the what would seem to be the most trivial problems when it comes to them.

So today I decided that I am once again going to try my hand at seeking the advice of people who are way smarter than me in the hopes that something profound will happen.

What can I do now that I already have the career of my dreams, with no time for school, to gain the basic CS knowledge that I find myself lacking in?

*[3 years ago]: 2011-07-15T00:29:15.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7083_05_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2765794.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7083-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7083_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:09:15">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=3056549</link><title>Political messiah original mission jesus christ</title><description>Political messiah original mission jesus christ

1 point

by wendellbravo666

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

&lt;p&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt; Wendell Bravo god creation the wonders of the earth (3:16 god gave it begotten son that who ever believe in son of god jesus christ will have the everlasting life) game begin&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;the garden of eden the devil/satan/tabernacle union of sun and moon zeus (the woman)(strength)&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;adan and eve/cain and abel&lt;&lt;noah&lt;&lt;abrahan &lt;&lt;kingdom of jerusalem kings/david root offsping&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;ancient egyot&lt;&lt;the 10 commandments of god /god of israel moses testatment&lt;&lt;&lt;birth of christ&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;b.c &lt;&lt;satan temptation mt sinai&lt;&lt;0a.d. 100-900 a.d //10th//11th//12th//13th//14th////15th16th//17th//death of lord jesus christ roman republic nero everything i do it for you live ,jesus christ vs terminator arnold bon jovi holy roman empire of spain powerful kingdom of normandy invasion french revolution american revolution american invasion american occupation america abolition of slavery american indians american native america on invasion of spain (modern aztec empire)spain republic/democrat party devil/satanic vatican )(richeleu)king richaracj I lionheart &gt;got the game &lt;byzantine empire the crusaders of god's government shut down ming dynasty)(the present china beast heads country power asia republic)a.d.@( rebalation (@:18th century 1841 1851 spanish invasion american republican democrat party of republicans (republic of invasion of nero roman republic)anscestor homeland fatherland east of eden god the nature dreamtime database k.k.k.( philippine revolution )jose rizal death : 12/30/1896 7:03 a.m.19th century philippine 1901 world war 1&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;1945 raid and history of ash restore disslove stop roosevelt/quezon/laurel dissolve dear fatherland anscestors battle of homeland of rights of freedom and democracy fought out alien colonizer disturbed of peace enemy of freedom presence of evils in the world jeus christ faced problem destroy them illussion tyranny of iron fist world domintion .everyone has its own conciense guilty or not but im pity with them "fools awaken me angel demon deception point on the game"sbirth code of second vatican young republic 1950 on philippine history kalibapi guerilla warfare resisted movement "post"the revolution"armageddon fall of mother of babilon mother of harlot the great whoar sex with all kings(of roman republic/democrat seven country of the beast blessed by pope pius XI devil/satan/666 powerful kingdom of human slavery of (beat back)minion of evils symtetycally enslaving killing last remnants of humanity) in abolition of human slavery that deceive the world by devil/satan/666 and corrupted the earth.war of middle east (iraq/k.s.a/iran)philippine accross nostradamus code1991/1995/+/hit by Wendell Bravo prejudice by republic of the philippines (term of arthur alonte marriage division:wendell bravo age 21 minor married agnes arcilla cocent arlene arcilla sister)(case set up for rehabilation for 4 monts lock theraphy then estafa robbery asset worth million trysikel 90,000.00 cash,nanlalaki plus double wed,store bussiness name wendell"s toyland pacita arcade ,account : bp.i. bank pacita complex account name checking : mr. wendell bravo or agnes bravo for robbery unsolved for 15 yrs since october 3 1996.)(witness rollie villanueva,danny arzola)municipality of binan,laguna philippines police(almadin ,raquel,bjmp,zaldy reyes) and barangay(term alfredo surot arcega)living surviving 20th century up to now life on the road. prejudice /2000/20th century war of giants computer revolution fantacy icon surrealism piracy by minion of evil kamikaze abs cbn 2 and gma 7 announcer t.v radio babilon audio commercil icon fantacy novel on dreamtime cloud forming image pilgrimage of god hidden treasure,2002 bible kartilla steal horse i ride end of the world lion hath prevailed by 666 one world government the beast cant kill the beast ,2007 in on day 1 set the game 2008,lost again by steel horse okey&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; (2009,2010,2011, october 30 resisted nov 1,dec. 21 2011 mark on the calendar 2012)&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;locked code of world war 3 armageddon philippine bushido patriot lord jesus christ political messiah new heaven new earth mdg's 2015 powered by partnership better world around the world .system of god's government freedom of humanity in hands of evil.kingdom of god that will wrath the earth judment day .the world on perfection after armageddon in rise and fall armageddon children generation to universal dream world free r.p. will meet the mdg's 2015 .resisted creating system of god's government allied to serve and protect humanity in i granting authorithy to seized evil act new world end of enslavery freedom of humanity "fall of the republic".amen ,,,&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;21st century information technoly the future beyond this .amen.&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

*[3 years ago]: 2011-09-30T11:36:13.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7083_06_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3056549.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7083-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7083_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:09:59">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=6506463</link><title>Pressing Issues: Reinventing Journalism</title><description>Pressing Issues: Reinventing Journalism

1 point

by bradmerrill

7 months ago

0 comment Follow

We've just launched Pressing Issues, a publication with the goal of reinventing journalism. See http://pressingissues.net

It all started when a small group of journalists decided they wanted something new to read. They were looking for a news magazine that not only told them everything that was happening around the world each week, but that did so in an entertaining way. Ideally it would be gleefully sweary and eager to offend the rich and powerful. They realized this meant it probably wouldn't include any ads.

Upon realizing that this magazine didn't actually exist, they decided to create it.

And thus Pressing Issues was born.

We don't have a mission statement, but if we did it would probably say something about "reinventing journalism." It's a broken business. Everyone wants to make an app to make journalism smaller and smaller. I say it's time to make journalism big again. That's why we're publishing 3,000-word pieces online, and 10,000-word pieces in print. We're serious about this.&lt;p&gt;We're launching digital-only, but our print edition is just down the road (assuming we don't run out of cash and/or get sued into oblivion).

We're also going to have a radio show / podcast where we talk to our contributors about their pieces and expand on our written coverage.

I'm the founder, so feel free to ask me anything. Questions, suggestions, and hate mail are welcome.

*[7 months ago]: 2013-10-07T04:01:18.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7083_07_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/6506463.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>