<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7091">don't listen to a word i say</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:29:55" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7091-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7091_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:30:35">http://www.thomasmonopoly.com</link><title>THOUGHTS REGARDING THE #TAKEWALLSTREET PROTEST IN PROGRESS RIGHT NOW:</title><description>THOUGHTS REGARDING THE #TAKEWALLSTREET PROTEST IN PROGRESS RIGHT NOW: (http://www.thomasmonopoly.com)

1 point

by thomasmonopoly

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

Here are a few tips. Let me say first that I agree that if this was a Tea Party protest with as many people as there are on Wall Street the protest would be headline news. But there's not a media blackout like y'all are claiming. Tea Party shit sells newspapers. There are many reasons why, but the chief reason is that Tea Party people are fucking nuts and most of the nation is waiting for them to get violent. No one's watching because they care about the Tea Party, they're watching for the spectacle. I don't propose that you guys create a violent spectacle, but I'll give you one example of why no one cares about radical leftist protests. It's because you over dramatize them so much. When the Tea Party people protest they just stand around looking pissed off and waving flags and polishing guns. You guys on Wall Street, and I know this because I have been watching your live stream for the past two hours while I work, you people are sitting around parroting whatever anyone who stands up to speak says. It's almost ironic. For people who haven't seen the protest, everyone is sitting around, one person stands up, gives their statement one sentence at a time, and after each sentence the crowd repeats what was said. It's a good tactic, I've been to alot of protests and I've never seen that. But here's a recap, and I am typing word for word as I listen to it now:

Person #1: i have a proposal Crowd: i have a proposal Person #1: that we all meet Crowd: that we all meet Person #1: over by the staten island ferry in one hour Crowd: over by the staten island ferry in one hour

Person #2: i propose Crowd: i propose Person #2: that we all love Crowd: that we all love Person #2: and respect each other Crowd: and respect each other Person #2: since we are Crowd: since we are Person #2: hoping to Crowd: hoping to Person #2: achieve the same goal Crowd: achieve the same goal

Person #3: i propose Crowd: i propose Person #3: that we don't Crowd: that we don't Person #3: get arrested tonight Crowd: get arrested tonight

Person #3: i can't Crowd: i can't Person #3: stay the night Crowd: stay the night Person #3: but i will come back Crowd: but i will come back Person #3: tomorrow Crowd: tomorrow Person #3: i propose Crowd: i propose Person #3: that we protest tomorrow too Crowd: that we protest tomorrow too

Person #4: more peanut butter Crowd: more peanut butter Person #4: is on the way Crowd: is on the way

Person #5: i propose Crowd: i propose Person #5: that we all stay Crowd: that we all stay Person #5: true to our revolution Crowd: true to our revolution

And so on. For the past few hours. Tune in for yourself to see. So my advice is slow down a bit. You've got alot of wound up anarchists camping out, maybe keep the chanting to a relevant minimum so as not to blow your proverbial load too quickly. And chill out. If you're hoping to make this protest last two weeks I recommend a sit-in style protest, not the let's-all-sit-around-for-two-weeks-chanting-irrelevant-facts style protest. I'm gonna make it down to join in for a night, and I was going to go tonight before I saw the self-righteous crap going on for the inaugural night. So I do support your protest but christ, you're acting like you've been out there on a salt march for weeks and it's only been 8 hours. What's with the call for more computers and batteries? You're in New York City, J&amp;R is right around the fucking corner. Get your own batteries. Or send someone home to charge up their phone. You're not under attack.

So to summarize: sit back, relax, get used to the idea of a two week protest. And get Tinhat off the microphone. If you're protesting the TARP bailout try to stay on topic, no one needs to be giving "September 11th was an inside job" speeches. Like I said before, there has to be an equivalent of Godwin's Law that estimates the amount of time a protest can exist before it's co-opted by ego-maniacal conspiracy theorists. That is where the left's protests always fail, in my opinion.

In Support, Thomas Monopoly

Edit: And the guy with the megaphone who is currently screaming about how we are all American political prisoners, and who has the gall to be equating the conditions of any American anywhere in America with actual political prisoners being tortured in third world countries, is doing your cause a great disservice and claims like that are an insult to true political prisoners everywhere. I should start my own protest. It would go:

Me: Most of us Crowd: Most of us Me: have it pretty good. Crowd: have it pretty good. Me: But some of us Crowd: But some of us Me: Don't. Crowd: Don't. Me: We demand Crowd: We demand Me: More quality. Crowd: More equality. Me: But we're not going to compare ourselves to Bhutto Crowd: But we're not going to compare ourselves to Bhutto Me: Just for dramatic effect. Crowd: Just for dramatic effect.

*[3 years ago]: 2011-09-18T23:39:51.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7091_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3011600.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>