<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7103">cystic fibrosis treatment</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:51:49" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7103-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7103_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:52:36">http://www.livescience.com/14138-teen-cystic-fibrosis-drug-cocktail-contest.html</link><title>Teen Discovers Promising Cystic Fibrosis Treatment</title><description>Teen Discovers Promising Cystic Fibrosis Treatment (http://www.livescience.com/14138-teen-cystic-fibrosis-drug-cocktail-contest.html)

3 points

by pwg

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

*[3 years ago]: 2011-05-13T23:03:06.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7103_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2546562.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7103-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7103_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 18:53:54">http://www.wewantababy.com</link><title>Fertility Treatment abroad in India</title><description>Fertility Treatment abroad in India (http://www.wewantababy.com)

1 point

by 24x7esubmission

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

Infertility means not being able to get pregnant after one year of trying, Or, six months, if a woman is 35 or older. Women who can get pregnant but are unable to stay pregnant may also be infertile. Infertility is not always a woman's problem. Both women and men can have problems that cause infertility. About one-third of infertility cases are caused by women's problems. Another one third of fertility problems are due to the man.The other cases are caused by a mixture of male and female problems or by unknown problems.

Infertility affects about 10 percent of the population, men and women equally.Fortunately,most infertility cases can be treated successfully with conventional medical fertility therapies including medication or surgery. Infertility?

Infertility can be considered a disease like any other and is defined as a disease of the reproductive system that impairs the conception of children.The process of producing a child is very complicated and it is a surprise that infertility is not more common.

Fertility of a woman depends on many factors which includes production of healthy sperm by the man,production of healthy eggs by the woman,unblocked fallopian tubes to allow the sperm to reach the egg,sperm's ability to fertilize the egg when they meet in the fallopian tube,the ability of the fertilised egg called an embryo to become implanted in the woman's uterus,quality of the embryo and adequate hormonal environment in the woman.Infertility can take place if any of these factors is missing.

It is not impossible to cope up with infertility.Emotion and stress plays an important role in coping up with infertility.

The most common infertility cause in women is an ovulation disorder.Other factors include blocked fallopian tubes and endometriosis.Sometimes a woman can be born with birth defects,called congenital abnormalities,involving distorted structure of the uterus and uterine fibroids which can cause repeated miscarriages.The most common infertility causes in men includes azoospermia,which is when no sperm cells are produced, and oligospermia, which is when few sperms are produced.In some rare cases infertility can be caused by a genetic disease such as chromosomal abnormalities or cystic fibrosis.

Most couples are advised to seek medical help if they are unable to achieve pregnancy after one year of unprotected sex. Your doctor will then conduct a physical examination of both partners to diagnose their general state of health and evaluate physical disorders which may cause infertility.An interview may also be taken of the doctor.If neither the examination nor the interview proves successful,then more specific tests can be recommended.For the man,most tests focus on sperm analysis.For the woman this can include an analysis of body temperature at ovulation,a laparoscopy and an x-ray of the fallopian tubes and uterus.

In 85 to 95 percent of cases,infertility can be treated with conventional therapies,such as drug treatment and surgical repair of ones reproductive organs.Infertility or fertility treatment include fertility drugs,surgery,IVF - in vitro fertilisation,GIFT,ZIFT,donor egg and surrogacy.

When you are diagnosed with infertility problem the next problem that arises with it is the cost involved in this treatment. The costs of IVF treatments can be high,depending upon what tests are required,the type and dose of medication(s) used, and the number of IVF cycles required to become pregnant.All the tests and treatment cost considerable money,and since there is no prescribed time and the no of cycles, budgeting for medical expenses can be really difficult.On an average,IVF in the U.S. costs about $12,000 to $14,000U.S. Dollars (USD) for one cycle.Patients can spend up to $75,000 USD in treatments before becoming pregnant.IVF in other countries can cost as little as $2500 USD to $5000 USD per treatment.Fertility tourism is very attractive because a couple can plan a week long holiday, have the procedure done in a different country, and still return home with money saved by having the procedure done elsewhere.

Infertility treatment in India has become the most promising infertility treatment destination for a wide range of international tourists coming from all the corners of the world.It is not only within their budget,but also is available with high international class surgical facilities with quick medical appointments,plus medical care and service operations at the hands of experienced infertility treatment experts.The quality of Indian clinics and doctors expertise accompanied with the most competitive prices and lower treatment charges is attracting many patients and infertile couples from, USA, South Africa, Europe, East Asia and Canada.

Medical treatment is done in India at a fraction of the cost at which it is done abroad - in Europe or America.In the developed countries patients experience significant waiting times for diagnosis,treatment and face a lot of inconvenience that makes them seek medical treatment options abroad.People who seek medical treatment and facilities which is either not available in their country or is highly expensive and unaffordable are attracted by the benefits of low cost surgery and infertility treatment in India.The advantages of having medical facilities in India are

1] Availability of top Surgeons, Best doctors and Efficient medical staff 2] World Class Medical Treatment 3] Advanced diagnostic and surgery equipments 4] Excellent infrastructure of the Hospitals 5] Affordable Costs of Surgery 6] Optimum care for the privacy of the patient 7] No waiting list to follow 8] Patients without insurance are benefited the most 9] Easy availability of medical visa etc.

Patients seek infertility services in India for various reasons.These procedures are regulated in most European countries and the legal framework within which assisted reproductive technology can be practiced in a given country varies considerably. In some countries, the number of eggs that can be fertilized is limited,the number of embryos selected for transfer is limited,or the number of embryos that can be transferred is regulated.In addition,certain procedures like donor gamete use and surrogacy may be allowed in some,but not all,European countries.This fertility treatment options are available in India at the most economical cost.

The pregnancies achieved thanks to assisted reproduction techniques are not different from natural pregnancies.Thousands of couples have been benefited by these techniques and today are very proud and happy parents.

For more on IVF treatment options like Infertility Surgery,Operative Laparoscopy,Diagnostic laparoscopy, Hysteroscopy,Tubal blockage,Endometriosis,Menstrual issues,Problems with ovulation,polycystic ovarian disease when trying to start a family contact the IVF Infertility specialist doctors India,Male infertility,Doctors and specialist in male and female infertility from India.

Contact for Fertility Treatment India,Affordable IVF Infertility Surgery,IVF Treatment, Infertility Clinic India,IVF Clinic Mumbai,India at Rotunda Fertility Clinic. Phone: +91 22 26390044 or +91 22 26390088 http://www.rotunda.co.in or http://www.wewantababy.com or http://www.iwannagetpregnant.com or email at info.wewantababy@gmail.com

*[2 years ago]: 2012-03-23T06:19:04.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7103_02_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3743938.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>