<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7112">facebook icons</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:13:19" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7112-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7112_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:14:43">http://www.web3mantra.com/2010/10/04/ultimate-set-of-facebook-twitter-icons-vector-material/</link><title>Ultimate Set Of Facebook &amp; Twitter Icons Vector Material</title><description>Ultimate Set Of Facebook &amp; Twitter Icons Vector Material (http://www.web3mantra.com/2010/10/04/ultimate-set-of-facebook-twitter-icons-vector-material/)

1 point

by web3mantra

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

Finding decent hi-quality vector icons for free from search engines is very hard now, Because I found many results Which leads to sites that wanted to sell you icons. I Think there is no need to pay for things which is available for free. So today I compiled ultimate icons set of Facebook and twitter you can download and use it for free. Enjoy

*[3 years ago]: 2010-10-27T08:41:01.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7112_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/1837801.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7112-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7112_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:15:54">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=5916069</link><title>Disqus violating Twitter TOS and users trust</title><description>Disqus violating Twitter TOS and users trust

2 points

by faulkner8

10 months ago

2 comments Follow

In the dark of night, without notifying their users/customers, Disqus made a change that negatively affected their users and their users' commenters.

Whereas before, you could login directly to Twitter or Facebook to make a comment, now you are required to create a Disqus account before being allowed to login via Twitter or Facebook ( http://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/1165015-merging-your-social-login-to-a-disqus-account-has-important-benefits ).

That being said, Disqus still utilizes the Twitter and Facebook marks. When a user clicks on the Twitter/Facebook icons, after a series of redirects, they are prompted to create a Disqus account. This pretty clearly violates the Twitter "Developer Rules of the Road" (i.e. Principle #1 Don't Surprise Users). A user clicks on a Twitter icon and is prompted to register for Disqus...how is that not "Surprising users"?

Over a number of years Disqus has done a great job of building the trust of businesses to use their product. Now, if a business uses Disqus comments, when a user goes to login with their social profile on a businesses website, they are prompted to create an account with a third party.

If a website owner doesn't ask users to register to make a comment on their website, why does Disqus?

I guess the options are a) disable social service logins, or b) switch to a different service (Intense Debate?). While, c) Disqus letting us pay to disable this "registration step", would be acceptable too...ironically, that seems the least likely to happen.

*[10 months ago]: 2013-06-21T01:57:46.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7112_02_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/5916069.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7112-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7112_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:16:59">http://blog.launch.co/blog/google-copies-facebook-badges-and-icons-pixel-for-pixel.html</link><title>Google Copies Facebook Badges and Icons Pixel for Pixel</title><description>Google Copies Facebook Badges and Icons Pixel for Pixel (http://www.launch.is/blog/google-copies-facebook-badges-and-icons-pixel-for-pixel.html)

6 points

by kirinkalia

2 years ago

3 comments Follow

*[2 years ago]: 2011-11-09T23:39:55.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7112_03_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3218086.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7112-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7112_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:18:11">http://bl.anthonysutardja.com/post/27224802544/fb-unify-your-icons-already</link><title>Facebook: Unify your icons already</title><description>Facebook: Unify your icons already (http://bl.anthonysutardja.com/post/27224802544/fb-unify-your-icons-already)

2 points

by emptystacks

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

*[2 years ago]: 2012-07-15T03:34:14.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7112_04_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/4246021.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7112-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7112_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:18:56">http://mobile.theverge.com/2012/7/3/3133833/facebook-same-sex-icon-marriage-timeline-event</link><title>Facebook adds new status icons for same-sex marriages</title><description>Facebook adds new status icons for same-sex marriages (http://mobile.theverge.com/2012/7/3/3133833/facebook-same-sex-icon-marriage-timeline-event)

1 point

by daedecai

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

*[2 years ago]: 2012-07-04T04:40:14.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7112_05_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/4197634.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7112-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7112_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:19:49">http://mashable.com/2012/07/02/facebook-same-sex-marriage/</link><title>Facebook Adds Same-Sex Marriage Icons for Couples</title><description>Facebook Adds Same-Sex Marriage Icons for Couples (http://mashable.com/2012/07/02/facebook-same-sex-marriage/)

5 points

by popshopp

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

*[2 years ago]: 2012-07-02T16:25:18.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7112_06_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/4189496.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7112-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7112_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:21:29">http://www.engadget.com/2013/04/04/facebook-home-official-replaces-your-app-icons-with-social-info/</link><title>Facebook Home, replaces your app icons with social info</title><description>Facebook Home, replaces your app icons with social info (http://www.engadget.com/2013/04/04/facebook-home-official-replaces-your-app-icons-with-social-info/)

1 point

by hypr_geek

about a year ago

0 comment Follow

*[about a year ago]: 2013-04-04T17:40:58.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7112_07_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/5493970.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7112-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7112_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:22:54">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=5178840</link><title>User Experience - Adding Functionality to Navigation Menu - Worth It?</title><description>User Experience - Adding Functionality to Navigation Menu - Worth It?

2 points

by jhacks

about a year ago

0 comment Follow

I have a decision to make. Most standard navigation menus are simple. You click (or hover) and a menu appears with a list of links and each leads you directly to a new page. However, I was contemplating adding a bit of functionality to my navigation menu.

It must be mentioned that my web app is for video, although not quite the same, think youtube or even udemy as an example.

When my navigation displays, it does so without interfering with the video. What I was looking to do was just give each navigation item an extra layer. For instance, if "watch later" or "messages" are items in the navigation, you wouldn't be sent to a new page right away. You'd go down another layer where you could scan through a minimal list within the menu. You could still click to go through to the respective page, but you wouldn't be forced to as you would with a standard navigation menu.

I suppose Facebook does this with their notification icons. You can see your messages and friend requests without leaving the page. Or you can choose to "view all" and go to a new page.

I personally find this useful. But I wonder if others feel the same? I especially find it useful to have on a video site that then can't pull you away from what you are currently watching. The functionality could be enhanced further, enabling you to write a message or upload a video within the menu. I wonder if it's worthwhile implementing this for those that don't want to be forced to leave the page?

What are your guys thoughts / opinions? Anything helps. Thanks!

*[about a year ago]: 2013-02-06T21:09:28.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7112_08_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/5178840.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7112-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7112_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:24:30">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=2750533</link><title>Ideas for Google+ improvements</title><description>Ideas for Google+ improvements

3 points

by ignifero

3 years ago

13 comments Follow

Since HN likes Google+ so much, maybe we can point out what we don't like in the social service.

Here's my list:

\- The 'Buzz' tab : Why is that thing there? If i want to share something with the world, i just would. New users don't know what Buzz is and it's confusing, maybe it's best to just remove it.

\- Stream: Add more people: "Public" - Why not just add "The Whole World" as a circle - it's catchy

\- "Suggestions": This is a very facebooky/spammy type of thing. I want controlled social, not to be constantly reminded to friend people.

\- Post calendar: Since posts are usually long, and many people use their feed as a blog, add a calendar so we can browse the user's feed archive

\- Threaded comments: Be better than facebook, allow fully threaded comments. Also, smaller icons on comments (and possibly smaller font)

I m gonna stop here. You can add yours own below.

*[3 years ago]: 2011-07-11T13:22:13.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7112_09_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2750533.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7112-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7112_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 19:26:14">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=6958037</link><title>What are good open source or free social icons?</title><description>What are good open source or free social icons?

1 point

by fjordinbork

4 months ago

1 comment Follow

Bootstrap no longer includes fontawesome icons, and I need icons which they do not have. Does anyone know where I can get icons for meetup, github, goole, and facebook?

*[4 months ago]: 2013-12-24T03:13:18.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7112_10_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/6958037.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>