<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7141">Cambridge must do</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:21:47" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7141-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7141_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:22:43">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=4230082</link><title>GIS Engineer</title><description>GIS Engineer

1 point

by camsys

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

Cambridge Systematics, Inc. is the national leader in developing high quality, innovative solutions to the transportation industry. We are transportation specialists, dedicated to ensuring that transportation investments deliver the best possible results. By providing innovative policy and planning solutions, objective analysis, and technology applications, we help our clients meet future transportation needs while improving the performance of existing infrastructure and operations. Above all, we are committed to our clients' success in making transportation better for future generations.

Do you have a passion for all things geospatial? Do you speak Python? Do you know OGC from SDE and XML? Can you optimize an enterprise GIS? If so, we want you to join our team building spatially-enabled desktop- and web-based applications for our public sector transportation clients. These products include rich interactive data exploration and visualization systems, complex mathematical modeling tools, real-time information delivery, and sophisticated business transaction processing systems, all dedicated to improving transportation efficiency and safety. Every project is unique and our clients diverse.

You will work closely with the software developers to integrate spatial technology into these applications, through manipulating and populating spatial databases, developing high-performance map services, and providing advanced GIS expertise.

Requirements: BS or MS degree in GIS or Computer Science; hands-on-experience developing and maintaining enterprise GIS using ArcGIS Server &amp; ArcSDE, Microsoft SQL Server, Oracle and/or MySQL; experience developing GIS software/scripts using Python, C# and ArcObjects in a production environment. You must have excellent communication skills, be passionate about GIS and software, and enjoy working with clients to solve their spatial problems. Familiarity with GIS web technologies is a big plus.

CS is employee-owned with exceptional compensation and benefits. Qualified candidates please send resume to resume@camsys.com and reference Job Code CVO000301.

We are an Equal Opportunity Employer.

*[2 years ago]: 2012-07-11T17:01:23.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7141_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/4230082.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>