<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7150">senior java developer</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:56:31" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7150-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7150_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:57:19">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=3890474</link><title>Senior Java Developer \- Mobile Payments</title><description>Senior Java Developer \- Mobile Payments

1 point

by adamadmeris

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

Admeris Payment Systems Inc is a leading provider of PCI-compliant merchant processing solutions for e-commerce and m-commerce. Backed by a global acquiring network, Admeris can process in 144 currencies and settle funds in 19 currencies the next business day. Admeris supports Visa, Mastercard, Interac Online, Discover, China Union Pay and American Express with its payment gateway platform and supports merchant business needs with core API, hosted, silent redirect, mobile payment gateways and virtual terminal options.

We are seeking to expand our team of software developers/engineers/architects and are open to new candidates submitting resumes. If being on the cutting edge of industry changing payment technologies excites you, we want to hear from you!

Please send all resumes to careers@admeris.com ; when we see a good fit, the next step will be to take a quick 3 question online test to assess your skills.

Experience and Skills: Must possess a Bachelor level technical degree (Engineering, Computer Science, Math, etc.) or equivalent level of experience Must 8 or more years experience in java platform development Must have lead development as senior developer on a major project Must have expert knowledge on the JDK 6 and/or JDK 7 platform and frameworks Must have good knowledge of UML Must be familiar with Test-Driven Design, Domain-Driven Design and Model-Driven Architecture Must have good knowledge of architectural and design patterns, enterprise integration patterns, programming idioms and best practices Must be familiar with and have worked in major web development frameworks including but not limited to HTML, CSS, JavaScript, servlet/JSP, spring MVC, and JavaServer Faces Must have good working knowledge of java web services technologies including SOAP, REST, WS-* protocols, Axis, Spring Web services Must have deep knowledge about JPA including implementation (Hibernate, EclipseLink), mapping, caching, etc. Must have deep knowledge in database programming including JDBC, and specific database products such as PostgreSQL, MySQL, Oracle, etc. Must have good working knowledge of enterprise frameworks such as ESBs, JMS, EJB and JCA containers Be very comfortable with web security frameworks and protocols Have good system administration knowledge to be able to configure and setup software on Linux based systems including common security and middleware products Understand the mechanics of and be able to manage web system deployments on production grade hardware Have excellent knowledge of agile software practices such as software version control (such as GIT, SVN, etc.), issue tracking systems (such as JIRA, Bugzilla, You Track, etc.), continuous integration, test driven development, code reviews and quality metrics Have excellent English oral and written communication skills

Duties: Design and development a major web framework for high availability, high scalability, and solid security requirements Mentor more junior developers to develop software Be responsible to delivering an assigned schedule of development to required specification Implementation of more challenging portions of the software development projects Research advanced topics for possible future development Code review

Reporting to: Team/Project Manager as assigned by Company

Compensation: To be discussed based on experience, skills and test scores.

*[2 years ago]: 2012-04-25T18:56:22.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7150_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3890474.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7150-02"><link>http://www.questsearch.co.uk/jobs/q86233_senior-java-software-developer--3</link><title>Senior Java Software Developer \- 45,000-50,000 - North West</title><description>Senior Java Software Developer \- 45,000-50,000 - North West (http://www.questsearch.co.uk/jobs/q86233_senior-java-software-developer\--3)

1 point

by rhufnagel

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

*[2 years ago]: 2012-01-27T23:23:53.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7150_02_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3520680.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7150-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7150_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:58:50">https://www.netflix.com/entrytrap?locale=en-NL</link><title>Netflix Hires: Senior Java Developer \- Personalization</title><description>Netflix Hires: Senior Java Developer \- Personalization (http://www.netflix.com/Jobs?id=7563&amp;jvi=ooECVfwj)

1 point

by eishay

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

*[3 years ago]: 2011-07-05T18:05:22.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7150_03_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2730848.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7150-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7150_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:59:53">http://jobsburn.com/job-unavailable/</link><title>[Hiring] Senior Java Developer in Cape Town, South Africa</title><description>[Hiring] Senior Java Developer in Cape Town, South Africa (http://www.memejobs.com/job/2341/senior-java-developer-at-ad-dynamo/)

1 point

by Grape

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

*[3 years ago]: 2011-07-05T16:20:54.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7150_04_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2730416.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7150-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7150_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:00:32">http://traxia.com/</link><title>Job posting: Columbia Missouri</title><description>Job posting: Columbia Missouri (http://traxia.com/)

1 point

by jgaboury

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

Senior Java Developer Traxia of Columbia, Missouri is Cutting Edge Software Company for the Resale, Consignment and Antique Mall industry. The Company has been in in Business since 2005 and recently released a small business POS and inventory control program. The name of the application is Simple Consign and can be accessed at simpleconsign.com. Traxia is searching for an experienced Java Developer able to maintain and work with an existing team to complete a professionally designed program. Traxia is looking for a seasoned developer who is looking to work in a highly creative and innovative small business work environment.

Education and Work experience: Bachelors degree in software engineering or computer science, or equivalent experience A minimum of 4 years of professional experience designing, developing and supporting web-based applications Prefers an Agile Approach to software development

Required Knowledge and Skills:

Able to design, build and maintain a Java web application Need experience setting up and maintaining many Linux servers using Amazon AWS and Rackspace cloud platforms Agile Software development experience: Scrum, Extreme Programming (XP), or other Agile Software development practices, including Test-Driven Development (TDD) Have been successful leading a Java development Team Is comfortable monitoring and mentoring other developers on OOD and TDD Experienced in finding and hiring development talent Able to lead in the assessment and development of new technologies and development practices Likes working in a team environment and works well with other aspects of the company (Sales, IT, Administration) Has a working knowledge of integration of hardware and web applications including PC and Mac and POS hardware Maintain and improve established software environment and able to review and learn existing code environment Professional experience with MySQL, Java Script, Java, and AJAX

Preferred Knowledge and Skills:

Good understanding of Object Oriented Design and Design Patterns Professional experience with related database platforms Professional experience developing multi-threaded distributed systems Professional experience with HTML and UI web sites Experience with Play! Framework Have built and maintained automatic deployment process using Gradle

Experience with GWT Experience deploying and maintaining Apache and Tomcat Professional experience with Spring and Hibernate (or other JPA libraries) Experience with common source code control tools, especially Mercurial Familiar with common server operating systems, especially Linux Experience in Open Source technologies, projects, and communities Systems Integration experience

How to Apply:

To apply for this position, please send your resume to joe@traxia.com

*[2 years ago]: 2012-05-22T19:32:13.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7150_05_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/4009516.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7150-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7150_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:01:53">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=1960140</link><title>Which Job Board is good to find senior java talent?</title><description>Which Job Board is good to find senior java talent?

1 point

by windust

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

Looking for a good job posting place to find a senior java developer (we know that referrals are best, but nothing so far, so we are going to go out to the net and ask). JoelOnSoftware? Hacker News doesn't accept job postings from outside, so where would you post if you were looking to find talent?

The position is here http://www.optionscity.com/jobs/seniordeveloper.htm

Thanks!

*[3 years ago]: 2010-12-01T23:09:42.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7150_06_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/1960140.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7150-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7150_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:02:28">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=6679418</link><title>Senior Application Engineer (Java Developer)</title><description>Senior Application Engineer (Java Developer)

1 point

by mollyflynn

6 months ago

0 comment Follow

MTV Artists is a platform that helps artists connect with an audience and make money. Using the power of the MTV Music Groups 600 million television households and 60 million online visitors, artists of all sizes, shapes and sounds are invited to claim or create pages, promote what they want, submit songs for use in TV shows, submit videos for use on-air, and connect with a passionate audience of engaged music fans worldwide. Were looking for a Senior Application Engineer who loves to code, has experience building scalable infrastructures and systems, and is excited about working on the future of music from the inside one of the most powerful brands in the space. &lt;p&gt;Your responsibilities Design and build new services Must have Web application or internet application development experiences Collaborate with front-end engineering team and outside vendors who consume the services you build Work with product team to develop prototypes Provide high-level support for live sites and services &lt;p&gt;Required skills and experience Expertise in designing and building Java web applications with an emphasis on the Spring framework. Expertise in designing relational database schema and understanding how to optimize complex database queries. Comfort and efficiency operating in a Linux environment. Strong knowledge of the fundamentals of how common Internet technologies work (HTTP, DNS, etc.) A solid grasp of how common browser technologies work (CSS, JavaScript, Ajax, JSONP) A creative and solution-oriented mentality Writing and UI design skills a plus &lt;p&gt;If this sounds like you, and youre ready to join an awesome team and a great company, please send your resume and cover letter to ArtistPlatformJobs@viacom.com.

*[6 months ago]: 2013-11-05T23:51:35.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7150_07_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/6679418.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7150-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7150_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:03:21">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=2783125</link><title>20+ New Positions in Boston &amp; NYC at Game Changing Me-Commerce Retailer Gemvara</title><description>20+ New Positions in Boston &amp; NYC at Game Changing Me-Commerce Retailer Gemvara

3 points

by dmarques1

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

Gemvara is transforming how people shop. With our innovative customization technology, just-in-time manufacturing, personalization technology, and virtual inventory, we are creating the future of retail every day.

Some of our current open positions include: 
\- VP Engineering

\- Build/Release Engineer

\- Director of User Experience

\- Director of Analytics

\- Director/VP Merchandising

\- Seniro Systems Engineer

\- CAD Renderer Extraordinaire

\- E-commerce Software Developer

\- Senior Website Copywriter

\- Flex/Coldfusion Developer

\- Senior Web Designer

\- IT Support Engineer

\- Java Software Developer

\- Interns and Apprentices

\- Customer Care Specialists

For more details visit - http://www.gemvara.com/Careers/pages/v/about/careers/

*[3 years ago]: 2011-07-19T21:19:38.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7150_08_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2783125.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7150-09"><link>http://bit.ly/16upmth</link><title>Senior Tester - READING - SALARY DOE</title><description>Senior Tester - READING - SALARY DOE (http://bit.ly/16upmth)

1 point

by darylk

9 months ago

0 comment Follow

java developer needed easy to aplly just check it out if your looking for an It job

*[9 months ago]: 2013-08-05T12:06:29.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7150_09_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/6159613.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7150-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7150_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:06:03">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=6231688</link><title>Moving to USA (NYC) Need Advice</title><description>Moving to USA (NYC) Need Advice

39 points

by JackOfAll

8 months ago

56 comments Follow

Hello All, I need a bit of advice as my research on google has not cleared my doubts. I am based out of Hong Kong as a C++ and Java developer (10 years exp) and my company (an Investment Bank) has decided to move my role to New York. I have persuaded my bosses to relocate me to NYC and they have agreed. Though the HR talks have not yet happened regarding salaries, i would like to prepare and set mine and their's expectations.

After a lot of research on google/glassdoor/etc, i have come to the following conclusions: 1\. I might not get the best market salaries (Asian/NYC being high cost center/non native English speaker/first timer to USA/etc) 2\. I should range my salary expectations in a range of 130K-150K just to be safe in the zone and not miss out on the job. Is this fair? 3\. I have no option but to work in NYC and live in NJ. It seems that this is the sanest thing to do. 4\. Taxes being high compared in NYC, I can safely assume 40% of my salary being cut. So that leaves me in a range of 78K-90K after tax. Assuming my rental will be around 2k and monthly expenses around 1k, that would leave me with 42K-54K. This i believe should be more than enough. 5\. My life-work balance might go for a toss given that longer hours are the norm in NYC (Wall Street). Am i right? 6\. Given that i will be moving to USA on an L1 B visa? (not a senior management guy) i can apply for a GC (as in Green Card, not the other GC) as soon as i join and get it in around 2-3 years. Am i right?

My preparation for my move has not yet started and i am sure that i will have more questions. Since i have no one in USA (friends/family/etc) i am completely reliant on YC.

Please let me know on the above points and if any of my assumptions are wrong. Also please feel free to advice me on anything that you think would be a appropriate.

Warm regards from Hong Kong...

*[8 months ago]: 2013-08-18T04:47:14.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7150_10_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/6231688.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>