<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7154">stones satisfaction</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:22:40" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7154-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7154_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:23:44">http://www.gmb.in/contactus.htm</link><title>Gita Murti Bhandar is an established and respected name within India</title><description>Gita Murti Bhandar is an established and respected name within India (http://www.gmb.in/contactus.htm)

1 point

by gmbstatues

6 years ago

0 comment Follow

Gita Murti Bhandar is an established and respected name within India. GMB.in has built upon this solid foundation to offer the highest possible level of products and satisfaction to our invaluable people located in India as well as outside India. We use the best quality marble and stones for these statues so that they retain their sheen for a long period of time.

Gita Murti Bhandar is an established and respected name within India. GMB.in has built upon this solid foundation to offer the highest possible level of products and satisfaction to our invaluable people located in India as well as outside India. We use the best quality marble and stones for these statues so that they retain their sheen for a long period of time.

My Information: http://www.gmb.in/

Tel: +91 (0) 79 65129611

Mobile: +91 (0) 9327010087

E-Mail: enquiry@gmb.in Address: Gita Murti Bhandar 48, Super Mall, C. G. Road Ellisbridge, Ahmedabad - 380006 Gujarat, India

*[6 years ago]: 2008-09-04T10:55:06.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7154_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/294685.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7154-02"><link>http://fireside-stove.com/</link><title>Fireside Stove Shop | Massachusetts Stove</title><description>Fireside Stove Shop | Massachusetts Stove (http://fireside-stove.com/)

1 point

by lexseo

5 years ago

0 comment Follow

This has a stylish look and effective performance making this brand stand apart from the others. With their eco-friendly technology and dedication to customer satisfaction, their stoves and products will leave a smile on any one's face.

*[5 years ago]: 2009-04-10T14:52:12.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7154_02_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/556121.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7154-03"><link>http://www.glazeworks.us/</link><title>GLAZE Inc. - GLASS | STONE | STEEL</title><description>GLAZE Inc. - GLASS | STONE | STEEL (http://www.glazeworks.us/)

1 point

by prosite123

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

At GLAZE we are dedicated to providing exceptional, quality high-end finished work. We believe in complete satisfaction by creating a successful partnership with our clients, designers and architects.

*[2 years ago]: 2012-03-25T12:08:17.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7154_03_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3752370.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7154-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7154_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:25:52">http://www.livescience.com/10783-worry-happiness-levels-set-stone.html</link><title>Don't Worry: Happiness Levels Not Set in Stone</title><description>Don't Worry: Happiness Levels Not Set in Stone (http://www.livescience.com/health/happiness-life-satisfaction-change-101004.html)

1 point

by jkaljundi

4 years ago

0 comment Follow

*[4 years ago]: 2010-10-14T10:48:26.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7154_04_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/1790473.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7154-05"><link>http://www.classifiedads.com/real_estate_services-ad6315002.htm</link><title>Do-it-yourself Pool Problems</title><description>Do-it-yourself Pool Problems (http://www.classifiedads.com/real_estate_services-ad6315002.htm)

1 point

by edroyhuang

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

Upkeep of a backyard pool is ideally done in a weekly basis. Common problems with pool water require immediate attention, while issues on the pool structure itself can be delayed until your next break. But to be able to maintain the beauty and the satisfaction that you get during your pool recreation, all of these problems should be mended and given utmost attention. Maybe one of the problems that a pool owner has to encounter is green algae formation and cloudy water. Green algae create a slimy feel on the pool surface and this problem is usually caused by poor filtration system or inactive levels of sanitizer. The good news is that, this could be fixed easily! Check the ph of your pool. Adjust it if is beyond 7.5. Brush the walls and floors and voila, problem solved.

With age, cracks in pools are apparent. As years pass, your pool would show signs of wear and tear. This problem usually leads to leaks. To prevent this, replacement is needed. For minor problems, this could be fixed without help from professionals. Start the process by cutting the crack area using a grinder or a diamond blade. The crack must be allowed to dry and be free from any substance. Then, it is best to apply a caulk to the crack. Once dried, create sand and cement mixture that would cover the crack. The use of knife or trowel is necessary in this process. The lining of pools usually have problems too. Town or ripped vinyl liners are common especially if the pool had undergone constant water imbalance. Age is also a reason for this problem. However, the solution for this is easy. The vinyl lining could be mended by purchasing kits that are available in hardware stores. There are different instructions for each manufacturer on how to best patch the lines tear.

Upkeep of pools is actually easy and does not require help from professional. However, for more complicated problems, it is necessary to consult trusted builders to solve it. Not only that it would require much of your time. But at the same time, prevent further damage on your pools.

Poulson Tile and Masonry is the leading pool repair system in San Diego. They are known for their outstanding workmanship and excellent results. For a trusted builder in San Diego, visit http://poolssandiego.com/.

*[3 years ago]: 2011-09-22T02:59:11.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7154_05_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3024676.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>