<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7166">pita recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:27:20" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7166-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7166_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:27:46">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=57538</link><title>Food Ideas for Startup Guys</title><description>Food Ideas for Startup Guys

36 points

by majimojo

7 years ago

65 comments Follow

Share your food hax.

Stay happier programming by eating good. When you're not in the mood for Cup Ramen and the Dollar Menu at MickyD's.

My favorite relaxer when under stress is Basil Tomato Soup. It really helps me clear my head for more programming. Takes 5-10 minutes to prepare and put in pot. Then forget about it for 40 minutes while it cooks (don't even have to stir).

When I only have 1 minute to microwave something, I make a 1337 Haxor Boca (my own concoqtion). Recipes below.

1) 1337 Haxor Boca

Buy Spicy Chicken Boca Burger at Safeway, some Spicy Hummus, and Pita Bread. Microwave the spicey chicken boca burger for 1 minute. Toast the pita bread if u want to. Cut the pita in half. Cut the boca in half. Put one half of the boca into each pita half. Use a knife and wedge some Spicy Hummus in. Done. Tastes great. Fills you up for 6 hrs. Nothing to clean.

Needs: Box of Spicy Chicken Boca Burger, Pita Bread, Hummus, Microwave

2) Basil Tomato Soup (is this a tuscan thing?):

(Best when you have stale hard bread laying around that you don't want to waste)

Chop 4 garlic cloves into chunks (like the size of rice or bigger). In a saucepot, heat 2 tbsp olive oil on medium. Throw in the garlic. Put a layer of the stale (hopefully not moldy) bread on the bottom. Toast the bread a little in the pot. If you don't have stale bread, throw a handful of rice in instead (abt 2 tbsp). Then put 1 can of whole tomatoes in ($1 from safeway). Canned tomatoes are better than produce section tomatoes because they are easier to use and canned when they're the freshest (food hack!). Put half a can of water in. When it boils. Turn the heat to the low setting. Chop a handful of basil. Throw it in. Come back in 40 minutes for something great. Add salt to taste.

Needs: Can of whole tomatoes, Basil, Garlic, Stale Bread, Olive Oil, a Stove.

*[7 years ago]: 2007-09-20T19:03:23.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7166_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/57538.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>