<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7239">roundabout safety</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:08:17" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7239-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7239_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:08:48">http://www.theory-test.co.uk/asp/hpt_flashdisplay.asp</link><title>Why hazard perception skills are important while passing DSA driving test</title><description>Why hazard perception skills are important while passing DSA driving test (http://www.theory-test.co.uk/asp/hpt_flashdisplay.asp)

1 point

by johngraham

4 years ago

0 comment Follow

Hazard perception element in DSA driving theory test -

Hazard perception test forms a second section of the theory test and must be passed at the same time. Integrating theoretical hazard perception test training into the practical training sessions will ensure that as competence is achieved in each of the necessary skills, they can be strengthened and applied while you are on the road to increase the road safety benefits.

If you follow good driving practices you can avoid potentially dangerous situations while driving. Hazard percpetion test more information can be gathered here online http://www.theory-test.co.uk/asp/hpt_flashdisplay.asp

THINK road safety advice to keep everyone safer on the UK urban roads -

Why speeding is a bad idea

Deciding what speed to drive at is a continuous process and can be a difficult judgement to make. THINK! has put together some tips to raise drivers' awareness of the dangers of driving too fast.

Driving too fast is bad driving

Drivers rightly think things like poor lane discipline (e.g: not getting into the right lane before a turn-off or roundabout, or failing to keep to the left when not overtaking on motorways and dual carriageways), failure to signal and driving too close are examples of poor driving.

Excessive speed is a criminal offence

"Excessive speed" means going over the speed limit. Doing this is a criminal offence and, if you're caught, it's likely to result in a fine and penalty points on your licence. In most cases, you'll get a standard fine and licence endorsement. But more serious cases may result in you being taken to court.

Inappropriate speed is too fast

You don't have to be driving over the speed limit to be driving too fast. "Inappropriate speed" means driving within the speed limit, but too fast for the road and traffic conditions. It includes approaching a bend or junction too fast, not negotiating narrow roads properly and overtaking where it's inappropriate.

Inappropriate speed can also be a factor in poor weather conditions and when driving at night. Choosing the appropriate speed is about judgement, most people think they get it right. Sadly, the statistics show many get it wrong.

Follow the advice, make yourself aware of the potential driving hazards and you can be safer driver of the roads.

About hazard perception test

New drivers are involved in accidents, especially in the first months after passing a driving test. It has been proven that drivers who have taken hazard perception test training have much better hazard perception test skills.

Are you preparing for UK DSA driving theory test?

Do not spend your money on multiple DSA theory test attempt. For online driving theory test questions including new case studies and how to prepare for driving test, Pass at first attempt. Pass with confidence.

On the website, you can access entire official DSA driving theory test question bank as well as interactive hazard perception clips for car and bike driving theory test. Access online dsa theory test questions here: http://www.theory-test.co.uk/asp/daily_mock_test_car.asp

About Company -

Theory-test.co.uk is the leading website to help prepare for the UK driving test. It is the official license holder of DSA theory test question set from the controller of HMSO and the DSA. The site witnesses multimillion hits every year and is the leading choice of users all over UK.

Contact Us -

Theory-test.co.uk
St. Helier, Channel Islands,
Jersey.
JE2 3GF. UK
http://www.theory-test.co.uk
admin@theory-test.co.uk
*[4 years ago]: 2010-08-19T11:15:02.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7239_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/1617018.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>