<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7250">collagen vascular disease</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:32:13" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7250-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7250_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:33:20">http://www.unsafedrugs.com/zestril/</link><title>Zestril</title><description>Zestril (http://www.unsafedrugs.com/zestril)

1 point

by unsafedrugs

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

Zestril is a drug prescribed for treatment of hypertension. It contains Lisinopril as main active ingredient. Lisinopril belongs to Angiotensin converting enzyme or ACE inhibitors group of drugs. It is a synthetic peptide derivative and administered orally. It comes in 2.5 mg, 5 mg, 10 mg, 20 mg, 30 mg and 40 mg tablets. It contains calcium phosphate, magnesium stearate, mannitol, red ferric oxide, starch as inactive ingredients.

Zestril lowers the blood pressure and hence is used for treatment of high blood pressure or hypertension. It is also used for treatment of congestive heart failure. It improves survival after a heart attack.

People who are allergic to Lisinopril or suffer from any other allergy should avoid using this medicine. Patients should also consult their doctor about their medical history or any medication being used as it may interact with other drugs or could worsen certain medical conditions. Use of this drug could produce allergic reactions such as swelling of the face, lips, tongue or throat, dizziness, lightheadedness or other allergic reactions. Patients suffering from angioedema, high level of potassium in the blood, collagen vascular disease should not use this drug. Patients going under blood filtering procedures such as LDL apheresis, dialysis should also avoid this medicine. It could worsen their condition.

This medication is not meant for pregnant woman. If a patient is pregnant or planning to conceive, should not use this drug as use of this drug could harm an unborn baby or cause birth defects. Nursing mothers should also avoid this medicine as it may harm the baby. Use of this drug could cause serious liver problem in some patients. If a patients experience yellowing eyes or skin, dark urine, severe stomach pain, persistent nausea or vomiting while using this medicine, he should immediately call the doctor, as it may be a symptom of liver problems including Jaundice.

Use of this drug could also cause muscle weakness, pounding or uneven heartbeats, chest pain or rapid weight gain. Some patients could also experience muscle cramp while using this drug. It could also produce too much sweating, diarrhea, or vomiting and could lead to dehydration. People who take Zestril after a heart attack are likely to develop extremely low blood pressure or kidney problems. It could also make patient suffer from pelvic pain, Pancreatitis, heartburn or urinary tract infections. Use of alcohol while using this drug could even worsen the condition of the patient.

*[2 years ago]: 2012-01-24T12:31:45.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7250_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3504430.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>