<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7293">basil recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:00:23" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7293-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7293_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:00:52">http://pegasuslegend-whatscookin.blogspot.nl/2013/07/bruschetta-basil-insalta-caprese-style.html</link><title>Bruschetta Basil Insalta Caprese Style Recipe Video</title><description>Bruschetta Basil Insalta Caprese Style Recipe Video (http://pegasuslegend-whatscookin.blogspot.com/2013/07/bruschetta-basil-insalta-caprese-style.html#.UeptTzphxaM.hackernews)

1 point

by pegasuslegend

9 months ago

0 comment Follow

*[9 months ago]: 2013-07-20T10:58:28.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7293_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/6074880.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7293-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7293_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:02:21">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=4934588</link><title>Hacker fuel: lifeguard's red beans &amp; rice/potato/noodle recipe</title><description>Hacker fuel: lifeguard's red beans &amp; rice/potato/noodle recipe

6 points

by lifeguard

about a year ago

4 comments Follow

Save money, be healthy, eat good food!

Every Monday I cook some red beans.

99 cents for 8 servings of dry red beans. One serving is over 33% RDA for protein, 15% Iron, 10% Vitamin C. Add rice or potato and you are full! 5 lbs of potatoes is 1 - 3 dollars. Ramen 99 cents for 4 - 8 packs.

1\. before you go to sleep for the night, put 1/2 cup of dried red beans in pot full of cold water to soak at least 8 hours (or bring to a boil, let set for 10 min, change water and follow recipe)

2\. two hours before you want to eat, start cooking beans: drain old water, add 3 cups fresh water and bring to a boil, then reduce to a low simmer for around an hour

3\. add 2 spoons wershishire sauce, 2 spoons catsup, 4 spoons oil, salt, pepper, bay leaves, oregano, basil , hot sauce. add optional chopped onion/garlic/bell pepper/jalapeo and simmer for 40 more minutes

4\. use a big spoon to smoosh 1/4 of beans against side of pan to thicken sauce and start boiling water to cook rice/potato/noodle. About 20 minutes.

Serve beans over rice/noodles.

OR -- just cut a potato into chunks and throw into pot to cook for 20 minutes

OR -- just throw in a ramen noodle packet in beans and cook last 10 min

OR -- microwave/bake a big potato and pour beans over this with some fresh chopped onion if avail.

Make a double size batch and save half of it and make burritos or whatever in a few days.

*[about a year ago]: 2012-12-17T21:50:03.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7293_02_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/4934588.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7293-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7293_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:02:57">http://www.paprikaapp.com</link><title>Rate my app: Paprika Recipe Manager for iPad</title><description>Rate my app: Paprika Recipe Manager for iPad (http://www.paprikaapp.com)

30 points

by stevenwei

4 years ago

32 comments Follow

http://www.paprikaapp.com

I've always been big into cooking and when the iPad came out I figured it would be the perfect replacement for the massive stack of printed recipes I had collected over the years.

But after trying out the iPad recipe apps in the store, I realized that most of them did not allow you to enter your own recipes, and the ones that did were incredibly cumbersome to use. (E.g. having to enter recipes from an external website, or having to fill out 24 fields to get a single recipe entered.)

So the idea for Paprika Recipe Manager was born, and a few months later, it is now available in the App Store.

The basic premise of Paprika is basically an Instapaper for recipes. It comes with a built in web browser that lets you save recipes from the web. (Which is mostly how I discover my new recipes.)

We designed the app to be as simple as possible to create and save recipes. Some of the other apps in the store require you to enter ingredients one at a time, specifying quantity and units separately, and then entering your recipe directions one step at a time. This makes the process for entering a single recipe way too cumbersome and takes up too much time.

We took the opposite approach and basically give you two big text fields for your ingredients and directions. Entry is completely freeform and you can basically put in whatever you want. This also makes it very easy to save recipes from the web (since they can be presented in all sorts of arbitrary formats).

Features include:

- Ability to type in your own custom recipes in a fairly easy manner.
- Ability to save recipes from the web.
- A grocery list that lets you add recipe ingredients as well as your own items.
- Fully customizable categories, search, favorites, and emailing recipes.
- Preventing the screen from turning off while cooking.

Here are a few promo codes to get you guys started:

E7LL36X4EJYP
7A7M9LXXLRJJ
LLK9KAWAYXLJ

Any and all feedback is greatly appreciated. The response has been fairly positive so far (in terms of ratings and reviews), although there is definitely room for us to improve.

I'm especially interested if anyone has thoughts on marketing and promotion. I've done the standard tasks of posting a press release and emailing a bunch of websites/blogs...but don't really know where to go from there. Has anyone had success with a Youtube teaser, or Facebook/Google ads, or buying ad banners on other sites?

*[4 years ago]: 2010-10-16T19:52:31.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7293_03_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/1798717.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7293-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7293_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:03:30">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=2135562</link><title>Ask HN: Review my startup - YumTab, universal recipe box, Delicious replacement</title><description>Ask HN: Review my startup - YumTab, universal recipe box, Delicious replacement

14 points

by jkkramer

3 years ago

24 comments Follow

YumTab started as a weekend project to help my girlfriend and I manage recipes we found online and cooked. Many weekends and week nights later, YumTab is close to where I want it to be.

http://yumtab.com/

It's a universal recipe box that saves recipe bookmarks along with things like ingredients, which get extracted from the page automatically. It also has a basic planner, shopping list, and sharing features.

Existing solutions were inadequate. There are a few "universal recipe box" / recipe bookmarking sites out there, but they all suffer from one or more of: restricted site support, need to copy &amp; paste ingredients manually, or cumbersome, ad-riddled interface.

I tried to focus on making YumTab a useful complement to recipe sites for actual cooks, rather than just another source of food porn (not that there's anything wrong with that -- there's just plenty of good solutions already).

The homepage design has gone through many iterations. Comments about that would be appreciated.

I'm more coder than hustler at this point, so promotion &amp; monetization suggestions welcome. I've considered requiring one-time payments, a la pinboard.in (maybe with a free limit of 100 recipes or so) but I'm not sure how well that would work. I'd like to avoid plastering the site with ads.

FYI, it uses PHP on the frontend and Clojure on the backend.

Thank you!

*[3 years ago]: 2011-01-24T16:28:52.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7293_04_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2135562.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7293-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7293_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:04:16">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=2249760</link><title>Recipe: Easy to remember, service specific and secure passwords</title><description>Recipe: Easy to remember, service specific and secure passwords

4 points

by torstesu

3 years ago

6 comments Follow

People, even tech-savvy ones, have a tendency to use a single or a low multiple of different passwords for different services, making them vulnerable to unauthorized access.

The challenge is how to make strong, service specific passwords which are easy to remember. Here is a recipe:

1\. Construct a complex password key with a minimum length of 8 characters, e.g -Kr/2.pq4. 
2\. Make an algorithm based on the URL. E.g. news.ycombinator.com 
a) Take the last 4 characters in the URL, excluded the domain suffix: ator 
b) Shuffle the letters in a based on your algorithm: orat 
3\. Combine the password key and the output of your algorithm: orat-Kr/2.pq4 
4\. Always enjoy individual, secure and easy to remember passwords for any services.

The algorithm you use can off course be more complex, e.g. adding a characters in between, but the basic idea should be explained.

*[3 years ago]: 2011-02-22T13:13:12.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7293_05_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2249760.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7293-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7293_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:04:46">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=57538</link><title>Food Ideas for Startup Guys</title><description>Food Ideas for Startup Guys

36 points

by majimojo

7 years ago

65 comments Follow

Share your food hax.

Stay happier programming by eating good. When you're not in the mood for Cup Ramen and the Dollar Menu at MickyD's.

My favorite relaxer when under stress is Basil Tomato Soup. It really helps me clear my head for more programming. Takes 5-10 minutes to prepare and put in pot. Then forget about it for 40 minutes while it cooks (don't even have to stir).

When I only have 1 minute to microwave something, I make a 1337 Haxor Boca (my own concoqtion). Recipes below.

1) 1337 Haxor Boca

Buy Spicy Chicken Boca Burger at Safeway, some Spicy Hummus, and Pita Bread. Microwave the spicey chicken boca burger for 1 minute. Toast the pita bread if u want to. Cut the pita in half. Cut the boca in half. Put one half of the boca into each pita half. Use a knife and wedge some Spicy Hummus in. Done. Tastes great. Fills you up for 6 hrs. Nothing to clean.

Needs: Box of Spicy Chicken Boca Burger, Pita Bread, Hummus, Microwave

2) Basil Tomato Soup (is this a tuscan thing?):

(Best when you have stale hard bread laying around that you don't want to waste)

Chop 4 garlic cloves into chunks (like the size of rice or bigger). In a saucepot, heat 2 tbsp olive oil on medium. Throw in the garlic. Put a layer of the stale (hopefully not moldy) bread on the bottom. Toast the bread a little in the pot. If you don't have stale bread, throw a handful of rice in instead (abt 2 tbsp). Then put 1 can of whole tomatoes in ($1 from safeway). Canned tomatoes are better than produce section tomatoes because they are easier to use and canned when they're the freshest (food hack!). Put half a can of water in. When it boils. Turn the heat to the low setting. Chop a handful of basil. Throw it in. Come back in 40 minutes for something great. Add salt to taste.

Needs: Can of whole tomatoes, Basil, Garlic, Stale Bread, Olive Oil, a Stove.

*[7 years ago]: 2007-09-20T19:03:23.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7293_06_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/57538.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7293-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7293_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:05:28">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=452241</link><title>Ask HN: The best PHP book for Ruby programmer?</title><description>Ask HN: The best PHP book for Ruby programmer?

4 points

by 1gor

5 years ago

3 comments Follow

I need to learn some PHP after several years of serious hacking in Ruby. Of all Ruby books I've read "The Ruby Way" by Hal Fulton was the most practical and fun to follow. For example, while telling you about basic data structures it would also give you a recipe for implementing a sparse matrix or how to use arrays as mathematical sets.

What is the best book that focuses on PHP as a programming language, rather than on building websites?

*[5 years ago]: 2009-01-27T15:47:14.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7293_07_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/452241.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7293-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7293_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:06:05">http://www.national-kitchen-recipes.com/2012/07/armenian-dolma.html</link><title>Armenian Dolma</title><description>Armenian Dolma (http://national-kitchen-recipes.blogspot.com/2012/07/armenian-dolma.html)

1 point

by nationalkitchen

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

Dolma national dish of Armenian cuisine needs grape leaves, minced beef meat, rice, onion, basil and other spices.

*[2 years ago]: 2012-08-17T07:14:18.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7293_08_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/4395412.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7293-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7293_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:06:58">http://pastrybakeryrecipes.blogspot.nl/</link><title>Pastry bakery recipes</title><description>Pastry bakery recipes (http://pastrybakeryrecipes.blogspot.com/)

1 point

by abahdodi

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

This blog contains various articles about the pastry and bakery recipes like Pastry Basic Products,Breads and Fermented Goods, Cakes and Biscuits, Sweet and Petit Four, Ices, Special Event Cake, Wedding Cake, Soup, Meat Dishes, Fish and Seafood, Fondant, Roast Duck Recipes, Savoury Goods, Chocolate and Sugar Confectionery and cookie recipes and other dishes,Bali and Java Cuisine

*[3 years ago]: 2011-07-31T11:19:32.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7293_09_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2828114.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7293-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7293_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:07:37">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=2028985</link><title>Ask HN: Chicken and egg problem in a community startup with a slow velocity?</title><description>Ask HN: Chicken and egg problem in a community startup with a slow velocity?

5 points

by dbingham

3 years ago

2 comments Follow

Here is my startup, Fridge to Food. It is crowd sourcing for recipes: http://www.fridgetofood.com

A couple of months ago I posted this and got great feedback. I've been through quite a few iterations since then and have what is now a site that is minimally feature complete. I'm beginning to work on the more advanced reputation dependent features, but have a bit of a chicken and egg problem with the community. I have about 150 users, of whom some 20 maybe visit on a regular basis. And a handful post recipes on a regular basis. The site has a pretty slow velocity, because even the most dedicated users only have recipes to post a few times a month.

The issue I'm facing is that I'll need enough of a community to test the reputation dependent features when I implemented them. And I don't really have that right now. Unless I make the reputation threshold incredibly low, which beats the point.

So I'm facing the classic community based chicken and egg problem. I've pretty much mined my solid connection network out. The ones who cook regularly already use my site. The ones who don't, well, don't. I've been working pretty hard on Twitter and the various food-based subreddits to try and draw in some new early adopter users. But I've experienced limited success with that. Those who comment love it, and join. But the slow velocity often prevents them from doing much before forgetting about it. I've been trying to build connections with food bloggers, however, that is slow going. I'm not naturally a marketer type, so I have to spend a great deal of effort doing that. And it takes time away from writing code. I've considered cold e-mailing bloggers with a basically canned e-mail, but haven't tried it much. And when I have, I experienced pretty limited success there too.

So how can I solve the chicken and egg problem? People seem to love the concept of my site, and like the implementation. But the slow velocity and small community is preventing me from... well building a big enough community to have a higher velocity. Also, I'm having trouble just finding ways to get the link to it out there. Despite being pretty active on reddit and twitter I've only garnered about 3,000 unique views in about 1 month and a half. What are some other places I can put it out there?

*[3 years ago]: 2010-12-21T19:31:22.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7293_10_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2028985.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>