<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7458">rice recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:55:00" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7458-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7458_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:55:28">http://pegasuslegend-whatscookin.blogspot.nl/2013/11/grandmas-italian-style-rice-pudding.html</link><title>Grandma's Italian Style Rice Pudding Recipe</title><description>Grandma's Italian Style Rice Pudding Recipe (http://pegasuslegend-whatscookin.blogspot.com/2013/11/grandmas-italian-style-rice-pudding.html#.UnmGpq7d2zs.hackernews)

1 point

by pegasuslegend

6 months ago

0 comment Follow

*[6 months ago]: 2013-11-06T00:00:44.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7458_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/6679481.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7458-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7458_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:56:06">http://pegasuslegend-whatscookin.blogspot.nl/2013/11/grandmas-italian-style-rice-pudding.html</link><title>Secret Recipe Ingredient Grandma's Italian Style Rice Pudding Recipe</title><description>Secret Recipe Ingredient Grandma's Italian Style Rice Pudding Recipe (http://pegasuslegend-whatscookin.blogspot.com/2013/11/grandmas-italian-style-rice-pudding.html#.UnY4eE1hi2U.hackernews)

1 point

by pegasuslegend

6 months ago

0 comment Follow

*[6 months ago]: 2013-11-03T11:50:33.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7458_02_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/6662880.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7458-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7458_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:56:50">http://pegasuslegend-whatscookin.blogspot.nl/2013/05/crockpot-mushroom-wine-chicken-and-wild.html</link><title>Crockpot Mushroom Wine Chicken and Wild Rice Recipe</title><description>Crockpot Mushroom Wine Chicken and Wild Rice Recipe (http://pegasuslegend-whatscookin.blogspot.com/2013/05/crockpot-mushroom-wine-chicken-and-wild.html#.UZdcuLH9jrw.hackernews)

1 point

by pegasuslegend

11 months ago

0 comment Follow

*[11 months ago]: 2013-05-18T10:49:34.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7458_03_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/5728484.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7458-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7458_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:57:59">http://pegasuslegend-whatscookin.blogspot.nl/2012/04/crockpot-spanish-rice-recipe.html</link><title>Crockpot Spanish Rice Recipe</title><description>Crockpot Spanish Rice Recipe (http://pegasuslegend-whatscookin.blogspot.com/2012/04/crockpot-spanish-rice-recipe.html#.T46q7_eZr3g.hackernews)

1 point

by pegasuslegend24

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

*[2 years ago]: 2012-04-18T11:52:24.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7458_04_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3857490.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7458-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7458_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:59:41">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=4934588</link><title>Hacker fuel: lifeguard's red beans &amp; rice/potato/noodle recipe</title><description>Hacker fuel: lifeguard's red beans &amp; rice/potato/noodle recipe

6 points

by lifeguard

about a year ago

4 comments Follow

Save money, be healthy, eat good food!

Every Monday I cook some red beans.

99 cents for 8 servings of dry red beans. One serving is over 33% RDA for protein, 15% Iron, 10% Vitamin C. Add rice or potato and you are full! 5 lbs of potatoes is 1 - 3 dollars. Ramen 99 cents for 4 - 8 packs.

1\. before you go to sleep for the night, put 1/2 cup of dried red beans in pot full of cold water to soak at least 8 hours (or bring to a boil, let set for 10 min, change water and follow recipe)

2\. two hours before you want to eat, start cooking beans: drain old water, add 3 cups fresh water and bring to a boil, then reduce to a low simmer for around an hour

3\. add 2 spoons wershishire sauce, 2 spoons catsup, 4 spoons oil, salt, pepper, bay leaves, oregano, basil , hot sauce. add optional chopped onion/garlic/bell pepper/jalapeo and simmer for 40 more minutes

4\. use a big spoon to smoosh 1/4 of beans against side of pan to thicken sauce and start boiling water to cook rice/potato/noodle. About 20 minutes.

Serve beans over rice/noodles.

OR -- just cut a potato into chunks and throw into pot to cook for 20 minutes

OR -- just throw in a ramen noodle packet in beans and cook last 10 min

OR -- microwave/bake a big potato and pour beans over this with some fresh chopped onion if avail.

Make a double size batch and save half of it and make burritos or whatever in a few days.

*[about a year ago]: 2012-12-17T21:50:03.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7458_05_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/4934588.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7458-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7458_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:00:20">http://recipesforrice.com/rice-and-peas-recipe/</link><title>Rice and Peas Recipe</title><description>Rice and Peas Recipe (http://recipesforrice.com/rice-and-peas-recipe/)

1 point

by lucky7013

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

*[3 years ago]: 2011-08-25T02:25:08.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7458_06_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2923494.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7458-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7458_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:01:04">http://onlywire.com/?src=osurl</link><title>Recipe for Rice Vanilla Puff Pineapple Crunch</title><description>Recipe for Rice Vanilla Puff Pineapple Crunch (http://onlywire.com/r/49967165)

1 point

by lucky7013

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

*[3 years ago]: 2011-08-23T18:02:15.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7458_07_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2917578.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7458-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7458_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:01:52">http://recipesforrice.com/recipe-for-hawaiian-fried-rice/</link><title>Hawaiian Fried Rice</title><description>Hawaiian Fried Rice (http://recipesforrice.com/recipe-for-hawaiian-fried-rice/)

1 point

by lucky7013

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

*[3 years ago]: 2011-08-22T23:44:16.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7458_08_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2914672.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7458-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7458_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:02:37">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=6619468</link><title>Ask HN: What are your favorite Bachelor Chow recipes?</title><description>Ask HN: What are your favorite Bachelor Chow recipes?

11 points

by derekp7

6 months ago

16 comments Follow

Many of us here are almost too busy to cook, so we end up eating out a lot. This is costly, and not as healthy as it can be. To remedy that, I'd like to start a thread for your favorite quick to prepare, cheap, healthy recipes, which I like to refer to as "Bachelor Chow" (you know, like the stuff that Fry eats on Futurama). There are no hard qualifications, but basically anything that can either be prepared in about 5 minutes (even if it has to cook for a half hour or so), and/or something that you can make a large quantity of and it keeps good for leftovers.

For example: Chicken and yellow rice \-- get a bag of frozen chicken breasts (about $7, usually has 4 - 6 pieces of various sizes), a bag of mixed frozen vegetables, and a package of yellow rice (essentially, rice with turmeric and other seasonings). Boil 1 - 2 pieces of chicken (takes about 15 minutes to boil), cut or tear into small pieces, throw chicken pieces, frozen peas, yellow rice, and appropriate amount of water in a pan (the rice package gives how much water to add), cover and cook for about half an hour. Total time in front of stove, 5 minutes (broken down into two separate sessions), total cooking time about 45 minutes. Variations include using strips of boneless pork chops (brown pork first in skillet, doesn't have to be cooked all the way through), and you can slice up red potatoes on top instead of peas.

Both of these are awesome even a few days later (or fill small bags with the leftovers and throw them in the freezer.

Another quick recipe is beef stew -- basically a package of stew meat ($6.00 or so), a large bag of soup-mix vegetables (this should include potatoes, or you can cut up red potatoes -- reds, so you don't have to peel the skins), a package of stew seasoning. About $9, makes enough for about 6 meals.

So, any others? If this thread gets some up-votes, I'll add a few more in the comments section.

*[6 months ago]: 2013-10-26T21:27:15.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7458_09_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/6619468.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7458-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7458_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:02:59">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=612898</link><title>Ask HN: What do you eat?</title><description>Ask HN: What do you eat?

49 points

by pj

5 years ago

109 comments Follow

A little lighter subject for this late saturday evening. I have considered starting a site along the lines of "startup recipes."

These recipes would be focused on inexpensive meals that don't take a lot of time away from coding but still provide excellent nutrition and lasting energy.

Of course we all know the "ramen profitable" stage, but Ramen is horrible for the body. Restaurants in general produce not that great of food and the amount of time saved by having them cook it isn't always advantageous considering you have to drive there, stand in line and be away from the computer. Not to mention the expense of convenience makes them not the best choice economically.

I went to college in New Orleans, so I became aware quickly of lots of inexpensive dishes that could be cooked without a lot of distraction: Red beans 'n' Rice, Gumbo, and Jambalaya. I also like to make a nice Pot Roast with potatoes, onions, and carrots in there.

So, my question for you is, what do you eat to keep yourself going while you are coding or working on your startup or just living?

*[5 years ago]: 2009-05-17T03:28:46.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7458_10_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/612898.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>