<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7475">software consultant work at home</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:39:56" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7475-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7475_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:40:45">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=2828462</link><title>Ask HN: Should I go freelance? Right now?</title><description>Ask HN: Should I go freelance? Right now?

33 points

by maybeindie

3 years ago

37 comments Follow

I'm considering going the freelance/bootstrapping/contracting route. Currently very close to resigning a cushy salaried job as an Enterprise Java consultant. Would love your honest opinions on whether I'm in good shape for striking out on my own.

I have two reasons for doing so: A) I want to be able to call my own shots in how I spend my time. The commute is killing me, for one thing. B) I also want to bootstrap my own products. Have launched one web application a few years ago (didn't catch on, but I learned a lot.) I have a long list of ideas I'm eager to execute on, but unable to do so while working fulltime at a BigCo (I'd like to, and I've tried once earlier, but it didn't work out and probably won't while I work a fulltime salaried job.)

I'm 33 yrs old. Ten years experience as a paid developer. Competent Java/Ruby/JavaScript programmer. Frontend, backend and some mobile experience. I've done some speaking in the local developer community, got some open repos in GitHub in multiple languages and have a couple of public webapps/websites in my portfolio. I'm certainly no "rock star" though!

I have a decent network, but mainly composed of developers, not too many product owners/stakeholders/gatekeepers.

I'm a family man, but we've gotten our living expenses down to the point where we can live well if I pull in at average 3k each month (take-home pay). Have saved up a nest egg which will carry us for 6 months if I'm unable to get any contracting work at all. If I'm able to get work charging around 100-150$/hr I'd only need to work around 16 full weeks a year or on average 2 days a week to get by. This is a very rough calculation and subject to differences in currencies and living expenses from the US, but I think you get the idea: I've done my homework.

Oh and I live in a Scandinavian country, near one of the capitals (where most of the web/software work is going on).

So. How does my situation sound to you? I think this should work but I need some outside validation. What are my chances?

Really, one of the biggest things holding me back is a small fear that the current debt situation in the US turns into worldwide financial armageddon - would I be better off on my own or continuing work at a BigCo in that case?

*[3 years ago]: 2011-07-31T14:58:45.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7475_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2828462.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7475-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7475_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:41:33">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=2504416</link><title>Ask HN: Does never having a "real" job hurt me</title><description>Ask HN: Does never having a "real" job hurt me

48 points

by zbruhnke

3 years ago

36 comments Follow

So I am sure this topic has come up before, but I couldn't find much on the search feature. I am basically just looking for some opinions on this subject.

A little about me:

24, college dropout, 1 exit (which is why I dropped out)

I founded a small software company while in college as a business/political science double major and accidentally sold it to a much larger company at the beginning of my senior year. They wanted me on as a consultant for a minimum of 8 months and after i finished up almost a year consulting for them I moved back to my home town and began doing mainly freelance work and living off of savings as well.

I'm getting to a point in life where I need a daily challenge and I want to get excited about working on a product on a daily basis again. I have a few ideas and always have some sort of small project going on, however I look at a lot of companies out there and think I would love to go to work for a company out there that is already making a dent in their market (e.g. Twilio) but I just don't know if I am "qualified" enough to work for some of these companies.

I do not really have a resume and even the one I have put together just consists of the companies I have owned over the years basically.

What have you done in this situation? anyone with some advice of what a guy like me can/should do?

Keep working on my own things? Apply fo jobs at a few interesting companies and just see what happens?

Thanks in advance for your input!

*[3 years ago]: 2011-05-01T23:45:03.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7475_02_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2504416.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7475-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7475_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:42:17">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=4422771</link><title>Ask HN: Career advice - don't know my value, or my prospects</title><description>Ask HN: Career advice - don't know my value, or my prospects

1 point

by askingforadvice

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

So, HN, I need some advice, career-wise. (Sorry for the throwaway account, but I'm already including way too much personally identifiable information for my comfort.)

I'm 28, and I've been at my employer for 7 years. I'm the only developer for my employers' ServiceNow platform. We were one of SN's first 10 clients, and I've been working with the software since SN was &lt;10 employees. (ServiceNow is a Javascript-focused SaaS ITIL system, went public recently.)

I'm the only internal person maintaining our platform, and a group of consultants who are recognized SN experts have recently vindicated a number of my design decisions. (Building out a billing/invoicing system using SN/Javascript and (sigh) Crystal, some data synch stuff, tons of metrics/reporting, etc.)

After 7 years, I'm making $47.5k a year. On the flip side, I've only got a 2 year degree, and I work from home. (Home currently being Nebraska, since I can afford a mortgage there.)

I've been told that my current salary is low for my time at my employer and my skillset. At this point, I'm very burnt out. When I was able to solve problems and help people at work, I loved it, but now, it's just maintaining code. I've also got to think about my future prospects; the whole "current salary affects future salary" thing. I like to negotiate, be diplomatic, and prevent conflict. I've never fought for a raise in my life.

I really don't know where to go from here. I have a salary review coming up soon, and I don't know whether I should make a case for more money, or just take what they give me. I don't even know if what I'm earning is unreasonable or not. It's absolutely not about the money, it's about my future prospects. (If that makes sense.)

Any suggestions or advice? Even just some information on whether I'm being paid fairly or not would be a huge help. I've considered asking this on StackExchange, but I trust the HN community and thought this would be a good place to ask.

*[2 years ago]: 2012-08-23T15:08:38.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7475_03_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/4422771.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7475-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7475_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:42:56">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=460693</link><title>Ask HN: Is a team of work-at-home employees realistic?</title><description>Ask HN: Is a team of work-at-home employees realistic?

32 points

by abalashov

5 years ago

50 comments Follow

Hi everyone,

I was wondering what you think about the feasibility of building a team consisting of employees who work at home. I don't mean a completely remote team; I am talking about local people, and certainly with some measure of face-to-face meetings and physical interaction when that level of collaboration is required. I just mean people who work mostly at home on a day-to-day basis.

As far as I can tell, corporate America is mostly terrified of telecommuting. Admittedly, it can be legitimately said to pose some very real management challenges. But no matter how much I consider that, I just can't see a justification for paying for office space and forcing people to spend time there for 8+ hours a day. I think I agree very strongly with what PG has had to say on the topic of corporate office space and its relationship to talented individuals and their productivity.

I agree that it's harder to manage remote people, and I've certainly taken stock of the allegedly widespread tendency for remote workers to take advantage of their independence and lack of direct oversight. And lack of consistent and direct communication can certainly be an obstacle. But I think there are technological solutions to these problems: better backoffice tools, better collaboration and messaging tools, VoIP, instant messaging, presence, good ticketing and workflow management systems, etc. I think the technology is there to make up for the shortfall.

Now, admittedly, the angle from which I am approaching this problem is a little bit orthogonal to the typical dilemmas of web startup entrepreneurs. I am 23, and at the moment, I am trying to grow my VoIP / telecom systems integration and engineering consultancy beyond a one-man show so that I can get to the point where I can be a product company. In other words, I suppose it's fair to say I am taking the "consulting route" that PG speaks of in his various essays on startup funding. Good, bad, I have various reasons for that, but the goal in the end is to end up with actual "deliverables" - no mistake about it.

Still, the reason I mention that is because consulting is a business model that lends itself to measurement of individual productivity a bit better than, say, a software startup. Product development and engineering - pure CAPEX, none of which is directly rebilled or amortised any way (especially in a short time to market) - is a little more murky. And certainly, there are some business models where almost the entire risk can be shifted onto the employee, as one sees with commission-only work-at-home salespeople. In my case I think I'm in a happy middle.

Regardless, I'm not going to go all Japanese quantitative management on people. I want to build a progressive and humanity-affirming company where people are happy and proud to work on interesting problems in the telecommunications space. I am just wondering if I am being too idealistic here about remote work; are people just going to take advantage of me, in the main? Or is it reasonable to suppose that I should be able to afford them the benefit of working wherever they want as long as they meet certain criteria as far as productivity, availability, and good communication? (All my prospective employees are excellent written and verbal communicators, and I would not have it any other way.)

I am in Atlanta, a city notorious for its vast, empty suburban sprawl, unconscienable freeway distances, and gridlock traffic. I really, really don't want to compel anyone to trek through this disaster of urban planning and infrastructure design to my office if there is no real point.

Does anyone here have experience building a team like this? If so, can you share tips on what strategies you used to make it work better?

Thanks a lot!

*[5 years ago]: 2009-02-01T08:16:04.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7475_04_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/460693.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7475-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7475_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:43:23">http://geniteam.com</link><title>Want to do a startup with bootstrapping!</title><description>Want to do a startup with bootstrapping! (http://geniteam.com)

1 point

by hira_khan

7 years ago

2 comments Follow

Want to do a startup with bootstrapping!&lt;p&gt;By Khurram Samad: Founder &amp; CEO GeniTeam&lt;p&gt;The write up is based on my personal experience and learning while working with serial entrepreneurs. After having helped various startups, I launched GeniTeam in 2006 to provide dedicated software engineers to help entrepreneurs develop products with bootstrapping. Over the years, my own startup has gained momentum and helping promising startups based in North America, Netherland and Israel. &lt;p&gt;GeniTeam Business Model:- Many people come across innovative idea but fail to materialize it for lack of resources. The barriers for high tech startup are high for huge upfront investment requirement. Hence, many people seek funding from venture capitalists, by giving up significant amount of equity or give up idea for lack of access to funding. GeniTeam provides an alternate to such entrepreneurs by allowing them hire virtual team members with GeniTeam, at fraction of cost to help entrepreneurs materialize their dreams. The dedicated virtual team members are hosted with GeniTeam in Lahore, Pakistan and whose growth is linked to growth of startup. The time difference allows entrepreneurs to monitor and instruct virtual team members in evening and generating cash flows for startup by doing consulting or job in day time. &lt;p&gt;How my faith strengthened on business model:- The company's business model has evolved out of my personal consulting for CambridgeDocs, an XML conversion company. I worked single handed from my home in Pakistan, to help the startup expand its product line. During my consulting, I refined "virtual team" model and build the confidence to expand virtual team in Pakistan. After 6-8 month of successful work, the company decided to start its offshore operation in Lahore, Pakistan. This strengthened my faith on my business model, as most of the engineers working with CambridgeDocs were graduates of Massachusetts Institute of Technology, USA. After establishing and training initial resources for offshore office, I started helping multiple companies. Over last 3 years, I have refined the processes for virtual team and created few more success stories.&lt;p&gt;Does GeniTeam take Equity:- We only take equity if we invest with the startup. Our resource cost is pretty nominal, and hence startup's generally don't need to share equity. The partnering startups are free to change vendor or quit us, if they wish. They also have an option of acquiring virtual team to own the startup team. &lt;p&gt;Then how does GeniTeam make money:- GeniTeam primary cash flows are through product development. GeniTeam is working on "Team Room", "Multiplayer Mobile Games over GPRS", and online tutoring application, developed in rich internet applications. In future, GeniTeam would like to help startups refine ideas and develop marketing plans.&lt;p&gt;Is GeniTeam a traditional outsourcing company? Our philosophy is radically different from traditional outsourcing companies. GeniTeam believes in building partnerships with startups, and growing with them. GeniTeam is serving niche high tech startup segment, not catered by traditional outsourcing companies. Distinguished by vision, our model allows partnering companies build and retain expertise X as they could do by hiring resource with them. &lt;p&gt;How can people manage people from 10000 miles away? This is the most frequent question I hear on sales. I believe internet has revolutionized our lives, and also the work environments. With such changes, virtual team and virtual office have become reality. However, the processes to manage virtual team are slightly different and require enhanced communication and reporting techniques. It requires almost 1 to 2 months, to fully reap the benefits of virtual team. I personally believe, it really worth investing time and few bucks in idea.&lt;p&gt; How to Contact GeniTeam? Please visit www.geniteam.com to know us more and contact us at sales@geniteam.com for details.&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;

*[7 years ago]: 2007-08-18T17:51:43.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7475_05_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/43832.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>