<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7478">protect kids online</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:56:20" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7478-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7478_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:56:43">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=6386364</link><title>How should hacker parents protect their kids online?</title><description>How should hacker parents protect their kids online?

6 points

by yaniv_aknin

7 months ago

5 comments Follow

I have a two year old son and bunch of three-to-seven year old niblings. Recently my sister asked me what should she do to protect her seven year old online, and I realised I don't have a good answer. I gave my sister the typical sensible advice (talk to him about his online experiences, don't let him use Internet devices in an overly private setting like a closed room, etc), but I wasn't happy with the answer I gave. I realised that like so many other things about parenting, I don't know the answer.

I'm not overly conservative, I don't think I'm overly porn-protective or predator-hysteric or whatever, heck, I might've leeched a naked lady or two myself as a teen (at 2400 baud!) and don't think I became a Fox newsesque freak. That said, I don't think it's a good idea to let a seven year old roam the Internet freely (I cringe just thinking about my niblings reddit.com/r/wtf , and I know there's much much worse online). I think it's probably a very bad idea to let the government/an ISP protect the said seven year old, but I don't think s/he should be left alone on the Internet. I'm not even sure what are reasonable cutoff parameters by which to decide when and how give your child more freedom as they approach online adulthood.

What should a sensible, liberal and caring parent do to protect a child online over various ages? I'm interested in answers protecting toddlers to late teenagers, in answers targeting the whole range of tech-savvy to tech-clueless parents, including 'tech clueless but with a tech savvy friend/sibling who'll help set things up' and finally I'd definitely appreciate pointers to good, techie-oriented, not tawdry and not disgustingly commercialised information/opinion sources.

*[7 months ago]: 2013-09-14T17:40:36.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7478_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/6386364.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7478-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7478_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:57:34">http://www.pcmag.com/article2/0,2817,2413411,00.asp</link><title>FTC Unveils New Rules to Protect Kids Online</title><description>FTC Unveils New Rules to Protect Kids Online (http://www.pcmag.com/article2/0,2817,2413411,00.asp)

1 point

by Lukeas14

about a year ago

0 comment Follow

*[about a year ago]: 2012-12-19T19:48:45.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7478_02_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/4944385.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7478-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7478_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:58:35">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=1925172</link><title>Ask HN: How do you protect your kids online?</title><description>Ask HN: How do you protect your kids online?

1 point

by tamersalama

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

I'm looking for advice on software and other resources for online activities (web, I'M, social, ... ).

*[3 years ago]: 2010-11-20T20:04:17.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7478_03_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/1925172.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7478-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7478_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:59:20">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=2816692</link><title>Startup Qustodio launches killer parental control app</title><description>Startup Qustodio launches killer parental control app

1 point

by edcross

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

Qustodio is a new innovative app that helps parents protect kids online. Qustodio helps parents understand and manage how their kids use the internet, and protects them against dangerous content, cyberbullying and predators.

Kids increasing digital-life independence is becoming one of the newest and hardest challenges for today's parents. Making sure that kids stay out of trouble online and use the internet responsibly is one of the hottest topics in the average household.

Qustodio is a better way to protect kids online, and brings best in class parental control and internet monitoring technologies not available in today's top priced solutions.

Here's a few of the reasons why we're proud of Qustodio: \- It does true social network monitoring of all friends and connections, incl. facebook and twitter \- It classifies websites dynamically and can pick out bad content on sites immediately \- It has a cool and informative monitoring dashboard that's easy to use from any device \- It's child proof \- It's FREE.

What can parents do with Qustodio? \- Understand how their kids use the internet \- Protect their privacy and reputation online \- Block dangerous online content \- Manage their kids internet time

So what's happening next? We are going Beta. This means we're offering the product to early adopters to learn how Qustodio works with a bigger audience. Here's how to participate:

Sign up to become a beta tester Sign up here: http://www.qustodio.com Your feedback is the most precious asset to us.

...Press &amp; Journalists Are you a journalist or blogger? Please feel free to email us at qustodio@qustodio.com if youd like to preview our service or cover our launch.

*[3 years ago]: 2011-07-28T13:36:40.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7478_04_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2816692.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7478-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7478_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:00:10">http://www.earnestparenting.com/2011/07/18/protect-your-kids-from-online-scammers/</link><title>The Highest Rated Antivirus Software For Protecting Your Kids</title><description>The Highest Rated Antivirus Software For Protecting Your Kids (http://www.earnestparenting.com/2011/07/18/protect-your-kids-from-online-scammers/)

1 point

by AndrewThomas

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

*[3 years ago]: 2011-10-09T06:08:51.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7478_05_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3089809.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7478-06"><link>http://www.charlotteobserver.com/2012/08/22/3470518/3-tips-to-protect-your-kids-inheritance.html#</link><title>3 Tips to Protect Your Kid's Inheritance Online</title><description>3 Tips to Protect Your Kid's Inheritance Online (http://www.charlotteobserver.com/2012/08/22/3470518/3-tips-to-protect-your-kids-inheritance.html#)

1 point

by jenniewong

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

*[2 years ago]: 2012-08-22T19:50:38.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7478_06_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/4419211.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7478-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7478_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:01:36">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=4235775</link><title>Show HN: Securly - Keep your kids safe on your home network</title><description>Show HN: Securly - Keep your kids safe on your home network

15 points

by bmadhu

2 years ago

22 comments Follow

http://www.securly.com

To keep kids safe online, we felt it wasnt enough anymore to rely simply on blocking websites (domain filtering). We also need to protect them on trusted social media sites like Facebook, YouTube and Wikipedia. We couldnt find any solution that does this for the entire home network. We are two security hackers who have worked in the enterprise firewall space for several years and felt this was an important problem to solve.

The video on our front page gives you a pretty good idea of what we do. You can also use us as a free premium DNS server by pointing your DNS to the IPs here:

http://www.securly.com/setup

We would love some honest feedback on what we have built so far.

*[2 years ago]: 2012-07-12T18:08:52.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7478_07_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/4235775.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7478-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7478_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:02:17">http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00BCO2YCK</link><title>Facebook and Kids: A Parents Guide to Facebook Privacy and Security</title><description>Facebook and Kids: A Parents Guide to Facebook Privacy and Security (http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00BCO2YCK)

1 point

by chriscrosby

about a year ago

0 comment Follow

Millions of parents have come to realize that Facebook isn't a place where you can just send children to fend for themselves.

A recent survey revealed that parents are growing more concerned with the threats they present to their children.

Yet, Facebook and other social networks are here to stay. It's our jobs as parents to educate ourselves on these mediums and do our part to protect and guide our children. Whether your child is just coming online to Facebook or they have been there for years, this eBook is a must read.

*[about a year ago]: 2013-02-11T19:03:07.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7478_08_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/5202576.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7478-09"><link>http://techli.com/2012/06/tech-that-protects-kids/</link><title>How Startups Can Help Protect Your Child Online</title><description>How Startups Can Help Protect Your Child Online (http://techli.com/2012/06/tech-that-protects-kids/)

1 point

by MRonney

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

*[2 years ago]: 2012-06-16T20:16:19.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7478_09_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/4121495.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7478-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7478_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:03:36">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=3526132</link><title>Ask HN: Android project for introducing teenagers to programming?</title><description>Ask HN: Android project for introducing teenagers to programming?

4 points

by chrismanfrank

2 years ago

4 comments Follow

I'm one of the founders of ImagineK12-backed Tutorcloud.com. We've been talking to lots of parents who want their kids to learn a little programming. We'd like to help them, and we need your help.

Specifically....Recommend a project we can use in our Intro to Android Programming workshop.

These kids are 12-16 years old. No programming experience. Eager to learn. Dying to build "cool apps". What could we build with them?

The workshop is only 4 hours long. Can we build something kids will think is cool in that time?

Comment here, or contact me directly. And if you're interested in teaching teenagers in the Bay Area, or online, drop me a line as well. [chris@tutorcloud.com].

*[2 years ago]: 2012-01-29T20:25:55.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7478_10_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3526132.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>