<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7486">board games teenagers</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:26:52" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7486-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7486_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:27:46">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=3854326</link><title>Should tech talks be rated</title><description>Should tech talks be rated

2 points

by arranrp

2 years ago

2 comments Follow

Should there be a standard rating of conference talks? Should events advise attendees of content that might take a talk beyond a U rate? The bellow rating systems are those of British Board of Film Classification and used for film, videos an games ( http://www.bbfc.co.uk ).

U: Suitable for all \- No discriminatory language or behaviour unless clearly disapproved of. \- No references to illegal drugs or drug misuse unless they are infrequent and innocuous, or there is a clear educational purpose or anti-drug message suitable for young children. \- Scary sequences should be mild, brief and unlikely to cause undue anxiety to young children. The outcome should be reassuring. \- Infrequent use only of very mild bad language. \- Occasional natural nudity, with no sexual context. \- Mild sexual behaviour (for example, kissing) and references only (for example, to making love).

12: Suitable for 12 years and over \- Discriminatory language or behaviour must not be endorsed by the work as a whole. Aggressive discriminatory language or behaviour is unlikely to be acceptable unless clearly condemned. \- Any misuse of drugs must be infrequent and should not be glamorised or give instructional detail. \- Moderate language is allowed. The use of strong language (for example, fuck) must be infrequent. \- Nudity is allowed, but in a sexual context must be brief and discreet. \- Sexual activity may be briefly and discreetly portrayed. Sex references should not go beyond what is suitable for young teenagers. Frequent crude references are unlikely to be acceptable.

18: Suitable only for adults In line with the consistent findings of the BBFCs public consultations and The Human Rights Act 1998, at 18 the BBFCs guideline concerns will not normally override the principle that adults should be free to choose their own entertainment. Exceptions are most likely in the following areas:

\- where material or treatment appears to the BBFC to risk harm to individuals or, through their behaviour, to society for example, any detailed portrayal of violent or dangerous acts, or of illegal drug use, which may cause harm to public health or morals. This may include portrayals of sexual or sexualised violence which might, for example, eroticise or endorse sexual assault

*[2 years ago]: 2012-04-17T18:48:44.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7486_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3854326.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7486-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7486_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:28:50">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=3543178</link><title>What would you do if you were me?</title><description>What would you do if you were me?

11 points

by tony_elk

2 years ago

11 comments Follow

I feel as if I'm stuck in a no-win situation in my career, and I'm wondering HN readers, what would you do if you were me?

Here's my story: I'm in my late 40s and have been involved in information technology professionally for my entire adult life (and even did board-level repair of early personal computers when I was in high-school). For the past 20+ years I've been involved in IT audit and information security as an auditor and consultant, and as an information security manager. I'm technical enough that I'm currently a security-architect / sales-engineer for a large telecommunications vendor. I've tried two startups in the past (mobile robotics and security consulting). Neither were overly successful, but I learned a lot. I currently live in the upper midwest, am married (for 20+ years), have three children (ages 12-18), and make a decent living. Sounds great, right? I should be happy.

Here's the problem: I'm not making anything! I'm not creating! I strongly feel I'm a "Maker", a "Developer", but I may have realized this too late.

During the evening, I program for fun (mostly Ruby on Rails, these days, but Lisp, Python, C, and micro-controller assembly in the past). I'm not the greatest programmer, mostly because I can only do it a few hours each week (let's say ~10 hours per week), but I can get by. And, I really enjoy it. So, I'd like to do more programming. And, I'd like to do another startup. I have SaaS B2B application in mind. But, it seems at my age it is going to be impossible to shift from my current career to a programming career or to do another startup because the lifestyle change (read "drop-in-income, at least for a while") will be intolerable, especially for my family. Does that mean I'm done? Game over? At this point, am I doomed to sitting on the side-lines and only watching or being a cheerleader to other developers and startups? What have other professionals who have been in my situation ("golden handcuffs") done to get around this? I've had a successful career (especially for someone who didn't complete college), but with three teenagers, it's not like I have a stash of cash available to make the transition.

What would you do if you were me?

*[2 years ago]: 2012-02-02T16:02:34.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7486_02_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3543178.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>