<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7490">convert wav mp3</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:36:10" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7490-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7490_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:37:13">http://www.alifesoft.com/blog/2011/7/20110714080415.html</link><title>Free download best mac audio converter -convert audio to mp3/aac/wav/aiff</title><description>Free download best mac audio converter -convert audio to mp3/aac/wav/aiff (http://bit.ly/oVrBTX)

1 point

by jessiezhang67

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

*[3 years ago]: 2011-07-14T12:20:31.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7490_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2762681.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7490-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7490_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:38:15">http://www.avchd-converter-mac.com/convert-import-avchd-to-itunes-converter-for-mac-os.html</link><title>AVCHD to iTunes Converter for Mac, convert/import AVCHD to iTunes for Mac OS</title><description>AVCHD to iTunes Converter for Mac, convert/import AVCHD to iTunes for Mac OS (http://www.avchd-converter-mac.com/convert-import-avchd-to-itunes-converter-for-mac-os.html)

1 point

by jobs105

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

Mac AVCHD to iTunes Converter allows you to convert AVCHD to MP4, MOV, DV, MPEG-1, 3GP, MP3, WAV. Its easy to import AVCHD to iTunes and play AVCHD in iTunes on Mac OS X.

*[2 years ago]: 2011-11-06T02:15:26.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7490_02_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3201577.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7490-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7490_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:39:11">http://www.alifesoft.com/Mac-mp3-converter.html</link><title>MP3 Converter for Mac helps you convert any audio formats to MP3 on Mac OS X</title><description>MP3 Converter for Mac helps you convert any audio formats to MP3 on Mac OS X (http://www.alifesoft.com/Mac-mp3-converter.html)

1 point

by maggie198651

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

MP3 Converter for Mac supports convert any formats audio, like AAC, AC3, AIFF, FLAC etc to MP3 and extract audio from video and save as MP3 on Mac os x

* Convert MKA, WAV, M4A, M4V, AAC, AC3, AIFF, AMR, FLAC, WMA, MP2 to MP3 Mac
* Extract audio from video like MP4, MOV, DV, MPEG, WMV, AVI etc to MP3 on Mac
* Edit audio files: Clip, Merge, Set different Bitrate, Sample rate, Channels for output audio
*[3 years ago]: 2011-07-04T02:50:47.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7490_03_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2725210.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7490-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7490_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:40:17">http://www.sharekits.com/how-to-convert-3ga-to-mp3.html</link><title>3GA to MP3 Converter Convert 3GA to MP3, M4A, AC3, WAV, WMA</title><description>3GA to MP3 Converter Convert 3GA to MP3, M4A, AC3, WAV, WMA (http://www.sharekits.com/how-to-convert-3ga-to-mp3.html)

1 point

by katrinwhibley

7 months ago

0 comment Follow

Free download 3GA to MP3 Converter to convert 3GA to MP3 for play 3GA with Windows Media Player, iTunes, or anywhere with ease.

*[7 months ago]: 2013-09-13T03:04:44.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7490_04_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/6378329.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7490-05"><link>http://itmaverix.net/xilisoft-video-converter-ultimate-6-5-inc-serial/</link><title>Xilisoft Video Converter Ultimate 6.5 [Inc. Serial]</title><description>Xilisoft Video Converter Ultimate 6.5 [Inc. Serial] (http://itmaverix.net/xilisoft-video-converter-ultimate-6-5-inc-serial/)

1 point

by itmaverix

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

There is no comparison of other converters with Xilisoft Video Converter because it is easy, fast, reliable, and loaded with features. Its capable of converting videos of all popular formats like AVI, MPEG, WMV, DivX, MP4, H.264/AVC, AVCHD, MKV, RM, MOV, XviD, 3GP, and audio MP3, WMA, WAV, RA, M4A, AAC, AC3, OGG. Now you can convert video, audio, and animated images to play on your PSP, PS3, iPod, iPhone, Apple TV, Xbox, Google phones, iPad, iPad2 and other digital multimedia devices. All made possible with Xilisoft Video Converter.

*[3 years ago]: 2011-08-04T18:46:07.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7490_05_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2847205.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7490-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7490_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:42:31">http://www.aimersoft.com/mac-ipad-video-converter.html</link><title>IPad Video Converter for Mac to Convert various videos for your iPad</title><description>IPad Video Converter for Mac to Convert various videos for your iPad (http://www.aimersoft.com/mac-ipad-video-converter.html)

1 point

by LynnLU

4 years ago

0 comment Follow

iPad Video Converter for Mac is a professional Mac video to iPad converter that enables you to convert all popular video and audio formats to iPad compatible Video Mp4, MOV, M4V, Mp3, M4A, AAC, WAV. With easy-to-use editing functions like trim, crop, merge etc., you can watch your favorite videos on your iPad with ease.

iPad Video Converter for Mac is one of the best iPad video converters that enable you to convert almost any video format for enjoying on your iPad on Mac OS X.

*[4 years ago]: 2010-07-09T06:07:48.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7490_06_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/1499907.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7490-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7490_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:43:27">http://ww38.shareware7.com/dvd-video/video-converter/ipad-video-converter.html</link><title>IPad Video Converter - converts any video format to iPad</title><description>IPad Video Converter - converts any video format to iPad (http://www.shareware7.com/dvd-video/video-converter/ipad-video-converter.html)

1 point

by dekker05

4 years ago

0 comment Follow

iPad video converter supports various media files formats including popular standard formats and audio formats like AVI, WMV, MP4, MKV, MOV, MP3, WMA?3G2, M4A, MP3, AC3, AAC, WAV, OGG, H.264 etc. You can convert videos to iPad video and audio on Windows, making the most use of iPad's big screen and HD feature, and it's also called iPad H.264 converter for Windows. This iPad Video Converter provides a series of useful functions such as crop, trim, merge; add watermark and video effects like brightness, contrast and saturation. Also it supports Windows 7.

*[4 years ago]: 2010-10-23T15:13:50.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7490_07_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/1823635.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>