<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7500">roof isolation</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:08:41" name="HNSearch" id="FW14-e110"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e110-7500-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7500_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:09:18">http://www.steelroofpanels.com/foam-insulated-panels.html</link><title>Structural Insulated Roof Panels</title><description>Structural Insulated Roof Panels (http://www.steelroofpanels.com/foam-insulated-panels.html)

1 point

by steelroofpanels

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

Steel Roof Panels offers Structural Insulated Roof Panels, Foam Insulated Panels, Insulated Roof Panels &amp; Insulating Wall Panel Systems. Structural Insulated Panels (SIPs) with High R-value Polyurethane Foam Insulation.

*[2 years ago]: 2012-07-30T13:16:58.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7500_01_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/4312136.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7500-02"><link>http://blogs.moneyandmarkets.com/blog/real-wealth</link><title>Get Ready for Phase II of the Greatest Commodities Bull Market, Ever!</title><description>Get Ready for Phase II of the Greatest Commodities Bull Market, Ever! (http://blogs.moneyandmarkets.com/blog/real-wealth)

1 point

by weissinc

6 years ago

0 comment Follow

Yes, thats right. Thats what Im forecasting. Phase II of the natural resource and commodity boom is about to begin. And it will be the most powerful surge higher yet.

How do I know? I wont go into all the details of my trading and forecasting models, but I will support this with a fundamental argument that I think every investor should be thinking about right now. Hardly anyone is talking about it, which makes it even that much more significant.

Let me pose it in terms of two scenarios and a couple of questions.

First, suppose, just for a moment, that the U.S. economy does not slump as badly as most expect, and instead, actually picks up some steam going ahead. Since Asian economies are still largely firing away on 12-cylinders, what to you think would happen to global growth -- and hence the natural resource markets -- if the U.S. economy springs back, even if it does so just slightly?

Demand for natural resources will go through the freaking roof, and natural resource prices along with it.

Now suppose that the U.S. economy instead of bouncing back, slumps even more. The Fed and Bernanke will print even more money, weakening the dollar even more.

What do you think would happen under that scenario? Inflation will pick up an even greater head of steam, and natural resource prices will take off yet again.

Sound like a win-win situation for the natural resource markets? It does to me!

*[6 years ago]: 2008-05-22T20:31:46.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7500_02_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/197531.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7500-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7500_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:10:41">http://www.globeroofing.com/</link><title>Roof fort lauderdale</title><description>Roof fort lauderdale (http://www.globeroofing.com/)

1 point

by QuilabegeSine

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

Global Roofing Fort Lauderdale has been building and repairing roofs in Ft Lauderdale. We focus on providing you with the most cost effective solution.

*[2 years ago]: 2012-01-07T09:47:14.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7500_03_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3436685.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7500-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7500_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:11:20">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=7499035</link><title>Ask HN: I can't do this anymore, I need help</title><description>Ask HN: I can't do this anymore, I need help

147 points

by kriptonic

26 days ago

135 comments Follow

Hello.

I've had enough.

Hear me out. I've spent the last 5 years of my life slaving away on startups and new business ideas and I'm failing, bad. So tonight I've come to the conclusion that I clearly have no fucking idea what I'm doing. I've lost pretty much all my friends because of the time I've spent trying to make my ideas work. I have spent money I can't afford on ideas that have never came to light. And now it's 2:31am on a Sunday evening and my girlfriend is in bed wondering why I won't come give her a cuddle, but I can't. Because I know I have to wake up tomorrow morning and hit the repeat button on my life again. I have to work all day just to put a roof over our heads. She wants to travel and damn I want to take her so bad, but I can't. I hate what my life has become.

But I have a solution, because I know complaining won't change this. Truth is, I have no idea about business. That's why I can't do it. I come from a working class family, I have working class friends, no one I know has any idea about business or even any interest in the topic. I've read a lot though: on business, development, management &amp; self help. I can do it, I know I can, I just need some guidance. So here I am; asking for guidance. I have about $5000 and I'm willing to put that into an idea, and I have some of those too. So who's ready to play ball with me? I can guarantee the technical skills, could you guarantee the business skills? Maybe together we won't need to press the repeat button on our alarm clocks next Monday.

Let me know, 
hnineedhelp [at] gmail.com

*[26 days ago]: 2014-03-31T01:53:47.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7500_04_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/7499035.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7500-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7500_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:12:11">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=3278696</link><title>Ask HN: can I get a parking ticket?</title><description>Ask HN: can I get a parking ticket?

5 points

by valgaze

2 years ago

5 comments Follow

I think I have stumbled on an exploitable parking lot system by the beach, but I am curious about other perspectives.

Here's the setup (numbers are simplified for clarity): 
1) Bunch of parking spaces numbered 1 to 500; 
2) You park and note your number and go to the central payment machine; 
3) At the payment machine you type in your space  number and pop in your coins (crucially you don't get any type of ticket to put on your dashboard or anything to physically indicate you have parked); 
4) No gate, no guards, no roof (open-air),no sensors on the spaces themselves, basically no way to know when a car is over its time except by looking at it and checking the machine

I dont think they have any credible enforcement mechanism here. I have seen a car get a parking ticket, but I learned later that its owner made it an obvious target by leaving parked overnight.

HN, is there any credible way for the enforcement folks to catch people who don't pay? If you were in charge of parking revenues for the city what simple solution would you use in this system to catch HN readers who would get away with free parking?

*[2 years ago]: 2011-11-26T00:30:06.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7500_05_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3278696.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7500-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7500_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:12:54">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=4233078</link><title>Thoughts on Healthcare Reform and the Republican Party (from a Moderate).</title><description>Thoughts on Healthcare Reform and the Republican Party (from a Moderate).

1 point

by nrwayn

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

Healthcare. The ideal solution? Free-market forces and capitalism. Need surgery? Call up five hospitals compare prices, Hospital A may be expensive but they have the best surgeon and a guarantee to resolve post-op complications at no additional fee. Hospital B is less expensive, but has a longer wait to take new patients, etc. So in essence as a consumer you have a choice, and a market that responds to that. Unfortunately, healthcare in America doesn't work like that.

Is free-market healthcare a pipe dream? Just look at plastic surgery where there is no insurance for elective procedures. Doctors and their offices know that, so they deal with consumers directly. You find the best plastic surgeon, you get recommendations from friends/internet, compare prices, visit the office, and make your decision as a consumer. That's how healthcare should work.

So great, lets get rid of insurance companies altogether. Well not so fast, unlike most plastic surgery procedures where you have a choice, you have no choice if you find out unexpectedly that you need dialysis or chemotherapy. So to cover unexpected health risks, there's two options, have so much wealth that it doesn't matter, or buy insurance to cover your risk. So insurance is the answer for the majority of Americans. But here's the rub.

You buy a Ferrari, call up Geico and find out your monthly premium is thru the roof. Well fine, that's your own damn fault for buying an expensive car. But you find out you have cancer and call up looking for private health insurance, is it your own damn fault too when you can't afford the premiums? A large part of America will say 'absolutely', you should have chosen a career in a more stable field, gotten an advance degree, etc. In essence there is no difference between a high-risk car and a person with high-risk care.

As much as I love capitalism and laissez-faire economics, I can't accept that. A human with no choice in their medical condition, should not be left without an option for care, nor should they suffer a demeaning or lessened life because of it.

So I want balance. I want healthcare that allows as much free-market forces in, but smart government regulation to ensure there's a sensible option for those that need it. Definitely not universal healthcare, and certainly not anything remotely socialist.

Is the Affordable Care Act the answer? To me, yes and no. The restrictions placed on insurance companies make sense, which the same companies themselves offered to enact irrespective of the Supreme Court decision. A penalty for not carrying insurance doesn't make me smile, but its not intolerable unless you can explain why it makes economic sense for your typical American not to have insurance. However, the expansion of state-run medicare/medicaid is something that I think could have been addressed separately, left out of the bill altogether, or as recommended by the Supreme Court, refined with further legislation. I personally would like to see an alternative to medicaid/medicare not an expansion of it, for example - can we do things smarter with private vouchers for at-risk Americans that comes at a lesser cost to the government and less burden to our private medical system?

But all this seems like something that as a country we should be able to figure out. Healthcare reform should be a bi-partisan wet dream come true.

So I'm beyond frustrated that I don't know a single Republican position on healthcare reform. I want conservative viewpoints to moderate liberal ideas. Instead all the Republican party gives me is, "Obamacare evil. End of America unless we repeal." Well, if that's the case, the American people should pay the Republican party to go on vacation until they have a super majority in both houses. Oh wait.

*[2 years ago]: 2012-07-12T04:55:40.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7500_06_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/4233078.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7500-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7500_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:13:27">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=3779521</link><title>Questions about surrogate mothers egg donors and surrogacy for Intended Parents</title><description>Questions about surrogate mothers egg donors and surrogacy for Intended Parents

1 point

by 24x7esubmission

2 years ago

0 comment Follow

The journey of surrogacy for Intended Parents-Intended parents, surrogate mothers egg donors and egg donation-Steps to surrogacy process in India-10 Tips for intended parents to consider before surrogacy-10 steps to successful surrogacy and parenting-Gestational Surrogacy FAQ for Intended Parents-Questions about surrogate mothers egg donors and surrogacy for Intended Parents.

Intended Parents are the infertile couples who intend to have a child through the process of surrogacy.The individual or individuals who enter into a surrogacy agreement with surrogate mother with intent to become legal parent or legal parents of the child born to the surrogate are known as intended parents.

People of all sexualities [Gay, LGBT, Same Sex and straight]who want to have a child of their own but cannot conceive due to reasons out of their control become the intended parents in the process of surrogacy. Intended parents are either biological parents or need the help of egg donor, sperm donor and the surrogate mother. The parties to the agreement will be intended parent or intended parents, surrogate and the surrogates husband if any.

The community of intended parents is very big and come from all walks of life and every corner of the world. They may be infertile couples, single mom or dad or gay and lesbian couples. They all have one thing in common - a burning desire to become a parent or parents. It is very important for the Intended couple to select the right surrogate based on the review of complete medical records, checking family history, and social/criminal background and education level. It is also necessary to get a perfect psychological evaluation of the surrogate before selecting for surrogacy or Egg donation. Surrogacy or Egg donation is the best solution for infertility and other relative problems.

Intended parents are people who use conventional methods to have the children. Some intended parents opt for adoption or traditional surrogacy, while others choose gestational surrogacy. Gestational surrogacy has the advantage of offering intended parents the chance to have a child that is biologically related to one or both of them. All couples with infertility issues to single people to gay and lesbian couples can enjoy the parenthood with surrogacy. They all want to be parents and cannot do so without the help of a surrogate mother and/or egg and sperm donors.

Types of Intended Parents:

The parents that contract for a commercial surrogacy and bring the baby home, are actually referred to as intended parents in surrogate motherhood. There are three main types of intended parents: traditional couples, same-sex couples, and single intended parents.

Traditional Intended Parents: The term intended parents usually refers to a male/female couple who are the parents of the child conceived via commercial surrogacy. Most of the time, at least one of the parents is the biological parent of the child conceived, though quite commonly, both the intended mother and the intended father are the biological parents of the child.

Same sex couple: Intended Fathers called as gay couple has to sought help of a surrogate mother to help them have their own children. These men will either seek a traditional surrogate mother and use the sperm of one of the fathers, or will seek a gestational surrogate mother, and also an egg donor. Most likely, sperm of one father will be used, but in the case of a gestational surrogacy, it is not uncommon for intended fathers to use sperm from both partners.

Though uncommon, there are some circumstances where a set of homosexual intended mothers would seek a surrogate mother. The reason this is rare is that with two women, the chances of both experiencing fertility problems becomes rarer.

Single intended parents: Occasionally an unmarried man or woman will enter into commercial surrogacy. The reasons for an unmarried woman to seek a surrogate are usually the same as that of a male/female couple, but for the single male, he is most likely ready to start a family, and has not found the perfect partner.

It is very important for the Intended couple to select the right surrogate based on the review of complete medical records, checking family history, and social/criminal background and education level. It is also necessary to get a perfect psychological evaluation of the surrogate before selecting for surrogacy or Egg donation. Surrogacy or Egg donation is the best solution for infertility and other relative problems.

All Intended Parents must consider following 10 most important steps while entering into the Successful journey of surrogacy.

1] Intended Parenting: Determine beforehand whether surrogacy is right for you. Intended Parents opting for surrogacy must seriously consider all issues prior to making a decision to go ahead with a surrogacy arrangement.

2] Make all necessary inquiries for surrogacy agency, surrogate process, surrogate mothers, egg donors,egg donation, surrogacy cost and surrogacy law.Read the surrogacy contract agreement properly. Educate yourself thoroughly about surrogacy related questions.

3] Create a letter or profile about yourself. To help you find an ideal match, it is best to create a letter or profile about you and your partner. Describe your personal data, why you need surrogacy, surrogacy plans, time frames and any requirements you may have for your potential surrogate mother.

4] Screening of surrogate mothers and Surrogate Selection Process. This is the most important and challenging part of the whole surrogacy process. While choosing a surrogate one must consider the surrogates reproductive history, diet pattern, previous transfer, height, weight, Surrogate's support of the spouse and the family. Besides this entire surrogate has to go through extensive medical screening for any infections or diseases should be undertaken. Physiological screening as well as a thorough background check is also done.

5] Screening and Egg donors Selection Process before egg donation. Egg donor has to go through medical and physiological examination to evaluate their genetic history. Surrogates and egg donor are selected simultaneously. Egg donor profiles and photos are provided for selection.

6] Surrogacy Legal Agreements. A legal agreement is the most essential step in the whole process of surrogacy. Intended parents should comply with the legal aspects of surrogacy. Complete research should be done regarding laws pertaining to the intended parents country and arrive at a customized legal agreement. Concerned parties should sign the surrogacy agreement.

7] Payments to surrogate mothers. Never send any payments prior to signing a Surrogacy Agreement. Do not send money to your surrogate mother before signing a surrogacy agreement. All payments should be reimbursed after a receipt has been made. Some surrogate mothers use retainer fees before attempts at pregnancy, be sure the retainer agreement complies with law and has been checked by your lawyer.

8] Cost involved in surrogacy. The surrogacy is very expensive. Intended parents must consider their financial position before deciding for surrogacy. It has been observed that surrogacy overseas is very cheaper rather than in western countries. Hence intended parents must keep this option also open.

9] Confirmation of pregnancy of surrogate mother. When the IVF process is completed and it is confirmed that surrogate is pregnant, Intended parents are curious to know the state of pregnancy of the surrogate. They should remain in touch with surrogates health, progress in pregnancy and with the fertility clinic. The birth of a baby is a joyful movement for any parents. Here intended parents have the option to be present during the delivery of their baby.

10] Post Birth Formalities. Once the baby is born through surrogacy, intended parents should starts legal formalities for taking the possession of baby. Educate yourself on the legal status of surrogacy in your province, state or country. Not being aware of current laws and taking shortcuts could result in jeopardizing your parental rights. One of the best way to make sure you are properly adhering to the laws and (often changing) regulations, is to hire a lawyer that specializes in third party reproduction or surrogacy consultant to help guide you through the surrogacy process.

At the end of the whole surrogacy process take a deep breath, remain patient and try to focus on the end result... your baby! Get ready to enjoy the parenthood.

Many people globally are now choosing India a destination for Surrogacy.Simple reasons like: Surrogacy Treatment is Economical In India, Best Of IVF Doctor Easy to find Surrogate Mother In India,Legal Aspect of Surrogacy as law are in favor of the Intended parents going for surrogacy treatment.

Hence Surrogacy or Egg donation is the best solution available to intended parents for infertility and other relative problems. Whether it is financial, legal, immigration, travel or medical issues that Intended Parents had to contend with; these issues are no longer going to keep anyone from their dream of beginning a family.

"Surrogacy Mumbai", a website hosted by Rotunda-The Center for Human Reproduction gives you an insight into the surrogacy in India, egg donors services, surrogate mothers, egg donation and is Surrogacy IVF specialty clinic in India. Seeking surrogacy is by no means an easy decision both emotionally and financially, no matter how compelling the reason to seek it may be.

Whether it is financial,legal,immigration,travel or medical issues that Intended Parents had to contend with; these issues are no longer going to keep anyone from their dream of beginning a family.

We demystify the process making it as easy and comfortable Surrogacy journey as possible for the intended parent(s) We have every service relevant and pertinent to surrogacy under one roof. With a ground logistics team helping with the accommodations and travel, years of experience, we are fully geared to help clients of nearly all nationalities realize their dream for parenthood through surrogacy.

The most fascinating thing is that you may not have to come to India at first, You have to just send your sperm by The Rotunda CryoShip Global service.We find an egg donor,we get your surrogate pregnant."You just come down,pick up your baby, and go back home."

Start Creating your family today by contacting:

Rotunda-The Center for Human Reproduction Mumbai India. http://surrogacymumbai.com http://surrogacymumbai.wordpress.com surrogacymumbai.india@gmail.com +91 22 2640 5000

*[2 years ago]: 2012-03-31T05:49:52.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7500_07_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/3779521.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7500-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7500_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:13:59">http://onliveinfotech.com</link><title>Bulk SMS India</title><description>Bulk SMS India (http://onliveinfotech.com)

1 point

by brahmdatt

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

Onlive Infotech is a leading IT solution provider for Web Services, Software Development &amp; Bulk SMS Services organization dedicated to small and medium sized business applications. The Company has been promoted by some highly experienced Professionals dedicated to provide total IT solutions under 1 roof. It possesses not only the latest technology gadgets but also the most knowledgeable and experience hands to offer most user friendly customized solutions

*[3 years ago]: 2011-09-08T08:24:35.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7500_08_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2973101.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e110-7500-09"><link>http://www.nationalenergysummit.com</link><title>National Energy Investment Summit 2011</title><description>National Energy Investment Summit 2011 (http://www.nationalenergysummit.com)

1 point

by events4naseba

3 years ago

0 comment Follow

National Energy Investment Summit is an exclusive platform to propel investments into the Indian energy sector. More than 200 key stakeholders from the global energy sector including investors, capital raising firms, solution providers, technology partners, consultants, government agencies and industry associations will gather under one roof.

*[3 years ago]: 2011-06-28T10:09:54.000Z</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e110/7500_09_thumb.png">https://drcs9k8uelb9s.cloudfront.net/2704795.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>