<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7014">Asian culture</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:12:19" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7014-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.psychiatry.org/mental-health/people/asian-americans</link><title>Mental Health in Asian American and Pacific Islanders</title><description>... upon Asian patients’ mind-body connection. In many Asian cultures, the mentally ill are so stigmatized that sufferers ... The conflict between traditional family values and mainstream culture may cause ... Asian youth. Older Asian Americans and Pacific Islanders</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7014-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cdc.gov/hiv/risk/racialethnic/asians</link><title>HIV Infection among Asians in the United States and Dependent Areas</title><description>... fear of bringing shame to their families. Traditional Asian cultures emphasize male-dominated roles that highlight Asian women’s lack of sexual negotiating power in female- ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7014-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cdc.gov/nceh/lead/tips/folkmedicine.htm</link><title>Folk Medicine</title><description>... used by East Indian, Indian, Middle Eastern, West Asian, and Hispanic cultures. Folk medicines can contain herbs, minerals, metals, or ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7014-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.abta.org/.../treatments/alternative-medicine.html</link><title>Alternative and Integrative Medicine</title><description>... are the healthcare rituals practiced by a given culture (eg, Asian, Indian, African). Homeopathic Medicine: This alternative medicine system ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7014-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/womenshealth.gov/minority-health/asian-americans</link><title>Minority Women's Health: Asian-Americans</title><description>... a high risk group for heart disease, although Asian-Americans overall are at lower risk. Genes, culture, environment, and access to care play a role in the health status of specific ethnic groups. Asian-Americans face some of the same limitations to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7014-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.ssa.gov/aapi</link><title>Social Security Is Important to Asian Americans and Pacific Islanders</title><description>... same in terms of benefits. Who Are We? Asian Americans and Pacific Islanders (AAPIs) come from nearly 50 countries and ethnic groups, each with distinct cultures, traditions and histories. AAPIs speak over one hundred ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7014-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/womenshealth.gov/.../fact-sheet/anorexia-nervosa.html</link><title>Anorexia Nervosa</title><description>... not known for sure whether African American, Latina, Asian/Pacific Islander, and American Indian and Alaska Native people develop eating disorders because American culture values thin people. People with different cultural backgrounds ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7014-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.womenshealth.gov/.../fact-sheet/bulimia-nervosa.html</link><title>Bulimia Nervosa</title><description>... not known for sure whether African American, Latina, Asian/Pacific Islander, and American Indian and Alaska Native people develop eating disorders because American culture values thin people. People with different cultural backgrounds ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7014-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/newsroom.heart.org/...rican-fast-food-increasing-235780.aspx</link><title>American Fast Food Increasing Heart Disease Risk in Southeast Asians</title><description>... has increased heart and diabetes risk among southeast Asians. The study’s results suggest the need for more attention to global behavioral and dietary changes that occur as cultures interact with one another. EMBARGOED UNTIL 3 pm ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7014-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.plasticsurgery.org</link><title>American Society of Plastic Surgeons</title><description>... Trade-Offs' in Breast Reconstruction 03/31/2014 Culture, Anatomy Are Key Factors for Plastic Surgeons Performing 'Asian Rhinoplasty' 03/31/2014 Stats Show Growth of ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>