<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7020">synovial joint</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:19:07" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7020-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/imagepages/9245.htm</link><title>Joint aspiration (image)</title><description>... analysis is a series of tests performed on synovial (joint) fluid to help diagnose and treat joint-related abnormalities. To obtain a synovial fluid sample, a needle is inserted into the knee between the joint space. When the needle is in place the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7020-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/.../body_basics/bones_muscles_joints.html</link><title>Bones, Muscles, and Joints: The Musculoskeletal System</title><description>... give the spine its flexibility. Freely movable, or synovial, joints move in many directions. The main joints of ... ankles — are freely movable. They are filled with synovial fluid, which acts as a lubricant to help the joints move easily. Three kinds of freely movable joints ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7020-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/orthoinfo.aaos.org/topic.cfm?topic=A00217</link><title>Viscosupplementation Treatment for Arthritis</title><description>... is a naturally occurring substance found in the synovial (joint) fluid. It acts as a lubricant to enable ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7020-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/labtestsonline.org/understanding/analytes/uric-acid/tab/test</link><title>Uric Acid Test</title><description>... diagnose gout, a test for monosodium urate in synovial fluid (joint fluid) can. Some people may have a high ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7020-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/labtestsonline.org/understanding/analytes/synovial/tab/test</link><title>Synovial Fluid Analysis</title><description>... culture may be ordered in addition to the synovial fluid analysis. Joint injury, surgery, and joint replacement can increase the ... is it performed? Arthrocentesis is the removal of synovial fluid from a joint with a needle and syringe. A local anesthetic ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7020-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/article/003629.htm</link><title>Synovial fluid analysis</title><description>... analysis is a group of tests that examine joint (synovial) fluid. The tests help diagnose and treat joint- ... Joint fluid analysis; Joint fluid aspiration</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7020-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/article/004015.htm</link><title>Aging changes in the bones - muscles - joints</title><description>... Instead, they are cushioned by cartilage in the joint, synovial membranes around the joint, and fluid. Muscles provide the force and strength ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7020-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cancer.org/...ult-soft-tissue-cancer-soft-tissue-sarcoma</link><title>What Is a Soft Tissue Sarcoma?</title><description>... more common in women than in men. Malignant joint tumors Synovial sarcoma is a malignant tumor of the tissue around joints. The most common locations are the knee and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7020-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/article/000422.htm</link><title>Gout</title><description>... acid builds up in the fluid around the joints (synovial fluid), uric acid crystals form. These crystals cause the joint to swell and become inflamed. The exact cause ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7020-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/labtestsonline.org/understanding/analytes/lyme/tab/test</link><title>Lyme Disease Test</title><description>... spinal tap. Sometimes a sample of joint fluid (synovial fluid) from an infected joint will be drawn. NOTE: If undergoing medical tests ... genetic material ( DNA ) of B. burgdorferi in the joint fluid (synovial fluid). Very rarely, a sample, such as a ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>