<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7024">reinforcement learning</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:47:00" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7024-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/.../ency/patientinstructions/000460.htm</link><title>Maximizing your teaching moment</title><description>As you are teaching, provide reinforcement for learning. Tell your patient they are doing a good job. Acknowledge when your patient has overcome a challenge. Offer hints, tips, and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7024-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/article/001406.htm</link><title>Developmental reading disorder</title><description>... instruction Private, individual tutoring Special day classes Positive reinforcement is important as many students with learning disabilities have poor self-esteem. Psychological counseling may ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7024-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.autismspeaks.org/.../AS-HFA_Tool_Kit.pdf</link><title>Asperger Syndrome and High Functioning Autism Tool Kit</title><description>... on the behavior. The consequence can include positive reinforcement of the desired behavior, or no reaction for the incorrect response. ABA targets the learning of skills and the reduction of challenging behaviors. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7024-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cdc.gov/ncbddd/tourette/treatments.html</link><title>Tourette Syndrome (TS): Treatments</title><description>... specific to these problems. The training might include learning about the effective use of positive reinforcement and discipline that is effective with their particular ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7024-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.ctf.org/images/pdf/nf1aboutlearningdisabilities.pdf</link><title>About Learning Disabilities and NF</title><description>... mistakes. • Give verbal descriptions to promote understanding and reinforcement of visual information. • Use graph paper when doing ... the child’s strengths rather than their weaknesses. • Positive reinforcement has been shown to be very effective in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7024-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/effectivehealthcare.ahrq.gov/...displayproduct&amp;productID=709</link><title>Therapies for Children with Autism Spectrum Disorders: A Review of the Research for Parents and Caregivers</title><description>... analysis” (commonly known as ABA) strategies like positive reinforcement. Do they help? Some children in the TEACCH ... included in the cost of the school or learning center, so there may not be any other ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7024-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/parent/emotions/behavior/adhd.html</link><title>What Is ADHD?</title><description>... tasks into smaller, more manageable pieces. Give positive reinforcement. Always be on the lookout for positive behaviors. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7024-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.aacap.org/cs/root/facts_for_families/physical_punishment</link><title>Physical Punishment</title><description>... and help change their behavior. Examples include positive reinforcement, time-out, taking away of privileges, and physical ... behavior. Praising a good behavior is called positive reinforcement and leads to more of that behavior. As ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7024-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.help4adhd.org/en/education/rights/WWK4</link><title>Educational Rights for Children with AD/HD</title><description>... notes. Using positive behavioral intervention techniques, including positive reinforcement. Having a nurse or administrator oversee a student's ... qualify if the ADHD seriously impacts the child's learning and/or behavior at school. Some children with ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7024-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.marchofdimes.com/baby/hearing-impairment.aspx</link><title>Hearing Impairment</title><description>... in older infants and children include (2): Visual reinforcement audiometry (VRA): This test is used in children ... loud Appear inattentive at school and have trouble learning to read or perform simple mathematics. How is ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>