<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7083">I'm on the road again</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:16:01" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7083-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.orlive.com/.../carpal-tunnel-release?view=displayPageNLM</link><title>Carpal Tunnel Release</title><description>... are simply a matter of persisting compression on \-- I'm sorry, residual ... exert some compression again later in life. But again, those numbers are ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7083-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.orlive.com/...tic-vitrectomy-surgery?view=displayPageNLM</link><title>Diabetic Vitrectomy Surgery</title><description>... for bleeding or scarring inside the eye. And again, I'm just working on the vitreous gel here. We're working in the ... I've gone back in with our forcep again. And there's a little blood vessel ... try to pull that off. The blood vessel growth is attached to the regular ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7083-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.orlive.com/...surgery-the-male-sling?view=displayPageNLM</link><title>Innovative Incontinence Surgery: The Male Sling</title><description>... for blocking everybody’s view, but as you see I’m pushing down on the needle and it’s going to again come out on my finger in just a ... definitely improved the quality of my life. Although I’m not completely ... walk five to six miles a day on the beach and I ride my bicycle again, ten ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7083-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.orlive.com/...d-the-weekend-warriors?view=displayPageNLM</link><title>Knee Pain and the Weekend Warriors</title><description>... back to you. Okay. We’re back on. Again, we’re working on the knee here. We have repaired our meniscus. I’m going to show you that in a min second. This, again, is our anterior cruciate ligament right here. You ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7083-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.orlive.com/.../awake-craniotomy?view=displayPageNLM</link><title>Awake Craniotomy</title><description>... 12 I don’t remember that promise, but I’m make good on it. And, again, even as we’re working, we can still interact with the patient and talk with them. And, in fact, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7083-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.orlive.com/...e-fibroid-embolization?view=displaypageNLM</link><title>Uterine Fibroid Embolization</title><description>... weigh in together if this is, in fact, the endpoint. Again, slow flow, a little bit of flow maintained. I'm sorry, we should be on that for you. We can replay that run, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7083-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.orlive.com/...l-of-the-thyroid-gland?view=displayPageNLM</link><title>Surgical Removal of the Thyroid Gland</title><description>... tracheal tubes. Am I on? Yes, you’re on. Go ahead. Okay. Again, I’m Dr. Kulkarni. And what I’m going to show you is the difference between a normal endotracheal tube, which is ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7083-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.orlive.com/...-brain-surgery-program?view=displayPageNLM</link><title>Acoustic Neuroma Procedure</title><description>... to see footage from the live procedure in the O.R., and again, I'm going to turn it over to Dr. Reichard and Dr. Harvey to walk us through what we're actually seeing on screen here. 00:25:43 KENNETH REICHERT, MD: ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7083-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.orlive.com/...g-treatment-procedure2?view=displayPageNLM</link><title>Bone Anchored Hearing Treatment Procedure</title><description>... we're going to help her nicely today. I'm just going to show you how we close up. So now again the skin's been closed, and we have what we call -- this is a healing cap. Simply snaps on to the abutment. And then we wind a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7083-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.orlive.com/...-cardiac-defibrillator?view=displayPageNLM</link><title>Automatic Implantable Cardiac Defibrillator</title><description>... you can decanulate and this is my lead I'm ready to advance there. Once the lead get on the coronary sinus, we have to worry about at couple of things. You're going to see further down the road where we pacing with a big difference, a ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>