<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7091">don't listen to a word i say</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:30:47" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7091-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/kid/feeling/friend/family_friend_died.html</link><title>Somebody in My Friend's Family Died. What Should I Do?</title><description>... say: "If you want to talk about it, I will listen." That's a really kind thing to say. Don't be surprised if your friend doesn't want ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7091-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.amputee-coalition.org/inmotion/may_jun_02/talk.pdf</link><title>Let's Talk...and Listen</title><description>... patient, “How are you?” A. Mean it. B. Listen to the response – Don’t start taking notes. C. Respond appropriately. D. Care! 5. Be aware that your patients will not respect you any less if you say, “I don’t know,” as long as you continue with “but I will ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7091-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cancer.org/...-loved-one-helping-someone-who-is-grieving</link><title>Helping Someone Who is Grieving</title><description>... to comfort someone who is grieving. Many people don’t know what to say or do. Use the following tips as a guide. What to say Acknowledge the situation. Example: “I heard that your_____ died.” Use the word “died.” This shows that you are more open ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7091-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nidcd.nih.gov/health/voice/pages/stutter.aspx</link><title>Stuttering</title><description>... reduce time pressures the child may be experiencing. Listen attentively when the child speaks and wait for him or her to say the intended word. Don't try to complete the child’s sentences. Also, help the child learn that a person can communicate successfully even when stuttering occurs. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7091-05"><link>https://www.americanhospice.org/...spice-care-what-to-do-what-to-say</link><title>Visiting People Receiving Hospice Care: What to Do, What to Say</title><description>... want to talk, that’s fine and if not, I’m grateful to just be with you and we don’t have to talk at all." The most loving act you can do for people who are facing death is to listen to their thoughts. You could say—perhaps with a sense of humor or sincere sense in your ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7091-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e072/7091_06.pdf" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:38:12">https://store.samhsa.gov/shin/content//SMA-3715/SMA-3715.pdf</link><title>Building Self-Esteem: A Self-Help Guide</title><description>... happy, peaceful, loving, enthusiastic, warm. Avoid using negative words such as worried, frightened, upset, tired, bored, not, never, can't . Don't make a statement like " I am not going to worry any more. " Instead say " I focus on the positive " or whatever feels ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7091-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nia.nih.gov/...w-ad-changes-people-challenges-and-coping</link><title>Understanding How Alzheimer's Disease Changes People: Challenges and Coping Strategies</title><description>... What would you like for dinner?" Use different words if he or she doesn't ... you remember?" or "I told you." Helping a Person Who Is Aware ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7091-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.americasheroesatwork.gov/forEmployers/factsheets/tips</link><title>Tips for Communicating with People with Traumatic Brain Injury (TBI) &amp; Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD)</title><description>... Treat the individual with dignity, respect and courtesy. Listen to the ... to respond to a person's needs or requests. Be mindful that symptoms ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7091-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nia.nih.gov/...or_a_person_with_alzheimers_disease_0.pdf</link><title>Caring for a Person with Alzheimer's Disease</title><description>... What would you like for dinner?” • Use different words if he or she doesn’t ... or “I told you.” Caring for a Person with AD ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7091-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.healthychildren.org/...roving-Family-Communications.aspx</link><title>Improving Family Communications</title><description>... such as, "When we go to the store I expect you to be polite and stay with me." Make ... your talking times as teachable moments – do not miss opportunities to show ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>