<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7103">cystic fibrosis treatment</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:27:47" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7103-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cff.org/treatments/Therapies</link><title>Therapies for Cystic Fibrosis</title><description>... to Cystic Fibrosis Foundation-supported research, people with cystic fibrosis (CF) have more therapy options than ever before. There are drugs to ... airways directly. Other Drugs Research supported by ... led to other respiratory treatments that are now considered “standard therapies” for many ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7103-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.genome.gov/10001213</link><title>Learning about Cystic Fibrosis</title><description>... Therapy Research Offers Promise of a Cure for Cystic Fibrosis Gene therapy offers great promise for life-saving treatment for ... often it needs to be repeated. The first cystic fibrosis gene therapy experiments have involved lung cells because these cells ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7103-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/.../tutorials/cysticfibrosis/htm/index.htm</link><title>Cystic Fibrosis</title><description>... identify the digestive abnormalities that are typical of cystic fibrosis. Treatment At present, there is no cure for cystic fibrosis. Treatment consists of reducing symptoms and slowing down the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7103-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nhlbi.nih.gov/.../health-topics/topics/cf/treatment.html</link><title>How Is Cystic Fibrosis Treated?</title><description>... Home » Health Information for the Public » Health Topics » Cystic Fibrosis » Treatments Cystic Fibrosis Explore Cystic Fibrosis What Is ... Other ... acid and help oral pancreatic enzymes work better. Treatments for Cystic Fibrosis Complications A common complication of CF is diabetes . ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7103-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/.../issues/fall12/articles/fall12pg6-7.html</link><title>Symptoms, Diagnosis, Treatment &amp; Living with CF | NIH MedlinePlus the Magazine</title><description>... please turn Javascript on. Feature: Steady Advances Against Cystic Fibrosis Symptoms, Diagnosis, Treatment Past Issues / Fall 2012 Table of Contents Click ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7103-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/cysticfibrosis.html</link><title>Cystic Fibrosis</title><description>... occurred in children and teenagers. Today, with improved treatments, some people who have CF are living into their forties, fifties, or older. NIH: National Heart, Lung, and Blood Institute</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7103-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/article/000107.htm</link><title>Cystic fibrosis</title><description>... BC; Clinical Practice Guidelines for Pulmonary Therapies Committee; Cystic Fibrosis Foundation Pulmonary Therapies Committee. Cystic fibrosis pulmonary guidelines: pulmonary complications: hemoptysis ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7103-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/article/003010.htm</link><title>Lung transplant</title><description>... BC; Clinical Practice Guidelines for Pulmonary Therapies Committee; Cystic Fibrosis Foundation Pulmonary Therapies Committee. Cystic fibrosis pulmonary guidelines: Pulmonary complications: hemoptysis ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7103-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/.../issues/fall12/articles/fall12pg4-5.html</link><title>Steady Advances Against Cystic Fibrosis | NIH MedlinePlus the Magazine</title><description>... living longer than ever due to advances in treatment. Cystic fibrosis (CF) is a genetically inherited chronic disease of ... one is a better example of improvements in cystic fibrosis (CF) research and treatment than Gunnar Esiason. The 21-year-old Boston ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7103-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cff.org/treatments/Pipeline</link><title>Drug Development Pipeline</title><description>... the world. In keeping with this business model, Cystic Fibrosis Foundation Therapeutics, Inc., the Foundation's nonprofit drug development affiliate, customarily ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>