<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7119">chocolate photo</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:13:34" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7119-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/default.htm</link><title>Recalls, Market Withdrawals and Safety Alerts</title><description>... Issues Allergy Alert On Undeclared Milk In Dark Chocolate Blueberries PHOTO \- Wolfgang B. Gourmet Foods, Inc. Issues Allergy Alert ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7119-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.ccakids.com/newsletters.html</link><title>CCA Newsletters</title><description>... director - friends of jeremy - choose kind - pete's oktoberfest - chocolate festival - ryan's road - holiday parties CCA 2012 Issue 3 Newsletter - message from the development director - hartley golf outing - choose kind - craniofacial acceptance month picnic photos \- raegan's rally - links of love - cca kid's blog ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7119-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.fda.gov/.../AnimalHealthLiteracy/ucm186940.htm</link><title>Potentially Dangerous Items for Your Pet</title><description>... Some of the more hazardous food items include: Photo courtesy of Robert Inouye Alcohol products (beer and wine) Avocado Coffee Chocolate Fruit/Seed pits (including corn cobs) Garlic Macadamia ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7119-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.usaid.gov</link><title>United States Agency for International Development</title><description>... News and Information Press Releases Congressional Testimony Speeches Photo Gallery The Impact Blog Fact ... U.S. and Mexico Partner to Increase Cacao Production in El Salvador Learn More United Nations, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7119-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.heart.org/...per-about-superfoods_UCM_457937_Article.jsp</link><title>What's So Super about Superfoods?</title><description>... Research has shown that bioactive compounds in dark chocolate may have health benefits, but watch out for ... the calories. “Don’t eat so much dark chocolate that you overshoot your daily calorie goal and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7119-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.heart.org/.../Sugar-101_UCM_306024_Article.jsp</link><title>Sugar 101</title><description>... fruit yogurt, 6 oz. container 77.5 Milk chocolate, 1 bar (1.55 oz) 77.4 Cake ... 1 Angel food cake, 1 piece 60.4 Chocolate puff cereal, 1 cup 56.4 Vanilla ice ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7119-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.skincarephysicians.com/eczemanet/contact_dermatitis.html</link><title>Contact Dermatitis</title><description>... found in jewelry and many foods, including tomatoes, chocolate, nuts, and soy. Mercury (used in dental fillings), ... as many foods, including canned goods, tomatoes, and chocolate. A dermatologist can help the patient devise a ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7119-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.rosacea.org/patients/materials/coping/tripwires.php</link><title>Coping with Rosacea: Tripwires</title><description>... necessary to keep enjoying coffee, tea and hot chocolate, for example. Or try reducing the number of ... included cheese, sour cream, yogurt, citrus fruit, liver, chocolate, vanilla, soy sauce, yeast extract (though bread is ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7119-09"><link>https://ebusiness.avma.org/.../HouseholdHazards-En.pdf</link><title>Household Hazards to Pets</title><description>... be hazardous to pets. Halloween treats such as chocolate or candy sweetened with xylitol can make a ... of your pet’s menu: Coffee groundsFatty foods Tea Chocolate Avocado Alcohol Yeast dough Grapes/raisins Salt Macadamia ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7119-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.heart.org/.../Smart-Substitutions_UCM_302052_Article.jsp</link><title>Smart Substitutions for Healthy Cooking</title><description>... free egg substitute (1/4 cup) Unsweetened baking chocolate (1 ounce) 3 tablespoons unsweetened cocoa powder or ... free egg substitute (1/4 cup) Unsweetened baking chocolate (1 ounce) 3 tablespoons unsweetened cocoa powder or ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>