<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7125">psychological effects of obesity in children</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:49:58" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7125-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.healthychildren.org/...-a-Pediatric-Endocrinologist.aspx</link><title>What Is a Pediatric Endocrinologist?</title><description>... have special needs related to growth and development. In addition, their psychological needs are different from those of adults. Hormone problems affecting growth or sexual development can have significant effects on a child’s physical and emotional well-being. Pediatric endocrinologists are ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7125-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.ihs.gov/healthyweight/documents/HW4L_Communities.pdf</link><title>Healthy Weight for Life: Actions for Communities, Individuals, and Families</title><description>... cancers, as well as orthopedic, oral health, and psychological problems. ... or obese; among children and youth, between 45 percent and 51 percent ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7125-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/mda.org/.../files/MDA_Quest_Excercise_Package_2009.pdf</link><title>Exercising with a Muscle Disease</title><description>... of motion. And it’s important for cardiovascular health, psychological health and prevention of obesity to ... a 10-year-old child with dermatomyositis whose disease has been well controlled ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7125-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/patients.gi.org/topics/functional-abdominal-pain-in-children</link><title>Functional Abdominal Pain in Children</title><description>... threatening. However, functional abdominal pain may have negative effects on ... regarding the location of abdominal pain, the frequency (number of times per ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7125-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/news/fullstory_144644.html</link><title>Bullying May Have Lasting Health Effects on Kids</title><description>... of being bullied and their health, such as obesity and chronic illnesses. They ... Crimes Against Children Research Center at the University of New Hampshire, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7125-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.entnet.org/HealthInformation/Pediatric-Obesity.cfm</link><title>Pediatric Obesity and Ear, Nose, and Throat Disorders</title><description>... sleep apnea, and irregular metabolism. Additionally, there are psychological consequences; ... children, such as: Sleep apnea: Children with ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7125-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.help4adhd.org/en/living/relandsoc/WWK15</link><title>Social Skills in Adults with AD/HD</title><description>... pharmacologic interventions for hyperactive boys: Comparative and combined effects . ... Psychological Association Press. 14. Novotni, M. (2000). What Does ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7125-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nhlbi.nih.gov/health/public/sleep/healthy_sleep.pdf</link><title>Your Guide to Healthy Sleep</title><description>... become agitated and may be considered hyperactive. The effects of sleep apnea in children may include poor school performance and difficult, aggressive ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7125-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/mchb.hrsa.gov/chusa11/more/downloads/pdf/c11.pdf</link><title>Child Health USA 2011</title><description>... pressure, high cholesterol, and Type 2 diabetes. Obese children are also at increased risk of obesity in adulthood, which is associated with a host of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7125-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cdc.gov/nchs/data/databriefs/db141.htm</link><title>Physical Activity in U.S. Youth Aged 12-15 Years, 2012</title><description>... KV, Taimela S, Telama R, Rasanen L, Viikari JS. Effects of persistent physical activity and inactivity on coronary risk factors in children and young adults. The Cardiovascular Risk in Young ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>