<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7134">history of yoga</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:31:14" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7134-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/nccam.nih.gov/health/yoga/introduction.htm</link><title>Yoga for Health</title><description>... as heart disease, lung disease, and a prior history of heatstroke may want to avoid this form of yoga. Women who are pregnant may want to check ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7134-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/pregnancy.html</link><title>Pregnancy</title><description>So you're going to have a baby! Whether you are pregnant or are planning to get pregnant, you will want to give your baby a healthy start. You need to have ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7134-03"><link>https://www.michaeljfox.org/.../i-have-got-what.php</link><title>Advice for the Newly Diagnosed</title><description>... window will close soon, so make the most of it while you can — for your own ... walking and yoga as favorites. Engage in challenging activities that you ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7134-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/nccam.nih.gov/health/pain/chronic.htm</link><title>Chronic Pain and Complementary Health Approaches: What You Need To Know</title><description>... Evaluation of the effectiveness and efficacy of Iyengar yoga therapy on chronic ... without history of recurrent depression. Journal of Consulting and Clinical ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7134-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/womenshealth.gov/.../LifetimeGoodHealth-English.pdf</link><title>Lifetime of Good Health: Your Guide to Staying Healthy</title><description>... of a disease? People with a family health history of chronic dis- ease may have the most to ... disease early. People who have a family health history of a chronic disease may benefit the most from ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7134-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.hiv.va.gov/.../alternative-therapies/single-page.asp</link><title>Alternative (Complementary) Therapies for HIV/AIDS</title><description>... you can learn about examples of these types of therapies. Yoga Yoga is a set of exercises that people ... health care provider. There are many different types of yoga and various classes you can take. You can ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7134-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nhlbi.nih.gov/health/public/heart/other/hhw/hdbk_wmn.pdf</link><title>Healthy Heart Handbook for Women</title><description>... Some risk factors, such as age and family history of early heart disease, can’t be changed. For ... develop other risk factors for heart disease. Family history of early heart disease is another risk factor that ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7134-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/nccam.nih.gov/health/RA/getthefacts.htm</link><title>Rheumatoid Arthritis and Complementary and Alternative Medicine</title><description>... Chhabra V, Leibman C, et al. The benefits of yoga for rheumatoid arthritis: results of a preliminary, structured ... Howard P, et al. Functional and physiological effects of yoga in women with rheumatoid arthritis: a pilot study. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7134-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nhlbi.nih.gov/.../other/your_guide/healthyheart.pdf</link><title>Your Guide to a Healthy Heart</title><description>... risk factors during this stage of life. Family history of early heart disease is another risk factor that ... contributors to high blood pressure are a family history of the disease, overweight, and dietary salt. Older individuals ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7134-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.ninds.nih.gov/disorders/headache/detail_headache.htm</link><title>Headache: Hope through Research</title><description>... age 50. New headaches in someone with a history of cancer or HIV/AIDS. Diagnosing Your Headache How ... notes about other family members who have a history of headache or other disorder. A pattern may emerge ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>