<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7137">Cat movies</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:15:20" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7137-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/kid/closet/movies/video_ctscan.html</link><title>Getting a CAT Scan</title><description>... Injuries Jellyfish The Pink Locker Society Getting a CAT Scan (Video) KidsHealth &gt; Kids &gt; Movies &amp; More &gt; Movies &gt; Getting a CAT Scan (Video) Print A A A Text Size ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7137-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nia.nih.gov/...ivities-you-enjoy-more-just-fun-and-games</link><title>Participating in Activities You Enjoy - More Than Just Fun and Games</title><description>... activities, play bingo Sunday evenings, go to the movies together, have a knitting club, and even organize ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7137-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/womenshealth.gov/.../LifetimeGoodHealth-English.pdf</link><title>Lifetime of Good Health: Your Guide to Staying Healthy</title><description>... whether the x-ray is necessary. • Avoid changing cat litter. It can carry and cause an infec- ... go for a walk, or go to the movies. Reduce stress with exercise, meditation, hot baths, or ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7137-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cancer.gov/.../coping/When-Your-Sibling-Has-Cancer.pdf</link><title>When Your Brother or Sister Has Cancer: A Guide for Teens</title><description>... a bone to be examined under a microscope CAT scan or CT scan (Computerized axial tomography) Uses ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7137-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/kid/ill_injure/bugs/flea.html</link><title>Hey! A Flea Bit Me!</title><description>... People, Places &amp; Things That Help Feelings Q&amp;A Movies &amp; More Quizzes Games Kids' Medical Dictionary En Español ... their blood. If you have a dog or cat, chances are pretty good that you've seen ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7137-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/kid/stay_healthy/body/cant_sleep.html</link><title>What to Do if You Can't Sleep</title><description>... they watch scary or violent TV shows or movies or read scary books or stories before bedtime. ... habit to break, but your lovable dog or cat could be keeping you awake. As your pet ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7137-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/kid/watch/house/animals.html</link><title>How to Stay Safe around Animals</title><description>... water away. Don't tease a dog or cat or pull its tail or ears. Never bother ... take a toy or bone away from a cat or dog or hold it out of reach ... near a pet with its babies (like a cat with kittens or a dog with puppies). Animal ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7137-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/mda.org/.../files/MDA_Quest_Excercise_Package_2009.pdf</link><title>Exercising with a Muscle Disease</title><description>... I could work, read, listen to music, watch movies and surf the Internet. The idea of just ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7137-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/kid/feeling/thought/pet_death.html</link><title>My Pet Died - How Can I Feel Better?</title><description>... day when Elena came home from school, her cat Tomaso would run to greet her. Then Elena would pick up Tomaso and give the cat a hug. One day, though, Elena came home ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7137-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/kid/watch/out/thunderstorms.html</link><title>Thunderstorms</title><description>... you and can make you jump. No wonder movies use thunder, lightning, and dark stormy nights when ... or even a pet. Imagine your dog or cat was the one who was scared. You would ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>