<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7146">why do leaves fall</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:15:08" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7146-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/kid/watch/er/scars.html</link><title>Story on Scars</title><description>... have one or two scars already. Most people do. Why? Because a lot of things leave behind scars — from falls, like the one Holly had, to surgeries. Scars ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7146-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.intelihealth.com/.../falls-frequently-asked-questions</link><title>Falls: Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)</title><description>... and their answers — about falls among the elderly: Why do older people fall more frequently than younger people? What are the ... is the role of exercise and balance training? Why do older people fall more frequently than younger people? Factors that contribute ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7146-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/teen/expert</link><title>Teens Health: Expert Answers</title><description>... Should I Do If I Can't Sleep? Why Do I Feel Paralyzed Before I Fall Asleep? Why Does My Body Jerk Before I Fall Asleep? Doctors, Hospitals &amp; Medicine Can I Get My Medical Records if a Doctor Moves ... Your Pelvic Exam If You've Had Sex? Do I Have to Get All Three HPV Vaccine ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7146-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/main.zerotothree.org/.../18-24Handout.pdf?docID=6083</link><title>Your Child's Development 18 to 24 Months</title><description>... Make an indoor “sandbox” of dry oatmeal or fall leaves. Help your child solve a problem but don’t do it all for him. The more he does, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7146-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/teen/your_body/medical_care/wounds.html</link><title>Wound Healing and Care</title><description>... healing is done, the scab dries up and falls off, leaving behind the repaired skin and, often, a scar. Why do scars look different from normal skin? Our skin ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7146-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.orlive.com/...ney-transplant-surgery?view=displayPageNLM</link><title>Living Donor Kidney Transplant Surgery</title><description>... perceive that on the scales. And another question. “Why do you cut off the extra tissue on the kidney, and is the adrenal gland removed with the kidney or is it left behind?” We do leave the adrenal gland behind. There’s no reason to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7146-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.bt.cdc.gov/radiation/emergencyfaq.asp</link><title>Frequently Asked Questions about Radiation Emergencies</title><description>... and your family until it is safe to leave the area. Learn more Back to top If I was outside when a radiation emergency happened, what should I do to remove radioactive material from myself? Radioactive material can fall from the air like dust or sand and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7146-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/parent/general/sleep/cosleeping.html</link><title>Cosleeping and Your Baby</title><description>... where an infant belongs. But is it safe? Why Do Some People Choose to ... babies fall asleep more easily, especially during their first few ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7146-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/.../girls/irregular_periods.html</link><title>Irregular Periods</title><description>... isn't fertilized by sperm, it starts to fall apart. About 2 weeks later, the lining and egg leave a girl's body as her period and the whole thing starts all over again — that's why we use the word "cycle." All this sounds ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7146-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/.../girls/menstrual_problems.html</link><title>Coping with Common Period Problems</title><description>... it usually disappears when her period ... both of these hormones begin to fall. The thinking is that these changing hormone levels ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>