<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7168">fabric glue</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:55:39" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7168-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.epa.gov/iaq/pubs/insidestory.html</link><title>Inside Story: A Guide to Indoor Air Quality</title><description>... and environmental tobacco smoke. Durable press drapes, other textiles, and glues. Health Effects: Eye, nose, and throat irritation; wheezing ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7168-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.epa.gov/iaq/formaldehyde.html</link><title>Formaldehyde</title><description>... and environmental tobacco smoke. Durable press drapes, other textiles, and glues. Top of page Health Effects Formaldehyde, a colorless, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7168-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/familydoctor.org/...lated-skin-problems.printerview.all.html</link><title>Skin Problems: How to Protect Yourself from Job-Related Skin Problems</title><description>... work-related skin allergies include acrylate glues (super glues), epoxies, textile dyes or resins, and latex. A list of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7168-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cancer.gov/cancertopics/factsheet/Risk/formaldehyde</link><title>Formaldehyde and Cancer Risk</title><description>... wood products, such as particleboard, plywood, and fiberboard; glues and adhesives; permanent-press fabrics; paper product coatings; and certain insulation materials. In ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7168-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cancer.org/...-and-paranasal-sinuses-cancer-risk-factors</link><title>What Are the Risk Factors for Nasal Cavity and Paranasal Sinus Cancers?</title><description>... and other wood-related industries Dusts from textiles (textile plants) Leather ... Formaldehyde Organic solvents Smoking Some studies have found ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7168-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.drugabuse.gov/publications/drugfacts/inhalants</link><title>Inhalants</title><description>... felt-tip marker fluid, electronic contact cleaners, and glue Aerosols —sprays that contain propellants and solvents Household aerosol propellants in items such as spray paints, hair or deodorant sprays, fabric protector sprays, aerosol computer cleaning products, and vegetable ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7168-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cpsc.gov/...de-to-Preventing-Inhalant-Abuse-text-version</link><title>Parent's Guide to Preventing Inhalant Abuse</title><description>... The following categories of products are reportedly abused: glues/adhesives, nail ... whipping cream aerosols, and air conditioning coolants. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7168-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/kid/feel_better/things/stitches.html</link><title>How Stitches Help Kids Heal</title><description>... way of closing a cut is to use glue! Sometimes, if a cut isn't too deep ... the forehead, the doctor will use special skin glue to keep the cut's edges together until it ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7168-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/teens.drugabuse.gov/drug-facts/inhalants</link><title>Inhalants</title><description>... any home or workplace. Examples are some paints, glues, gasoline, and cleaning fluids. Many people do not ... by Type? Inhalant Examples Effects TOLUEENE Spray paint Glue Dewaxer Fingernail polish Hearing loss Damage to white ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7168-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.redcross.org/.../m4540081_repairingFloodedHome.pdf</link><title>Repairing Your Flooded Home</title><description>... stone (with waterproof mortar) • Styrofoam insulation • Water resistant glue Products that resist water damage 42 8 S T ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>