<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7173"> severed spinal cord</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:48:58" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7173-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/.../spring13/articles/spring13pg11.html</link><title>College Athlete Stands Again…On His Own! | NIH MedlinePlus the Magazine</title><description>... Summers, scientists believed that patients with a completely severed spinal cord would never be able to regain voluntary control ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7173-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.ninds.nih.gov/.../chronic_pain/detail_chronic_pain.htm</link><title>Pain: Hope through Research</title><description>... and cordotomy , where bundles of nerves within the spinal cord are severed. Cordotomy is generally used only for the pain of terminal cancer that does not respond to other therapies. ... or DREZ, in which spinal neurons corresponding to the patient's pain are destroyed ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7173-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/imagepages/19588.htm</link><title>Central nervous system (image)</title><description>... of nerves that run up and down the spinal cord are severed.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7173-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.ninds.nih.gov/.../brachial_plexus/brachial_plexus.htm</link><title>Brachial Plexus Injuries</title><description>... avulsion , is caused when the nerve root is severed or cut from the spinal cord. There is also an incomplete form of avulsion ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7173-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.ninds.nih.gov/disorders/backpain/detail_backpain.htm</link><title>Low Back Pain</title><description>... fibers on one or both sides of the spinal cord are intentionally severed to stop the transmission of pain signals to the brain; and dorsal root entry zone operation, or DREZ , in which spinal neurons transmitting the patient’s pain are destroyed surgically. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7173-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.christopherreeve.org/.../k.901E/Newly_Paralyzed.htm</link><title>Newly Paralyzed</title><description>... oxygen related to surgical or underwater mishaps. The spinal cord does not have to be severed in order for a loss of function to occur. The spinal cord can be bruised, stretched, or crushed. Since the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7173-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.ninds.nih.gov/disorders/sci/detail_sci.htm</link><title>Spinal Cord Injury: Hope through Research</title><description>... below the level of injury, even if the spinal cord was not completely severed. Studies have shown that people with incomplete injuries have a greater chance of recovering some function in the affected limbs than ... of Spinal Cord Injury (ISNCSCI) to measure the extent of neurologic ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7173-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.ninds.nih.gov/.../detail_peripheralneuropathy.htm</link><title>Peripheral Neuropathy</title><description>... can cause nerves to be partially or completely severed, crushed, compressed, or stretched, sometimes so forcefully that they are partially or completely detached from the spinal cord. Less dramatic traumas also can cause serious nerve ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7173-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.anausa.org/.../overview/types-of-post-treatment-issues</link><title>Types of Post-Treatment Issues</title><description>... will take time to heal. If it was severed, the balance nerve on the other side ... brain and spinal cord. It is continuously produced and absorbed. On occasion, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7173-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nichd.nih.gov/.../conditioninfo/Pages/default.aspx</link><title>What Is Spinal Cord Injury?</title><description>... NICHD Research Information Clinical Trials Resources and Publications Spinal Cord Injury (SCI): Condition Information Skip sharing on social ... with SCI is the lowest point on the spinal cord below which sensory feeling and motor movement diminish ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>