<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7207">earthquake</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:49:13" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7207-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/earthquakes.html</link><title>Earthquakes</title><description>An earthquake happens when two blocks of the earth suddenly slip past one another. Earthquakes strike suddenly, violently, and without warning at any time of the day or night. If an earthquake occurs in a populated area, it may cause ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7207-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.redcross.org/prepare/disaster/earthquake</link><title>Earthquake</title><description>... Disaster or Emergency › Types of Emergency › Earthquake Preparedness Earthquake Preparedness About About Earthquake An earthquake is a sudden, rapid shaking of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7207-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.bt.cdc.gov/disasters/earthquakes</link><title>Earthquakes</title><description>... Hurricanes Landslides Tornadoes Tsunamis Volcanoes Wildfires Winter Weather Earthquakes Language: English Español (Spanish) Surviving an earthquake and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7207-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.ready.gov/earthquakes</link><title>Earthquakes</title><description>... time. Before During After More Information Before an Earthquake The following are things you can do to ... most of the destruction during earthquakes. During an Earthquake Drop, cover and Hold On. Minimize your movements ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7207-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.usfa.fema.gov/citizens/home_fire_prev/earthquakes.shtm</link><title>Earthquakes and Fire Safety</title><description>... gov USFA Home Citizens Home Fire Prevention Earthquakes Earthquakes and Fire Safety This page may contain links ... Fire Related Hazards Present During and After an Earthquake Appliances, furniture, and household products can shift, fall, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7207-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/earthquake.usgs.gov/learn/kids</link><title>Earthquakes for Kids</title><description>Earthquakes for Kids Kid's Privacy Policy Earthquake Topics for Education FAQ Earthquake Glossary For Kids Prepare Google ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7207-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/earthquake.usgs.gov/learn/facts.php</link><title>Earthquake Facts</title><description>The largest recorded earthquake in the United States was a magnitude 9.2 that struck Prince William Sound, Alaska on Good Friday, March ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7207-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nctsn.org/...rents_Talk_to_Children_about_Earthquake.pdf</link><title>Parent Guidelines for Helping Children After an Earthquake</title><description>Parent Guidelines for Helping Children after an Earthquake Being in an earthquake is very frightening, and the days, weeks, and months following are very stressful. Your children and family will recover ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7207-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nctsn.org/.../Earthquake_Caregiver_071008_Formatted.pdf</link><title>Guidance for Caregivers: Children or Teens Who Had a Loved One Die in the Earthquake</title><description>... WHO HAD A LOVED ONE DIE IN THE EARTHQUAKE July 2008 About the National Child Traumatic Stress ... WHO HAD A LOVED ONE DIE IN THE EARTHQUAKE Introduction to trauma The earthquake was a terrifying ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7207-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.redcross.org/find-help/disaster-recovery</link><title>Recovering After a Disaster or Emergency</title><description>... Learn More Now Respond To and Recover From Earthquakes Earthquakes Learn More Now Respond To and Recover From ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>