<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7215">squamous cell carcinoma</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:12:56" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7215-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.aad.org/.../dermatology-a-to-z/squamous-cell-carcinoma</link><title>Squamous Cell Carcinoma</title><description>... Diseases and treatments Q - T Squamous cell carcinoma Squamous cell carcinoma Squamous cell carcinoma : This man's skin has been ... treatment, SCC is highly curable. Learn more about squamous cell carcinoma: Squamous cell carcinoma: Signs and symptoms Squamous cell ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7215-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.skinsight.com/adult/squamousCellCarcinomaSCC.htm</link><title>Squamous Cell Carcinoma (SCC)</title><description>newsletter | contact Share | Squamous Cell Carcinoma (SCC) Information for adults A A A Squamous cell carcinoma typically develops in sun-damaged skin in fair-skinned ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7215-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cap.org/.../docs/reference/myBiopsy/cervicalsquamous.pdf</link><title>Cervical Squamous Cell Carcinoma</title><description>What is cervical squamous cell carcinoma? According to the American Cancer Society, in 2010 more than 12,200 American women will be diagnosed with invasive ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7215-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cap.org/.../reference/myBiopsy/head_and_neck_larynx.pdf</link><title>Squamous Cell Carcinoma of the Larynx</title><description>What is squamous cell carcinoma of the larynx? Squamous cell carcinoma represents more than 90 percent of all head and neck cancers. In ... 80 percent. Who is most likely to have squamous cell carcinoma? Males have this type of cancer about twice ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7215-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cap.org/.../myBiopsy/head_and_neck_lip_oral.pdf</link><title>Head and Neck Cancer Squamous Cell Carcinoma/Lip and Oral Cavity</title><description>What is squamous cell carcinoma of the lip and oral cavity? Squamous cell carcinoma represents more than 90 percent of all head and ... 80 percent. Who is most likely to have squamous cell carcinoma? Males have this type of cancer about twice ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7215-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.skincarephysicians.com/.../squamous_cell_carcinoma.html</link><title>Squamous Cell Carcinoma: What It Looks Like</title><description>Squamous Cell Carcinoma: What it Looks Like Squamous cell carcinoma accounts for approximately 16% of all new skin cancer ... and human immunodeficiency virus (HIV). Diagnosed Cases of Squamous Cell Carcinoma This tumor developed rapidly over a six-month ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7215-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cap.org/.../myBiopsy/squamous_cell_skin_cancer.pdf</link><title>Squamous Cell Carcinoma</title><description>What is squamous cell skin carcinoma? The second most common skin cancer, squamous cell skin carcinoma affects 250,000 Americans each year. This type ... to spread. Who is most likely to have squamous cell skin carcinoma? This slow-growing disease affects individuals who have ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7215-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/article/000829.htm</link><title>Squamous cell carcinoma</title><description>Squamous cell carcinoma is a type of skin cancer. Skin cancer falls into two groups: nonmelanoma and melanoma. Squamous ... D, et al. Nonmelanoma skin cancers: basal and squamous cell carcinomas. In: Abeloff MD, Armitage JO, Nierderhuber JE, Kastan ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7215-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cancer.gov/cancertopics/pdq/treatment/esophageal/patient</link><title>Esophageal Cancer (PDQ): Treatment</title><description>... lung cancer . The following stages are used for squamous cell carcinoma of the esophagus: Stage 0 (High-grade Dysplasia) ... is also called high-grade dysplasia . Stage I squamous cell carcinoma of the esophagus Stage I is divided into ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7215-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/imagepages/18017.htm</link><title>Squamous cell carcinoma (image)</title><description>Squamous cell carcinoma commonly starts in the bronchi and may not spread as rapidly as other lung cancers.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>