<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7216">salmonella</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:32:37" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7216-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/salmonellainfections.html</link><title>Salmonella Infections</title><description>Salmonella is the name of a group of bacteria. In the United States, it is a common cause of foodborne illness. Salmonella occurs in raw poultry, eggs, beef, and sometimes ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7216-02"><link>https://www.avma.org/.../Dry-Pet-Foods-and-Salmonella-FAQs.aspx</link><title>Salmonella: Dry Pet Foods and Pet Treats (FAQ)</title><description>... Currently selected Market Research Statistics Reference Guides Reports Salmonella: Dry Pet Foods and Pet Treats (FAQ) Originally ... 2008, there was a prolonged multistate outbreak of Salmonella enterica serotype Schwarzengrund infections in humans. A total ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7216-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/article/000294.htm</link><title>Salmonella enterocolitis</title><description>Salmonellosis; Nontyphoidal salmonella ... Salmonella infection is one of the most common types of food poisoning . It occurs when you swallow ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7216-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cdc.gov/Features/SalmonellaBabyBirds</link><title>Risk of Human Salmonella Infections from Live Baby Poultry</title><description>... Favorites Delicious Digg Google Bookmarks Risk of Human Salmonella Infections from Live Baby Poultry Risk of Human ... items into their mouths. How do people get Salmonella infections from live baby poultry? View Large Version [ ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7216-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cdc.gov/Features/SalmonellaFrogTurtle</link><title>Reptiles, Amphibians, and Salmonella</title><description>... Favorites Delicious Digg Google Bookmarks Reptiles, Amphibians, and Salmonella Reptiles, Amphibians, and Salmonella Did you know that ... aquariums where they live. How do people get Salmonella infections from reptiles and amphibians? Reptiles and amphibians ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7216-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cdc.gov/Features/SalmonellaEggs</link><title>Tips to Reduce Your Risk of Salmonella from Eggs</title><description>... Google Bookmarks Tips to Reduce Your Risk of Salmonella from Eggs Eggs are one of nature's most ... can take to reduce my risk of a Salmonella infection from eggs? Like other foods, keep eggs ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7216-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cdc.gov/healthypets/diseases/salmonellosis.htm</link><title>Salmonella Infection (Salmonellosis) and Animals</title><description>... Professionals Glossary Resources Outbreak Response and Prevention Branch Salmonella Infection (salmonellosis) and Animals Important Tip! Protect yourself ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7216-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cdc.gov/.../dfbmd/diseases/salmonella_enteritidis</link><title>Salmonella Serotype Enteritidis</title><description>Salmonella serotype Enteritidis General Information Frequently Asked Questions Salmonella serotype Enteritidis infection Egg and chicken contamination Who ... Pages in this Report General Information Additional Information Salmonella serotype Enteritidis infection Salmonella serotype Enteritidis (SE) is ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7216-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cdc.gov/salmonella/general/diagnosis.html</link><title>Salmonella Diagnosis and Treatment</title><description>... Digg Google Bookmarks Diagnosis and Treatment How Can Salmonella Infections Be Diagnosed? Many different kinds of illnesses ... testing can determine its specific type. How Can Salmonella Infections Be Treated? Salmonella gastrointestinal infections usually resolve ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7216-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cdc.gov/healthypets/salmonella_pocketpets.htm</link><title>Salmonella from Pocket Pets</title><description>... Professionals Glossary Resources Outbreak Response and Prevention Branch Salmonella from Pocket Pets The Salmonella germ is actually ... has been cleaned and disinfected. Tips for Preventing Salmonella from Rodents Washing hands with soap and water ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>