<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7242">hague convention</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:16:11" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7242-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.childwelfare.gov/pubs/f_adoptoption.cfm</link><title>Adoption Options</title><description>... web section on Adopting Children From Another Country . Hague Convention Country Adoption Parents who adopt from a Hague ... for the list of about 75 countries. Non-Hague Convention Country Adoption Parents adopting from a non-Hague ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7242-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/adoption.state.gov</link><title>Intercountry Adoption</title><description>... Summary Reporting Requirements Hague Certificate Child Citizenship The Hague Convention on Intercountry Adoption: A guide for prospective adoptive ... there are two distinct intercountry adoption processes: the Hague Convention process and the non-Hague Convention process. Which ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7242-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/adoption.state.gov/about_us/statistics.php</link><title>Adoption Statistics</title><description>... Summary Reporting Requirements Hague Certificate Child Citizenship The Hague Convention on Intercountry Adoption: A guide for prospective adoptive ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7242-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.childwelfare.gov/pubs/f_start.cfm</link><title>Adoption: Where Do I Start?</title><description>... adoption, what country will our child come from? (Hague Convention or non-Hague Convention country? See box below.) The way you choose ... plan to adopt is a party to the Hague Convention on Protection of Children and Co-operation in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7242-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.childwelfare.gov/pubs/f_inter</link><title>Intercountry Adoption: Where Do I Start</title><description>... Adjusting to your new family Additional Resources The Hague Convention The Hague Convention on Protection of Children and Co-operation in ... adoption will reflect the safeguards enacted by the Hague Convention. For more information, see the Information Gateway factsheet ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7242-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.childwelfare.gov/pubs/f_homstu.cfm</link><title>Adoption Home Study Process</title><description>... plan to adopt is a party to the Hague Convention on Protection of Children and Co-operation in ... is, your home study will be subject to Hague Convention requirements. These requirements mandate which agencies or service ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7242-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.childwelfare.gov/pubs/f_milita.cfm</link><title>Military Families Considering Adoption</title><description>... a country that is a member of the Hague Convention on Intercountry Adoption is different from adopting a child from a non-Hague Convention country. Read Information Gateway's Intercountry Adoption From Hague ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>