<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7250">collagen vascular disease</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:11:30" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7250-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/article/001223.htm</link><title>Collagen vascular disease</title><description>Collagen vascular disease occurs when problems with the immune system affect collagen. Collagen is a tough, fiber-like protein ... As a group, these diseases are known as collagen vascular diseases. ... include: Ankylosing spondylitis Dermatomyositis Polyarteritis ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7250-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.insidermedicine.com/..._Health_Sciences_Center_2855.aspx</link><title>If I Had - Shortness of Breath</title><description>... disease? If you have what is known as collagen vascular disease, such as lupus, rheumatoid arthritis, scleroderma, polymyositis, mixed ... help clear it up. It you have a collagen vascular disease, often time the standard treatment for a collagen ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7250-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nationalmssociety.org/Symptoms-Diagnosis/Diagnosing-MS</link><title>Diagnosing MS</title><description>... Lyme disease, a group of diseases known as collagen-vascular diseases, certain rare hereditary disorders, and AIDS. Other tests ( ... that lead to inflammation of blood vessels (the "collagen-vascular diseases"), and some rare hereditary disorders. Demyelination of the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7250-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/article/003657.htm</link><title>Blood differential</title><description>... be due to: Addison's disease Allergic reaction Cancer Collagen vascular disease Hypereosinophilic syndromes Parasitic infection An increased percentage of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7250-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/vasculitis.html</link><title>Vasculitis</title><description>Vasculitis is an inflammation of the blood vessels. It happens when the body's immune system attacks the blood vessel by mistake. It can happen because of an infection, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7250-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/rheumatoidarthritis.html</link><title>Rheumatoid Arthritis</title><description>Rheumatoid arthritis (RA) is a form of arthritis that causes pain, swelling, stiffness and loss of function in your joints. It can affect any joint but is common ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7250-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/scleroderma.html</link><title>Scleroderma</title><description>... National Institute of Arthritis and Musculoskeletal and Skin Diseases</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7250-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/lupus.html</link><title>Lupus</title><description>If you have lupus, your immune system attacks healthy cells and tissues by mistake. This can damage your joints, skin, blood vessels and organs. There are ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7250-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/myositis.html</link><title>Myositis</title><description>Myositis means inflammation of the muscles that you use to move your body. An injury, infection, or autoimmune disease can cause it. Two specific kinds are polymyositis ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7250-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/article/003535.htm</link><title>Antinuclear antibody panel</title><description>... blood may be due to: Chronic liver disease Collagen vascular disease Drug-induced lupus erythematosus Myositis (inflammatory muscle disease) ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>