<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7263">hospital acquired pneumonia</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:36:40" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7263-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/article/000146.htm</link><title>Hospital-acquired pneumonia</title><description>Hospital-acquired pneumonia is an infection of the lungs that occurs during a hospital stay. This type of pneumonia ... breathing machine (respirator). This machine helps them breathe. Hospital-acquired pneumonia can also be spread by health care workers, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7263-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/imagepages/17276.htm</link><title>Hospital-acquired pneumonia (image)</title><description>Pneumonia acquired in the hospital is a very serious infection because the patient's defense mechanisms are often impaired by illness, and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7263-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/familydoctor.org/.../pneumonia.printerview.all.html</link><title>Pneumonia</title><description>... after you have a cold or the flu. Hospital-acquired pneumonia (also called institution-acquired pneumonia) is a type ... Pneumonia that you catch in a hospital (called hospital-acquired pneumonia) can be more serious than other types of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7263-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/pneumonia.html</link><title>Pneumonia</title><description>Pneumonia is an infection in one or both of the lungs. Many germs, such as bacteria, viruses, and fungi, can cause pneumonia. You can also get pneumonia by inhaling ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7263-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/article/000093.htm</link><title>Pneumonia \- weakened immune system</title><description>... as "pneumonia in an immunocompromised host." See also: Hospital-acquired pneumonia Pneumocystis jirovecii (previously called Pneumocystis carinii ) pneumonia Pneumonia \- ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7263-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/article/000145.htm</link><title>Pneumonia \- adults (community acquired)</title><description>... affects persons in health care facilities is called hospital-acquired pneumonia . ... Bronchopneumonia; Community-acquired pneumonia; CAP</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7263-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/article/003804.htm</link><title>Chest x-ray</title><description>... failure Histoplasmosis; acute (primary) pulmonary Histoplasmosis Hodgkin’s lymphoma Hospital-acquired pneumonia Hypersensitivity pneumonitis Hypertensive heart disease Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy Hypothyroidism ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7263-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/.../tutorials/pneumonia/htm/index.htm</link><title>Pneumonia</title><description>... such as at school, work or the gym. Hospital-acquired or nosocomial pneumonia is a serious pneumonia acquired at a hospital or a healthcare facility. It usually affects patients ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7263-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/druginfo/meds/a605003.html</link><title>Cefditoren</title><description>... is used to treat infections such as community acquired pneumonia (a lung infection that developed in a person who was not in the hospital), flare-ups of chronic bronchitis (infection of the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7263-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/druginfo/meds/a614002.html</link><title>Tigecycline Injection</title><description>... used to treat certain serious infections including community acquired pneumonia (a lung infection that developed in a person who was not in the hospital), skin infections, and infections of the abdomen (area ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>