<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7293">basil recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:15:09" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7293-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/...tes_recipes.html?tracking=P_RelatedArticle</link><title>About Recipes for Kids with Diabetes (For Parents)</title><description>... their blood sugar levels. Check out these delicious recipes: Breakfast on the Go Club Wrap Cranberry Spritzer Grilled Cheese Sandwich Nutty Chocolate Chip Cookies Vegetable Skillet Frittata Strawberry Cheese Tart Taco Popcorn Tomato Basil Pizza Snack Zesty Turkey Tenderloin With Vegetables Sign ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7293-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nhlbi.nih.gov/health/public/heart/other/sp_recip.pdf</link><title>Delicious Heart-Healthy Latino Recipes</title><description>... Appetizers and Soups Delicious and Heart Healthy Latino Recipes Lentil Soup n 2 tablespoons olive oil ... 1 teaspoon dried basil n ½ teaspoon ground black pepper n 2 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7293-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nhlbi.nih.gov/.../Dinners_Cookbook_508-compliant.pdf</link><title>Keep the Beat Recipes: Deliciously Healthy Dinners</title><description>... to plan and prepare the meals in this cookbook. These ingredients can be used in both main-dish meals and side dishes. They are available in most grocery stores and are easy to use. herbs and spices (fresh and dried): add flavor Basil Ground black pepper Cayenne pepper Chili powder Cilantro ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7293-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nhlbi.nih.gov/.../heart/other/chdblack/cooking.pdf</link><title>Heart-Healthy Home Cooking: African American Style</title><description>... spray ½ teaspoon black pepper ½ teaspoon dried basil ½ teaspoon oregano 1\. Rinse green beans and ... but not soft. Stir occasionally. 6. Sprinkle dried basil and oregano over green beans. Mix and serve. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7293-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.heart.org/...tes-Friendly-Recipes_UCM_313900_Article.jsp</link><title>Diabetes-Friendly Recipes</title><description>... flavorful omelets, full of fresh vegetables and fragrant basil. Spinach-Parmesan Quiche Bites Serve these savory bites ... flavor from the pan juices. Salmon with Tomato-Basil Salsa The fresh tomato-basil salsa will have ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7293-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.bestbonesforever.gov/recipes_main</link><title>Recipes \-- Best Bones Forever</title><description>... low-fat cottage and mozzarella cheeses, garlic and basil with cooked pasta and covering it with your ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7293-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.aicr.org/.../Nov2007_After_50_FINAL.pdf?docID=1571</link><title>Nutrition After Fifty: Tips and Recipes</title><description>... oil 1 Tbsp. honey 1 Tbsp. rosemary or basil or 1 tsp. dried 2 Tbsp. balsamic vinegar, ... mix together canola oil, honey and rosemary or basil. Place in microwave and warm for 10 seconds. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7293-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cdc.gov/.../ndep/cdcinfo/ndep_pdf/tasty-recipes-508.pdf</link><title>Tasty Recipes for People with Diabetes and Their Families</title><description>... cup low-fat ricotta cheese ½ tsp. dried basil 1 small onion, minced 2 cloves garlic, minced ... 16 • Mix low-fat ricotta cheese with dried basil, onion, garlic, and salt. Spread this mixture over ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7293-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.kidney.org/atoz/pdf/diabetes.pdf</link><title>Diabetes and Chronic Kidney Disease</title><description>... onion, diced medium carrots, diced 1 teaspoon dried basil 1/ teaspoon dried oregano 1/ teaspoon dried thyme ... carrots, and cook until onions become translucent. add basil, oregano, thyme, and garlic; cook for another minute. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7293-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nhlbi.nih.gov/health/public/heart/hbp/dash/new_dash.pdf</link><title>Your Guide To Lowering Your Blood Pressure with DASH</title><description>... zucchini, sliced 1 Tbsp oregano, dried 1 Tbsp basil, dried 1 8 oz can tomato sauce 1 ... 2 cups low-sodium tomato sauce 2 tsp basil, dried 2 tsp oregano, dried 1 /4 cup ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>