<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7303">what causes itchy feet</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:22:16" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7303-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.skinsight.com/diseaseGroups/itchyBumpsChild.htm</link><title>Itchy Bumps on the Skin in Children</title><description>... begin… Dyshidrotic Eczema Dyshidrotic eczema appears as small, itchy, fluid-filled blisters on the hands and feet. It is not known what causes dyshidrotic eczema. Sweating does not seem to cause ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7303-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/effectivehealthcare.ahrq.gov/...isplayproduct&amp;productID=1139</link><title>Medicines for Early Stage Chronic Kidney Disease: A Review of the Research for Adults with Kidney Disease and Diabetes ....</title><description>... change, nausea, and swelling in the ankles and feet. End stage CKD can also make you feel sick and tired and have itchy or dry skin. What causes CKD? The most common causes of CKD are ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7303-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/.../fall13/articles/fall13pg24-25.html</link><title>What is Psoriasis? | NIH MedlinePlus the Magazine</title><description>... Psoriasis? Past Issues / Fall 2013 Table of ... palms, and soles of the feet. Psoriasis may also affect the fingernails, toenails, the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7303-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/kid/talk/qa/germs.html</link><title>What Are Germs?</title><description>... example of something caused by fungi is athlete's foot, that itchy rash that teens and adults sometimes get between their ... What Do Germs Do? Once germs invade our bodies, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7303-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.niams.nih.gov/.../atopic_dermatitis_ff.asp</link><title>What Is Atopic Dermatitis?</title><description>... common symptoms of atopic dermatitis are: Dry and itchy skin Rashes on the face, inside the ... Causes Atopic Dermatitis? How Is Atopic Dermatitis Diagnosed? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7303-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/familydoctor.org/.../psoriasis.printerview.all.html</link><title>Psoriasis</title><description>... also bleed at times) Skin that burns, is itchy or sore Thick, pitted fingernails Pus-filled blisters on the red ... What causes psoriasis? Psoriasis starts with the immune system. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7303-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.healthychildren.org/...worm-Athletes-Foot-Jock-Itch.aspx</link><title>Tinea Infections (Ringworm, Athlete's Foot, Jock Itch)</title><description>... may advise the use of antibacterials. When fungi cause athlete’s foot, the skin can become itchy and red with cracking and flaking between the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7303-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/kid/health_problems/skin/fungus.html</link><title>Fungal Infections</title><description>... you and a parent can look for: Athlete's foot causes symptoms that include red, dry, cracked, and itchy skin between the toes. Some people also have red, scaly bumps filled with pus on the bottoms and sides of their feet. Jock itch appears as a rash with elevated ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7303-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.skinsight.com/diseaseGroups/itchyHandsFeet.htm</link><title>Itchy Hands or Feet</title><description>... hands and/or feet can have several possible causes. Many of these conditions on the hands or feet are itchy, but, in some people, they may not itch ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7303-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/labtestsonline.org/understanding/analytes/fungal/tab/test</link><title>Fungal Tests</title><description>... Superficial fungal infections are very common. They may cause nail infections or itchy red scaly skin infections such as those commonly known as athlete's foot, jock itch, and ringworm, or yeast infections that ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>