<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7307">causes of the cold war</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:16:03" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7307-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/stress.html</link><title>Stress</title><description>... hurt or killed. Examples include a major accident, war, assault, or a natural ... such as the flu or common cold. Vaccines, such as the flu shot, are less ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7307-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.entnet.org/HealthInformation/antibiotics.cfm</link><title>Antibiotics and Sinusitis</title><description>... in 1929, but it was not until World War II that the effectiveness of ... can also cause sinus problems. Antibiotics are effective only against sinus ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7307-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.ninds.nih.gov/.../CounterACT_Tawfik_PON1.htm</link><title>Scientists Could Turn Natural Enzyme into Defense against Man-Made Nerve Agents</title><description>... can protect against V-type agents, a class of organophosphate-based nerve toxins developed during the cold war era. (According to the U.S. Army's Chemical Materials ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7307-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.niehs.nih.gov/.../resources/bioethics/timeline/index.cfm</link><title>Research Ethics Timeline (1932-Present)</title><description>... The Soviet Union tests a hydrogen bomb; the Cold War begins. 1953 James Watson and Francis Crick discover the structure of DNA, for which they eventually would share the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7307-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/emergency.cdc.gov/.../winter/pdf/extreme-cold-guide.pdf</link><title>Extreme Cold: A Prevention Guide to Promote Your Personal Health and Safety</title><description>... risk of household fires increases, as well as the risk of carbon monoxide poisoning. Exposure to cold temperatures, whether indoors or outside, can cause other serious or life-threatening health problems. Infants ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7307-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/womenshealth.gov/...feedingGuide-AfricanAmerican-English.pdf</link><title>Your Guide to Breastfeeding for African-American Women</title><description>... serve at room temperature. Some moms serve it cold. Thaw frozen milk in the refrigerator overnight, • by holding the bottle or frozen bag of milk under war m r unning water, or setting it in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7307-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/womenshealth.gov/.../BreastfeedingGuide-General-English.pdf</link><title>Your Guide to Breastfeeding</title><description>... serve at room temperature. Some moms serve it cold. Thaw frozen milk in the refrigerator overnight, • by holding the bottle or frozen bag of milk under war m r unning water, or setting it in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7307-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/wwwnc.cdc.gov/.../injuries-and-safety</link><title>Travelers' Health: Injuries and Safety</title><description>... Death of US citizens abroad by non-natural causes. Washington, DC: US Department of State; 2012. ... 2-13. Ranking of the countries with the 20 highest estimated traffic death ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7307-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/jama.jamanetwork.com/.../JAMA/4476/jpg0819_816_816.pdf</link><title>JAMA Patient Page: Inappropriate Use of Antibiotics</title><description>... and are not effective against the viruses that cause many illnesses including influenza and most upper respiratory tract infections, including the common cold, or fungal infections like those caused by yeast. The inappropriate use of antibiotics for these types of infections as well ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7307-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.headaches.org/.../Viral_Infection_Headache</link><title>Viral Infection Headache</title><description>... the upper respiratory tract, such as the common cold virus, the Rhinovirus. This particular infection may produce intense congestion in the nasal passages, which at times causes a blockage of the sinus drainage passages, and can also cause ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>