<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7328">reduce acne redness</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:44:00" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7328-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.aad.org/...-benefits-and-a-place-on-their-medicine-shelf</link><title>Over-the-Counter Acne Products Can Have Benefits and a Place on Their Medicine Shelf</title><description>... anti-inflammatory that can be taken orally to reduce the redness and bumps caused by acne inflammation. Dr. Graber advises patients to talk with ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7328-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.skincarephysicians.com/...e_topical_acne_medication.html</link><title>Topical Acne Medication Can Clear Acne</title><description>... pores) moisturizer immediately after applying the medication can reduce the redness, drying, and peeling. Do you experience itching or stinging after applying a topical acne medication? These indicate that your skin is dry ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7328-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/article/000879.htm</link><title>Rosacea</title><description>... and will not improve with over-the-counter acne treatment. In severe cases, laser surgery may help reduce the redness. Surgery to remove some swollen nose tissue may ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7328-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/womenshealth.gov/.../our-publications/fact-sheet/acne.html</link><title>Acne</title><description>... your dermatologist may suggest surgery to help heal acne lesions and remove scarring. A laser can reshape scar tissue and reduce redness. Dermabrasion is a type of surgery that can ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7328-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.skincarephysicians.com/rosaceanet/laser_treatment.html</link><title>Is Laser Treatment Right for Your Rosacea?</title><description>... studies conclude that IPL can safely and effectively reduce the following signs of rosacea in some patients: Dilated blood vessels Persistent redness Flushing Acne-like breakouts To investigate the safety and effectiveness, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7328-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.healthychildren.org/.../skin/pages/Eczema.aspx</link><title>Eczema</title><description>... people sleepy). Prescription Medication Topical steroids —Used to reduce pain, redness, and swelling and to stop the itch. Uncommon side effects, including thinning of the skin, stretch marks, or acne, may occur if not used as recommended and ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7328-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/druginfo/natural/113.html</link><title>Tea tree oil</title><description>... tree oil may kill bacteria and fungus, and reduce allergic skin reactions.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7328-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/aidsinfonet.org/fact_sheets/view/513</link><title>Molluscum</title><description>... can be treated with drugs used to treat acne such as tretinoin (Retin-A) or isotretinoin (Accutane). This is a newer approach. These drugs reduce the amount of oil in the skin. The top layer of skin dries out and peels off. These drugs can cause redness and soreness. Retin-A is a cream that ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7328-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/article/001462.htm</link><title>Keratosis pilaris</title><description>... appear on the face and be mistaken for acne</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7328-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/familydoctor.org/.../acne.printerview.all.html</link><title>Acne</title><description>... help treat acne. These treatments may also help reduce acne scars. Individual large acne cysts often respond dramatically ... Complications Does acne cause scars? Acne, especially cystic acne, can cause scars in some people. You can help reduce scarring by not squeezing or picking at blemishes. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>