<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7405">light therapy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:54:28" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7405-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.mayoclinic.org/.../basics/definition/PRC-20009617?p=1</link><title>Light Therapy</title><description></description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7405-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.apa.org/.../releases/2013/02/seasonal-disorder.aspx</link><title>Seasonal Affective Disorder Sufferers Have More Than Just Winter Blues</title><description>... comparing the effectiveness of cognitive-behavioral therapy with light therapy. What have you learned? Dr. Rohan: For the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7405-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.skincarephysicians.com/acnenet/article_lasers.html</link><title>Laser Treatment for Acne: What You Should Know</title><description>... this type of acne treatment. Laser treatment or light therapy might be a part of an acne treatment ... as medicine applied to the skin. Laser or light therapy may help when other acne treatment has not ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7405-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/teen/your_mind/mental_health/sad.html</link><title>Seasonal Affective Disorder</title><description>... winter months and might help with mild symptoms. Light Therapy Stronger symptoms of SAD may be treated with light therapy (also called phototherapy ). Light therapy involves the use ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7405-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.niams.nih.gov/Health_Info/Psoriasis/default.asp</link><title>Psoriasis</title><description>... water in the skin, reducing scaling and itching. Light Therapy Natural ultraviolet (UV) light from the sun and ... used in treating psoriasis. It is important that light therapy be administered by a doctor. Spending time in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7405-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.aad.org/.../vitiligo-diagnosis-treatment-and-outcome</link><title>Vitiligo: Diagnosis, Treatment and Outcome</title><description>... another treatment such as topical corticosteroid. 4. PUVA light therapy: Uses UVA light and a medicine called psoralen ... monitored. 5. Surgery: May be an option when light therapy and medicines applied to the skin do not ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7405-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.skincarephysicians.com/rosaceanet/laser_treatment.html</link><title>Is Laser Treatment Right for Your Rosacea?</title><description>... bruising, and skin lightening. Thinking about laser or light therapy? If you are considering laser therapy or IPL ... results can be long-lasting, neither laser nor light therapy cures rosacea. You still need to continue to ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7405-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.skinsight.com/cosmetics/phototherapy.htm</link><title>Phototherapy</title><description>... types of UV light treatment include: Broadband UVB light therapy (280–320 nanometer wavelengths) Narrow band UVB light treatments (311 nanometer wavelength only) UVA light therapy (320–400 nanometer wavelengths of light) PUVA (320– ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7405-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.skincarephysicians.com/...treatment_thickening_skin.html</link><title>Rosacea Treatment: Thickening Skin</title><description>... describes each of these treatments: Lasers and other light therapies. While earlier laser treatments removed the top layers ... a significant portion of skin. Other lasers and light therapies also may be used. To see best results, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7405-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.skincarephysicians.com/rosaceanet/treatment_redness.html</link><title>Rosacea Treatment: Redness, Flushing, and Visible Blood Vessels</title><description>... for a day or two. Lasers and Other Light Therapies Effectiveness: The redness, flushing, and visible blood vessels may be effectively treated with lasers and other light therapies. While the number of treatments varies, most people ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>