<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7406">does my child have adhd</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:06:16" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7406-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/familydoctor.org/...ivity-disorder-adhd.printerview.all.html</link><title>Attention-Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD)</title><description>... Doctor What treatment is best for me? Why does my child have ADHD? What can I do to help my child? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7406-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nimh.nih.gov/.../index.shtml</link><title>Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder</title><description>... both medication and therapy. How can I help my child? Give your ... easy. Teens with ADHD can have a tough time. While hyperactivity tends to get ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7406-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.help4adhd.org/faqs.cfm</link><title>Frequently Asked Questions about AD/HD</title><description>Living with ADHD: A Lifespan Disorder</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7406-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.autismspeaks.org/.../AS-HFA_Tool_Kit.pdf</link><title>Asperger Syndrome and High Functioning Autism Tool Kit</title><description>... Telling Family Members The following article, adapted from Does My Child Have Autism?, by Wendy L. Stone, Ph.D., provides ... 100 days! Comparing Treatment Methods &amp; Providers Adapted from: Does My Child Have Autism? By Wendy L. Stone, Ph.D. with ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7406-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.hormone.org/.../FS_GD_Delayed_Puberty_EN web.pdf</link><title>Delayed Puberty</title><description>... out their feelings. Questions to ask your doctor • does my child have delayed puberty? • What’s causing my child’s delayed puberty? • does my child need treatment for delayed puberty? • What ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7406-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nimh.nih.gov/health/publications/pandas/index.shtml</link><title>PANDAS: Frequently Asked Questions about Pediatric Autoimmune Neuropsychiatric Disorders Associated with Streptococcal ....</title><description>... studies at the NIMH are restricted to children. My child has PANDAS. Should he have his tonsils removed? The NIH does not recommend tonsillectomies for children with PANDAS, as ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7406-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/...ttentiondeficithyperactivitydisorder.html</link><title>Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder</title><description>... still? Does your child act without thinking first? Does your child start but not finish things? If so, your child may have attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD). Nearly everyone shows some of these behaviors ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7406-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.healthychildren.org/...isruptive-Behavior-Disorders.aspx</link><title>Disruptive Behavior Disorders</title><description>... not typically involve this level of aggression.) A child with ADHD and CD does have a greater chance of experiencing learning disabilities such as reading disorders and verbal impairment. But what distinguishes children with ODD ... or anxiety disorder. A child with family members with ADHD/ODD or ADHD/ ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7406-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cdc.gov/ncbddd/adhd/treatment.html</link><title>My Child Has Been Diagnosed with ADHD \- Now What?</title><description>... Treatment for Preschoolers ADHD and School Related Pages My Child Has Been Diagnosed with ADHD \- Now What? It is understandable for parents to have concerns when their child is diagnosed with ADHD, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7406-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.tsalliance.org/documents/earlyyears web version.pdf</link><title>Early Years Guide of the Life Stages Program: A Resource Guide for Families of Infants and Young Children with Tuberous ...</title><description>... of a parent’s Social Security earnings record. How Does My Child Qualify? To qualify for disability benefits from the SSA, an individual must have a physical or mental condition that results in “ ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>