<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7439">make crown</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:24:16" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7439-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.simplestepsdental.com/.../t.31914/pr.3/c.307661.html</link><title>Crowns</title><description>... is made. Some dentists have a machine that makes a crown in one visit. With the traditional approach to ... is fed into the unit. Then a computer makes the crown from a block of porcelain. The dentist places ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7439-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.simplestepsdental.com/.../t.29584/pr.3/c.332780.html</link><title>Crown Lengthening</title><description>... the lengthened tooth. Then he or she will make the final crown. How It's Done Crown lengthening is done using ... only soft tissue is removed. The periodontist will make cuts ... dentist to place a crown or filling. However, in most cases, the periodontist ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7439-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.simplestepsdental.com/.../t.34982/pr.3/c.358870.html</link><title>Who Is an Implant Candidate?</title><description>... general dentist or prosthodontist. The restorative dentist will make the crowns, bridges or dentures that the implant or implants will support. Your first step is to make an appointment with one of these professionals for ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7439-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.simplestepsdental.com/.../t.34984/pr.3/c.358872.html</link><title>Placing Dental Implants</title><description>... your jawbone. A prosthodontist or general dentist will make your crowns, bridges or dentures, which will look like natural ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7439-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.simplestepsdental.com/.../t.35546/pr.3/c.367256.html</link><title>Single-Tooth Implants</title><description>... take two to three weeks, or less, to make a permanent crown. The crown can be created from a model ... can look at how the implant, abutment and crown fit together and make sure that there are no problems. Possible Complications ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7439-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.oif.org/site/PageServer?pagename=Dental</link><title>OI Issues: Dental Care for Persons with OI</title><description>... from the center of the root to help make the new crown of the tooth stronger. A bridge is at ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7439-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.simplestepsdental.com/.../t.31912/pr.3/c.307664.html</link><title>Bridges</title><description>... parts of the teeth will be removed to make space for the crowns. Traditional bridges are made either of porcelain fused ... prepares the teeth and covers them with temporary crowns. The dentist may also make impressions of the teeth. The bridge is placed ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7439-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.stutteringhelp.org</link><title>Stuttering Foundation of America</title><description>... fight for the championship, he was set to make another attempt for the world crown when he was erroneously arrested and wrongfully convicted ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7439-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.simplestepsdental.com/.../t.31883/pr.3/c.305984.html</link><title>Parts of Your Teeth and Gums</title><description>... more of your tooth roots. This also can make the tooth become loose and unstable. The anatomical crown also can get smaller as we age because ... Dentin — Dentin is the bone-like substance that makes up most of the ... just under the enamel in the crown and under the cementum in the root. Dentin ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7439-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/.../htm/index.htm</link><title>Temporomandibular Joint Disorders</title><description>... not been proven to be effective - and may make the problem worse - include orthodontics to change the bite; crown and bridge work to balance the bite; grinding ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>