<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7451">buy animal farm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:07:33" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7451-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cdc.gov/parasites/crypto/gen_info/prevent_ic.html</link><title>Cryptosporidium: Prevention - Immunocompromised Persons</title><description>... A, Salmonella , Shigella , and amebas. 3. Avoid touching farm animals. If you touch a farm animal, particularly a calf, lamb, or other young animal, or visit a farm where animals are raised, wash your hands well with soap ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7451-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.fsis.usda.gov/.../game-from-farm-to-table</link><title>Game from Farm to Table</title><description>... antelope, American elk, boar, pheasant, and other game animals are now farm raised in the United States. For an increasing ... game animals. What is game? Game are wild animals and birds. Farm-raised game are originally wild species of animals ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7451-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/womenshealth.gov/.../LifetimeGoodHealth-English.pdf</link><title>Lifetime of Good Health: Your Guide to Staying Healthy</title><description>... work Maid service, waiting tables, feeding or grooming farm animals, manually milking cows, picking fruits or vegetables, walking while carrying a mailbag Teaching an aerobic dance class, heavy farm work Call for free health publications: 800-994- ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7451-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.noisyplanet.nidcd.nih.gov/...KeepingItDownontheFarm.aspx</link><title>Noise: Keeping It Down on the Farm</title><description>... t always the case. Combines, tractors, and even farm animals can create a noisy environment that puts your hearing at risk. The following tips can help parents teach children who live or work on a farm how to prevent hearing loss from too much ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7451-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cdc.gov/ounceofprevention/docs/oop_brochure_eng.pdf</link><title>Ounce of Prevention Keeps the Germs Away: Seven Keys to a Safer Healthier Home</title><description>... soap and warm running water after contact with animals. • Be particularly careful when visiting farms, petting zoos, and fairs. This healthy message is ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7451-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.fda.gov/ForConsumers/ConsumerUpdates/ucm180996.htm</link><title>Cooperative Program Ensures Safe Shellfish</title><description>... Under state supervision, Chuck Steidle, owner of Coastal Farms Inc. in Southampton, N.Y., buys clams from marginally polluted waters and “transplants” them ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7451-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cdc.gov/foodsafety/facts.html</link><title>Questions and Answers about Foodborne Illness</title><description>... or limit contamination all the way from the farm to the table. A variety of good agricultural and manufacturing practices can reduce the spread of microbes among animals and prevent the contamination of foods. Careful review ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7451-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/teen/food_fitness/nutrition/organics.html</link><title>Organic and Other Environmentally Friendly Foods</title><description>... meat, poultry, eggs, and dairy foods — come from animals that are fed 100% ... certifier has inspected the farm where it was produced to ensure that the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7451-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.fda.gov/Food/ResourcesForYou/Consumers/ucm271595.htm</link><title>Questions and Answers: Apple Juice and Arsenic</title><description>... of apple juice concentrate. Even if a company buys concentrate from only one supplier in a country, such as Argentina, that supplier may be getting juice from a dozen or more different farms within Argentina. If you test enough juice from ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7451-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.fsis.usda.gov/.../shell-eggs-from-farm-to-table/ct_index</link><title>Shell Eggs from Farm to Table</title><description>... Service (FSIS), Agricultural Research Service (ARS), and the Animal and Plant Health Inspection ... USDA Agencies Agricultural Marketing Service (AMS) ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>