<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7453">pc 2 games reviews</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:22:02" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7453-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/ndep.nih.gov/publications/PublicationDetail.aspx?PubId=75</link><title>It's Not Too Late to Prevent Diabetes</title><description>... first step today To learn more, visit: Your GAME PLAN to Prevent type 2 Diabetes . Weight-control ... Plain Language Review Download Complete List of NDEP Publications Ver publicaciones ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7453-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.ndep.nih.gov/am-i-at-risk/family-history/index.aspx</link><title>Family Health History and Diabetes</title><description>... Family Helpful Resources Small Steps. Big Rewards. Your GAME PLAN to Prevent Type 2 Diabetes: Information for Patients Choose more Than 50 ... for more information: Small Steps. Big Rewards. Your GAME PLAN to Prevent Type 2 Diabetes (NDEP-60) This three-booklet package helps ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7453-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.ndep.nih.gov/.../PublicationDetail.aspx?PubId=154</link><title>Tips for Kids: How to Lower Your Risk for Type 2 Diabetes</title><description>... risk for diabetes. Small Steps. Big Rewards. Your GAME PLAN to Prevent Type 2 Diabetes: Information for Patients (NDEP-60) This three- ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7453-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/ndep.nih.gov/publications/PublicationDetail.aspx?Pubid=103</link><title>Tips for Teens: Lower Your Risk for Type 2 Diabetes</title><description>... they are overweight. Small Steps. Big Rewards. Your GAME PLAN to Prevent Type 2 Diabetes: Information for Patients (NDEP-60) This three- ... a program to lower risk factors for type 2 diabetes in middle school students. ^ ... Plain Language Review Download Complete List of NDEP Publications Ver publicaciones ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7453-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/ndep.nih.gov/publications/PublicationDetail.aspx?PubId=97</link><title>Helping the Student with Diabetes Succeed: A Guide for School Personnel</title><description>... they understand their respective roles in diabetes management. Review the Actions sheets with school personnel during Level 2 and Level 3 diabetes management training to ensure ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7453-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/orthoinfo.aaos.org/topic.cfm?topic=A00297</link><title>ACL Injury: Does It Require Surgery?</title><description>... Ligament Reconstruction. Am J Sports Med 2002;30(2):214-220. 62\. Starch DW, Alexander JW, Noble PC, et al. Multistranded Hamstring Tendon Graft Fixation with ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>