<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7477">china bird flu</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:47:24" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7477-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/news/fullstory_144433.html</link><title>China's New Bird Flu Might Put People At Risk, Report Says</title><description>... sharing features on this page, please enable JavaScript. China's New Bird Flu Might Put People at Risk, Report Says Genetic ... people. An elderly woman living in Nanchang City, China, recently died from ... of H10N8 bird flu virus. Testing revealed the virus contained genes from ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7477-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/birdflu.html</link><title>Bird Flu</title><description>Birds, just like people, get the flu. Bird flu viruses infect birds, including chickens, other poultry, and wild birds such as ducks. Most bird flu viruses ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7477-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/internationalhealth.html</link><title>International Health</title><description>The spread of a disease doesn't stop at a country's borders. With more people traveling to other countries and living in crowded cities, it's easier for ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7477-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cdc.gov/flu/avianflu/h7n9-faq.htm</link><title>H7N9: Frequently Asked Questions</title><description>A new strain of H7N9 bird flu has been found in birds and people in China. No ongoing person-to-person spread of this virus has been found at this time. Here are some common questions and answers ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7477-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cdc.gov/flu/avianflu/h7n9-virus.htm</link><title>Avian Influenza A (H7N9) Virus</title><description>... take some common sense precautions, like not touching birds or other animals and washing hands often. Poultry and poultry products should be fully cooked. CDC will ... Influenza (Flu) 2013-2014 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7477-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.cdc.gov/flu/pdf/avianflu/h7n9-reassortment-diagram.pdf</link><title>Genetic Evolution of H7N9 Virus in China, 2013</title><description>The eight genes of the H7N9 virus are closely related to avian influenza viruses found in domestic ducks, wild birds and domestic poultry in Asia. The virus ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7477-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.flu.gov/about_the_flu/h5n1/index.html</link><title>H5N1 Avian Flu (H5N1 Bird Flu)</title><description>... H5N1 (Avian/Bird Flu) H5N1 Avian Flu (H5N1 Bird Flu) H5N1 is a highly pathogenic avian (bird) flu ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7477-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/.../fall06/articles/fall06pg18-21.html</link><title>Understanding Flu</title><description>... Bonny McClain Whether the topic is seasonal influenza, bird flu or something called a pandemic, everyone seems to ... development of new strains of flu, including avian (bird) flu. Photo courtesy of St. Judes Children's Research Hospital ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7477-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.who.int/.../factsheets/avian_influenza/en/index.html</link><title>Avian Influenza</title><description>... 2014 Key facts Avian influenza (AI), commonly called bird flu, is an infectious viral disease of birds. Most avian influenza viruses do not infect humans; ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7477-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/.../spring08/articles/spring08pg10-11.html</link><title>Good Health Is a Global Issue</title><description>... The recent outbreak of SARS and the ongoing bird flu epidemic in Asian poultry both show that diseases ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>