<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7489">make skull mask</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:58:33" name="MedlinePlus" id="FW14-e072"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e072-7489-01"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.orlive.com/...rapy-for-brain-tumors1?view=displayPageNLM</link><title>Stereotactic Radiation Therapy for Brain Tumors</title><description>... roll the tape. It shows you how we make the reproducible, non-invasive fixation mask. And here you see aquaplast material, which is ... MD: This is the top portion of the mask system, and it is quite snug. We want to make sure the patient's in the same position every ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7489-02"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/kidshealth.org/teen/your_body/skin_stuff/safe_tattooing.html</link><title>Tattoos</title><description>... Back Continue Avoiding Infection It's very important to make sure the tattoo studio is clean and safe, and that all equipment used is disposable (in the case of needles, gloves, masks, etc.) and sterilized (everything else). Some states, cities, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7489-03"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/ency/article/000302.htm</link><title>Hepatic encephalopathy</title><description>... or benzodiazepine tranquilizers) Disorders that can mimic or mask ... Wernicke-Korsakoff syndrome Hepatic encephalopathy may occur as ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7489-04"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nidcd.nih.gov/health/hearing/Pages/tinnitus.aspx</link><title>Tinnitus</title><description>... some things to do on your own to make the noise less noticeable, to help you relax during the day, or to fall asleep at night. Wearable sound generators are small electronic devices that fit in the ear and use a soft, pleasant sound to help mask the tinnitus. Some people want the masking sound ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7489-05"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.healthychildren.org/.../Pages/Sleep-Apnea-Detection.aspx</link><title>Sleep Apnea Detection</title><description>... to wear a mask while he sleeps. The mask delivers steady air pressure through ... or craniofacial (skull and face) abnormalities , are at higher risk for ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7489-06"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.uptodate.com/...a-in-adults-beyond-the-basics?view=print</link><title>Sleep Apnea in Adults (Beyond the Basics)</title><description>... air-tight attachment to the nose, typically a mask, connected to a tube and a blower which ... treatment after experiencing better sleep. However, difficulty with mask comfort and nasal congestion prevent up to 50 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7489-07"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.radiologyinfo.org/en/info.cfm?pg=IntracranialVasc</link><title>Intracranial Vascular Treatments</title><description>... shaped head frame will be attached to your skull using specially designed pins to keep your head from moving until the treatment session is finished. This lightweight aluminum head frame is also a guiding device that makes sure the Gamma Knife beams are focused exactly ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7489-08"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.radiologyinfo.org/en/info.cfm?PG=stereotactic</link><title>Stereotactic Radiosurgery and Stereotactic Body Radiotherapy (SBRT)</title><description>... shaped head frame will be attached to your skull using specially designed pins to keep your head from moving within the frame until the treatment session is finished. This lightweight aluminum head frame is also a guiding device that makes sure the Gamma Knife beams are focused exactly ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7489-09"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.radiologyinfo.org/en/info.cfm?PG=protonthera</link><title>Proton Therapy</title><description>... tumor. For treatments above the neck, a custom mask can be placed around the face, or custom ... room to assist the patient in removing the mask or immobilization device. top of page • What you' ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e072-7489-10"><link>http://vsearch.nlm.nih.gov/vivisimo/cgi-bin/www.nidcr.nih.gov/.../PressStatements/ChronicTMJD.htm</link><title>Study Evaluates Risk Factors for Chronic Temporomandibular Joint and Muscle Disorders</title><description>... conditions, such as fibromyalgia and chronic fatigue, which mask or modify the symptoms of the TMJD. With ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>