<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7125">psychological effects of obesity in children</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:55:40" name="U. Twente" id="FW14-e014"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e014-7125-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7125_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:55:41">http://doc.utwente.nl/89164/</link><title>A serious exergame for patients suffering from chronic musculoskeletal back and neck pain: a pilot study.</title><description>1.

Kosterink, Stephanie M. and Huis in 't Veld, Rianne M.H.A. and Schönauer, Christian and Kaufmann, Hannes and Hermens, Hermie J. and Vollenbroek-Hutten, Miriam M.R. (2013) A serious exergame for patients suffering from chronic musculoskeletal back and neck pain: a pilot study. Games for health journal, 2 (5). pp. 299-307. ISSN 2161-783X Item availability restricted.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7125_01_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/style/images/fileicons/application_pdf.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7125-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7125_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:57:28">http://doc.utwente.nl/86736/</link><title>Service tailoring: a method and tool for user-centric creation of integrated IT-based homecare services to support independent living of elderly.</title><description>2.

Zarifi Eslami, Mohammad (2013) Service tailoring: a method and tool for user-centric creation of integrated IT-based homecare services to support independent living of elderly. thesis.

Preview</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7125_02_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/style/images/fileicons/application_pdf.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7125-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7125_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:59:09">http://doc.utwente.nl/87372/</link><title>Feedback presentation for mobile personalised digital physical activity coaching platforms.</title><description>3.

Klaassen, Randy and Akker, Rieks op den and Akker, Harm op den (2013) Feedback presentation for mobile personalised digital physical activity coaching platforms. In: 6th International Conference on PErvasive Technologies Related to Assistive Environments, PETRA 2013, 29-31 May 2013, Island of Rhodes, Greece. Item availability restricted.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7125_03_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/style/images/fileicons/application_pdf.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7125-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7125_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:01:47">http://doc.utwente.nl/85411/</link><title>Ambulatory feedback at daily physical activity patterns: a treatment for the chronic fatigue syndrome in the home environment?</title><description>4.

Evering, Richard Maria Hermanus (2013) Ambulatory feedback at daily physical activity patterns: a treatment for the chronic fatigue syndrome in the home environment? thesis.

Preview</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7125_04_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/style/images/fileicons/application_pdf.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7125-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7125_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:04:02">http://doc.utwente.nl/87796/</link><title>Effects of nutrition label format and product assortment on the healthfulness of food choice.</title><description>5.

Aschemann-Witzel, Jessica and Grunert, Klaus G. and Trijp, Hans C.M. van and Bialkova, Svetlana and Raats, Monique M. and Hodgkins, Charo and Wasowicz-Kirylo, Grazyna and Koenigstorfer, Joerg (2013) Effects of nutrition label format and product assortment on the healthfulness of food choice. Appetite, 71 . 63 - 74. ISSN 0195-6663 Item availability restricted.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7125_05_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/style/images/fileicons/application_pdf.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7125-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7125_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:05:14">http://doc.utwente.nl/88641/</link><title>Weighing information from item data in GWAS meta-analyses.</title><description>6.

Berg, Stephanie van den and Moor, Marleen de and Schwabe, Inga (2013) Weighing information from item data in GWAS meta-analyses. Behavior genetics, 43 (6). 545 -. ISSN 0001-8244

Preview</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7125_06_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/88641/1.hassmallThumbnailVersion/art%253A10.1007%252Fs10519-013-9623-9.pdf</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7125-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7125_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:05:59">http://doc.utwente.nl/86037/</link><title>Spaces of genomics : exploring the innovation journey of genomics in research on common disease.</title><description>7.

Bitsch, L. (2013) Spaces of genomics : exploring the innovation journey of genomics in research on common disease. thesis.

Preview</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7125_07_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/style/images/fileicons/application_pdf.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7125-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7125_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:09:00">http://doc.utwente.nl/88748/</link><title>Design of the SHAPE-2 study: the effect of physical activity, in addition to weight loss, on biomarkers of postmenopausal breast cancer risk.</title><description>8.

Gemert, Willemijn A.M. van and Iestra, Jolein I. and Schuit, Albertine J. and May, Anne M. and Takken, Tim and Veldhuis, Wouter B. and Palen, Job van der and Wittink, Harriet and Peeters, Petra H.M. and Monninkhof, Evelyn M. (2013) Design of the SHAPE-2 study: the effect of physical activity, in addition to weight loss, on biomarkers of postmenopausal breast cancer risk. BMC Cancer, 13 (395). ISSN 1471-2407

Preview</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7125_08_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/88748/1.hassmallThumbnailVersion/1471-2407-13-395.pdf</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7125-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7125_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:09:31">http://doc.utwente.nl/82515/</link><title>Smoking and medication during pregnancy predict repeated unintentional injuries in early childhood but not single unintentional injuries.</title><description>9.

Junger, M. and Japel, C. and Cote, S. and Xu, Q. and Boivin, M. and Tremblay, R.E. (2013) Smoking and medication during pregnancy predict repeated unintentional injuries in early childhood but not single unintentional injuries. Prevention Science, 14 (1). 13 - 24. ISSN 1389-4986

Preview</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7125_09_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/style/images/fileicons/application_pdf.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7125-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7125_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:13:10">http://doc.utwente.nl/85146/</link><title>The role of genes in talking about overweight: an analysis of discourse on genetics, overweight and health risks in relation to nutrigenomics.</title><description>10.

Komduur, R. and Molder, H.F.M. te (2013) The role of genes in talking about overweight: an analysis of discourse on genetics, overweight and health risks in relation to nutrigenomics. Public understanding of science . ISSN 0963-6625 Item availability restricted.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7125_10_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/style/images/fileicons/application_pdf.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>