<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7242">hague convention</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:40:22" name="U. Twente" id="FW14-e014"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e014-7242-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7242_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:40:24">http://doc.utwente.nl/90271/</link><title>Anomaly detection in SCADA systems: a network based approach.</title><description>1.

Barbosa, Rafael Ramos Regis (2014) Anomaly detection in SCADA systems: a network based approach. thesis.

Preview</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7242_01_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/90271/1.hassmallThumbnailVersion/thesis_R_Barbosa.pdf</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7242-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7242_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:40:58">http://doc.utwente.nl/88365/</link><title>Experiences with formal engineering: model-based specification, implementation and testing of a software bus at Neopost.</title><description>2.

Sijtema, M. and Belinfante, A. and Stoelinga, M.I.A. and Marinelli, L. (2014) Experiences with formal engineering: model-based specification, implementation and testing of a software bus at Neopost. Science of computer programming, 80 (Part A). pp. 188-209. ISSN 0167-6423 Item availability restricted.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7242_02_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/style/images/fileicons/application_pdf.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7242-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7242_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:43:49">http://doc.utwente.nl/88732/</link><title>Websites for childen: search strategies and interface design. Three studies on children's search performance and evaluation.</title><description>3.

Jochmann-Mannak, Hanna Ewoudia (2014) Websites for childen: search strategies and interface design. Three studies on children's search performance and evaluation. thesis.

Preview</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7242_03_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/88732/1.hassmallThumbnailVersion/thesis_H_Jochmann-Mannak.pdf</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7242-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7242_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:45:04">http://doc.utwente.nl/89258/</link><title>Sustainable, efficient, and equitable water use: the three pillars under wise freshwater allocation.</title><description>4.

Hoekstra, Arjen Y. (2014) Sustainable, efficient, and equitable water use: the three pillars under wise freshwater allocation. Wiley interdisciplinary reviews. Water, 1 (1). 31 - 40. ISSN 2049-1948 Item availability restricted.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7242_04_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/style/images/fileicons/application_pdf.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7242-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7242_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:47:02">http://doc.utwente.nl/90239/</link><title>Designing the biomethane supply chain through automated synthesis.</title><description>5.

Weidenaar, Taede Durk (2014) Designing the biomethane supply chain through automated synthesis. thesis.

Preview</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7242_05_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/90239/1.hassmallThumbnailVersion/thesis_T_Weidenaar.pdf</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7242-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7242_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:47:48">http://doc.utwente.nl/88253/</link><title>Distributed deep web search.</title><description>6.

Tjin-Kam-Jet, Kien-Tsoi Theodorus Egbert (2013) Distributed deep web search. thesis.

Preview</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7242_06_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/88253/1.hassmallThumbnailVersion/thesis_K_Tjin-Kam-Jet.pdf</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7242-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7242_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:48:53">http://doc.utwente.nl/88378/</link><title>Electromagnetic interference of equipment in power supply networks.</title><description>7.

Timens, Roelof Bernardus (2013) Electromagnetic interference of equipment in power supply networks. thesis.

Preview</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7242_07_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/88378/1.hassmallThumbnailVersion/thesis_R_Timens.pdf</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7242-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7242_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:51:43">http://doc.utwente.nl/89520/</link><title>LOFAR: the low-frequency array.</title><description>8.

Haarlem, M.P. van and Wise, M.W. and Gunst, A.W. and Heald, G. and McKean, J.P. and Hessels, J.W.T. and Bruyn, A.G. de and Nijboer, R. and Swinbank, J. and Fallows, R. and Brentjens, M. and Nelles, A. and Beck, R. and Falcke, H. and Fender, R. and Hörandel, J. and Koopmans, L.V.E. and Mann, G. and Miley, G. and Röttgering, H. and Stappers, B.W. and Wijers, R.A.M.J. and Zaroubi, S. and Akker, M. van den and Alexov, A. and Anderson, J. and Anderson, K. and Ardenne, A. van and Arts, M. and Asgekar, A. and Avruch, I.M. and Batejat, F. and Bähren, L. and Bell, M.E. and Bell, M.R. and Bemmel, I. van and Bennema, P. and Bentum, M.J. and Bernardi, G. and Best, P. and Birzan, L. and Bonafede, A. and Boonstra, A.J. and Braun, R. and Bregman, J. and Breitling, F. and Brink, R.H. van de and Broderick, J. and Broekema, P.C. and Brouw, W.N. and Brüggen, M. and Butcher, H.R. and Capellen, W. van and Ciardi, B. and Coenen, T. and Conway, J. and Coolen, A. and Corstanje, A. and Damstra, S. and Davies, O. and Deller, A.T. and Dettmar, R.-J. and Diepen, G. van and Dijkstra, K. and Donker, P. and Doorduin, A. and Dromer, J. and Drost, M. and Duin, A. van and Eislöffel, J. and Enst, J. van and Ferrari, C. and Frieswijk, W. and Gankema, H. and Garrett, M.A. and Gasperin, F. de and Gerbers, M. and Geus, E. de and Griessmeier, J.M. and Grit, T. and Gruppen, P. and Hamaker, J.P. and Hassall, T. and Hoeft, M. and Holties, H. and Horneffer, A. and Horst, A. van der and Houwelingen, A. van and Huijgen, G. and Iacobelli, M. and Intema, H. and Jackson, N. and Jelic, V. and Jong, A. de and Juette, E. and Kant, D. and Karastergiou, A. and Koers, A. and Kollen, H. and Kooistra, E. and Koopman, Y. and Koster, A. and Kuniyoshi, M. and Kramer, M. and Kuper, G. and Lambropoulos, P. and Law, C. and Leeuwen, J. van and Lemaitre, J. and Loose, M. and Maat, P. and Macario, G. and Markoff, S. and Masters, J. and McKay-Bukowski, D. and Meijering, H. and Meulman, H. and Mevius, M. and Middelberg, E. and Millenaar, R. and Miller-Jones, J.C.A. and Mohan, R.N. and Mol, J.D. and Morawietz, J. and Morganti, R. and Mulcahy, D.D. and Mulder, E. and Munk, H. and Nieuwenhuis, L. and Nieuwpoort, R. van and Noordam, J.E. and Norden, M. and Noutsos, A. and Offringa, A.R. and Olofsson, T. and Omar, A. and Orrú, E. and Overeem, R. and Paas, H. and Pandey-Pommier, M. and Pandey, V.N. and Pizzo, R. and Polatidis, A. and Rafferty, D. and Rawlings, S. and Reich, W. and Reijer, J.-P. de and Reitsma, J. and Renting, A. and Riemers, P. and Rol, E. and Romein, J.W. and Roosjen, J. and Ruiter, M. and Scaife, A. and Schaaf, K. van der and Scheers, B. and Schellart, P. and Schoenmakers, A. and Schoonderbeek, G. and Serylak, M. and Shulevski, A. and Sluman, J. and Smirnov, O. and Sobey, C. and Spreeuw, H. and Steinmetz, M. and Sterks, C.G.M. and Stiepel, H.-J. and Stuurwold, K. and Veelen, M. van and Veen, A.-J. van der and Veen, S. ter and Verbiest, J.P.W. and Vermeulen, R. and Vermaas, N. and Vocks, C. and Vogt, C. and Vos, M. de and Wal, E. van der and Weeren, R. van and Weggemans, W. and Weltevrede, P. and White, S. and Wijnholds, S.J. and Wilhelmsson, T. and Wucknitz, O. and Yatawatta, S. and Zarka, P. and Zensus, A. and Zwieten, J. van (2013) LOFAR: the low-frequency array. Astronomy &amp; astrophysics, 556 (A2). pp. 1-53. ISSN 0004-6361 Item availability restricted.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7242_08_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/style/images/fileicons/application_pdf.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7242-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7242_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:54:37">http://doc.utwente.nl/86252/</link><title>How 'digital' is traditional crime?</title><description>9.

Montoya, Lorena and Junger, Marianne and Hartel, Pieter (2013) How 'digital' is traditional crime? In: European Intelligence and Security Informatics Conference, EISIC 2013, 12-14 August 2013, Uppsala, Sweden. Item availability restricted.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7242_09_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/style/images/fileicons/application_pdf.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7242-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7242_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:57:46">http://doc.utwente.nl/85494/</link><title>Study and development of an in situ acoustic absorption measurement method.</title><description>10.

Tijs, E. (2013) Study and development of an in situ acoustic absorption measurement method. thesis.

Preview</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7242_10_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/style/images/fileicons/application_pdf.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>