<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7477">china bird flu</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:17:20" name="U. Twente" id="FW14-e014"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e014-7477-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7477_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:17:23">http://doc.utwente.nl/80827/</link><title>Tuning in to the right wavelength: The importance of culture for effective crisis negotiation.</title><description>1.

Giebels, E. and Taylor, P (2012) Tuning in to the right wavelength: The importance of culture for effective crisis negotiation. In: The psychology of crisis intervention. Editions Yvon Blais, Montreal, Canada, 277 - 298. Item availability restricted.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7477_01_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/style/images/fileicons/application_pdf.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7477-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7477_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:18:12">http://doc.utwente.nl/84232/</link><title>Elements at Risk.</title><description>2.

van Westen, C. and Kingma, N. and McCall, M. and Montoya Morales, A.L. (2011) Elements at Risk. In: Multi-hazard Risk Assessment. Distance Education Course Guide Book . UNU - ITC DGIM, Enschede, pp. 401-443. Item availability restricted.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7477_02_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/style/images/fileicons/application_pdf.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7477-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7477_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:19:12">http://doc.utwente.nl/90397/</link><title>Endogenous vs. exogenous models for innovation policy in late industrialising countries.</title><description>3.

Rennkamp, Britta and Kuhlmann, Stefan (2010) Endogenous vs. exogenous models for innovation policy in late industrialising countries. In: World Conclave of Scientists on Regional Cooperation in Science and Technology: Opportunities and Challenges in the Context of Globalisation, New Delhi, November 26-29, 2010, 26-29 November 2010, New Delhi (pp. pp. 419-446).

Preview</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7477_03_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/90397/1.hassmallThumbnailVersion/Proceedings.pdf</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7477-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7477_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:20:53">http://doc.utwente.nl/58713/</link><title>Biomass char as an in-situ catalyst for tar removal in gasification systems.</title><description>4.

Abu El-Rub, Ziad Yousef Kamel (2008) Biomass char as an in-situ catalyst for tar removal in gasification systems. thesis.

Preview</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7477_04_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/style/images/fileicons/application_pdf.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7477-05"><link>http://doc.utwente.nl/89104/</link><title>Reliability analysis of flood defence structures and systems in Europe.</title><description>5.

Gelder, Pieter van and Buijs, Foekje and Horst, Wouter ter and Kanning, Wim and Van, Cong Mai and Rajabalinejad, Mohammad and Boer, Elisabet de and Gupta, Sayan and Shams, Reza and Erp, Noel van and Gouldby, Ben and Kingston, Greer and Sayers, Paul and Wills, Martin and Kortenhaus, Andreas and Lambrecht, Hans-Jorg (2008) Reliability analysis of flood defence structures and systems in Europe. In: Flood Risk Management: Research and Practice: proceedings of the European conference on flood risk management research into practice (Floodrisk 2008), Oxford, 30 September-2 October 2008: extended abstracts. CRC Press, pp. 109-110. ISBN 9780415485074

Preview</description><thumb>http://doc.utwente.nl/89104/1.hassmallThumbnailVersion/Flood%20Risk%20Management-%20Research%20and%20Practice-%20Extended%20Abstracts%20Volume.pdf</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7477-06"><link>http://doc.utwente.nl/76401/</link><title>Hybrid photoacoustic - ultrasound transmission parameter imaging in a miniature photoacoustic imager (A).</title><description>6.

Manohar, Srirang and Willemink, Rene G. (2008) Hybrid photoacoustic - ultrasound transmission parameter imaging in a miniature photoacoustic imager (A). Journal of the Acoustical Society of America, 123 (5). p. 3371. ISSN 0001-4966 Item availability restricted.</description><thumb>http://doc.utwente.nl/style/images/fileicons/application_pdf.png</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e014-7477-07"><link>http://doc.utwente.nl/38707/</link><title>The endurance of Mexican amate paper: exploring additional dimen sustainable development concept.</title><description>7.

López Binnqüist, Rosaura Citlalli (2003) The endurance of Mexican amate paper: exploring additional dimen sustainable development concept. thesis.</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e014/7477_07_thumb.png">http://doc.utwente.nl/style/images/fileicons/application_pdf.png</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>