<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7002">exhaled NO IBS papers</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:15:32" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7002-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7002_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:15:33">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/02/consumers-for-paper-options-wants-the-government-to-push-more-paper/</link><title>“Consumers for Paper Options” wants the government to push more paper</title><description>... Consumers for Paper Options turns out to be an astroturfing group funded by the Envelope Manufacturers Association (EMA) and the paper industrys largest trade group, several of North Americas biggest paper manufacturers.What do these paper-pushing people want? More paper delivery of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7002-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7002_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:17:49">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/08/papers-please-review-paper-trail-of-tears/</link><title>Papers, Please Review: Paper trail of tears</title><description>... papers and confirming or denying someone's entry into Arstotzkan. Often, that means finding fake... tourist publicity. Papers, Please looks intentionally unrefined, using pixelated designs, sullen..., or delivering bombs.Yet the most terrifying part about Papers, Please is the sheer satisfaction...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7002-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7002_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:19:28">http://arstechnica.com/business/2014/01/facebooks-paper-is-facebook-without-the-facebook/</link><title>Facebook’s Paper is Facebook without the Facebook</title><description>... into a more streamlined format. The app, called Paper, presents content from both users and brands in a new interface and organizes it into sections for browsing.The announcement of Paper has been rumored... Businessweek).Paper presents user updates as stories: captions overlaid on large-format photos, auto...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7002-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7002_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:21:01">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/02/ars-exclusive-review-papers-for-iphone/</link><title>Ars exclusive: Review of Papers for iPhone</title><description>... about it at the time, and continue to do so just about every chance I get. That app was Papers, which has done for scientific literature what iTunes did for music files. Now, the company behind Papers, Mekentosj...-looking interface from which to read papers, search for new ones, and even export them to bibliographic...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7002-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7002_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:23:03">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/08/university-of-california-to-allow-open-access-to-new-academic-papers/</link><title>University of California to allow open access to new academic papers</title><description>...-reviewed papers on the paper's publication date. The UC then posts the paper online to eScholarship, its open access publishing site, where the paper will be available to anyone, free... publishes over 40,000 scholarly papers a yearagainst the power of publishers who would otherwise lock...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7002-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7002_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:24:14">http://arstechnica.com/security/2009/03/forget-the-watermarks-secure-the-paper/</link><title>Forget watermarks; new technique "fingerprints" paper</title><description>... on the print medium itself. Is it possible to fingerprint a single sheet of paper?According to the study's abstract, the answer is yesand it can be done with commodity hardware. "This paper... imperfections in paper texture," says the document. "We introduce a new method for measuring...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7002-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7002_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:24:53">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/06/evolving-bacteria-through-a-game-of-rock-paper-scissors/</link><title>Evolving bacteria through a game of rock-paper-scissors</title><description>..."Imagine a nontransitive community in which, for convenience, we call the players Rock, Paper, and Scissors." It's a rather unusual line to find in a scientific paper, but the study it comes from is part of a special edition of PNAS on the evolution of social behavior. And rock-paper...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7002-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7002_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:28:18">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2011/05/papers-2-your-new-best-os-x-research-management-app/</link><title>Papers 2: your new best OS X research management app?</title><description>...In 2007, a talented pair of scientist-programmers called Mekentosj released Papers, a Mac OS X app... of Papers with an iPad is pretty good when it comes to catching up on your reading. Still, that was then and this is now, as they say, and a new and rebuilt Papers 2 is here to take over your research...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7002-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7002_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:33:14">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/03/review-paper-pilot-for-iphone-brings-office-flying-fun-1/</link><title>Review: Paper Pilot for iPhone brings office flying fun</title><description>...If flying a paper airplane to catch floating paperclips sounds like an appealing way to waste some time, then Paper Pilot for the iPhone is the game for you. In this first-person flier, you maneuver... your car into a nearby light post. Paper Pilot lets you control your speed as well as your angles...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7002-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7002_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:34:13">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/06/wwdc10-papers-will-stay-on-the-mac-as-long-as-scientists-do/</link><title>Papers will stay on the Mac as long as scientists do</title><description>... X software this week. The winner of our Best Mac OS X App for Education category was Papers by Mekentosj, and we sat down with (most of) the Papers team for a quick chat about their future on the Mac and where the mobile space is going.For those who aren't familiar with it, Papers is largely...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>