<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7007">Allen Ginsberg Howl review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:54:16" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7007-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7007_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:54:17">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/07/wolves-howls-have-distinct-identities-voice-recognition-study-shows/</link><title>Wolves’ howls have distinct identities, voice recognition study shows</title><description>...The ominous howl of the wolf has long been a source of fear and fascination for mankind. But new.... By recording and analyzing wolf howls, scientists have discovered a new way of identifying individual... that can tell which wolf is howling with 100% accuracy. Previously, pitch was used to tell wolves apart...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7007-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7007_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:55:49">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/lily-allens-new-single-success-partially-due-to-web-game/</link><title>Lily Allen's new single: success partially due to web game</title><description>...Lily Allen is one of those musicians who understands that the Internet is a powerful tool when it comes to attracting attention. After all, MySpace proved to be one of major factors behind... single, "The Fear."The game, Escape the Fear, is a fun platformer that involves a Lily Allen...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7007-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7007_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:58:45">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/12/paul-allens-patent-infringement-lawsuit-dismissed/</link><title>Paul Allen's patent infringement lawsuit dismissed</title><description>...Microsoft cofounder Paul Allen has hit a snag in his massive patent infringement suit against Apple, Google, Netflix, Facebook, YouTube, and numerous others. US District Judge Marsha Pechman dismissed the lawsuit on Friday, according to court documents, saying that Allen's company failed...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7007-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7007_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:02:03">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/12/microsoft-cofounder-paul-allen-tries-again-with-patent-megasuit/</link><title>Microsoft cofounder Paul Allen tries again with patent megasuit</title><description>...Microsoft co-founder Paul Allen has renewed his patent fight with a large contingent of the tech industry this week. Per a federal judge's orders, Allen's Interval Licensing LLC filed... were originally awarded to Interval Research, a tech RD firm founded by Allen and former Xerox executive...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7007-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7007_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:03:16">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/01/judge-cant-order-yelp-user-to-edit-negative-review/</link><title>Judge can't order Yelp user to edit negative review</title><description>... womans negative online review of a local contractor. The defendants attorneys say that the case marks... of the review in question.The reason I got involved is that a preliminary injunction was issued here, Paul Allen Levy, a well-known free speech lawyer with Public Citizen, told Ars. Levy is representing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7007-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7007_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:05:20">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/07/probes-confirm-earth-acts-like-a-giant-particle-accelerator/</link><title>Probes confirm Earth acts like a giant particle accelerator</title><description>... actually discovered something new: the Van Allen belts. These areas of high-energy particles are held... and equipment that orbit within them.Initially, the Van Allen belts were thought to be largely static... zone.The debate was left unsolved until NASA put the Van Allen Probes into space. These satellites...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7007-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7007_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:07:25">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/08/us-govt-snowden-also-took-secret-docs-while-working-at-dell-in-april-2012/</link><title>US gov’t: Snowden also took secret docs while working at Dell in April 2012</title><description>... documents during his time at Booz Allen Hamilton in 2013; he also grabbed some while working for Dell... the secret British spy agency.After leaving Dell in early 2013, Snowden began working for Booz Allen Hamilton as a systems administrator. Recently, Booz Allen announced that it had fired around 90...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7007-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7007_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:11:06">http://arstechnica.com/staff/2010/12/year-in-review-2010s-most-popular-stories/</link><title>Year in review: 2010's most popular stories</title><description>...These are the most popularby pageviewsstories that ran on Ars Technica during 2010. We've split them into two categories: multipage features and reports. Without further ado:Multipage features10. Tentacular, tentacular!: Beware, mortals: Cthulhu has returned, and he's armed with bacon and an unhealthy obsession with geek brains. Battle your way through our first-ever interactive adventu...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7007-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7007_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:11:44">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/05/review-datura-forces-you-to-figure-it-out-for-yourself/</link><title>Review: Datura forces you to figure it out for yourself</title><description>... a Move controller to a homemade clip on the side of a Sony Personal 3D Viewer.For this review, I...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7007-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7007_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:12:29">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/05/why-were-not-review-brink-and-why-you-shouldnt-buy-it-yet/</link><title>Why we're not reviewing Brink , and why you shouldn't buy it (yet)</title><description>... arrived too late for us to play it for any significant amount of time, the state of the review code... remains that the game reviewers have been playing for the past week will not be the same game you play... be offline when the game launched. I made a joke about it being awkward for reviewers to ask...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>