<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7008">jesse van ruller solo transcriptions</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:13:48" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7008-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7008_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:13:50">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/08/guitar-hero-van-halen-underage-bassists-solos-as-songs/</link><title>Guitar Hero: Van Halen: underage bassists, solos as songs</title><description>..., and one would assume that Van Halen is one of them. For a band that's known for guitar work and has any number of famous riffs and solos under its belt, you'd think it would be easy to create a game that focuses only on Van Halen songs. Unfortunately, the trailer does a great job of pointing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7008-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7008_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:17:09">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/12/guitar-hero-van-halen-is-a-big-lump-of-coal-in-my-stocking/</link><title>Guitar Hero: Van Halen a big lump of coal in our stockings</title><description>... itself is odd. Van Halen songs and solos only make up about half of the track list. The rest...Guitar Hero: Van Halen was rumored long before the game became fact, and the promise of the title... for a past Guitar Herotitle. Title Guitar Hero: Van Halen Developer Neversoft Publisher Activision...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7008-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7008_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:18:36">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/08/surprise-van-halen-free-and-early-with-guitar-hero-5/</link><title>Surprise! Van Halen free, and early, with Guitar Hero 5</title><description>... marked copy, and you can send away for a free copy of Guitar Hero: Van Halen. Even weirder, you get... to Guitar Hero 5, and if you're a Van Halen fan, you get to enjoy the game before everyone... songs to play. You mail in for your free copy of Van Halen, and wait up to six weeks for delivery. Still...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7008-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7008_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:20:09">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/05/codel-buffer-management-could-solve-the-internets-bufferbloat-jams/</link><title>CoDel buffer management could solve the Internet’s bufferbloat jams</title><description>... together. Having packets stuck in buffers unnecessarily means communication slows down. Van Jacobson... spots, mobile device access networks. Van has seen data on the latter that convinces him that what...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7008-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7008_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:22:36">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/11/e-coli-adapts-to-minimal-media-by-deleting-parts-of-its-rna-polymerase/</link><title>E. coli adapts to starvation by deleting parts of an essential gene</title><description>... transcription at a subset of genes, including ribosomal RNA genes, which are essential for making... the transcriptional network in these bacteria that has been so illustrative in defining universal methods of transcriptional regulation. PNAS, 2010. DOI: 10.1073/pnas.0911253107 (About DOIs)....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7008-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7008_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:23:31">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/07/probes-confirm-earth-acts-like-a-giant-particle-accelerator/</link><title>Probes confirm Earth acts like a giant particle accelerator</title><description>... actually discovered something new: the Van Allen belts. These areas of high-energy particles are held... and equipment that orbit within them.Initially, the Van Allen belts were thought to be largely static... zone.The debate was left unsolved until NASA put the Van Allen Probes into space. These satellites...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7008-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7008_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:26:54">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/01/no-more-dutch-sandwich-the-netherlands-reviews-its-role-in-tax-evasion/</link><title>No more “Dutch Sandwich”? The Netherlands reviews its role in tax avoidance</title><description>... should not be a tax haven, Ed Groot told Bloombergs correspondent, Jesse Drucker...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7008-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7008_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:29:47">http://arstechnica.com/business/2014/01/sayit-is-the-civic-software-for-publishing-smart-transcripts/</link><title>SayIt is the civic software for publishing “smart” transcripts</title><description>... a piece of civic software called SayIt, which publishes transcripts of speeches in a way... that can keep track of what politicians and other powerful people say. Transcripts can be stripped out of PDFsa... directly to any part of the transcripts. SayIt can be used as a hosted service or it can be built...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7008-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7008_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:30:27">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/03/source-activision-to-debut-van-halen-band-hero-in-2009/</link><title>Source: Activision to debut Van Halen, Band Hero in 2009</title><description>..., it could be as many as seven, thanks to unknowns like Guitar Hero: Van Halen and Band Hero. "Eurogamer has been told by a source close to the publisher that Hard Rock Van Halen (August), Guitar... Guitar Hero game every year since 2005. The rumored Van Halen version and Band Hero versions...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7008-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7008_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:33:06">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2010/09/premier-chat-006-transcript-kyle-wiens-of-ifixit/</link><title>Premier Chat 006 Transcript: Kyle Wiens of iFixit</title><description>...Ars hosted iFixit founder Kyle Wiens for one of our subscriber chats this week. We normally make the transcripts available only to subscribers, but Kyle had some interesting insights that we wanted to share with all of our readers.If you want access to future subscriber chats...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>