<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7009">linkedin engineering</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:34:45" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7009-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7009_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:34:46">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/10/a-behind-the-scenes-look-at-linkedins-mobile-engineering/</link><title>A behind-the-scenes look at LinkedIn’s mobile engineering</title><description>...LinkedIn is the career-oriented social network that prides itself on professional excellence... only seven or eight percent of the LinkedIn population, the company's original mobile build required... user base.Now, a little over a year has passed since LinkedIn relaunched its mobile applications...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7009-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7009_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:36:55">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/09/linkedin-sued-by-users-who-say-it-hacked-their-e-mail-accounts/</link><title>LinkedIn sued by users who say it hacked their e-mail accounts</title><description>... that LinkedIn used its members' identities without consent and broke into their third-party e-mail... details many instances in which users complained to LinkedIn about this practice, especially in instances where LinkedIn sent e-mails to the addresses of spouses, clients, opposing counsel, etc.LinkedIn...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7009-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7009_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:38:17">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/10/fear-of-economy-job-loss-has-linkedin-buzzing-with-activity/</link><title>Fear of economy, job loss has LinkedIn buzzing with activity</title><description>... like LinkedIn and Xing have grown this year, along with other social networks, but have become... latest numbers, LinkedIn was the second fastest growing social networking site in the month... that LinkedIn was the fourth fastest-growing social networking site over the last year, showing a 193 percent...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7009-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7009_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:40:47">http://arstechnica.com/security/2012/06/10-or-so-of-the-worst-passwords-exposed-by-the-linkedin-hack/</link><title>10 (or so) of the worst passwords exposed by the LinkedIn hack</title><description>...;s the kind of thing an idiot would have on his luggage."Or, apparently, on LinkedIn. You've probably heard about the 8 million passwords leaked from LinkedIn and a dating site (likely eHarmony...;s only because LinkedIn requires passwords to be at least six characters. 123456, 1234567, and 12345678 were all leaked...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7009-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7009_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:46:10">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/03/court-hijacking-ex-employees-linkedin-account-violates-pa-law/</link><title>Court: Hijacking ex-employee's LinkedIn account violates PA law</title><description>... of her LinkedIn account after firing her. In his October ruling, Judge Ronald Buckwalter of the District...;s LinkedIn account violated the anti-hacking provisions of the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act. But in a Tuesday ruling, Judge Ronald Buckwalter found that seizing an employee's LinkedIn account...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7009-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7009_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:49:12">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/06/your-iphone-calendar-isnt-privateat-least-if-you-use-the-linkedin-app/</link><title>Your iPhone calendar isn't private—at least if you use the LinkedIn app</title><description>...Today's not a good day to be a LinkedIn userdoubly so if you use LinkedIn's iPhone... the data back up to its servers, even when those calendar items were created outside of the LinkedIn app..., and any attached meeting notes (such as dial-in details and passcodes).The LinkedIn app manages to gain access...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7009-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7009_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:52:49">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/10/linkedins-new-application-platform-takes-your-resume-social/</link><title>Linkedin's new application platform takes your r?sum? social</title><description>...The folk at LinkedIn, the social network for professionals, have grown bored of the traditional rsum filled with bullet points and buzzwords. Announcing a new application platform, LinkedIn now...! Built on Googles OpenSocial application platform, LinkedIn offers nine inaugural apps that were hand...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7009-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7009_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:55:57">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/04/linkedin-leak-points-to-xbox-live-monetization-changes-for-holiday-season/</link><title>LinkedIn leak points to Xbox Live "monetization" changes for holiday season</title><description>...Where would we be, as journalists and news consumers, without LinkedIn and its members' penchant for listing upcoming projects and pending accomplishments well before the public relations... planner Praveen Rutnam's LinkedIn page to thank. Rutman's profile contained word...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7009-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7009_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:59:40">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/09/linkedin-integrated-with-windows-live-facebook-chat-hits-hotmail/</link><title>LinkedIn integrated with Windows Live, Facebook chat hits Hotmail</title><description>... book to include data from LinkedIn. LinkedIn status updates will now be visible in Messenger, just like... from Windows Live will be visible in LinkedIn.Users can also update LinkedIn status from within... profiles to LinkedIn is available immediately. Visibility of LinkedIn contact...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7009-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7009_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:03:42">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/04/exclusive-a-behind-the-scenes-look-at-facebook-release-engineering/</link><title>Exclusive: a behind-the-scenes look at Facebook release engineering</title><description>... to second largest website in the world. But few know the equally intriguing story about the engine... as the company's release engineers rolled out the new "timeline" feature for brand.... During my two days at Facebook, I learned about the important role that release engineering...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>