<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7010">manchester united FC football</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:08:13" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7010-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7010_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:08:15">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/06/quickhit/</link><title>RPG-like Quickhit Football inks deal with NFL</title><description>...Since 2005, it's been pretty rough going for football video games that aren't made by EA. Ever since EA inked an exclusive deal with the NFLfor its Madden franchise, other football games... for the 2010 season, Quickhit Football, a free-to-play browser-based game, has announced a deal with the NFL...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7010-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7010_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:13:07">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/06/yahoo-blitzes-nfl-with-fantasy-football-stats-lawsuit/</link><title>Yahoo blitzes NFL with fantasy football stats lawsuit</title><description>...Yahoo has filed a lawsuit against the National Football League demanding access to player stats... of it for fantasy football leagues. Given a 2007 ruling on the same topic for Major League Baseball... it out for millions of dollars so that only certain fantasy football leagues are "legit" while...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7010-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7010_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:14:38">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/12/drumline-meets-rock-band-360-in-black-college-football-game/</link><title>Drumline meets Rock Band, 360 in Black College Football game</title><description>...Launching a video game based on American football is rough going these days; EA has the lock... for a football product, however, as the Madden series has all but ignored Historically Black Colleges and Universities, or HBCUs. The Black College Football Experience, an upcoming Xbox 360 title, seeks...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7010-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7010_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:18:57">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/06/united-kingdom-game-ratings-to-be-provided-by-pegi/</link><title>United Kingdom game ratings to be provided by PEGI</title><description>...There has been a long battle between the British Board of Film Classification and the Pan-European Game Information System over who gets to rate games for the UK, and now we know which system has won out. From now on, PEGI will be providing game ratings for the entirety of the United Kingdom."The Government has made absolutely the right decision for child safety. By choosing PEGI as the sing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7010-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7010_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:22:11">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/02/students-think-that-bigger-numbers-must-mean-something/</link><title>The "unit effect" makes 31 days seem better than a month</title><description>..., but apparently it's even worse than thateven when they do know what the units are, people tend... because we don't understand the units. It's hard to do some conversions in our heads... kilocalories or a much smaller unit, the kilojoule. Depending on whether they were interested in watching...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7010-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7010_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:23:06">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/10/how-the-feds-busted-a-top-silk-road-seller/</link><title>How the feds busted a top Silk Road seller</title><description>... from the United States Postal Service mail stream, using a combination of drug-sniffing dogs and parcel... Crime Agency (NCA) arrested three men from Manchester and one from Devon who they believed...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7010-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7010_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:24:00">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/06/intel-talks-details-on-its-tiny-next-unit-of-computing-system/</link><title>Intel talks details on its tiny "Next Unit of Computing" system</title><description>... more about its so-called Next Unit of Computing (NUC), including price targets and future plans...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7010-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7010_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:24:59">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/08/madden-11-a-roster-update-for-the-masses/</link><title>Madden 11 : a roster update for the masses</title><description>...If the football-obsessed coworker that normally resides in the cube next to yours is absent... do both offensively and defensively? The diehard football fan can tailor the mode by editing those... much football knowledge to play the game effectively, it also allows for a quicker game. Last year...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7010-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7010_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:28:09">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/07/this-week-in-game-releases-july-13-19-2009/</link><title>This week in game releases: July 13-19, 2009</title><description>...Pick of the week: NCAA Football 10 (PSP, PS2, PS3, 360)It's about as slow a week as we've... there is at least one game that some will get excited for: NCAA Football 10\. The long-running college football... PortableNCAA Football 10PlayStation 2NCAA Football 10PlayStation 3N...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7010-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7010_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:32:16">http://arstechnica.com/staff/2013/09/at-the-age-of-32-i-finally-get-sports-thanks-to-dota-2/</link><title>At the age of 32, I finally get sports, thanks to Dota 2</title><description>...I was always at a disadvantage as a child, because I never liked football. In the UK, football... of pop culture, but football was the consistent mainstay of discussion, with the performance of your team being of singular importance. Football being a winter sport in the UK, there would be a few...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>