<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7014">Asian culture</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:57:03" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7014-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7014_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:57:06">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/10/first-evidence-of-invasive-asian-carp-reproducing-in-great-lakes/</link><title>First evidence of invasive Asian carp reproducing in Great Lakes</title><description>... a ubiquitous ecological nuisance. But several of its cousinscollectively referred to as Asian carphave set... fish.)But thats not what has biologists and fisheries managers worried. Asian carp can take... Lakes. The people who have witnessed the incredible degradation of that ecosystem viewed Asian carp...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7014-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7014_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:57:52">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2008/11/afew-thoughts-on-copyright-and-culture/</link><title>A few thoughts on copyright and culture</title><description>... culture and copyright that I think merits a closer look. Many of the central ideas here should be familiar... interaction moves online, ordinary acts of cultural sharing (retelling a story, showing someone a funny... is the observation that culturethat is to say, copyingis itself the basis of our demand for cultural...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7014-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7014_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:01:19">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2008/11/ubuntu-launches-free-culture-showcase/</link><title>Ubuntu launches Free Culture Showcase</title><description>...The Ubuntu project has announced the launch of its second Free Culture Showcase initiative. The developers behind the popular Linux distribution are giving artists in the free culture community...;The Ubuntu Free Culture Showcase is an opportunity to bring the best of two great worlds together...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7014-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7014_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:01:47">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/05/why-we-often-view-digital-culture-through-insect-metaphors/</link><title>Why we often view digital culture through insect metaphors</title><description>...Humanity has often looked to the insect world for its technological metaphors, and now for digital inspirationSwarms. Hive minds. The web*.It can be hard to avoid talking about our digital culture without using insect metaphors.Yet for new media theorist Jussi Parikka, it may be more than just a metaphor. Parikka is a reader in Media and Design at Winchester School of Art and author of the Anne F...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7014-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7014_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:02:48">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/08/when-geek-cultures-collide-a-day-at-baltimores-otakon/</link><title>When geek cultures collide: a day at Baltimore’s Otakon</title><description>... on Sunday.Otakon focuses largely on the community around Japanese pop culture, including anime...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7014-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7014_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:05:45">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/02/asian-economic-powerhouses-are-also-broadband-slowpokes/</link><title>Asian economic powerhouses are also broadband slowpokes</title><description>... and 53 percent, respectively.But India still leads the Southeast Asian region in the hyper-pokey...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7014-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7014_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:08:41">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/12/policing-the-intersection-of-nanotechnology-and-culture/</link><title>Policing the intersection of nanotechnology and culture</title><description>..., a number of psychological studies have found cultural factors such as religious, egalitarian... with cultural influences. Dan Kahan from Yale Law School led researchers in a study designed to determine if people judged nanotechnology based on familiarity or cultural cognition. If familiarity...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7014-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7014_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:11:34">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/10/the-math-gap-its-cultural/</link><title>The math gap: it's cultural (so stop mocking nerds)</title><description>... is cultural rather than biological. A new report looks beyond standardized tests of mathematical skills... some suggestions as to how to eliminate the people who get lost due to this cultural math gap. The study... achievement. Their first point is that people from Asian nations and Central Europe do extraordinarily well...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7014-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7014_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:15:34">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/03/clovis-culture-may-not-have-been-the-first-in-the-americas/</link><title>Clovis culture may not have been the first in the Americas</title><description>...Since the 1930s, many archeologists have thought that the Clovis culture (prehistoric Paleo-Indian... inhabitants. However, the notion of pre-Clovis culture in the Americas is highly controversial... that they have found 15,528 artifacts from a pre-Clovis culture that dates back 13,200 to 15,500 years. Waters...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7014-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7014_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:19:16">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/09/canada-probing-apples-ibookstore-over-cultural-heritage-worries/</link><title>Canada probing Apple's iBookstore over "cultural heritage" worries</title><description>...On August 20, Canada's Privy Council Office issued an order targeting Apple and the company's new Canadian version of the iBookstore. Referred to simply as an "order authorizing a review under the Investment Canada Act of Apple Canada, Inc.s proposed establishment of a new cultural business carried on by iBookstore in Canada," the order means that Apple's investment in Ca...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>