<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7015">the raven</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:23:41" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7015-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7015_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:23:44">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/05/ravens-show-that-consoling-one-another-is-also-for-the-birds/</link><title>Ravens show that consoling one another is also for the birds</title><description>... have to evolve, as well.The finding comes from a study of ravens which spend up to a decade in socially... occurred. The research involved a flock of 13 ravens kept in an aviary, a social group in which a number...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7015-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7015_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:27:36">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/07/time-is-the-fire-in-which-we-burn-ars-reviews-singularity/</link><title>Time is the fire in which we burn: Ars reviews Singularity</title><description>... for their own gain, or loss. Singularity Developer Raven Publisher Activision Blizzard Price $59.99...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7015-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7015_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:28:36">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/06/time-and-time-again-singularity-impressions-at-e3-2009/</link><title>Time and time again: Singularity impressions at E3 2009</title><description>... as dismal failures. Raven Software's upcoming Singularity, however, looks like it's set to spin...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7015-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7015_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:29:43">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/04/wolverine/</link><title>X-men Origins: Wolverine goes M-rated. Better than film?</title><description>... in the game. It's like Raven used the movie tie-in as an excuse to make the Wolverine game... on the surface this looks like what a Wolverine game should be. I asked what other character Raven...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7015-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7015_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:30:50">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/05/wolverine-1/</link><title>Violence is the answer: Ars reviews X-Men Origins: Wolverine</title><description>.... Title X-Men Origins: Wolverine Developer Raven Software Publisher Activision Price $59.99 Platform...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7015-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7015_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:35:02">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/09/wolfenstein-recalled-from-german-stores/</link><title>Swastikas lead to Wolfenstein recall in Germany</title><description>...Cultural sensitivity isn't something that is often considered when releasing a video game, but when it is, publishers usually have only a couple of options: censoring offensive content, not releasing a game in problematic regions, or recalling the title after the material has been recognized. Activision Blizzard has gone with the latter option, pulling Wolfenstein from store shelves because ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7015-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7015_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:39:39">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/03/wolfenstein-brings-the-supernatural-front-and-center/</link><title>Wolfenstein brings the supernatural front and center</title><description>...On the screen, some German soldiers slowly float to the ceiling, firing their weapons wildly. A few rounds into their bodies and they're toast, and gravity becomes normal again. The supernatural has always been a part of the Wolfenstein series, but the newest entry into the franchise, simply called Wolfenstein, brings the invisible world front and center. In the course of the game, B.J. Blaz...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7015-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7015_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:43:02">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/04/after-lucasarts-closure-jedi-outcast-and-jedi-academy-go-open-source/</link><title>After LucasArts closure, Jedi Outcast and Jedi Academy go open source</title><description>... a smile to programmer geeks everywhere comes from development house Raven, which has this morning...; noted Raven in a statement. "As a gift to the persistently loyal fanbase for our Jedi games...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7015-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7015_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:46:41">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/08/the-challenge-is-set-made-wolfenstein-a-hit-get-game-free/</link><title>The challenge is set: make Wolfenstein a hit, get game free</title><description>...This is one of the more interesting promotions in recent memory. If Wolfenstein outsells Madden 10 in August, one of the designers of the first-person shooter will refund you the cost of the game. At least, that's the deal laid out via Raven Software's Manveer Heir's Twitter...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7015-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7015_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:47:53">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/10/iphonelive-conference-indefinitely-postponed/</link><title>iPhoneLive conference indefinitely postponed</title><description>... of those who had agreed to participate in the event, particularly program co-chairs Raven Zachary...; and declined to elaborate further.Update: Statements from Raven Zachary and Bill Dudney....</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>