<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7018">audiobook Raymond e feist</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:51:40" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7018-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7018_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:51:43">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/09/zune-gaming/</link><title>Feist: a pretty, plain indie platformer for the Mac</title><description>... purchase of a MacBook, I decided to give it a shot. Designed by two Zurich arts students, Feist... a little blurry, and that can be distracting at times. But nevertheless, Feist is a feast for the eyes, as it were. But Feist makes it apparent that even in the indie world of innovation and unkempt...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7018-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7018_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:55:36">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/09/mac-only-feist-a-game-pc-users-might-get-jealous-over/</link><title>Mac-only Feist: a game PC users might get jealous over?</title><description>... that may put an end to our lack of gaming exclusivity. Feist, currently in Mac-only beta, is a game...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7018-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7018_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:00:09">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/10/new-e-paper-may-send-e-ink-running-for-its-e-mommy/</link><title>New e-paper may send e-ink running for its e-mommy</title><description>...A new type of electronic paper display has leaped several bounds ahead of its e-ink brethren...;e-paper" that can update the display at a video-level refresh rate and sustain a significantly brighter image than most e-ink displaysall without using any power. E-ink displays...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7018-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7018_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:01:36">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/03/modern-muggles-rejoice-harry-potter-e-books-finally-on-sale/</link><title>Modern muggles rejoice! Harry Potter e-books finally on sale</title><description>... series on sale, including both digital audiobooks and e-books compatible with all major electronic... to the Amazon Kindle store and other major e-book platforms. But starting today, the books are being sold directly by Rowling's online shop, with prices ranging from $7.99 to $9.99 for each e-book...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7018-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7018_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:03:05">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/06/congress-looks-to-tackle-abusive-e-waste-exporting/</link><title>Congress looks to tackle abusive e-waste exporting</title><description>... that are damaging to human health and the environment. A growing number of states have passed laws that mandate e.... Such policies seem like a win for the environment, but the truth about e-waste recycling is a lot grimier than it looks on the surface.The e-waste industry has a dirty little secret: a significant number...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7018-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7018_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:05:31">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2010/09/sonys-new-e-readers-who-needs-wireless/</link><title>Sony's new e-readers: who needs wireless?</title><description>...Sony has just dropped three new e-reader upgrades on the reading public, but the company seems... devices all look terrific. They use the same, higher-contrast E-Ink screens seen in the Kindle 3... in an e-reader, it does allow easier navigation of menu options and doesn't require button...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7018-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7018_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:09:11">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/02/white-house-embraces-e-book-readers/</link><title>White House embraces e-book readers</title><description>...;If only the White House would release the report in a native format for my e-book reader!" you...;s also a sign of the times; only a couple years ago, "e-book readers" were roundly mocked... have entered the popular consciousness to such an extent that e-book fever has even gripped the White House....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7018-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7018_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:13:08">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/03/kentucky-e-voting-fraud-manipulated-voters-not-machines/</link><title>Kentucky e-voting fraud manipulated voters, not machines</title><description>...-school, non-electronic crimes like racketeering, extortion, mail fraud, and so on. But even the e...-fashioned "social engineering." This entire incident says less about the perils of e-voting than it does about human nature, but this isn't to say that the e-voting vendor is entirely off...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7018-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7018_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:17:33">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/05/traditional-pigments-may-return-in-future-e-paper-displays/</link><title>Color e-paper displays look to pigmented past</title><description>...One of the constant refrains in discussions of the various e-book readers now (or soon to be) on the market is the request for color. For a large population of users, the current greyscale screens... part of the future of e-books. One of these techniques was the subject of a recent publication...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7018-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7018_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:21:21">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/06/jk-rowlings-pottermore-reveal-harry-potter-e-books-and-more/</link><title>J.K. Rowling's Pottermore reveal: Harry Potter e-books and more</title><description>..., allowing people to purchase the e-books and digital audiobooks in a selection of languages. The second... has revealed that she will release the long-awaited e-books of her mind-bogglingly popular fantasy series through her own e-commerce store and interactive online experience, Pottermore.Crucially...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>