<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7020">synovial joint</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:28:19" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7020-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7020_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:28:20">http://arstechnica.com/security/2009/04/chinese-hackers-nick-joint-strike-fighter-plans/</link><title>Chinese hackers nick Joint Strike Fighter plans</title><description>...Add top-secret plans for the expensive, much-delayed Joint Strike Fighter to the list of victims of alleged Chinese and Russian hack attacks, or so the Wall Street Journal reports. The paper cites "current and former government officials familiar with the attacks," and claims that the Air...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7020-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7020_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:28:43">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/01/storage-giant-emc-unites-with-pc-oem-lenovo-on-new-joint-venture/</link><title>Storage giant EMC unites with PC OEM Lenovo on new joint venture</title><description>... of their joint venture, called "LenovoEMC Ltd." The new outlet will specialize in selling network.... With the formation of the LenovoEMC joint venture, Iomega will no longer exist as a business unit... the spin-off also note the LenovoEMC joint venture isn't limited to selling SMB NAS boxesthe new...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7020-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7020_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:31:39">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/03/gone-house-hunting-online-controversial-lawsuit-revived-says-youre-a-joint-infringer/</link><title>Gone house hunting online? Revived patent lawsuit says you’re a “joint infringer”</title><description>... companies, together with their users, who are alleged to be "jointly infringing" the patent.Infringing together: Joint infringement gives new life to caseAfter two years of litigation, REAL... be engaged in what's called "joint infringement," a theory that was recently expanded...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7020-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7020_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:32:36">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/04/tech-workers-cant-jointly-sue-apple-google-for-cold-calling-deal/</link><title>Tech workers can’t jointly sue Apple, Google for “cold calling” deal</title><description>...In 2010, the government announced it had sued several large tech companies, including Apple, Google, Intel, Adobe, Intuit, and Pixar over their hiring practices. The companies' top execs had agreed to not "cold call" competitors' most valuable workers in an attempt to recruit them. That illegally stifled competition and held down the salaries of skilled employees, the governme...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7020-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7020_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:37:45">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/12/vmware-emc-spin-out-cloud-units-in-big-new-joint-venture/</link><title>VMware, EMC spin out cloud units in big new joint venture</title><description>...VMware and its owner EMC confirmed it will merge several product divisions into a new entity focused on cloud computing and big data.Rumors had been circling VMware for months about a plan to spin out its Cloud Foundry platform-as-a-service division, and it turns out the rumors were true. It's more than just Cloud Foundry, as the new venture will include VMware's Spring line of products...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7020-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7020_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:39:47">http://arstechnica.com/business/2011/12/att-stops-shopping-t-mobile-assets-as-death-of-merger-seems-inevitable/</link><title>ATandT stops shopping T-Mobile assets as death of merger seems inevitable</title><description>...; and that ATT is exploring alternativessuch as purchasing a minority stake in T-Mobile or creating a joint...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7020-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7020_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:42:50">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/08/intel-ge-join-to-spend-money-cpu-cycles-on-healthcare/</link><title>Intel and GE join to spend money, CPU cycles on healthcare</title><description>...Intel and GE have announced a joint healthcare venture that marks a major step in the progress... approval. Intel's and GE's joint statement explains that the venture will "focus... of joint ventures before, the most widely known of which is probably IM Flash, LLCan Intel/Micron joint...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7020-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7020_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:43:48">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/06/feds-investigating-stuxnets-architect-for-leaking-info-on-the-program/</link><title>Feds investigating Stuxnet’s architect for leaking info on the program</title><description>...NBC News reported on Thursday evening that the former vice chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff is now the target of an investigation as to who leaked classified information about the covert... States had designed before.Cartwright served as vice chairman of the Joint Chiefs from 2007 to 2011...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7020-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7020_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:46:21">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/01/international-space-station-set-to-receive-blow-up-extension/</link><title>International Space Station set to receive blow-up extension</title><description>... would presumably require some level of redesign. NASA and Bigelow Aerospace are set to hold a joint... details of the joint venture. Heres hoping that the ISSs astronauts will finally get that sewing room...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7020-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7020_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:47:18">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/07/facebook-yahoo-will-end-litigation-in-patent-peace-deal/</link><title>Facebook, Yahoo will end litigation in "patent peace deal"</title><description>... of their ongoing partnership, including a joint advertising sales effort, as well as cross-licensing..., in a joint press release....</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>