<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7022">hermitian conjugate</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:11:25" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7022-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7022_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:11:26">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/03/big-differences-in-conductivity-due-to-quantum-interference-in-a-single-molecule/</link><title>Single molecule circuit controlled through quantum interference</title><description>... properties of the molecules depend on whether they are linearly-conjugated or cross-conjugated. Linearly-conjugated means electron orbitals offer only one path for transport across the molecule. In contrast, cross-conjugated molecules effectively offer two paths of different lengths. This latter type...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7022-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7022_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:12:01">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/01/squeezing-a-circle-on-the-surface-of-a-sphere/</link><title>Squeezing a circle on the surface of a quantum sphere</title><description>... state generates a superposition state in its conjugate propertythe conjugate state of the amplitude... represents the uncertainty in one property, the second line the uncertainty in the conjugate property...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7022-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7022_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:14:26">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/03/cars-goes-wide-broad-spectrum-imaging-of-biological-samples/</link><title>CARS goes wide: broad spectrum imaging of biological samples</title><description>.... If this condition is satisfied, then the CARS signal will also be a self-conjugate, and, when multiplied with the self-conjugate pump light, will result in a single color. If, however...-conjugate light pulses that were generated by a technique called pulse-shaping. They didn't...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7022-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7022_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:16:03">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/07/reengineering-the-genomes-of-living-cells/</link><title>Genome-wide DNA editing performed in live bacteria</title><description>... of the bacterial version of sex, called conjugation. They inserted some DNA that initiates conjugation next...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7022-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7022_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:19:22">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/03/weird-science-smells-its-way-out-of-awkward-social-situations/</link><title>Weird Science smells its way out of awkward social situations</title><description>... violence in state prisons and found that it was lower in states that allowed their inmates conjugal...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7022-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7022_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:24:10">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/11/researchers-trap-antihydrogen-atoms/</link><title>CERN snags 38 antihydrogen atoms in magnetic trap</title><description>... fundamental symmetries in nature (charge conjugation/parity/time reversal) by examining the excited states...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7022-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7022_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:29:56">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/10/nobel-prizes-awarded-for-identification-of-immune-defenses/</link><title>Nobel Prizes honor immune work, but include recently deceased winner</title><description>... conjugates that set off septic shock, and the single-stranded RNA that carries the genetic information...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7022-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7022_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:33:03">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/08/plants-attract-predators-to-gobble-up-herbivores-embargo-thu/</link><title>Plants use spit of the insects eating them for self-defense</title><description>..., but they did eliminate several Manduca sexta components (fatty acid-amino acid conjugates, -glucosidase...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7022-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7022_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:34:27">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/02/science-is-slowly-building-towards-real-life-bioshock-like-plasmids/</link><title>Science inches closer to real BioShock -style plasmids</title><description>... conjugation is not F-plasmid's only trick. Infrequent cellular mishaps can cause an F-plasmid... conjugation one step further by horizontally transferring plasmids directly into the genome of plants...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>