<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7023">calculate jordan normal form</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:35:32" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7023-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7023_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:35:34">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/02/at-long-last-ti-releases-graphing-calculator-for-the-ipad/</link><title>At long last, TI releases graphing calculator for the iPad</title><description>...Texas Instruments has brought its graphing calculator functionality to a more modern platform... calculatorand has cloud integration for teachers to share files with students.TIs graphing calculators... the graphing calculator functionality into devices that students are likely carrying around with them...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7023-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7023_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:36:08">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/12/portals-physics-engine-rebuilt-in-25kb-on-a-graphing-calculator/</link><title>Portal's physics engine rebuilt in 25KB—on a graphing calculator</title><description>..., from the ground up, onwait for ita graphing calculator. In a display that puts the old calculator versions... on TI-83/84 calculators, execute more than 16 kilobytes of code.When Marcolina set out to rebuild Portal on TIs graphing calculator platform, he was 17. Now, hes a 20-year-old game design major a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7023-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7023_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:41:04">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/11/remember-ti-84-calculators-theyre-finally-getting-color-screens/</link><title>Remember TI-84 calculators? They're finally getting color screens</title><description>... that most graphing calculators have, inexplicably, forgone for ages. But finally, Texas Instruments... of its TI-84 calculator, according to a post Friday at TechPoweredMath.Calculators... operating system.In February 2011, Texas Instruments released a new graphing calculator named the TI...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7023-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7023_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:46:00">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/12/why-ti-80-series-graphing-calculators-took-22-years-to-go-color/</link><title>A big evolutionary step for a mystifyingly arcane device</title><description>... graphing calculators with a color screen next year, in large part because graphing calculators are near... decades ago. Why did TI wait so long? And after waiting so long, why now?Graphing calculators... Instruments created its first graphing calculator, dubbed the TI-81, for use by students in high school...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7023-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7023_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:46:42">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/03/how-nonlocal-can-we-make-the-universe/</link><title>Calculating the universe's lack of locality</title><description>... that the universe is not always local and certain forms of realism are on pretty shaky ground as well. Truly..., so let's start there. In strong forms of local realism, effects must happen after causes. Locality... we knew the quantum mechanics might well be nonlocal. Eventually, John Bell calculated how strongly...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7023-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7023_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:49:59">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/06/simulating-the-sounds-of-water/</link><title>Calculating the sounds of water</title><description>... more complex physical setups. Theyeventuallyplan to have these calculations complete in real time, allowing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7023-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7023_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:50:51">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/06/how-the-indie-jamestown-a-2d-shooter-and-instant-classic-was-born/</link><title>How the indie Jamestown , a 2D shooter and instant classic, was born</title><description>... that you can't," Mike Ambrogi of Final Form games told Ars. It's not just the graphics... gameplay, art, and music.This is a must-play for fans of the genreWhen Final Form games first contacted... in such a well-honed form is even rarer."We knew we had made a game that we loved, but we really...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7023-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7023_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:52:12">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/03/dont-publish-yet-with-world-ipv6-launch-ipv6-on-by-default-is-the-new-normal/</link><title>With World IPv6 Launch, IPv6 on by default will be the new normal</title><description>..., kicked things off by saying that "IPv6 'on by default' is the new normal." IPv6... Cable and Comcast representatives talked about what the new normal means to them. As part of World... increase in IPv6 traffic. And that will be just the beginning. It's the new normal...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7023-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7023_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:54:51">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/11/cleaner-shrimp-have-a-calculating-murderous-sex-life/</link><title>Cleaner shrimp have a calculating, murderous sex life</title><description>..., one of the species of cleaner shrimp engages in a sex life that's calculating and murderous. Lysmata... the animals towards forming pairs. For one, it simplifies the energetic cost of mating; the animals...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7023-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7023_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:56:37">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/10/littlebigplanet-used-to-create-1600-part-calculator-video/</link><title>LittleBigPlanet used to create 1,600-part calculator (video)</title><description>... has created a working electronic calculator using the games level editor. If you dont think thats impressive, be sure to watch the entire video. He claims the calculator uses: 610 magnetic switches500...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>