<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7024">reinforcement learning</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:02:01" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7024-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7024_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:02:02">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/04/testing-students-during-video-lectures-improves-learning/</link><title>Testing students during video lectures improves learning</title><description>... the time in class delving into issues they don't understand.But are they really improving learning... learning compared to classroom learning, but more rigorous studies were needed. After all, ease of access to the learning material comes with a bundle of distractions only a single click away...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7024-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7024_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:06:54">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/08/learning-in-your-sleep-can-really-stink/</link><title>Learning in your sleep can really stink</title><description>..., and found something a bit odd. Once learned, an association was equally strong in both REM and non-REM sleep. But when it was learned it had a curious effect: associations learned during REM sleep were stronger when a person was still asleep, but associations learned during non-REM sleep were stronger...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7024-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7024_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:10:40">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/10/how-forza-5-and-the-xbox-one-use-the-cloud-to-drive-machine-learning-ai/</link><title>How Forza 5 and the Xbox One use the cloud to drive machine-learning AI</title><description>... of Microsoft's cloud resources to power its adaptive, machine learning-based AI system, called Drivatar. And we learned how processing a massive amount of data on Microsoft's servers allows.... But previous games were only able to learn from local races and had to process and learn...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7024-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7024_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:14:08">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/12/in-mice-fear-learned-by-parents-is-transferred-to-their-offspring/</link><title>In mice, fear learned by parents is transferred to their offspring</title><description>...: learned fear. Mice can be taught to fear the smell of a specific odorant simply by giving them... for three weeks or more) gave ample opportunity for some form of social learning. But Dias and Ressler did... and the brain.The gap exists in the other direction as well. It's not clear how a learning process that takes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7024-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7024_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:17:19">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/03/turing-award-honors-learning-theory-parallel-computing-work/</link><title>Turing Award honors learning theory, parallel computing work</title><description>..., including machine learning, computational complexity, and parallel and distributed computingthe list... of practical advances. Learning from failures The ACM's description of Valiant's contributions to learning theory provide an excellent example of the sorts of problems a field faces...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7024-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7024_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:20:08">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/03/ted-moves-toward-the-classroom-with-the-launch-of-ted-ed/</link><title>TED moves toward the classroom with the launch of TED-Ed</title><description>... and discovering what they wanted from the program. They learned that video can provide a number of positives... that would be difficult or impossible to duplicate in a classroom. With video, kids can also learn... of Hack Education."While 'ideas worth spreading' might seem like a fabulous learning...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7024-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7024_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:24:18">http://arstechnica.com/business/2014/01/google-acquires-ai-pioneer-deepmind-technologies/</link><title>Google acquires AI pioneer DeepMind Technologies</title><description>... learning called "deep learning,"the development of algorithms that allow machines to learn as humans do. Deep learning models eschew pre-scripted forms of artificial intelligence and instead rely on experiential learning based on rudimentary capabilities. The models requir...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7024-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7024_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:25:01">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/06/study-powerpoint-animations-are-comprehension-killers/</link><title>Study: PowerPoint animations are comprehension killers</title><description>... that's conducive to learning. A study in the International Journal of Innovation and Learning... to nearly 25 percent, so it's clear that animation isn't uniformly harmful to learning... point out that we've actually got a well elaborated set of theories of learning, meaning...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7024-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7024_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:27:46">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/03/big-screens-and-viral-media-on-show-at-microsofts-techfest/</link><title>Big screens and viral media on show at Microsoft’s TechFest</title><description>... in Microsoft Research, continues to be studied. The company showed a machine learning-based system...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7024-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7024_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:32:37">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/03/north-pole-may-be-open-enough-for-reinforced-shipping-by-mid-century/</link><title>North Pole may be open enough for reinforced shipping by mid-century</title><description>... the numbers for two emissions scenarios. Based on their estimates, lightly reinforced vessels..., in some cases travelling close to the pole itself. Meanwhile, the reinforced PC6 ships can shoot directly...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>