<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7025">M/G/1 queue</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:33:50" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7025-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7025_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:33:51">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/02/tumblr-lets-users-call-in-queue-posts-integrate-twitter/</link><title>Tumblr lets users call in, queue posts, integrate Twitter</title><description>... are limited to two minutes in length.Also new today are queues, post-dating, and drafts. These... the latter two are pretty self-explanatory, Tumblr's new queue is somewhat interesting.Instead... queue, which can be set to automatically publish one post at specific intervals, such as 15 minutes, 12...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7025-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7025_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:37:22">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/04/iphone-dev-creating-length-controlled-data-sources/</link><title>iPhone dev: Creating length-controlled data sources</title><description>.... Normally, I'd recommend that he use an NSMutableArray as a queue, but then he pointed... items.A queue doesn't know much about delaying pops. Whereas a queue takes two operators:push... only when it had filled its capacity. Yes, you can emulate this with a queue by adding a lot...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7025-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7025_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:39:18">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/03/clogged-streets-simcity-launch-plagued-by-server-problems/</link><title>Clogged streets: SimCity launch plagued by server problems</title><description>..., whohighlights the 30-minute queue he encountered for what he notes is "a traditionally single player game...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7025-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7025_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:42:13">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/05/codel-buffer-management-could-solve-the-internets-bufferbloat-jams/</link><title>CoDel buffer management could solve the Internet’s bufferbloat jams</title><description>... between a good and bad queue. A good queue consists of a number of buffered packets that come in faster than the device in question can send them on their way. A good queue quickly drains as packets are transmitted. Such queues are necessary to smooth over the inherent bursts of arriving packets...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7025-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7025_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:42:54">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/07/mind-the-flows-and-the-packets-will-take-care-of-themselves/</link><title>Better router tech: Mind the flows, not the packets</title><description>... time processing each packet individually, then storing packets in a queue for during peak loads... subsequent packets in the same flow just like that first packet, doing away with queues... also mentions that he does away with queues. Upon reading his much more detailed whitepaper, it turns...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7025-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7025_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:47:38">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/08/netflix-for-iphone-hands-on-streaming-movies-in-your-pocket/</link><title>Hands on: Netflix for iPhone works well, needs higher-res icons</title><description>... press "Add to instant," the movie will be added to your streaming queue. You can also browse..., but they worked as advertised.When viewing your Instant Queue, the films are listed in the same order you... rearrange your queue from the iPhone once movies are in it, though; the best you can do is move something...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7025-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7025_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:48:51">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/03/netflix-social-lets-users-show-exactly-how-they-spend-nights-on-the-couch/</link><title>Netflix Social lets users show exactly how they spend nights on the couch</title><description>... each others queues. But Netflix pulled the feature after five years, allegedly due..., not their queues. If users dont want something shared socially, there is a dont share this button...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7025-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7025_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:49:50">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/11/nintendo-dsi-sells-170000-units-in-japan/</link><title>Nintendo DSi sells 170,000 units in Japan</title><description>... of availability in Japan. Many shoppers avoided long queues for the device by reserving a unit prior... reported. Queues formed at other retailers, but nothing like those typically seen for a game hardware...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7025-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7025_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:54:59">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/11/iphone-sdk-watch-new-avfoundation-framework/</link><title>iPhone SDK Watch: New AVFoundation framework</title><description>... of Audio Queues. Audio Queue programming is complicated and very "un-Cocoa" with its low-level C programming. Even the simplest of Audio Queue examples requires pages of code and callbacks...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7025-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7025_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:58:37">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/02/netflix-ceo-well-offer-streaming-only-plan-by-2010/</link><title>Netflix CEO: we'll offer streaming-only plan by 2010</title><description>..., which leveraged the Web by allowing customers to search the company's movie database and create a queue... of the queue. After watching a movie, the DVD was returned in the company's emblematic red envelope and the next movie from the queue would be sent. Netflix expanded it options with variations...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>