<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7027">prefered or preferred</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:23:51" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7027-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7027_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:23:52">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/03/greenlight-capital-drops-lawsuit-over-apples-preferred-stock/</link><title>Greenlight Capital drops lawsuit over Apple’s preferred stock</title><description>.... The proposal would have barred Apple from issuing preferred stock without a vote from shareholders first..., Einhorn wanted Apple to keep the preferred stock option available for that purposealthough Apple could return cash to shareholders through a variety of methods, Einhorn felt the preferred stock would do...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7027-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7027_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:28:06">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/09/apple-patents-reveal-better-iphone-alerts-preferences/</link><title>Apple patents hint at better iPhone alerts, preferences</title><description>... of missed messages, and adjusting application preferences. AppleInsider dug up a few Apple patents... is still kicking the tires on what to do about application preferences. The current HIG for iPhone OS recommend that developers place a preferences pane in the Settings application, while some argue...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7027-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7027_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:31:11">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/02/apple-were-in-active-discussions-on-returning-more-cash-to-shareholders/</link><title>Apple: We're in “active discussions” on returning more cash to shareholders</title><description>... evaluate Greenlight Capitals current proposal to issue some form of preferred stock. We welcome... to Greenlights statements, adoption of Proposal #2 would not prevent the issuance of preferred stock. Currently, Apples articles of incorporation provide for the issuance of blank check preferred stock...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7027-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7027_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:34:20">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/11/manipulating-interfaces-on-screens-you-cannot-see/</link><title>Manipulating interfaces on screens you cannot see</title><description>... up offered a command-line way to return to the extended desktop, whether by editing preferences... Displays of group 1end tellend tellend tellend tellend tell This script tells System Preferences to launch (activate) and switch to the Displays preferences. It then clicks the middle Arrangement...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7027-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7027_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:35:39">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/02/judge-blocks-apples-proxy-vote-over-preferred-stock/</link><title>Judge blocks Apple’s proxy vote over preferred stock</title><description>... of trying to eliminate an option for preferred stock and allegedly hoarding cash instead of returning... of preferred stock."In essence, Apple argued that its proposal to roll multiple issues into one vote doesn't mean Apple won't issue preferred stock. Still, the situation has received...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7027-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7027_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:37:12">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/03/iphone-dev-suite-preferences-fail-to-deliver-on-iphone/</link><title>iPhone dev: Suite preferences fail to deliver on iPhone</title><description>...On the Mac, suite preferences let you share your user defaults between many applications... far the iPhone would support suite preferences, so I promised to give it a try. Although the NSUserDefaults class will read suite preferences, they are most easily set using a few core foundation...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7027-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7027_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:37:43">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/02/apple-vs-greenlight-deconstructing-the-battle-over-preferred-stock/</link><title>Apple vs. Greenlight: deconstructing the battle over preferred stock</title><description>..."Mo Money Mo Problems," in the immortal words of Notorious B.I.G.Apple has more money than many nations, so it's only natural to expect the $137 billion cash and investment hoard to attract some controversy. Maybe even a few lawsuits.That's exactly what happened earlier this month. Hedge fund manager and billionaire David Einhorn, who runs the market-beating Greenlight Capital...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7027-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7027_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:42:19">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/03/gaming-community-still-favors-local-multiplayer-to-online/</link><title>It's personal: many gamers prefer local multiplayer to online</title><description>...As Sean "Puff Daddy" Combs so eloquently put it a few years ago when hawking Xbox Live, "It's good to play together." After all, one of the very first video games, 1958's Tennis for Two, was designed with multiplayer in mind. Four decades later and the legacy lives on: gaming is better when played with others. To that end, we have options: Try and schedule a session...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7027-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7027_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:44:34">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/04/facebook-users-prefer-profiles-over-newfangled-newsfeed/</link><title>Facebook users prefer profiles over newfangled(ish) newsfeed</title><description>...Since Facebook has become a pretty serious mainstay of social media, researchers have become interested in using it to find out which types of social interaction people prefer. A study done at the University of Missouri used physiological data to determine that Facebook users enjoy seeking...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7027-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7027_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:45:51">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/11/whats-preferable-exceptions-or-explicit-error-testing/</link><title>What's preferable: Exceptions or explicit error testing?</title><description>...Richard Keller asks:I often come across heated blog posts where the author uses the argument: "exceptions vs explicit error checking" to advocate his/her preferred language... are preferable to error testing? Disagree with the opinions expressed above? Bring your expertise to Stack...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>