<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7029">best buy store closings</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:08:02" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7029-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7029_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:08:05">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/06/microsoft-and-best-buy-to-create-600-stores-in-stores-by-september/</link><title>Microsoft and Best Buy to create 600 stores-in-stores by September</title><description>...Microsoft has announced new plans to extend its retail reach by partnering with Best Buy to create more than 600 stores-within-stores across the US and Canada.The companies plan 500 stores in the US, with an additional 105 in Canada split between the Best Buy and Future Shop brands. The first stores will open later this month, and the roll-out is expected to be completed by September.These will n...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7029-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7029_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:10:42">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/03/ipad-preorders-ship-new-preorders-delayed-best-buy-on-board/</link><title>iPad preorders ship, new preorders delayed, Best Buy on board</title><description>... for the "sold out" iPad. If you do plan to wait in line on Saturday, the Apple Store won't be your only option. Apple has confirmed that Best Buy will be selling the iPad too, though... will be there. Best Buy is also expected to receive new iPad shipments on April 11...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7029-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7029_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:13:39">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/06/best-buy-offers-littlebigplanet-wall-e-free-with-ps3/</link><title>Best Buy offers LittleBigPlanet, Wall-E free with PS3</title><description>...We've been running a higher than normal number of "hot deals" posts in the past week, and I apologize in advance for another one. Best Buy has quite the bundle for the PS3, however... their love for cute platformers and robots with a cockroach for a best friend.Those are two very solid pack...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7029-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7029_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:17:54">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/01/iphone-5-discount-wars-lead-to-65000-in-losses-for-best-buy/</link><title>iPhone 5 discount wars lead to $65,000 in losses for Best Buy</title><description>...The holiday battle over iPhone sales left Best Buy with $65,000 in losses, the company said on Friday. The Wall Street Journal cited Best Buy's claims as part of a piece on Walmart's advertising practices, pointing out that Best Buy was "compelled" to price-match Walmart's aggressive iPhone 5 discounts, leaving the big-box electronics retailer in the red.Both chains offer...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7029-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7029_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:20:14">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/08/best-buys-new-games-at-used-prices-promotion-starts-feud/</link><title>New games at used prices: Best Buy's Utah plan starts a feud</title><description>... it is surprising to see Best Buy make its new game prices competitive with GameStop's used game prices.In West Jordan, Utah, an eagle-eye Cheapassgamer reader snapped a picture of a sign at a local Best Buy. It said that Best Buy would price-match any use...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7029-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7029_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:22:35">http://arstechnica.com/security/2012/05/best-buy-collecting-email-passwords/</link><title>Best Buy's surprisingly insecure approach to new PC setup</title><description>... are "stored at a Best Buy store as protected customer information and destroyed after three years... down" (over-aggressive change requirements often have this effect, for instance).Best Buy.... He had settled on an HP Windows 7 machine and was in th...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7029-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7029_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:26:26">http://arstechnica.com/business/2008/10/circling-the-drain-circuit-city-contemplates-store-closings/</link><title>Circling the drain: Circuit City contemplates store closings</title><description>...Circuit City aint sitting pretty these days. The electronics retailer is bleeding cash, shrinking rather than growing, and several turnaround efforts have failed badly. A $5 billion market cap has dwindled to just $68 million in less than three years. Can this troubled retailer survive? Pros and cons To Circuit Citys credit, the company carries very little debt on its balance sheet. Thats reassur...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7029-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7029_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:30:07">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/08/best-buy-launching-huge-360-game-sale-ps3-next-week/</link><title>Best Buy launching huge 360 game sale, PS3 next week</title><description>...In the mood to spend some money? Best Buy is running a rather insane deal, where you get 50 percent off certain Xbox 360 titles by purchasing the first game at the full price, and the list of games... by getting them together through Best Buy.A partial list of games and prices is included after the jump...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7029-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7029_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:30:55">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2010/09/amazon-to-offer-kindle-at-best-buy/</link><title>Amazon takes the Kindle offline for sales at Best Buy</title><description>...Amazon, which has remained dedicated to online sales from its start, is joining forces with traditional retailer Best Buy to put Kindle e-readers on sale in stores for the holiday buying season. The arrangement, announced this morning, will see both WiFi and 3G Kindles put on display alongside other e-reader offerings this fall; the larger DX will join them at some later date. Best Buy already ca...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7029-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7029_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:34:10">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2008/11/going-going-not-quite-gone-circuit-city-shutters-20-stores/</link><title>Circuit City in fight for survival, to close 155 stores</title><description>...Circuit has announced that it intends to close some 155 of its 721 US outlets in a desperate move to staunch the flow of red ink from the companys coffers. The announcement comes as no surprisethe company lost $162.7 million in the second quarter of this yearbut its further evidence that the other retail electronics company may be joining CompUSA in the choir invisible. In its statement today, Ci...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>