<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7030">Lyrics Bangarang</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:34:52" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7030-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7030_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:34:54">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/10/lyrics-site-liveuniverse-slammed-with-6-6-million-copyright-judgment/</link><title>Lyrics site LiveUniverse slammed with $6.6 million copyright judgment</title><description>...Several years after music publishers began pursuing websites that published lyrics on the Web... LiveUniverse makes it crystal clear: hosting an unauthorized lyrics site can get you in serious legal... by a Los Angeles federal judge this week for running a lyrics site that didn't pay for a license...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7030-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7030_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:39:26">http://arstechnica.com/security/2013/02/donald-trumps-twitter-seriously-hacked-tweets-lil-wayne-lyrics/</link><title>Donald Trump’s Twitter “seriously hacked,” tweets Lil Wayne lyrics</title><description>... lyric from Lil Wayne's verse in the will.i.am ditty "Scream Shout." Trump appeared...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7030-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7030_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:43:14">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/12/oh-lord-ken-levine-didnt-remove-religious-lyrics-from-bioshock-infinite-trailer/</link><title>Oh, Lord: Ken Levine didn't remove religious lyrics from Bioshock Infinite trailer</title><description>... claiming that song lyrics to such classical and powerful hymns shouldn't be touched for pop culture.... Let's take a look at one of those versions, and you'll notice the difference in lyrics..., and he claimed that the word "Lord" was not in the song's original lyrics. Maybe it's just...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7030-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7030_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:45:10">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/02/happy-birthday-copyright-defense-those-words-and-text-are-ours/</link><title>“Happy Birthday” copyright defense: Those “words” and “text” are ours</title><description>...; lyrics were in wide use by the early 1900s. The plaintiffs hoped to form a class action and make... that the 1935 copyright registration "was not intended to cover the lyrics to Happy Birthday to You."Even if the plaintiffs show that the lyrics were published elsewhere, "this would not show...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7030-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7030_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:47:25">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/06/bing-begins-to-entertain-with-music-movies-tv-and-games/</link><title>Bing begins to entertain with music, movies, TV, and games</title><description>...Microsoft has updated its search engine with Bing Entertainment, a new section that specializes in music, movies, TV, and games.Bing Music lets you discover and sample more than 5 million songs and lyrics for free, including search results tailored for songs, artists, albums, and lyrics. Songs...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7030-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7030_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:50:08">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/10/media-molecule-gutted-by-littlebigplanet-delay/</link><title>Media Molecule "gutted" by LittleBigPlanet delay</title><description>...Last Friday saw the much-anticipated PS3 title LittleBigPlanet delayed; lyrics in one of the games were deemed offensive by some Islamic gamers. The game will now be released on October 27 in the US... of hearing about this issue involving a lyric (in Somalian, I believe!), Media Molecule had prepared...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7030-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7030_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:51:03">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/05/easter-eggs-may-get-apps-approved-but-could-hurt-app-store/</link><title>Easter eggs may get apps approved, but could hurt App Store</title><description>...One iPhone developer has managed to skirt an App Store rejection by effectively hiding some "objectionable" song lyrics behind an Easter egga kind of hidden feature that many programmers add to software.Jelle Prins created an iPhone app called Lyrics that allows a user to search for the lyrics to any songeven NWA's "F*ck Tha Police" or Rage Against The Machine's &amp;quo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7030-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7030_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:53:52">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/05/song-basing-corporate-enablers-used-to-move-iphones/</link><title>Song bashing "corporate enablers" used to move iPhones</title><description>..., too), but a closer look at the song's lyrics makes it a surprising choice for the iPhone... their backs on US consumption patterns.It's a truly odd pairing of image and lyrics, which is no doubt part of the reason that the lyrics are not, in fact, in any of the commercials. (This is unlike...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7030-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7030_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:56:50">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/10/hands-on-google-music-streams-useful-not-revolutionary/</link><title>Hands-on: Google music streams useful, not revolutionary</title><description>...As expected, Google announced Wednesday that it was indeed adding music streams to its search results thanks to a partnership with Lala, MySpace (with streaming from iLike), Rhapsody, and imeem. The search giant has struck licensing deals with EMI, Universal, Warner Music, and Sony Music to bring streams of popular music to the search page via the streaming partners, while the likes of iLike and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7030-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7030_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:59:55">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/12/week-in-gaming-bioshock-infinite-goes-spiritual-nerf-review-raams-shadow/</link><title>Week in gaming: Bioshock Infinite goes spiritual, Nerf review, RAAM's Shadow</title><description>... but powerful Nerf gun and thoughts on the lyrics of a hymn used in the latest Bioshock Infinite trailer... you might have missed.Oh, Lord: Ken Levine didn't remove religious lyrics from Bioshock Infinite... is accurate to the time period of the game, and no lyrics were changed. The "best" of the VGAs...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>