<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7031">Thomas test</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:02:11" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7031-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7031_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:02:13">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/05/not-so-shocking-jammie-thomas-riaa-unable-to-settle/</link><title>Not-so-shocking: Jammie Thomas, RIAA unable to settle</title><description>...Jammie Thomas is heading back to court. Thomas, who was the first file-sharing defendant to proceed..., clearing the way for a Thomas retrial this summer.Thomas lost her first trial and found herself... from Thomas' computer, and that jurors the first time around perceived Thomas to be lying, this is ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7031-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7031_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:05:55">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/06/whats-next-for-jammie-thomas-rasset/</link><title>What's next for Jammie Thomas-Rasset?</title><description>...Now that Jammie Thomas-Rasset owed $1.92 million to the recording industry for sharing 24 songs on KaZaA back in 2005, the case might seem to be closed. In reality, though, Thomas-Rasset still has numerous options for dealing with the verdict. Let's run them down.Pay itAccording to Thomas...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7031-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7031_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:09:05">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/07/jammie-thomas-challenges-monstrous-192m-p2p-verdict/</link><title>Jammie Thomas challenges "monstrous" $1.92M P2P verdict</title><description>...It was only a matter of time: Jammie Thomas-Rasset has asked the federal judge overseeing her file... evidence of actual injury to the plaintiffs, the judgment fines Jammie Thomas $1.92 million... largely irrelevant. Thomas-Rasset wasn't sued simply for violating the "reproduction...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7031-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7031_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:11:29">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/06/jammie-thomas-retrial-verdict/</link><title>Thomas verdict: willful infringement, $1.92 million penalty</title><description>...A new lawyer, a new jury, and a new trial were not enough to save Jammie Thomas-Rasset. In a repeat of the verdict from her first federal trial, Thomas-Rasset was found liable for willfully..., Thomas-Rasset gasped and her eyes widened.Kiwi Camara, Thomas-Rasset's lead attorney, spoke briefly...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7031-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7031_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:12:59">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/06/researchers-undercut-anonymity-of-voting-test-taking/</link><title>Researchers undercut anonymity of voting, test-taking</title><description>..., tests, and surveys, and it's generally considered to be anonymous: if you don't put your name... students are taking a high-stakes test might be tempted to fill in some answers for his students...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7031-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7031_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:15:38">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/06/jammie-thomas-takes-the-stand-admits-to-major-misstep/</link><title>Jammie Thomas takes the stand, admits to major misstep</title><description>...After the morning's excitement, Jammie Thomas-Rasset took the stand this afternoon during... significant misstep just before he let her off the stand.First came the geeksBut before Thomas-Rasset raised... message that he or she had been caught sharing files) back in February 2005, Thomas-Rasset hauled...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7031-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7031_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:17:05">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/06/sony-music-exec-shocked-by-thomas-rasset-verdict/</link><title>Sony music exec "shocked" by Thomas-Rasset verdict</title><description>...The lawyer who appeared at the Jammie Thomas-Rasset trial as a witness for Sony now says that he was "shocked" by the size of the $1.92 million verdict.Gary Wade Leak spoke at an alumni event at Columbia this weekend, where he told the audience, "We were shocked. I suspected...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7031-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7031_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:17:54">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/06/lawyer-court-must-ban-all-mediasentry-evidence/</link><title>Thomas lawyer: court must ban all MediaSentry evidence</title><description>...Jammie Thomas was unable to convince a jury of her innocence the first time around. Now... has no case against Thomas. It was MediaSentry that found Thomas' IP address when browsing the KaZaA...."The recording industry has no patience for this approach. They want to keep focused on Thomas...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7031-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7031_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:20:38">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/06/jury-selected-in-thomas-retrial-shockingly-law-abiding/</link><title>Jury selected in Thomas retrial: shockingly law-abiding</title><description>...The file-sharing retrial of Jammie Thomas-Rasset began at 9am Monday morning on the 15th floor... paper the Copyright Office provides."Not that Thomas-Rasset's legal team will let... if it was just about the price of CDs, not a single hand went up. Throughout it all, Jammie Thomas...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7031-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7031_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:22:18">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/06/closing-arguments-in-the-thomas-trial-victim-or-liar/</link><title>Closing arguments in the Thomas trial: victim or liar?</title><description>...Jammie Thomas-Rasset's file-sharing retrial has just wrapped up here in Minneapolis...;s closing arguments, the technical issues were nowhere to be seen: could someone have spoofed Thomas... rested on the argument that all the evidence, even if accepted as true, only linked Thomas...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>