<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7034">sony vaio laptop</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:50:01" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7034-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7034_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:50:02">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/05/hands-on-sony-declares-war-on-1366x768-with-new-vaio-fit-laptops/</link><title>Hands-on: Sony declares war on 1366×768 with new VAIO Fit laptops</title><description>... one of the things that Sony wants to change with its new mainstream laptop lineup, dubbed the VAIO Fit series... to eventually clean up Sonys confusing laptop lineup, which currently consists of the E-series (low-end...We don't often pay attention to entry-level product launche...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7034-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7034_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:52:41">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2014/04/a-flaming-farewell-some-of-sonys-final-vaios-use-fire-prone-batteries/</link><title>A flaming farewell: Some of Sony’s final VAIOs use fire-prone batteries</title><description>... in Sony's Fit 11A convertible laptops "could overheat and catch fire."For now, Sony...Further ReadingSony sells off VAIO PC business amid prolonged industry slumpAfter years of losses, Sony is hacking off unprofitable parts of the company.Back in February, Sony announ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7034-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7034_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:55:31">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/09/hands-on-sonys-latest-vaios-are-convertible-pcs-done-right/</link><title>Hands-on: Sony’s latest Vaios are convertible PCs done right</title><description>... out last year. The Vaio Flip laptops can turn into tablets, but they focus first and foremost on being good laptops. The Vaio Tap 11, on the other hand, is a Haswell-equipped Surface Pro competitor..., the laptops feel well-built and they look good. Sony throw...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7034-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7034_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:56:46">http://arstechnica.com/business/2014/02/sony-sells-off-vaio-pc-business-amid-prolonged-industry-slump/</link><title>Sony sells off VAIO PC business amid prolonged industry slump</title><description>...Sony has announced that it will be selling its VAIO PC business to Japan Industrial Partners (JIP). The two companies will hammer out an agreement by the end of March, and in the meantime Sony "will cease planning, design, and development of PC products," the company said in a press release. "Manufacturing and sales will also be discontinued after the Spring 2014 lineup to be launc...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7034-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7034_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:58:58">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/10/review-sonys-vaio-flip-13-dies-the-death-of-a-thousand-cuts/</link><title>Review: Sony’s VAIO Flip 13 dies the death of a thousand cuts</title><description>...The best thing a convertible PC can do is make a call: does it want to be a laptop first or a tablet? Weve said this over and over in the year since Windows 8 unleashed a flood of touchscreen Ultrabooks and convertibles, and the OEMs are figuring it outif your computer tries to be good at everything, its often going to end up being an average effort all around.Sony in particular seems to have tak...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7034-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7034_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:00:02">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/10/windows-8-convertible-pcs-from-sony-one-lighter-one-larger-both-unique/</link><title>Windows 8 convertible PCs from Sony: One lighter, one larger, both unique</title><description>...;s Vaio Duo 11 is a convertible laptop, though it's almost thin and light enough to be a suitable...Following a trend, Sony announced pricing and availability for its touch-enabled Windows 8 lineup... products with added touchscreens, but two in particular stood out to us: the Vaio Duo 11, an Ultrabook...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7034-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7034_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:02:41">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/01/hands-on-sonys-3d-vaio-almost-cool-enough-to-justify-wearing-dorky-glasses-outside/</link><title>Hands-on: Sony's 3D Vaio almost cool enough to justify wearing dorky glasses outside</title><description>...Sony says that enabling portable 3D viewing experiences is part of its strategy for making 3D... to launch is a 3D-enabled Vaio F laptop.The Windows-based computer offers a rich 3D experience on the road.... It's a winner, however, if you want a laptop for playing 3D games or editing video from a 3D camera...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7034-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7034_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:03:52">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/09/chrome-celebrates-early-birthday-with-sony-distribution-deal/</link><title>Chrome celebrates early birthday with Sony distribution deal</title><description>... on Sony's line of Vaio PCs. According to reports in the Financial Times and The Wall Street Journal, machines bearing Chrome are already shipping, and may reach consumers shortly. Sony... from more OEMssomething this Sony deal might facilitateit will undoubtedly help raise its public profile...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7034-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7034_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:07:06">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/03/sony-preparing-chrome-os-laptop-google-working-on-ui-overhaul/</link><title>Sony preparing Chrome OS laptop, Google working on UI overhaul</title><description>...Documents submitted to the FCC reveal that Sony is preparing to launch a VAIO laptop..., currently ranks 27 in Amazon's bestselling laptop list.Google has worked to improve the visibility... that Sony's VAIO Chromebook will also be formally announced during the event....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7034-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7034_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:09:02">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/01/ces-09-sony-reveals-900-ultraportable-the-vaio-p-series-lifestyle/</link><title>CES 09: Sony reveals $900 netbook, the VAIO P Series Lifestyle</title><description>...Sony had some impressive products to show off at their pre-press event press event. One of the reveals the company was obviously proud of was the VAIO P Series Lifestyle PC. Its tiny, its light... to hit select retailers next month for about $900, so lets take a look at what Sony was able to fit...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>