<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7036">holiday houses ardennes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:29:32" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7036-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7036_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:29:33">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/12/ipod-still-remains-a-top-seller-for-the-holidays/</link><title>iPod still remains a top seller for the holidays</title><description>...Despite concerns that Apples iPod has hit the glass ceiling, the portable music player is still topping best seller lists this holiday season. The latest best seller rankings from online retailer... as gifts this holiday. Though there have been signs that the growth of iPod sales may be slowing, Apple...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7036-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7036_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:30:39">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/01/e-mail-meltdown-at-the-wired-white-house/</link><title>E-mail meltdown at the wired White House</title><description>...The rain, sleet, and snow blanketing the capital may not stay the mail carrier from his appointed rounds, but nobody said anything about server outages, did they? White House e-mail was down for most of Monday, to the horror of the Hill's hordes of Blackberry addicts, and messages sent during...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7036-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7036_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:31:57">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/12/holiday-appalooza-merry-christmas-to-you-and-your-android-device/</link><title>Holiday Appalooza: Merry Christmas to you and your Android device</title><description>... with the most holiday spirit. Check them out below.Amazon Santa, FreeEnlarge Surely all of your holiday... up this holiday season but both NORAD and Google now have their own separate Santa Tracker...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7036-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7036_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:32:30">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/01/logs-reveal-which-tech-execs-have-the-white-houses-ear/</link><title>Logs don't lie: Which tech execs have the White House's ear?</title><description>...Who has the ear of the White House when it comes to tech issues? Judging from the White House... the White House bowling alley and to attend a poetry reading.But when it comes to tech executives from the private sector, Google and Microsoft have both done well at getting into the White House...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7036-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7036_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:33:57">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/11/report-online-shoppers-cutting-back-this-holiday-season/</link><title>Report: Online shoppers cutting back this holiday season</title><description>...The holiday shopping season may be a little less of a consumer orgy this year..., it found that the online holiday shopping forecast is looking a little grim for retailers... their holiday shopping plans were. It found that a whopping 70.8 percent of customers said they planned...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7036-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7036_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:35:46">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/12/apples-holiday-get-a-mac-ads-warm-the-cockles-of-our-hearts/</link><title>Apple's holiday Get a Mac ads warm the cockles of our hearts</title><description>...Its that time of year again, when we set aside our differences with Apples long-running, snooty Get a Mac campaign and watch the holiday ads that... encourage us to set aside our differences. Besides, John Hodgman and Justin Long are just so disarming in animated form. Continuing last years...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7036-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7036_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:37:26">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/11/apple-store-tries-reserve-and-pick-up-for-holiday-shoppers/</link><title>Apple Store tries "reserve and pick up" for holiday shoppers</title><description>... this holiday season, Apple has added an additional buying option aimed at making life easier. In addition... to have items gift-wrapped, if you're the sort without patience or aptitude for the "holiday arts... during the holidays, you'll likely appreciate Apple's new reserve and pick up option...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7036-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7036_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:39:23">http://arstechnica.com/business/2008/11/analysts-differ-on-holiday-consumer-electronics-spending/</link><title>Analysts differ on holiday consumer electronics spending</title><description>... as no surprise to hear that analysts are projecting negative or, at best, flat e-commerce growth this holiday...) for the November-to-December holiday season. Specifically, they predict $29.2 billion worth of spending, unchanged from the same period in 2007. On the other side of the holiday retail spending coin is a study...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7036-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7036_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:41:16">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/house-of-the-dead-overkill-brings-grindhouse-to-wii/</link><title>House of the Dead Overkill brings Grindhouse to Wii</title><description>... play House of the Dead Overkill, you'll be laughing way too hard to care.Take a regular on-rails light gun game, such as the past House of the Dead titles, and add a love for profanity, sick...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7036-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7036_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:45:19">http://arstechnica.com/business/2008/12/mastercard-2008-holiday-sales-down-some-areas-not-as-bad/</link><title>Report: 2008 holiday sales way down, but ecommerce less so</title><description>...A drop in holiday sales is no surprise this year, and at this point, the only way to find good... from one of the most challenging holiday shopping seasons in decades. According to MasterCard Advisors report, holiday retail sales were down 5.5 percent in the month of November, and 8 percent...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>