<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7042">bmw c1</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:45:48" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7042-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7042_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:45:49">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2008/10/nxp-and-bmw-team-up-for-worlds-first-smart-key/</link><title>NXP and BMW team up for world's first smart key</title><description>...NXP and BMW Group Research have teamed up to develop and unveil the worlds first smart car key, and have prototyped a device that would be capable of far more than simply unlocking a vehicle... in BMW cars users own or drive. The SmartMX P5CD081 uses a small antenna and is an integrated dual...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7042-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7042_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:50:16">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2008/12/bmw-becomes-first-carmaker-to-drive-microsoft-surface/</link><title>BMW becomes first carmaker to drive Microsoft Surface</title><description>...: BMW. The two companies have been working together to develop software for the Surface that makes... excited by putting them in complete control of the features of their future vehicle. The BMW Product.... It's not yet clear when the BMW Product Navigator will be widely available, but so far the product...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7042-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7042_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:50:57">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/04/new-20-nokia-105-doesnt-have-wi-fi-does-have-35-days-standby-time/</link><title>New, $20 Nokia 105 doesn’t have Wi-Fi, does have 35 days standby time</title><description>... (or for that matter, anywhere else): 35 days of standby battery life (a previous model, the C1, had a six...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7042-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7042_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:51:39">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2008/12/the-week-in-microsoft-windows-7-windows-live-meshmobile/</link><title>The week in Microsoft: Windows 7, Windows Live, MeshMobile</title><description>.... BMW becomes first carmaker to drive Microsoft Surface. BMW is the first carmaker to adopt and implement Microsoft Surface into its business model. The result is the BMW Product Navigator, which lets...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7042-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7042_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:53:57">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/07/on-site-energy-generation-leads-to-epa-recognition/</link><title>On-site energy generation leads to EPA recognition</title><description>... power each year, and purchases another 415 million kilowatt-hours from green sources.If you drive a BMW Z4, then your car was made in a very green facility. The Greer, South Carolina BMW manufacturing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7042-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7042_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:55:31">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/09/lithium-ion-new-hotness-in-electric-carsexcept-for-toyota/</link><title>Lithium-ion new hotness in electric cars—except for Toyota</title><description>...For the past several years, almost all the electric action on the roads has come in the form of electric hybrids with gasoline engines, a concept that Toyota popularized with its Prius but adopted by a number of other manufacturers. But it's starting to look like, within the next several years, it will be possible to buy electric vehicles from a variety of manufacturers, many of which are ta...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7042-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7042_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:56:18">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/10/dell-locates-source-of-cat-pee-smell-in-laptops-after-four-months/</link><title>Dell locates source of cat pee smell in laptops after four months</title><description>... as a strengthening agent in manufacturing. Smart News points to Autoevolution, which describes how BMW had a set...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7042-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7042_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:57:42">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/11/the-dealmaster-laptops-desktops-monitors-chairs/</link><title>The Dealmaster: Laptops, desktops, monitors, chairs!</title><description>...)Haworth X99 Chair w/BMW feel for $762.80 with free shipping no sales tax (normally $897)...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7042-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7042_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:59:58">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/04/iphone-os-30-beta-suggests-80211n-video-publishing-coming/</link><title>iPhone OS 3.0 beta suggests 802.11n, video publishing coming</title><description>... the Pinto to 802.11n's BMW Z4.For aspiring iPhone videographers, support has been found...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7042-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7042_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:03:41">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/01/microsoft-surface-helping-with-security-at-the-super-bowl/</link><title>Microsoft Surface helping with security at the Super Bowl</title><description>..., and BMW. Microsoft is reportedly weighing its options for developing a version for consumers...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>