<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7044">song of ice and fire</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:21:18" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7044-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7044_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:21:19">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/05/george-rr-martins-ice-and-fire-series-to-adapted-to-games/</link><title>George R.R. Martin's Ice and Fire series adapted to games</title><description>...Gamers who have been keeping up with George R.R. Martin's long-running fantasy series "A Song of Ice and Fire" will be pleasedor incredibly apprehensiveat the news that the books... fans of 'A Song of Ice and Fire', so it is a true honour for our teams to be entrusted...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7044-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7044_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:25:09">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/12/mario-kart-is-a-beautiful-love-song-video/</link><title>Mario Kart is a beautiful love song (video)</title><description>...It seems impossible, but it seems like someone has written an honest-to-goodness love song based.... Its not enough that the song is wonderful, but the taped-on yarn mustache and the forlorn looks make... can in fact woo the woman of your dreams with songs about video games. Ive been watching this all morning...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7044-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7044_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:26:24">http://arstechnica.com/business/2011/03/million-song-dataset-take-it-its-free/</link><title>Million-song dataset: take it, it's free</title><description>... on how to deliver smart music delivery systems is underway, facilitated by a Million Song Dataset just... the components, and offer up new songs and compositions that you'll like. And that "freely...." A sample from the Million Song Dataset Robots need more music The impediment to the last goal...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7044-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7044_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:29:49">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/03/megaupload-will-drop-its-lawsuit-against-umg-over-mega-song/</link><title>Megaupload will drop its lawsuit against UMG over "Mega Song"</title><description>...;Megaupload Mega Song." Megaupload released the track a month before its shutdown. It showcased.... They obliged, prompting Megaupload to file against UMG. YouTube eventually reinstated the song several...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7044-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7044_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:31:41">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/04/ice-invaders-brings-classic-gaming-to-your-ice-cubes/</link><title>Ice Invaders brings classic gaming to your ice cubes</title><description>.... Yes, these are ice cube trays shaped like characters from Space Invaders.There is really no hook here, no big news. Just ice cubes shaped like Space Invaders. You can pour in different liquids...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7044-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7044_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:32:50">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/04/youth-of-arctic-sea-ice-revises-predictions-of-ice-free-pole/</link><title>Youth of Arctic sea ice revises predictions of ice-free pole</title><description>...Over the past several years, the amount of sea ice in the Arctic Ocean during the summer months..., the prospect of an ice-free summer in the Arctic, which would have consequences for everything from the local... is leading to a new understanding of how the age of the ice combines with natural variability to produce...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7044-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7044_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:36:48">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2014/04/ifixits-fire-tv-teardown-discovers-snapdragon-600-and-a-huge-heatsink/</link><title>iFixit’s Fire TV teardown discovers Snapdragon 600 and a huge heatsink</title><description>...Amazon's Fire TV is the newest set-top box on the block, and even though it costs the same $99... has hopes that the Fire TV will become the Android-based mini-game console that the Ouya has so far failed to be.Further ReadingAmazon reveals Fire TV video streaming box and gaming controllerTired of seeing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7044-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7044_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:41:42">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/02/groupon-ceo-andrew-mason-fired-after-ridiculously-poor-earnings/</link><title>Groupon CEO Andrew Mason fired after ridiculously poor earnings</title><description>...After Groupons financial earnings were so bad that they caused the company's stock to fall 25 percent in a single day on Thursday, Groupon promptly fired its CEO, Andrew Mason.After four... kiddingI was fired today. If youre wondering why you havent been paying attention.Interestingly, Wall...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7044-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7044_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:43:05">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/09/kindle-fires-4g-package-offers-250mb-of-data-a-month-for-50-a-year/</link><title>Kindle Fire's 4G package offers 250MB of data a month for $50 a year</title><description>...Amazon's just-announced Kindle Fire HD LTE, which sells for $499 and begins shipping... cellular support to an iPad costs $130. Still, the price of the Kindle Fire HD LTE is lower...: Amazon's product page for the Fire HD 4G also mentions that 3GB and 5GB plans will be available...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7044-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7044_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:47:08">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/10/adventures-in-rooting-running-jelly-bean-on-last-years-kindle-fire/</link><title>Adventures in rooting: Running Jelly Bean on last year's Kindle Fire</title><description>...If you purchased a Kindle Fire at any point before Amazon refreshed the lineup in September, I've got bad news for you: none of the improvements made to the software used by the 2012 Kindle Fire and the Kindle Fire HD are going to be brought to your tablet. If you have any particular...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>