<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7045">Natural Parks America</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:49:52" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7045-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7045_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:49:53">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/03/south-park-the-stick-of-truth-respect-its-authori-tah/</link><title>South Park: The Stick of Truth review: Respect its authori-tah</title><description>...Game DetailsDeveloper:South Park Studios/Obsidian EntertainmentPlatform: Windows (reviewed), Xbox... the latest South Park video game to its virtual predecessors. Up until this week, every game starring Stan..., had its characters slapped on every product imaginable. So yes,South Park: The Stick of Truth...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7045-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7045_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:51:11">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/09/new-mexico-park-earns-recognition-for-its-dark-skies/</link><title>New Mexico park earns recognition for its dark skies</title><description>... its International Dark Sky Parks program. To qualify, parks have to meet strict standards for viewing quality, use astronomy-friendly lighting in the park, and perform astronomy outreach.So far, a handful of national and state parks in the US (and a few internationally) have become part of the program...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7045-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7045_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:52:17">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/03/linkin-parks-iphone-game-brings-camp-chiptunes/</link><title>Linkin Park's iPhone game brings camp, chiptunes</title><description>...Bands getting into the world of gaming is nothing new in the time of rhythm games, but the trailer for the upcoming iPhone game centering around Linkin Park is delightfully screwball, and it seems to realize just how silly the whole thing looks. Even the name, LINKIN PARK 8-BIT REBELLION! is campy. You'll work with the band to keep the world safe for 8-bit games, fighting off the powers of P...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7045-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7045_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:55:17">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/11/better-to-watch-than-to-play-jurassic-park-the-game/</link><title>Better to watch than to play: Jurassic Park: The Game</title><description>...You might go into Jurassic Park: The Game thinking it's a basic adventure game, something.... The quintessential example of an interactive movie, Jurassic Park is a mini-series set during... up from the unnecessary third film, but there's simply too little gameplay.The plot of Jurassic Park...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7045-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7045_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:58:11">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/07/fracked-pennsylvania-shale-could-be-naturally-leaky/</link><title>Fracked Pennsylvania shale could be naturally leaky</title><description>... guess from its name, natural springs of salty water bubble to the surface in that park. That might... that there are likely natural areas of mixingsubdued versions of Salt Springs State Park...Hydraulic fracturingfrackingfor natural gas has revolutionized the energy industry in many...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7045-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7045_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:01:12">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/06/jurassic-park/</link><title>Telltale's Jurassic Park will delight film fans, frustrate everyone else</title><description>...After spending 20 minutes playing the upcoming PC and console titleJurassic Park: The Game, I... presentation is precisely why Jurassic Park is such an interesting piece of interactive storytelling... than exhilarating, this is Jurassic Park in all the right ways. Just know going in that it's a bit...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7045-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7045_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:05:15">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/02/south-park-iphone-app-rejected-as-potentially-offensive/</link><title>South Park iPhone app rejected as "potentially offensive"</title><description>...Score one more point against Apple and its nonsensical App Store approval process. ASouth Park... to the South Park Studios website. It gives direct access to streaming South Park clips, news, and the episode index. It also lets iPhone users set South Park-themed wallpapers and assign avatars of South...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7045-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7045_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:06:02">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/06/telltale-to-switch-up-formula-with-jurassic-park-bttf/</link><title>Telltale goes Back to the Future with Jurassic Park</title><description>... on Jurassic Park and Back To The Future, the developer won't necessarily be sticking to the formula that fans are used to."In the case of Jurassic Park, we've wanted to kind of step... is it? How is the game paced? And so you're going to find all of that stuff in the Jurassic Park...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7045-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7045_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:07:24">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/11/jurassic-park-devs-tried-to-game-user-reviews-but-who-doesnt/</link><title>Jurassic Park devs tried to game user reviews. Who hasn't?</title><description>...Jurassic Park: The Game was kept from the press until a few days after the game's releaserarely a good sign. The game did have a number of user reviews on Metacritic, though...."Telltale is finding that one out the hard way. The user review average for Jurassic Park...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7045-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7045_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:10:35">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/09/resurrecting-dinosaurs-will-remain-a-jurassic-park-dream/</link><title>Resurrecting dinosaurs will remain a Jurassic Park dream</title><description>...On the same day that the latest installment of the Jurassic Park film series has been confirmed..., depicts a theme park island filled with dinosaurs, resurrected from ancient DNA extracted from fossilized... nature of DNA and the huge expanse of time that has passed have led many experts to doubt claims...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>