<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7046">tuning fork</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:11:37" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7046-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7046_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:11:38">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/09/document-foundation-forks-openofficeorg-to-liberate-it-from-oracle/</link><title>Document Foundation forks OpenOffice.org, liberates it from Oracle</title><description>... called the Document Foundation to manage a community-driven fork of the popular open source office suite... for the idea of forking the OOo code base before Oracle acquired Sun, but the acquisition substantially... is creating a fork of OOo called LibreOffice that will be distributed independently of OOo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7046-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7046_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:14:10">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/06/a-character-not-a-voice-tuning-the-narration-in-bastion/</link><title>A character, not a voice: tuning the narration in Bastion</title><description>...," he continued. "The narrator is a character, not just a voice."Each lined was tuned...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7046-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7046_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:17:35">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2011/04/oracle-gives-up-on-ooo-after-community-forks-the-project/</link><title>Oracle gives up on OpenOffice after community forks the project</title><description>... of the OOo community and a number of major corporate contributors forked OOo to create a vendor-neutral... in a transparent and open way.A group of prominent OOo contributors eventually decided to fork the project... its commercial ambitions for OOo because the growing momentum of the more inclusive LibreOffice fork...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7046-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7046_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:20:39">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/10/googles-iron-grip-on-android-controlling-open-source-by-any-means-necessary/</link><title>Google’s iron grip on Android: Controlling open source by any means necessary</title><description>... is free to take it, clone the source, and create their own fork or alternate version.As we've seen... market, and Android's massive install base means it has a ton of apps. If a company forks Android... a company does ever manage to fork AOSP, clone the Google apps, and create a viable competitor...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7046-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7046_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:23:15">http://arstechnica.com/business/2011/09/oracle-may-fork-itself-with-recent-mysql-moves/</link><title>Oracle may "fork itself" with recent MySQL moves</title><description>... of forked-off projects, including: Drizzle, a lightweight MySQL alternative derived the now-deleted... performance engineer Peter Zaitsev's Percona; and MariaDB, a fork of MySQL 5.1 driven...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7046-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7046_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:27:28">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2011/09/a-year-after-the-fork-libreoffice-still-going-strong/</link><title>A year after the fork: LibreOffice is growing and going strong</title><description>...Today marks the one-year anniversary of The Document Foundation (TDF) and the LibreOffice project, a promising community-driven fork of OpenOffice.org (OOo). The project has seen considerable growth..., LibreOffice has accumulated 25,000 code commits since the fork. These commits were made by a diverse...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7046-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7046_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:30:36">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/10/five-year-old-wikipedia-fork-is-dead-in-the-water/</link><title>Citizendium turns five, but the Wikipedia fork is dead in the water</title><description>...Five years ago this month, Larry Sanger caused a stir when he launched a fork of Wikipedia, the site he helped create in 2001. Sanger believed Wikipedia had fatal weaknesses that could only be fixed... called Citizendium. It began as a fork of Wikipedia, but the site "unforked" in 2007...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7046-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7046_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:31:43">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/02/adobe-changes-its-tune-slightly-on-iphone-flash/</link><title>Adobe changes its tune slightly on iPhone Flash</title><description>..., and the company changed its tune somewhat by refusing to comment on a collaboration between Apple...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7046-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7046_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:32:23">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/08/singing-the-praises-of-weird-science-badly-off-tune/</link><title>Singing the praises of Weird Science, badly off tune</title><description>... than singing in tune, or there are dedicated pathways within the arcuate fasciculus that we can't...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7046-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7046_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:35:32">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/11/fork-off-mass-exodus-from-ooo-as-contributors-join-libreoffice/</link><title>Fork off: mass exodus from OOo as contributors join LibreOffice</title><description>... the LibreOffice project, a fork of the open source office suite. In an open letter published on the OOo... with the OOo development process and governance model. The fork was backed by The Document Foundation, a newly... that participating in both projects poses a conflict of interest and responded to the fork by forcing TDF me...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>