<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7048">pictures auvergne</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:08:09" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7048-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7048_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:08:10">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/10/legendary-pictures-looking-to-pick-up-epic-games/</link><title>Legendary Pictures looking to pick up Epic Games</title><description>...The world of film is coming ever closer to that of video games, as Variety is reporting that Legendary Pictures is in talks to purchase Gears of War developer Epic Games. The rumors come just a few weeks after Legendary boss Thomas Tull left game publisher Brash Entertainment, which he helped...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7048-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7048_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:12:15">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/09/steam-comes-to-the-living-room-tv-with-big-picture-mode-beta/</link><title>Steam comes to the living room TV with Big Picture mode beta</title><description>..., rectangular picture icons designed to be viewed from a living room couch rather than a desk chair. Navigation in Big Picture mode is handled with a standard handheld controller (like that on the Xbox 360... and text-based communication, Big Picture mode also features a unique on-screen keyboard...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7048-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7048_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:15:17">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/04/accused-lulzsec-member-pleads-guilty-to-hacking-sony/</link><title>Accused LulzSec member pleads guilty to hacking Sony</title><description>..., California, to felony charges associated with the breach of Sony Pictures Entertainment that occurred... in a SQL injection attack on the Sony Pictures site, and stole personal information from thousands... Forecasting. Sony Pictures Entertainment claims the attack that Kretsinger assisted ultimately cost...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7048-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7048_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:17:19">http://arstechnica.com/security/2008/10/apicture-is-worth-a-thousand-passwords/</link><title>A picture is worth a thousand passwords</title><description>... files over infrared or Bluetooth between two PDAs, and its as easy as taking a picture. Current methods... changes in hairstyle, makeup, etc. Users take a picture of themselves, then uses a random string... takes a picture of the other devices owner. The biometric data from this new picture is used to try...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7048-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7048_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:19:36">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/03/xi3-pushes-back-at-valve-calls-piston-more-than-just-a-steam-box/</link><title>Xi3 pushes back at Valve, calls Piston “more than just a Steam Box”</title><description>... and large monitors using Steam's Big Picture mode. But soon after Xi3 started taking preorders... in the living room through Steam's Big Picture interface. This usually means a small, simple, console...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7048-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7048_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:21:57">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/10/movie-licensing-group-to-irish-preschools-pay-up/</link><title>Movie licensing group to Irish preschools: pay up!</title><description>...Going after preschools is high on the list of ways to turn your licensing organization into a bad PR generator, but that hasnt stopped the Motion Picture Licensing Company from targeting Irish tots. The group, which offers licenses to show movies outside the home, has been trying to squeeze a few...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7048-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7048_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:22:29">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/05/2012s-solar-eclipse-in-pictures/</link><title>2012's solar eclipse in pictures</title><description>... to enlarge. Kunio Sayanagi.If you snapped a picture of the event, feel free to link...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7048-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7048_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:23:09">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/10/mavericks-an-operating-system-in-pictures/</link><title>Mavericks: An operating system in pictures</title><description>... better than Apple. (Google doesn't do maps, right?) 3D view in Apple's Maps. Not pictured...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7048-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7048_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:28:15">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/09/thomas-edisons-plot-to-destroy-the-movies/</link><title>Thomas Edison's plot to hijack the movie industry</title><description>.... But it should have been, because that was the night Thomas Edison tried to hijack the motion picture... treaty. Since 1891, when the Wizard of Menlo Park filed his first patent on a motion picture camera... man wanted it all, so he assembled his rivals and proposed that they join his Motion Picture Patents...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7048-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7048_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:31:04">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2010/01/ces-in-pictures-the-good-the-bad-the-elvis/</link><title>CES in pictures: the good, the bad, the Elvis</title><description>... picture taken with Elvis at a few different places, and if you knew were to look you could sit in Captain Kirk's chair. Welcome to our CES, in pictures. At the Panasonic booth, huge slabs of 3D... and take pictures with your cell phone. There was a cardboard cutout wearing a dress, and you...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>