<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7050">spotvps review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:59:48" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7050-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7050_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:59:49">http://arstechnica.com/staff/2010/12/year-in-review-2010s-most-popular-stories/</link><title>Year in review: 2010's most popular stories</title><description>...These are the most popularby pageviewsstories that ran on Ars Technica during 2010. We've split them into two categories: multipage features and reports. Without further ado:Multipage features10. Tentacular, tentacular!: Beware, mortals: Cthulhu has returned, and he's armed with bacon and an unhealthy obsession with geek brains. Battle your way through our first-ever interactive adventu...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7050-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7050_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:00:38">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/05/review-datura-forces-you-to-figure-it-out-for-yourself/</link><title>Review: Datura forces you to figure it out for yourself</title><description>... a Move controller to a homemade clip on the side of a Sony Personal 3D Viewer.For this review, I...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7050-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7050_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:03:23">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/05/why-were-not-review-brink-and-why-you-shouldnt-buy-it-yet/</link><title>Why we're not reviewing Brink , and why you shouldn't buy it (yet)</title><description>... arrived too late for us to play it for any significant amount of time, the state of the review code... remains that the game reviewers have been playing for the past week will not be the same game you play... be offline when the game launched. I made a joke about it being awkward for reviewers to ask...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7050-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7050_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:04:47">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/10/new-wave-of-online-peer-review-and-discussion-tools-frightens-some-scientists/</link><title>New wave of online peer review and discussion tools frightens some scientists</title><description>... were it not for the new directions that peer review and social media are taking science. I was alerted... these hidden details and pitfalls into clear view much earlier in the process.Peer review is leveling upThe discussion generated by those papers highlights the value of post-publication peer review...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7050-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7050_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:09:22">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/04/playing-against-the-gods-how-the-press-reviews-multiplayer-games/</link><title>Playing against the gods: how the press reviews multiplayer games</title><description>...Reviewing a single-player game is relatively easyyou just need to hunker down and play the darned.... You can always review the single-player portion of the game and come back to the multiplayer... we have a good time playing their game. Reviews written based on games played with the developers...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7050-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7050_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:11:00">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/11/ars-readers-react-to-our-reviews-editor-pulling-major-gs/</link><title>Ars readers react to our reviews editor pulling major Gs</title><description>...Ars did some cool things this week. First off, we got Senior Reviews Editor Lee Hutchinson to take...;s all about the batteries babyAs it hit the shelves this week, Kyle Orland wrapped up his full review of the Xbox... down the line. You can read some of Kyle's words on the subject atXbox One review...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7050-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7050_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:11:55">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/05/week-in-review-moblin-fair-use-crack-hos-and-the-penis-phone/</link><title>Week in Review: Moblin, fair use, crack hos, and the "penis phone"</title><description>... of source review: Court-ordered source code reviews of the software that is used to power...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7050-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7050_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:14:10">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/09/a-tale-of-two-papers-peer-review-under-the-microscope/</link><title>A tale of two papers: peer review under the microscope</title><description>... at peer review, the gatekeeping process that confers a stamp of validity on science. OK, so maybe that is an exaggeration; nevertheless, the purpose of peer review is to act as a minimal hurdle... of my own that highlight some of the good and bad points of the peer review system. A graduate student...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7050-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7050_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:15:24">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/04/review-fezs-world-spinning-puzzles-drive-us-to-distraction/</link><title>Review: Fez 's world-spinning puzzles drive us to distraction</title><description>...-hidden. Fez xbox* Release Date:now MSRP:$10 Official site * = platform reviewed Fez starts off like...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7050-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7050_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:16:40">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/12/imac-27-core-2-duo-review-yep-its-still-an-imac/</link><title>A review of the iMac 27" Core 2 Duo: yep, it's still an iMac</title><description>... option is now 27". For this review, we looked at the 3.06GHz Core 2 Duo 27" iMac model... (read our review of the Magic Mouse here). The wireless keyboard is the same as what Apple...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>