<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7051">dinosaur names</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:19:29" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7051-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7051_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:19:31">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/11/xenoceratops-the-alien-horned-face-dinosaur-discovered-in-canada/</link><title>Xenoceratops: the 'alien horned-face' dinosaur discovered in Canada</title><description>...A new species of horned dinosaur, called the xenoceratops"alien horned-face"has been discovered in fossil beds in Alberta, Canada.The discovery is based on remains from at least three adult-sized individuals, which were identified from fossils originally collected in 1958. The creatures would have been approximately six meters long and would have weighed more than two metric tons each.T...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7051-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7051_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:20:36">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/10/the-earliest-dinosaur/</link><title>Meet the earliest dinosaurs</title><description>...Dinosaurs ruled the Earth during the late Triassic through the late Cretaceous periods, a span... to be the earliest known evidence of dinosaurs in existence.For the first 20 million or so years... crocodile-like reptiles ruled the planet, and finding early dinosaur remains has been difficult. A new...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7051-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7051_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:25:20">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/11/four-winged-dinosaur-fossilized-after-swallowing-a-bird/</link><title>Four-winged dinosaur fossilized after swallowing a bird</title><description>...: it ate them. Microraptor, as its name implies, was a small dinosaur, maybe a meter long counting...Feathered dinosaurs existed for millions of years before the origin of birds and, for a time, there was a period where feathered dinosaurs and early birds coexisted with animals that don't fit...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7051-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7051_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:28:06">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/06/dinosaur-bones-reveal-evidence-against-cold-blooded-creatures/</link><title>Dinosaur bones reveal evidence against cold blooded creatures</title><description>...Who can get enough of dinosaurs? Were curious about what color they were, how fast they moved... through fossils from most groups of dinosaurs (except sauropods) reveal cycles in growth, including dark..., remains constant. Or so the story went.Some argued that the dinosaur bones actually showed signs...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7051-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7051_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:31:56">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/03/large-dinosaur-from-portugal-may-have-been-top-european-predator/</link><title>Large dinosaur from Portugal may have been top European predator</title><description>...Say hello to Torvosaurus gurneyi, a newly discovered theropod dinosaur that lived in Europe around... in Europe and one of the largest carnivorous dinosaurs from the late Jurassic period. The identification of this new species plays an important role in developing our understanding of how different dinosaurs...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7051-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7051_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:34:43">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/02/archaeologists-find-evidence-of-birds-dinosaur-ancestors/</link><title>Paleontologists find evidence of birds' dinosaur ancestors</title><description>...-legged, large-jawed dinosaurs. As different as they sound, paleontologists have found extensive... dinosaurs predate the earliest official birds, and shed light on the origin of feathers. Scientists have generally accepted that birds and theropods, bipedal dinosaurs la Tyrannosaurus rex, share...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7051-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7051_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:36:30">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/10/high-schooler-discovers-fossil-of-juvenile-dinosaur/</link><title>High schooler discovers fossil of juvenile dinosaur</title><description>...As our collection of fossils left by non-avian dinosaurs has grown, we've learned... dinosaurs. Many of these species had enormous extensions on the peaks of their skulls, formed... they're growing, dinosaurs form annual rings of different densities in their bones. Sections...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7051-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7051_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:38:06">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/02/cretaceous-meteor-arrived-just-in-time-to-wipe-out-the-dinosaurs/</link><title>Cretaceous meteor arrived just in time to wipe out the dinosaurs</title><description>... the one that wiped out the dinosaurs and ushered in the age of the mammals. Most of us know the storya hellish... in the dinosaurs? Well, that depends on when the bullets were fired.The debate started with the discovery... dinosaur lovers need not fret, as a new study using improved dating methods has found that the meteor...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7051-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7051_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:40:27">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/03/extinction-that-paved-way-for-dinosaurs-definitively-linked-to-volcanism/</link><title>Extinction that paved way for dinosaurs definitively linked to volcanism</title><description>... in the start of the era of the dinosaurs. The study provides a precise timing of events of the extinction... what are termed "flood basalt eruptions." These events are just what the name implies... eruptions in killing off the dinosaurs was only settled by finding something else to blame...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7051-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7051_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:41:49">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/03/dinosaur-killing-impact-set-the-world-on-fire/</link><title>Dinosaur-killing impact set the world on fire</title><description>... that killed off all the non-avian dinosaurs (along with a host of other species). A paper in the Journal...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>