<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7052">hotel bruges</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:44:11" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7052-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7052_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:44:12">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/06/arswwdc-meet-us-for-drinks-tonight-at-hotel-utah/</link><title>Ars@WWDC: Meet us for drinks tonight at Hotel Utah</title><description>... are banding together tonight at Hotel Utah, a bar located at 500 4th Street in San Francisco.We're going...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7052-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7052_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:47:19">http://arstechnica.com/security/2012/11/hotel-room-burglars-exploit-critical-flaw-in-electronic-door-locks/</link><title>Hotel room burglars exploit critical flaw in electronic door locks</title><description>...A Houston-based Hyatt is one of a handful of hotels in Texas targeted by digital tools... on Monday. Management for the hotel later concluded the thief accessed the room by exploiting... that insurance firm Petra Pacific issued an alert claiming that "several" Texas hotels...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7052-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7052_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:49:44">http://arstechnica.com/security/2012/12/fix-for-hotels-electronic-door-lock-hack-slow-to-roll-out/</link><title>Fix for hotels' electronic door lock hack slow to roll out</title><description>...Electronic lock manufacturer Onity has finally agreed to reimburse its customersmajor hotel chains... hotel rooms worldwide) could be disabled in a matter of seconds using a custom-designed kit... November.Last month, following the theft of a laptop from a Texas hotel room using this hardware...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7052-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7052_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:52:16">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2014/02/forget-its-hotels-sochis-tech-has-been-up-for-the-olympic-challenge/</link><title>Forget its hotels, Sochi’s tech has been up for the Olympic challenge</title><description>... in hotel rooms, weird bathrooms, and dangerous manholes. But complaints about the cell coverage, Wi... We have surveillance video from the hotels that shows people turn on the shower then leave the room... in Sochi hotel rooms or bathrooms.Emotionally unstable and attending the Olympics? Theoretically...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7052-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7052_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:56:07">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/10/fighting-a-data-grab-airbnb-attacks-vague-new-york-hotel-laws/</link><title>Fighting a data grab, Airbnb attacks “vague” New York hotel laws</title><description>... petitionis dedicated to directly attacking New York's hotel tax as unconstitutionally vague.Objecting... Airbnb legal brief also attacks the hotel tax directly, calling it "unconstitutionally vague... hotel taxes. And finally, Airbnb points out city rules say an accommodation "will be irrebuttably...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7052-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7052_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:00:12">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/05/airbnb-host-gets-fined-2400-for-breaking-hotel-laws/</link><title>Airbnb host gets fined $2,400 for breaking hotel laws</title><description>..., a New York administrative law judge ruled that Warren was in violation of the city's hotel laws... inthey are average New Yorkers trying to make ends meet, not illegal hotels that should be subject...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7052-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7052_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:03:15">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/06/news-sports-and-travel-go-metro-in-windows-8-release-preview/</link><title>Hands-on: News, Sports, and Travel go Metro in Windows 8 Release Preview</title><description>..., top attractions, hotels, restaurants, nightlife, shopping information and more. The hope is that, if you find a given destination interesting enough, you'll search for a flight and hotel...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7052-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7052_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:03:58">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/05/weird-science/</link><title>Weird Science looks for vacancies at the hermit crab hotel</title><description>...They may still be crabs, but they're not hermits: This is a fascinating bit of social behavior that I had no idea existed. For hermit crabs, decent shells are a scarce commodity, and they've evolved a social means of optimizing shell occupancy that researchers have termed a vacancy chain. This new observational study describes two types of vacancy chains, synchronous and asynchronous. T...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7052-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7052_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:08:47">http://arstechnica.com/staff/2012/06/orbitz-to-mac-users-give-us-the-money/</link><title>Orbitz to Mac users: show us the money!</title><description>... as being more willing to spend higher amounts of money on hotels than their PC-using friends. Mac users might spend $20-30 more per night on a hotel, and are 40 percent more likely to book a four- or five-star hotel than PC users. The demographic data is there, and it's not even that surprisingMacs...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7052-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7052_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:10:08">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/12/the-eagles-land-in-guitar-hero-world-tour/</link><title>The Eagles land in Guitar Hero: World Tour</title><description>...Just in case Hotel California wasnt enough to satiate your desire for The Eagles, Activision... from 1976s Hotel California are being released. Rounding out the list is Frail Grasp on the Big Picture... Points ($1.99) individually, while the entire pack will run virtual rockers 440 MSP ($5.49). Hotel...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>