<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7053">nintendo 3ds hack</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:11:22" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7053-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7053_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:11:23">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/02/3ds-launches-in-japan-handheld-sells-out-already-hacked/</link><title>3DS launches in Japan: handheld sells out, already hacked</title><description>... stopped Nintendo from launching the 3DS in Japan. With less than half a million units for sale... shouldn't be too long before the 3DS starts flooding shelves once agin, though, as Nintendo... emulator running on the Nintendo 3DS There were long lines for...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7053-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7053_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:15:09">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/03/nintendo-unveils-3ds-netflix-super-mario-at-gdc/</link><title>Nintendo unveils 3DS Netflix, Super Mario at GDC</title><description>... era. But since this is a GDC keynote, he is also expected to drop some big news about Nintendo 3DS... of the future. Selfishly, I hope people decide the next must-have is the Nintendo 3DS. Laughs.9:31 Nintendo selected the pre-installed software on the 3DS for...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7053-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7053_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:17:36">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/01/nintendo-confirms-3ds-content-locked-to-single-system-no-transfers/</link><title>Nintendo confirms 3DS content locked to single system, no transfers</title><description>...The good news about buying a Nintendo 3DS is that you'll be able to transfer your digital purchases from your DS system to your 3DS using an SD card, and Nintendo will be giving us more details..., is that restricted to that 3DS that I purchased it on?Trinen: That would be simil...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7053-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7053_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:19:00">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/03/fear-of-a-social-planet-how-nintendo-failed-with-3ds-friend-codes/</link><title>Fear of a social planet: how Nintendo failed with 3DS friend codes</title><description>...Now that the Nintendo 3DS has been released and gamers are picking up their systems, many of us... we can communicate. Yes, the 360 is a console while the 3DS is a portable, but Nintendo needs... with people we know. The 3DS has gotten rid of the per-game friend codes that were so an...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7053-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7053_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:21:43">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/03/a-beautiful-screen-a-weak-battery-a-door-to-the-future-ars-reviews-the-nintendo-3ds/</link><title>A beautiful screen, a weak battery, a door to the future: Ars reviews the Nintendo 3DS</title><description>...-on with the 3DS and experience a working 3D technology that didn't require glasses, I knew that Nintendo... of portable gaming devices. At $250, the 3DS isn't cheap, but Nintendo has to be tired of seeing.... The hardwareNintendo isn't exactly tripping over itself to share the exact tech sp...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7053-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7053_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:23:06">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/01/nintendo-3ds-to-max-out-at-five-hours-of-play-in-3d/</link><title>Nintendo 3DS to max out at five hours of play in 3D</title><description>...The Nintendo 3DS was a hit at E3 when it was first shown to an adoring public, and the 3D effect is both powerful and, well, effective. Nintendo has released the full technical specifications... battery life is one of the major pluses of that platform. Surely this is an area where Nintendo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7053-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7053_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:25:36">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/02/3ds-games/</link><title>Nintendo announces $40 3DS launch games, new 2011 Mario Kart</title><description>...The Nintendo 3DS is coming to the United States on March 27 for $250. We've known that for a while, but today Nintendo has released the official list of launch titles, which will be sold for $40... by. Anecdotally, my son just asked if we'd be getting a 3DS, so the 9 year-old crowd is talking...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7053-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7053_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:26:29">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/11/nintendo-under-fire-why-the-3ds-could-take-off-during-the-holidays/</link><title>Nintendo under fire: why the 3DS could take off during the holidays</title><description>... is that it's so often wrong. Despite soft sales on the Nintendo Wii and a slow start with the 3DS... it bluntly, make or break time for the 3DS, and Nintendo is coming out swinging.Nintendo.... Nintendo has stated that the 3DS sold 250,000 units in Octobe...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7053-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7053_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:28:05">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/01/nintendo-3ds-hits-shelves-march-27-for-249/</link><title>Nintendo 3DS hits shelves March 27 for $249: more details inside</title><description>...The Nintendo 3DS will be on available starting March 27 for $249, Nintendo announced at a press... games for the glassesless 3D handheld at the event. The 3Ds will initially be available in two colors: aqua blue and black. The game card slot on the back will accept both 3DS and DS ga...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7053-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7053_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:32:23">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/09/3ds-hits-japan-on-february-26-for-300-comes-to-us-in-march-1/</link><title>3DS hits Japan on February 26 for $300, comes to US in March</title><description>...Nintendo released a metric ton of official details on the 3DS at a press conference in Tokyo last night, including the Japanese release date (February 26, 2011) and price of 25,000 (about $300). The North American release date isn't as exact: we'll see the system in March of next year. The final version of the hardware was also shown, although the only difference from the systems we use...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>