<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7054">yarra valley sightseeing</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:35:18" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7054-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7054_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:35:19">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/04/review-a-valley-without-wind-remembers-a-new-past/</link><title>Review: A Valley Without Wind remembers a new past</title><description>..., I changed my world. A Valley Without Wind pc Release Date:Now MSRP:$14.99 Official site A Valley... teleport or summon a tornado to blow you to a new location.A Valley without Wind trailer Despite the wide...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7054-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7054_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:36:49">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/09/thanks-to-budget-cuts-silicon-valley-patent-office-wont-open/</link><title>Budget cuts mean Silicon Valley patent office won’t open anytime soon</title><description>... will be that agency's plan to open an office in Silicon Valley in the near future, according to a Sunday report by The Associated Press. The Silicon Valley office was an idea that has been suggested for years... Valley area with as many as 150 new examiners. Still, it's unclear when that might actually occur...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7054-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7054_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:38:20">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/10/short-star-wars-precursor-film-repremieres-will-come-to-netflix-itunes-in-2014/</link><title>Short that aired pre- Empire Strikes Back will come to Netflix, iTunes in 2014</title><description>... 2014.Christian attended a Black Angelscreeningat the Mill Valley Film Festival andtold The Los Angeles...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7054-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7054_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:41:09">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/06/the-savannah-fund-lays-a-pipe-from-east-africa-to-silicon-valley/</link><title>The Savannah Fund brings Silicon Valley to East Africa</title><description>... is also being backed by Silicon Valley players, includingYelp's Russ Simmons, Zynga'sDali Kilani,Tim Draper, Dave McClure, and Roger Dickey. This Silicon Valley connection gives the fund not just proven international expertise but it also puts the shine on the apple. Silicon Valley, however...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7054-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7054_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:43:09">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/05/silicon-valley-donations-to-obama-reach-record-levels/</link><title>Silicon Valley donations to Obama reach record levels</title><description>...Last week, President Barack Obama swung through Silicon Valley, taking in nearly $13 million... or more from Silicon Valley through this point in 2008 but only 6,400 so far in this election cycle... executives from his company to max out to Obama."Not surprisingly, the Valley largely swings...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7054-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7054_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:44:34">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/08/google-wifi-lawsuits-head-to-silicon-valley/</link><title>Google WiFi lawsuits head to Silicon Valley</title><description>...Whether Google is liable for damages for secretly intercepting data on open WiFi routers across the United States is to be aired out in a Silicon Valley federal court.Eight proposed class-actions... were collecting.The Panel on Multidistrict Litigation said it chose Silicon Valley because "Google...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7054-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7054_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:46:33">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2008/11/dash-express-woes-highlight-silicon-valley-challenges/</link><title>Dash Express woes highlight Silicon Valley challenges</title><description>... forced to change course, will soon become par for the course here in Silicon Valley, as the regions... announcement serves as a reminder that the problems here in Silicon Valley are more than just...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7054-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7054_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:49:03">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/11/san-jose-city-hall-to-be-permanent-home-for-silicon-valley-patent-office/</link><title>San Jose City Hall to be permanent home for Silicon Valley patent office</title><description>... and Trademark Office (USPTO).Further ReadingBudget cuts mean Silicon Valley patent office wont open... location for the Silicon Valley patent office. That choice makes sense as the city has been the site... Valley Office Director Michelle Lee and nine PTAB judges will continue working from that location...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7054-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7054_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:51:36">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/11/long-time-googler-will-head-silicon-valley-patent-office/</link><title>Long-time Googler will head Silicon Valley patent office</title><description>... about software patents, sponsored by Santa Clara University.Lee is a Silicon Valley native who grew... Journal earlier this year. She left a partnership at Fenwick West, a well-known Silicon Valley law...;The Silicon Valley office is one of three satellite offices to be opened, with the other two opening...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7054-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7054_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:52:11">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/02/in-bid-for-credibility-largest-bitcoin-exchange-moves-to-silicon-valley/</link><title>In bid for credibility, largest Bitcoin exchange moves to Silicon Valley</title><description>...The world's leading Bitcoin exchange, Mt. Gox, has announced a partnership with the Silicon Valley startup CoinLab. Under the agreement, CoinLab will handle Mt. Gox's American operations... allowed the firm to score a partnership with Silicon Valley Bank. That will allow the firm to offer...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>