<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7057">web of science</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:26:01" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7057-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7057_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:26:02">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2014/03/web-inventor-tim-berners-lee-calls-for-digital-magna-carta/</link><title>Web inventor Tim Berners-Lee calls for digital “Magna Carta”</title><description>... that would become the World Wide Web, a whip-smart young computer scientist named Al GoreTim Berners-Lee... have strained the open architecture of the Web, jeopardizing the independence, neutrality, and freedom upon which the system was originally built.In an attempt to democratically reclaim the Web from corporate...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7057-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7057_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:26:36">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/03/android-fragmentation-also-a-challenge-for-web-developers/</link><title>Android fragmentation also a challenge for Web developers</title><description>... the pain. A prominent Web developer has recently drawn attention to the challenges that Android version fragmentation poses for mobile Web development.As we explained in some of our recent Android browser coverage, the platform's default Web browser has historically not been very good at handling...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7057-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7057_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:29:19">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/03/100-hours-of-astronomy-with-a-telescope-a-world-away/</link><title>100 Hours of Astronomy with a telescope a world away</title><description>... is a web interface that allows visitors access to a handful of powerful telescopes around the world. Online... interested, they don't dumb down the science. The only downside to the SLOOH service that I...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7057-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7057_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:30:02">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/02/facebook-and-others-aim-to-make-the-mobile-web-a-competitive-app-platform/</link><title>Facebook and others aim to make the mobile Web a competitive app platform</title><description>...A coalition of 30 technology companies hopes to turn the Web into a competitive platform for building mobile applications. They have launched a Core Mobile Web Platform (coremob) community group through the W3C to provide a venue for collaborating on next-generation mobile Web standards.Facebook...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7057-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7057_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:33:47">http://arstechnica.com/staff/2013/08/applying-science-to-communicate-science/</link><title>Applying science to communicate science</title><description>...Anybody who communicates for a living faces a certain degree of frustration. No matter how hard you try, some people just don't get the intended message. For areas like politics and economics, this typically means that some people don't buy in to your interpretation of things. But when it comes to science, the failures end up involving an inability to convey basic facts. No matter how h...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7057-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7057_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:36:56">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/01/considering-the-future-of-science-journalism/</link><title>Considering the future of science journalism</title><description>.... Will the Web ultimately provide a killing blow or the resurrection of science journalism? I'll be given...I started my research career in what may have been the first and only age of science journalism. Newspapers were big and growing, and many had dedicated science sections; magazines like Scientif...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7057-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7057_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:37:30">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/01/microsoft-asks-open-source-developers-to-play-in-web-sandbox/</link><title>Microsoft asks open source developers to play in Web Sandbox</title><description>...Microsoft has announced plans to release the code of its Web Sandbox project under the open source... to interoperable standards-based Web technologies and also demonstrates the company's willingness to adopt well-established open source licenses for its own projects.The Web Sandbox project aims...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7057-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7057_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:39:02">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/10/web-served-the-finale-congrats-you-have-a-web-server-whats-next/</link><title>Web Served, the finale: Congrats, you have a Web server! What’s next?</title><description>...?Modern Web analytics is a highly refined science, and there are tons of vendors that will help you get...Welcome, dear readers, to the final piece in our long-running "Web Served" series. Starting last November, Ars has been helping to shed light on the fun world of DIY Web hostingwe started...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7057-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7057_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:42:22">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/10/web-tracking-firm-settles-charges-it-collected-passwords-financial-data/</link><title>Web tracking firm settles charges it collected passwords, financial data</title><description>...A Web analytics company that tracked the browsing behavior of millions of US consumers has agreed to settle federal charges that it collected credit card numbers, financial account information, and other sensitive data without proper notice.Boston, Massachusetts-based Compete Inc. agreed to obtain...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7057-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7057_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:46:34">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/05/whats-responsive-web-design-all-about/</link><title>What's responsive Web design all about?</title><description>...When you consider how many different tablets, laptops, Web browsers, and operating systems access the Internet on a day-to-day basis, it's a small miracle that Web designers and developers manage to stay sane. There are, of course, Web standards and entire organizations that exist for the sole...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>