<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7059">doctor Amsterdam</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:20:20" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7059-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7059_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:20:21">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/08/pop-culture-psa-bbcs-doctor-who-gets-peter-capaldi-to-play-the-12th-doctor/</link><title>Pop culture PSA: BBC’s Doctor Who gets Peter Capaldi to play the 12 th Doctor</title><description>...On Sunday, the BBC announced the new lead of the Doctor Who series in a special live broadcast... The Thick of It, a satire in which the actor plays a political party's spin-doctor. Capaldi also appeared in the 2008 Doctor Who episode The Fires of Pompeii, playing Caecilius, a Roman Merchant...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7059-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7059_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:23:53">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/03/doctors-try-to-silence-negative-reviews-from-patients/</link><title>Doctors try to silence negative reviews from patients</title><description>...Like donut shop owners, city councilmen, and smalltown gossip victims, doctors aren't terribly...;t taking the lawsuit routeat least not yet. Instead, doctors are asking patients to sign agreements... to have the reviews removed if they break the gag order.In fact, these doctors are going so far...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7059-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7059_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:26:36">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/03/how-amsterdam-was-wired-for-open-access-fiber/</link><title>How Amsterdam was wired for open access fiber</title><description>...The city of Amsterdam has been involved for several years in building Citynet, a partnership between the city and two private investors to wire 40,000 Amsterdam buildings with fiber. And it's not just fiber, it's open access fiberany ISP can sign up to use the infrastructure and deliver ultra-fast Internet access.In 2008, the European Union ruled that the city's involvement in the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7059-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7059_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:29:32">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/04/the-phd-problem-what-do-you-do-with-too-many-doctorates/</link><title>The PhD problem: are we giving out too many degrees?</title><description>... percent since 1998, reaching about 34,000 doctorates in 2008. This type of expansion sounds great... responded by offering rewards of about 4 million yen (or $47,000) to companies willing to hire doctoral... sciences and physical sciences alone, our universities bestowed nearly 20,000 doctorate degrees in 2009...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7059-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7059_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:30:46">http://arstechnica.com/science/2008/10/half-of-us-doctors-prescribe-placebos/</link><title>Half of US doctors prescribe placebos</title><description>... the use of placebos by doctors in the US. Nearly 700 MDs took part, evenly distributed between...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7059-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7059_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:33:05">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/05/doctors-save-babys-life-with-3d-printed-tracheal-implant/</link><title>Doctors save baby’s life with 3D-printed tracheal implant</title><description>...In an article published in the New England Journal of Medicine today, two doctors from the University of Michigan described how they saved an infant with a life-threatening respiratory disorder using...;s doctors to consult on the case. He and Dr. Scott Hollister, Ph.D., a professor of biomedical...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7059-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7059_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:35:44">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/03/mississippi-doctors-functionally-cure-a-toddler-of-hiv/</link><title>Mississippi doctors “functionally cure” a toddler of HIV</title><description>...Mississippi doctors are reporting they have "functionally cured" a two-year-old child of HIV, according to findings presented at the Conference on Retroviruses and Opportunistic Infections (CROI) today. "Functionally cured" in this scenario means the child is now without...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7059-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7059_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:39:15">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/04/celebrate-a-wibbly-wobbly-timey-wimey-50-years-of-dr-who-with-ars/</link><title>Celebrate a wibbly-wobbly, timey-wimey 50 years of Doctor Who with Ars</title><description>...Doctor Who has been around for 50 years. You read that correctly. Thats a whole half of a century... and forward in time. The Doctor has changed in appearance many times in his tenure on the air, but one thing... is giving away two sets of Doctor Who merchandise to two lucky people. Heres what youll find in each...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7059-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7059_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:40:15">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/03/majority-of-doctors-opposed-to-full-access-to-your-own-electronic-records/</link><title>Majority of doctors opposed to full access to your own electronic records</title><description>... records, you might think doctors and other caregivers would embrace transparency for patients... a recent survey by Harris Interactive,reported first at Computerworld,reveals that doctors aren't big fans of full transparency. A survey of 3,700 doctors in eight countries showed that only 31 percent...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7059-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7059_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:43:45">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/05/all-your-reviews-are-belong-to-us-medical-justice-vs-patient-free-speech/</link><title>Doctors and dentists tell patients, "all your review are belong to us"</title><description>... them from speaking out. And in any event, the fact that a doctor would try to gag his patients... Justice was taking advantage of medical professionals' lack of sophistication about the law. Doctors... his patients to sign.In any event, we think censoring patients is the wrong way for doctors to deal...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>