<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7060">jobs IBCN</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:44:18" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7060-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7060_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:44:19">http://arstechnica.com/staff/2013/08/announcing-arsjobs-our-new-jobs-board/</link><title>Announcing Ars/Jobs, our new jobs board</title><description>... for job seekers, we launched our first jobs board several years ago. Today, ArsTechnica is proud to announce the launch of Ars/Jobs, our most robust and extensive jobs board ever.With Ars/Jobs, we intend... recruitment network of jobs sites and search engines,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7060-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7060_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:45:34">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2011/11/why-steve-jobs-cried/</link><title>Why Steve Jobs cried</title><description>..., Jobs cried over just about everything. He cried at the beginning of Apple after Woz's father pushed his son to take more ownership of the company because he thought Jobs wasn't doing much work. Jobs went over to Woz's home and bawled his eyes out. Woz kept him on.Jobs cried...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7060-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7060_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:48:45">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/01/for-steve-jobs-we-expect-one-more-thing/</link><title>For Steve Jobs, we expect One More Thing</title><description>...Apples Tim Cook, Steve Jobs, and Phil Schiller Being the CEO of a publicly traded, massively... of personal privacy: your medical history. Reporters chase after Jobs medical privacy and spin tales about it in ways they hope never get applied to them. The current three-ring circus started after Jobs...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7060-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7060_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:51:23">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/06/jobs-spotted-back-on-campus-leave-may-be-over/</link><title>Jobs spotted back on campus, leave may be over</title><description>...After six months of being on leave due to unspecified health matters, Apple CEO Steve Jobs may be back to work. Numerous sources, includingReuters and The Mac Observer, are reporting that Jobs... in limited capacity.Steve Jobs took temporary leave in January of this year after months of speculation...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7060-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7060_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:52:12">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/02/happy-54th-steve-jobs/</link><title>Happy 54th, Steve Jobs</title><description>...Though still (hopefully) enjoying his hiatus from full-time CEO duty at Apple, Steve Jobs turns 54 years young today.I really wanted to get Steve a present, but what do you get a guy who runs Apple, runs Pixar, and is the biggest shareholder of Disney? A Gulfstream V jet? Well, he already...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7060-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7060_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:54:33">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/12/analyst-a-post-jobs-era-is-looming/</link><title>Analyst: A post-Jobs era is looming</title><description>...On the heels of the Apples announcement that Steve Jobs will not be giving the keynote... speculate that Munsters conclusion might have been drawn from Jobs previous bout with cancer... is not necessarily indicative of Jobs health. While he doesnt rule out Jobs health as the reason for the move...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7060-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7060_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:56:10">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2011/10/biographer-steve-jobs-regretted-not-having-cancer-surgery-earlier/</link><title>Biographer: Steve Jobs regretted not having cancer surgery earlier</title><description>...It's well-known that Steve Jobs put off surgery to treat his pancreatic cancer for nine months... [Jobs why he didn't get an operation then] and he said, "I didn't want my body... on sooner."Isaacson also reveals that Jobs continued to receive treatment for the cancer while...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7060-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7060_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:00:09">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/12/analyst-says-jobs-views-are-now-endemic-to-apple/</link><title>Analyst says Jobs' views are now endemic to Apple</title><description>...Now that the announcements about the Jobs-less Macworld 2009 keynote and the Apple-less Macworld... Jobs role at Apple. In a recent research note covered by AppleInsider, Kaufman Brothers analyst Shaw Wu opined that, although Jobs himself has done a massive amount of work for the company...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7060-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7060_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:04:17">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2011/01/apple-ceo-steve-jobs-back-on-medical-leave/</link><title>Apple CEO Steve Jobs back on medical leave</title><description>...Steve Jobs announced Monday morning that he is taking an indefinite medical leave from his duties... diagnosed with a rare form of pancreatic cancer in 2003.In 2004, Jobs underwent a complicated... the procedure is highly successful for the form of pancreatic cancer that Jobs had, it also removes much...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7060-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7060_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:05:55">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/01/steve-jobs-health-complex-on-medical-leave-through-june/</link><title>Steve Jobs on leave from Apple over "complex" health issues</title><description>...Apple CEO Steve Jobs health issues are more complex than he originally thought, leading him to take... this afternoon, Steve Jobs acknowledged that concerns about his health continue to act as a distraction... will be in charge until Steve Jobs return this summer. The letter, in full, reads as follows: Team, I am sure...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>