<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7061">startup advisors chicago</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:07:48" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7061-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7061_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:07:49">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/10/uber-under-fire-from-regulators-and-competitors-in-chicago/</link><title>Uber under fire from regulators and competitors in Chicago</title><description>...Uber, a startup that allows you to hail a car from your smartphone, is facing a fresh round of legal trouble, this time in Chicago. The Chicago Tribune reports that regulators have charged... a portion of that amount. Uber also faces lawsuits from its Chicago-based competitors, who claim...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7061-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7061_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:08:50">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/11/uber-says-chicago-is-trying-to-drive-its-sedans-out-of-the-city/</link><title>Uber says Chicago is trying to drive its sedans out of the city</title><description>...The battle between the city of Chicago and Uber, a startup seeking to disrupt the taxi and limo... for taxis conflicted with Chicago regulations. Now the city is introducing new regulations for Uber's separate sedan service that the company says could force it out of the Chicago market.Uber...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7061-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7061_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:12:46">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/02/week-in-science-its-cold-in-chicago-edition/</link><title>Week in Science: it's cold in Chicago edition</title><description>...The biggest happening in science this past week was the annual meeting of the American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS). AAAS is the world's largest scientific society, and John Timmer, Tim De Chant, and I braved the freezing cold of Chicago in February (and the total lack...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7061-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7061_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:14:05">http://arstechnica.com/business/2014/02/liquid-cooling-startup-iceotope-talks-about-the-basics-of-its-business/</link><title>Liquid cooling startup Iceotope talks about the basics of its business</title><description>...Iceotope has developed an efficient liquid cooling technology that allows supercomputers and data centers in the UK, and even in hot equatorial regions, to run as efficiently as those based the Arctic Circle. Iceotope's system was modeled using computational fluid dynamics, and eliminates the need for air conditioning units and fans to carry heat away. Wired.co.uk spoke to founder Peter Hopt...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7061-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7061_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:19:03">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/12/accidents-increase-at-chicago-red-light-camera-intersections/</link><title>Accidents increase at Chicago red light camera intersections</title><description>...The Chicago suburbs are buying into the red light camera movement, but the results are not very.... The Chicago Tribune put together a handy page that contains yearly accident data for every red light camera installed in the Chicago metropolitan area from 2006 and 2007. According to the data, the first...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7061-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7061_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:21:15">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/09/pre-wired-nextfest-ars-party-in-chicago-september-24/</link><title>Ars Party in Chicago: pre-NextFest beerfest on Sept 24</title><description>... Technica is headquartered here in Chicago, we thought wed throw a swanky mixer before NextFest for our readers, our local staff, and Chicago press to attend. Weve already invited a few of the local tech... are the pertinent details: Location: Lumen - 839 W. Fulton, Chicago, IL When: The event takes place Wednesday...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7061-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7061_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:21:59">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2014/02/ars-goes-to-the-chicago-auto-show/</link><title>Ars goes to the Chicago Auto Show</title><description>...The Chicago Auto Show bills itself as the "nation's largest auto show." There's certainly room for it to be the largest show of its kind in the US, as it takes place in McCormick Place, which is the largest convention center in North America. And the Chicago Auto Show is definitely big, using 1 million square feet of McCormick Place's 2.7 million square feet of available...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7061-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7061_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:24:28">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/10/startups-aboard-icebreaker-ship-could-face-eviction-soon-san-francisco-says/</link><title>Startups aboard “Icebreaker” ship could face eviction soon, San Francisco says</title><description>... that's been a startup incubator over the last two years. (It was first tricked out to be used... a unique workspace where startups contributing hundreds of millions of dollars to the city's economy... investors, advisors, and some of our first customers through the Icebreaker community. As you can see...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7061-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7061_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:28:13">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/03/surge-in-tech-hubs-give-african-startups-a-place-to-grow/</link><title>Surge in tech hubs give African startups a place to grow</title><description>...When Startup Garage Nairobi opened its doors last month in the Kenyan capital, it became the latest... (with investment as the prize), first in Prague, then, twice so far, in Kenya."The Startup Garage was the next step to make," Buch told Ars, "to bring together the African startups, to create...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7061-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7061_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:30:36">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/08/chip-veterans-form-new-startup-will-sell-high-end-bitcoin-miner-for-16000/</link><title>Chip veterans form new startup, will sell high-end Bitcoin miner for $14,000</title><description>...On Tuesday, a new Bitcoin startup called CoinTerraannounced that it raised $1.5 million in venture capital. This likely puts the company in a position to dominate the Bitcoin hardware marketassuming it can come through on its promises.Earlier this month, CoinTerra revealed the TerraMiner IV, a two...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>