<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7063">Spanish unemployment</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:53:43" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7063-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7063_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:53:44">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/02/new-online-job-listings-cratered-since-december/</link><title>New online job listings have cratered since December</title><description>...; currently, only North Dakota and Wyoming are offering more jobs than the official number of unemployed... are clearly making it increasingly hard for those who are unemployed to find new positions, said Gad Levanon, Senior Economist at The Conference Board. An expected increase in the unemployment numbers...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7063-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7063_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:56:38">http://arstechnica.com/security/2008/12/recession-could-trigger-blackhat-boom-crimeware-surge/</link><title>Report: recession could trigger blackhat, crimeware surge</title><description>..., citing it as evidence of an early trend of unemployed IT personnel finding new and easy income... studies into the relationship between poverty, unemployment, recession, and crime for decades... positive correlation between unemployment and crime, the correlation between the two can vary considerably...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7063-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7063_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:58:12">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/07/police-raid-spanish-collecting-society-in-embezzlement-case/</link><title>Police raid Spanish copyright society in embezzlement case</title><description>... performances of music and distributes them to artists and record companies.)According to Spanish... subsidiary called the Digital Society of Spanish Authors (SDAE).Neri faces charges of "fraud... have been taken and they are barred from leaving Spain.SGAE, the Spanish counterpart to American collecting...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7063-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7063_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:58:40">http://arstechnica.com/security/2010/03/spanish-arrests-mark-the-end-of-dangerous-botnet/</link><title>Spanish arrests mark the end of dangerous botnet</title><description>...A massive botnet of up to 12.7 million infected PCs has been dismantled after Spanish police... servers based in Spain, and so joined forces with Spanish firm Panda Security. With their input...;s harvesting of financial information made it much more dangerous.The hackers themselvesunnamed, per Spanish...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7063-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7063_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:01:06">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/08/seized-domain-owner-government-hasnt-a-leg-to-stand-on/</link><title>Spanish site claims forfeiture of link sites is illegal</title><description>...Puerto 80, the Spanish company that owns the Rojadirecta sporting website, has asked a federal judge to dismiss the government's forfeiture of its domain names. Calling the seizure "an unprecedented effort to expand both copyright liability and the reaches of civil forfeiture law," the firm argued that only direct infringement, not linking to infringing content, could be the basis...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7063-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7063_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:01:49">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2008/12/copyright-cop-wedding-crashers-fined-by-spanish-court/</link><title>Copyright cop wedding crashers fined by Spanish court</title><description>...The next time you have a wedding, make sure your videographer isnt a secret spy for the RIAA or similar copyright group. This real-life scenario happened to a couple in Spain thanks to the efforts of the Spanish General Society of Authors and Editors (SGAE), a rights group for musicians and artists...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7063-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7063_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:05:02">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/01/nobody-expects-the-spanish-inquisitionto-make-on-youtube/</link><title>Nobody expects the Spanish Inquisition--to make $$ on YouTube</title><description>...Monty Python isn't quite dead. The aging comedy troupe, which still flogs DVDs of its decades-old TV show and subsequent films with the dedication of a Spanish Inquisitor, has a new gambit for the digital age: put all of the most popular material on YouTube, free of charge... and make a ton...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7063-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7063_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:07:49">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/07/wikileaks-hires-noted-spanish-judge-to-defend-julian-assange/</link><title>WikiLeaks hires noted Spanish judge to defend Julian Assange</title><description>...WikiLeaks and Julian Assange have selected Spanish judge and lawyerBaltasar Garznto head their new legal team.In June 2012, Assange lost his appeal in the United Kingdom to avoid beingextradited..., the Spanish Supreme Court found Garzn guilty of illegally ordering wiretaps in Spanish jails...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7063-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7063_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:08:21">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/02/spanish-police-bust-alleged-ransomware-ring-that-took-in-1-34m-annually/</link><title>Spanish police bust alleged “ransomware” ring that took in $1.34M annually</title><description>...Spanish authorities announced Wednesday that they had arrested 10 people who were allegedly... ($1.34 million) per year."The Spanish Ministry of the Interior described (Google Translate.... (Spanish authorities posted a video (RAR) of the new arrests and raid.)Madrid dubbedthe ransomware...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7063-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7063_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:09:21">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/12/spanish-site-taking-our-domain-was-unconstitutional-prior-restraint/</link><title>Spanish site: seizing our domain was unconstitutional prior restraint</title><description>...This week has seen two developments in the case of RojaDirecta.com, the Spanish sports domain that the US federal government seized almost a year ago based on allegations that the site was promoting links to illegal streams of sporting events. On Tuesday, Puerto 80, the owner of the domain, filed...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>