<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7066">awk trim non-printable characters</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:53:52" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7066-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7066_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:53:54">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/the-road-to-gouken-in-defense-of-unlocking-characters/</link><title>The road to Gouken: in defense of unlocking characters</title><description>... as gamers everywhere buckle down and get to unlocking all the characters. This could be a simple process.... Unlocking all the characters in Street Fighter IV lands somewhere in the middle.I was one of the loud... the arcade stick back and forth as we discussed each character we played in turn. We didn't run...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7066-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7066_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:54:31">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/04/bioware-only-we-can-create-gay-star-wars-characters/</link><title>Bioware: only we can create gay Star Wars characters</title><description>..., transgendered or bisexual characters were shut down.The curt response from community manager Sean Dahlberg... Bioware fans know that while the terms may not exist in Star Wars, gay and lesbian characters certainly... lover. Juhanni would respond to your character romantically if you were a woman. So Bioware...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7066-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7066_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:54:54">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/01/askars-solid-state-drives-and-garbage-collection/</link><title>Ask Ars: Of solid state drives and garbage collection</title><description>... around. TRIM is a command that an OS can issue to help the SSDs realize they have this deleted data problem and fix it. An OS with TRIM support is able to tell an SSD to mark a deleted file..., so that it doesn't get kept around for an inordinate amount of time. TRIM can be a big speed-saver...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7066-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7066_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:55:55">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/the-road-to-gouken-part-2-capcom-posts-instructions/</link><title>The road to Gouken part 2: Capcom posts instructions</title><description>... all the characters in a post yesterday. Capcom has since updated its official blog with the real...;s no less tricky.So how does one unlock these elusive characters? It's a combination of perfects..., and then win all your matches with no continues and losses with a character you've already...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7066-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7066_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:57:08">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/10/google-turns-on-ocr-for-scanned-pdfs/</link><title>Google turns on OCR for scanned PDFs</title><description>... Google Blog, the company is now performing optical character recognition (OCR) on documents...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7066-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7066_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:01:18">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/more-characters-for-sf-iv-depends-on-demand/</link><title>More characters for SF IV? Depends on demand</title><description>..., delightful graphics, and a good selection of characters. However, hardcore Street Fighter fans are already grumbling that some of their favorite characters didn't make it into the game... case in point..., Capcom has revealed that a number of characters might actually be delivered to the game...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7066-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7066_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:04:50">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/03/game-characters-are-better-when-they-gossip-and-lie/</link><title>Game characters are better when they gossip and lie</title><description>...Getting characters to lie, gossip, and manipulate could help to create more realistic video games... has been working on models to introduce socially competent non-player game characters who can understand natural language, rather than characters using goal-driven dialogue where the player is limited...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7066-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7066_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:05:54">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/06/a-character-not-a-voice-tuning-the-narration-in-bastion/</link><title>A character, not a voice: tuning the narration in Bastion</title><description>... word. Kasavin wanted to sure assure us that the narration was provided by a character, not just...," he continued. "The narrator is a character, not just a voice."Each lined was tuned...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7066-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7066_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:08:29">http://arstechnica.com/security/2013/04/why-your-password-cant-have-symbols-or-be-longer-than-16-characters/</link><title>Why your password can’t have symbols—or be longer than 16 characters</title><description>... with unfamiliar social customs. This one requires eight characters; that one lets you have up to 64... company Charles Schwab has strict length limitspasswords can be no longer than eight characters... than 16 and no shorter than eight characters. Microsoft says that most attacks on accounts cannot...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7066-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7066_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:09:32">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/02/heavy-rain-characters-and-actors/</link><title>Reality blurs between Heavy Rain characters and actors</title><description>...Heavy Rain relies on its characters to deliver much of the gravity and story of the game, but what you might not know is that the actors often provided both the sound and the face of their characters... just how much the character models look like the actors. The resemblance is frightening...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>