<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7067">used kindle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:11:09" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7067-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7067_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:11:10">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/07/kindle-textbook-rentals-arrive-used-can-still-be-cheaper/</link><title>Kindle textbook rentals arrive; used can still be cheaper</title><description>... of using a Kindle textbook over the real thingespecially if you have to flip to the answers in the back... with a new Amazon rental program that gets them up to 80 percent off list prices. Kindle Textbook Rental allows students to rent textbooks and read them via the free Kindle reading apps, with book an...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7067-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7067_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:13:07">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/08/advertisements-may-lead-to-a-cheaper-kindle-fire/</link><title>Advertisements may lead to a cheaper Kindle Fire</title><description>...The next version of Amazon's Kindle Fire tablet may use advertisements to lower its price to consumers, sources have told the Wall Street Journal. According to the sources, the advertisements would appear on-screen after the user wakes the tablet from sleep.Amazon's E Ink Kindles have already been using a similar strategy for quite some timeboth the Kindle and Kindle Touch are offered i...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7067-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7067_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:14:58">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/09/a-first-look-at-amazons-new-kindles/</link><title>Hands-on with Amazon's new Kindles</title><description>... revamped its Kindle line and introduced a new mobile browser that relies on Amazon's content... was extremely guarded about its new hardware; the only device we were allowed to pick up and use is that low-end Kindle, which is supposed to be shipping already. The new Kindle Touch could barely...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7067-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7067_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:16:05">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/09/amazon-to-unveil-199-70inch-kindle-fire-tablet/</link><title>Amazon unveils $199 Android Kindle Fire tablet, $99 e-ink Kindle Touch</title><description>... Kindle Touch weighs 5.98 ounces and does not have a capacitive screen; instead, it uses infrared...Amazon has announced a new tablet called the Kindle Fire and a $99 Kindle Touch at a press event today in NYC. Like the successful Kindle e-reader, the Kindle To...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7067-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7067_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:18:51">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/04/amazon-releases-send-to-kindle-desktop-software-for-the-mac/</link><title>Amazon releases "Send to Kindle" desktop software for the Mac</title><description>... to Amazon, users can also use the Mac software to archive documents in your Kindle library...More than three months after releasing software for Windows-users to send documents to a Kindle, Amazon has now released the Mac version. Announced on Tuesday afternoon, the "Send to Kindle...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7067-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7067_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:22:08">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/11/ars-hands-on-the-kindle-touch/</link><title>Yes, that's a button! The Kindle Touch reviewed</title><description>... experience on the Kindle. Getting used to reading that material on the responsive color screens of tablets has made it seem even worse in comparison. You can use a Kindle for something other than books...When Amazon introduced its most recent crop of Kindles, the company kept the de...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7067-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7067_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:25:55">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/10/adventures-in-rooting-running-jelly-bean-on-last-years-kindle-fire/</link><title>Adventures in rooting: Running Jelly Bean on last year's Kindle Fire</title><description>...;ve got bad news for you: none of the improvements made to the software used by the 2012 Kindle Fire... Android experience, which makes using our rooted Kindle Fire more or less identical to using... Kindle Fire gave us our first chance to compare it directly t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7067-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7067_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:28:18">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/03/kindle-2-hacks-bypassing-whispernet/</link><title>Kindle 2 hacks: bypassing Whispernet</title><description>...Whispernet is one of the Kindle's most appreciated features. With it, you can download books anywhere in Sprint's US high-speed data network coverage area. But should you leave that network or step outside the United States, you lose your connection to that anywhere/anytime download service. Now Kindle-expert Jesse Vincent has worked out a way to let you connect your Kindle directly to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7067-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7067_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:29:36">http://arstechnica.com/staff/2009/03/ars-sxsw-win-a-kindle-2/</link><title>Ars @ SXSW: Win a Kindle 2</title><description>...Just wanted to give everyone a heads up on this little promotion. If you're at SXSW you might have picked up a card telling you to email us to enter, as we're giving away a brand, spanking new Kindle 2\. All you have to do to win is email us an Ars article that taught you something...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7067-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7067_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:32:22">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/09/kindles-are-shown-the-automatic-sliding-door-at-walmart/</link><title>Kindles are shown the automatic sliding door at Walmart</title><description>...Walmart will no longer carry Amazon's Kindles, the retail chain announced Thursday. Walmart...;s announcement of a slate of new Kindle products, including a line of Kindle Fire HDs and the Kindle Paperwhite. Given that the chain will continue to sell competitors to these Kindle ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>