<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7068">Speech and Language Processing: An Introduction to Natural Language Processing, Computational Linguistics, and Speech Recognition</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:35:16" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7068-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7068_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:35:17">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/02/lol-texting-and-txt-speak-linguistic-miracles/</link><title>LOL, texting, and txt-speak: Linguistic miracles</title><description>...LONG BEACH, CAIs texting shorthand a convenience, a catastrophe for the English language, or actually something new and special? John McWhorter, a linguist at Columbia University, sides with the latter. According to McWhorter, texting is actually a new form of speech, and he outlined the reasons why today at the TED2013 conference in Southern California.We often hear that texting is a scourge, da...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7068-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7068_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:38:19">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/06/google-launches-endangered-language-project/</link><title>Google launches Endangered Language Project</title><description>...Today, Google announced the launch of the Endangered Language Project, "a website for people to find and share the most up-to-date and comprehensive information about endangered languages." The project was built in conjunction with the Alliance for Language Diversity.Google and its partners hope the Endangered Language Project will help by providing "an online resource to record, a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7068-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7068_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:41:30">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/05/kids-learn-language-from-other-kids/</link><title>Kids learn language from other kids</title><description>...Childrenpick up language skills at a variety of speeds. Some master a large vocabulary of words... not only from listening to adults, but also from the language skills of their peers. It was thought that most language skills are either learned at home, as children listen to a parent talk to them...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7068-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7068_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:44:35">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/06/language-in-space-language-and-orientation-skills-correlate/</link><title>Language in space: language and orientation skills correlate</title><description>... spatial orientation tasks is tied in with a rather recent development: language. Unfortunately, language ability and spatial reasoning both improve as we mature, and language use is associated with many... have now taken advantage of a rare situation to test how language development impacts spatial...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7068-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7068_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:45:16">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/04/thinking-in-foreign-language-makes-decisions-more-rational/</link><title>Thinking in foreign language makes decisions more rational</title><description>... of experiments on more than 300 people from the US and Korea found that thinking in a second language reduced...;Would you make the same decisions in a foreign language as you would in your native tongue?" asked... study."It may be intuitive that people would make the same choices regardless of the language...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7068-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7068_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:48:55">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/05/my-favorite-programming-language-googles-go-has-some-coders-raving/</link><title>“My favorite programming language:” Google’s Go has some coders raving</title><description>... every language under the sun."But it was only recently that Kuehnl discovered Go, a programming language unveiled by Google almost four years ago. Go is still a new kid on the block, but for Kuehnl... language to work in." Kuehnl admitted he is "kind of a fanboy."I'm no expert...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7068-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7068_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:53:42">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/07/fracked-pennsylvania-shale-could-be-naturally-leaky/</link><title>Fracked Pennsylvania shale could be naturally leaky</title><description>...Hydraulic fracturingfrackingfor natural gas has revolutionized the energy industry in many places... there. In nature, however, its usually true that to consider something to be impossible... natural gas production wells in parts of Pennsylvania and New York. While that suggested the water...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7068-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7068_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:55:01">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/02/from-the-academy-balkin-on-digital-free-speech/</link><title>From the Academy: Balkin on digital free speech</title><description>... or disfavoring either particular speech or (more importantly) platforms for speechand the safe... for the speech of users.I think Balkin's general point is both important and broadly correctand I want... recognizing limited free speech rights even on private property (such as shopping malls) once they've...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7068-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7068_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:58:56">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/01/today-1-6-task-manager-brings-natural-language-to-ical/</link><title>Today 1.6 task manager brings natural language to iCal</title><description>...Second Gear has updated Today, its event and task manager that integrates with iCal and offers a condensed view of the days agenda. The new version supports natural language when creating events and to-dos, plays better with Spaces, and fixes a handful of bugs. Using natural language to create iCal...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7068-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7068_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:59:55">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/05/natural-gas-fracking-can-make-local-well-water-explosive/</link><title>Natural gas fracking can make local well water explosive</title><description>...As most forms of energy in the US have been going up in price, natural gas has gone in the opposite... of methane between 19.2 and 64 mg/l, enough to pose an explosive hazard, and high enough to qualify... into these wells. Finally, the authors suggest that the fracking process may open up natural fractures...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>