<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7070">compact flash memory card</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:21:52" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7070-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7070_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:21:53">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/12/250mbps-xqd-cards-to-replace-compactflash-in-high-end-cameras/</link><title>250MBps XQD cards to replace CompactFlash in high-end cameras</title><description>... and format to replace the venerable CompactFlash memory card. Tongue-twistingly dubbed "XQD," the PCI Express-based memory cards are smaller and faster than current CF cards, but should offer performance advantages over the current competing compact ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7070-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7070_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:23:41">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/04/want-12tb-of-flash-memory-for-your-server-rack-331000-please/</link><title>Want 12TB of flash memory for your server rack? $331,000, please</title><description>... is expecting a big return on that investment. IBM already purchased flash memory vendor Texas Memory Systems... the availability of all-flash storage appliances based on Texas Memory technology.The suggested price... infrastructures which depend on large quantities of locally attach...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7070-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7070_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:28:32">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/07/faster-and-stronger-next-generation-memory-tech-outperforms-flash/</link><title>Faster and stronger: next-generation memory tech outperforms flash</title><description>...Flash memory is the dominant nonvolatile (retaining information when unpowered) memory thanks to its appearance in solid-state drives (SSDs) and USB flash drives. Despite its popularity, it has issues when feature sizes are scaled down to 30nm and below. In addition, flash has a finite number of write-erase cycles and slow write speeds (on the order of ms). Because of these shortcomings, research...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7070-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7070_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:30:28">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/03/flash-memory-chip-built-out-of-single-atom-thick-components/</link><title>Flash memory chip built out of single-atom-thick components</title><description>... with some more traditional components to make a flash memory device. Although the work is very preliminary... basic outline of a flash memory device involves two electrodes that feed current through... through the semiconductor.To build a compact version of the device, the authors o...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7070-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7070_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:32:10">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/11/dropping-flash-memory-prices-may-help-apple-bottom-line/</link><title>Dropping flash memory prices may help Apple bottom line</title><description>... economic times, since low demand for many electronic devices means low prices on NAND flash memory. As our own Jon Stokes discussed in a recent piece on the flash market, NAND flash prices... flash memory in a fair number of devices, so these low prices give t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7070-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7070_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:34:19">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/turkish-game-part-of-memorial-for-slain-journalist/</link><title>Turkish game part of memorial for slain journalist</title><description>...;Forgetting is losing" campaign in Dink's memory; noteworthy in several ways... (Armenian for "hope") actually uses the same engine as the flash game Madrid, where players...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7070-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7070_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:34:54">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/11/apple-using-dodgy-tactics-to-get-better-nand-flash-prices/</link><title>Apple accused of manipulating NAND flash prices</title><description>... flash memory chips, used mainly in its iPod and iPhone devices. The practice is said to artificially deflate flash prices, casing harm to the NAND industry as a whole.According to The Korea Times... the last decade,Apple hashad a significant impact on the NAND flash memory market. N...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7070-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7070_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:37:42">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/10/intel-and-numonyx-announce-stackable-phase-change-memory/</link><title>Stackable memory advance brings flash-killer closer to market</title><description>... at the forthcoming IEDM conference. PCM, which combines the speed of DRAM and the non-volatility of flash memory... up in. Because the PCM memory cells are so much simpler than a flash cell, and because the basic... can be worked out, it'll take its place alongside flash in the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7070-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7070_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:38:20">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/09/intels-new-flash-tech-to-bring-back-turbo-memory-for-real/</link><title>Intel's new flash tech to bring back Turbo Memory, for real</title><description>...Intel's plan to improve the PC's performance and power efficiency by putting a chunk of flash memory cache on motherboards was previewed at the 2006 IDF under the codename "Robson," and when it was launched the next year as "Turbo Memory" it never took off. Now the company has a followup to Turbo Memory, codenamed "Braidwood," that will debut in the new 5-s...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7070-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7070_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:41:37">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/06/microsoft-offers-windows-embedded-compact-7-ctp/</link><title>Microsoft previews Windows Embedded Compact 7</title><description>...Microsoft has announced the Windows Embedded Compact 7 public Community Technology Preview (CTP). Windows Embedded Compact 7 is the next generation of the Windows Embedded CE platform... version also brings a major update to Internet Explorer that includes support for Adobe Flash 10.1....</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>