<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7071">buy LP politics yellowjackets</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:42:32" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7071-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7071_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:42:33">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/09/a-peek-inside-an-itunes-lp-file/</link><title>A peek inside an iTunes LP file</title><description>...On the shiny exterior, the new iTunes LP may seem like some sort of fancy proprietary format... resolution of at least 1280x800. Unfortunately, this means no iTunes LP on an iPhone or an AppleTV..., Apple will be adding iTunes LP support in future Apple TV updatesespecially since there are allusions...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7071-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7071_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:44:19">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/10/apples-10000-itunes-lp-fee-causing-stir/</link><title>Apple's $10,000 iTunes LP fee causing stir (Updated)</title><description>...As we explained in our look at the iTunes LP format, the insides are built with standard Web technologies: HTML, CSS, and JavaScript complemented by graphics, audio, and video media. The result of this is that any experienced Web developer should be able to produce an iTunes LP, and it's not outside the realm of possibility that web-savvy indie bands could even produce one themselves. Howeve...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7071-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7071_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:44:54">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/11/apple-releases-itunes-lp-and-extras-specs-tunekit-sdk/</link><title>Apple releases iTunes LP and Extras specs, TuneKit SDK</title><description>...It appears the hubbub over iTunes LP production feeswas indeed unfounded. As promised last month... iTunes LP for music and iTunes Extras for video content.Along with the relevant specifications... best practices, as well as how to test an iTunes LP or Extras package before submitting it to Apple...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7071-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7071_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:47:34">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/11/scientists-see-political-attacks-as-badge-of-pride/</link><title>Scientists see political attacks as badge of pride</title><description>... behaviors because of the current political environment, although less than a third agreed... to political attack. For a small minority of scientists surveyed, the consequences were even greater... and some anxiety. It seems that while there might be a chilling effect that results from political...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7071-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7071_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:48:41">http://arstechnica.com/science/2008/11/political-science-and-biology-at-a-crossroad/</link><title>Political science and biology at a crossroad</title><description>... and doing research that marries the worlds of biology to political science in order to ask... research that pointed towards a genetic component to participation in the political process... in the political process compared with those who are more apathetic. The possibility that certain ideas...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7071-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7071_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:50:51">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2008/12/exploiting-source-amnesia-in-political-search-ads/</link><title>Exploiting "source amnesia" in political search ads</title><description>... of political advertising is how to go on the attack without provoking voter backlash. Going negative... candidate as hostile. But Koster made an ingeniously simple observation: When youre buying a keyword...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7071-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7071_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:53:55">http://arstechnica.com/business/2014/01/the-long-term-effects-of-ugly-political-discussions-on-facebook/</link><title>The long-term effects of ugly political discussions on Facebook</title><description>...Political discussions on Facebook are, in fact, undermining both peoples relationships and use... who try to talk about politics on Facebook are often surprised by the political opinions... participants in the study had been involved in or witnessed a political discussion that turned ugly...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7071-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7071_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:56:29">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/10/feeling-superior-about-your-political-beliefs-is-a-bipartisan-issue/</link><title>Feeling superior about your political beliefs is a bipartisan issue</title><description>... about beliefs has been associated with conservative political thought. The political root of conservatism is a mistrust of change, and a variety of research has suggested that this political stance has deep... political issues like health care, immigration, abortion, taxes, and voter ID laws. Then, separa...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7071-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7071_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:57:39">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/04/open-secrets-releases-political-finance-data-under-cc-license/</link><title>Open Secrets releases political finance data under CC license</title><description>... collection of data related to political activities publicly accessible. OpenSecrets.org is run by the Center for Responsive Politics, which appears to be largely funded by charitable foundations... a clearing house of data on political contributions and lobbying efforts, with the hope that bringing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7071-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7071_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:58:37">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/11/when-to-wait-why-buying-games-at-launch-is-a-fools-errand/</link><title>When to wait: why buying games at launch is a fool's errand</title><description>... going to have some hard choices to make.We want to help. Buying games when they're released... to ask yourself when trying to decide what games to buy now, and when to wait.Is there a bunch... characters, and classic fatalities you could get by buying it at certain retailers or paying extra.You...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>