<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7072">price gibson howard roberts custom</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:02:23" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7072-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7072_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:02:24">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/07/william-gibsons-agrippa-mystery-challenge/</link><title>Solve 20-year-old mystery in William Gibson's "Agrippa," win prizes</title><description>... floppy disk that displays a poem penned by cyberpunk author William Gibson exactly once and then.... The first person to document the scheme will receive a copy of every William Gibson book ever..., so the routine remains a mystery. DuPont said Gibson has never been known as much of a technical person...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7072-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7072_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:06:21">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/03/e-book-price-fixing-settlements-land-in-amazon-customers-inboxes/</link><title>E-book price fixing settlements land in Amazon customers’ inboxes</title><description>... conspired with Apple to fix e-book prices in 2012.Amazon is not disclosing the formula... with the five publishers accused of price fixingHachette, HarperCollins, Simon Schuster, Macmillan, and Penguintotal $166 million nationwide. Customers who bought e-books from Barnes and Noble, Kobo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7072-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7072_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:09:17">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/04/star-citizens-chris-roberts-still-supports-a-facebook-owned-oculus/</link><title>Star Citizen ’s Chris Roberts still supports a Facebook-owned Oculus</title><description>... are no doubt relieved to hear thatChris Roberts,former Wing Commander developer and creator... letter to followers, Roberts cited a blog post from new Oculus hire (and former Valve VR guru.... Roberts said he understands the need for massive amounts of capital to launch a new hardware product...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7072-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7072_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:12:02">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/02/windows-7-boot-animation-customization-will-not-be-supported/</link><title>Windows 7 boot animation customization will not be supported</title><description>... Vista, but the software giant recently gave some news that many customizers and tweakers will not enjoy... to be (it's worth the read if you have time). Those who love to customize everything in Windows will be disappointed to learn that Microsoft will not support customizing the boot screen animation...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7072-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7072_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:14:11">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/02/dread-pirate-roberts-2-0-an-interview-with-silk-roads-new-boss/</link><title>Dread Pirate Roberts 2.0: An interview with Silk Road’s new boss</title><description>... Pirate Roberts (DPR). The name came from a character in The Princess Bride who passes his piratical...." What does it represent?Dread Pirate Roberts: We represent a right for the individual... Pirate Roberts?"A person can hold any school of libertarian view they would like to, but do...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7072-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7072_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:15:39">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/11/star-citizens-chris-roberts-discusses-upping-the-ante-on-pc-gaming/</link><title>Star Citizen 's Chris Roberts discusses upping the ante on PC gaming</title><description>...Say what you will about Chris Roberts, the guy knows how to make an entrance. After spending... to game development now? It's all about the technology, and Roberts tells Ars that the tech... of a movie to it."Roberts also said he was drawn back by the ability to interact directly...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7072-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7072_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:16:43">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/recent-channel-checks-indicate-ps3-price-cut-says-analyst/</link><title>Channel checks point to PS3 price cut, says analyst</title><description>...To price cut, or not to price cut? That is the question for Sony, and if Janco analyst Mike Hickey can be trusted, a PS3 price cut announcement is just around the corner. "Recent channel checks indicate increased speculation for a PS3 price cut announcement from Sony in the next couple of days...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7072-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7072_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:19:49">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/09/wing-commander-creator-chris-roberts-working-on-new-space-combat-game/</link><title>Wing Commander creator Chris Roberts working on new space combat game</title><description>...Chris Roberts is responsible for some massive milestones in PC gaming. As the man behind the Wing... in '42' and get very excited." The link points to a website named "Roberts Space... code entry form yields a message from Roberts himself."I always said the moment I became...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7072-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7072_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:23:12">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/10/wing-commanders-chris-roberts-returns-to-gaming-with-ambitious-mmo/</link><title>Wing Commander 's Chris Roberts returns to gaming with ambitious MMO</title><description>..., legendary game designer Chris Roberts left the industry to spend the last decade producing movies, includingLord of War, Lucky Number Slevin, and The Punisher. But today, Roberts announced he's coming... in the game. Roberts writes on the game's newly launched website that he hopes this dynamic...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7072-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7072_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:26:13">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/05/a-slippery-slope-why-apple-may-or-may-not-offer-cheaper-macs/</link><title>Cheap Macs? The pros and cons of an Apple price cut</title><description>...With Mac sales more or less plateauing during the last quarter, and Apple's market share growth down to nearly nothing, Apple has certainly gotten a few hints on how to increase market share in our current economic climate. The common refrain is that Apple should lower its prices, and a recent rumor suggested that Apple planned to do just that. But lowering prices won't necessarily be t...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>