<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7073">buy bausack</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:27:30" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7073-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7073_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:27:32">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/11/when-to-wait-why-buying-games-at-launch-is-a-fools-errand/</link><title>When to wait: why buying games at launch is a fool's errand</title><description>... going to have some hard choices to make.We want to help. Buying games when they're released... to ask yourself when trying to decide what games to buy now, and when to wait.Is there a bunch... characters, and classic fatalities you could get by buying it at certain retailers or paying extra.You...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7073-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7073_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:29:41">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/06/microsoft-and-best-buy-to-create-600-stores-in-stores-by-september/</link><title>Microsoft and Best Buy to create 600 stores-in-stores by September</title><description>...Microsoft has announced new plans to extend its retail reach by partnering with Best Buy to create..., with an additional 105 in Canada split between the Best Buy and Future Shop brands. The first... them a substantial presence. Microsoft will also be training 1,200 Best Buy blue-shirts to provide...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7073-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7073_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:30:29">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/06/best-buy-offers-littlebigplanet-wall-e-free-with-ps3/</link><title>Best Buy offers LittleBigPlanet, Wall-E free with PS3</title><description>...We've been running a higher than normal number of "hot deals" posts in the past week, and I apologize in advance for another one. Best Buy has quite the bundle for the PS3, however, and I thought it was worth passing on.Right now you can pick up the 80GB model of the hardware...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7073-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7073_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:33:01">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/08/the-ars-pc-laptop-buying-guide-back-to-school-edition/</link><title>PC laptop buying guide—back to school edition</title><description>.... If youve got an extra $200 or so on hand and you dont mind losing the capacity, buying a 256GB solid... that buying from Apples education store knocks the base price of the 13 Air down to $1,149 and makes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7073-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7073_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:33:53">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/10/best-buy-now-on-the-buy-2-get-1-more-free-wagon/</link><title>Best Buy offering "Buy 2 Get 1 More Free" games</title><description>...'Tis the season for retailers to start offering discounts and announcing sales. Between all the new games that are coming out ahead of the Holidays, this is always a rough time on gamers' wallets. Best Buy has announced its own Buy 2 Games, Get 1 Free promotion.Last week, both Amazon...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7073-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7073_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:37:25">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/01/iphone-5-discount-wars-lead-to-65000-in-losses-for-best-buy/</link><title>iPhone 5 discount wars lead to $65,000 in losses for Best Buy</title><description>...The holiday battle over iPhone sales left Best Buy with $65,000 in losses, the company said on Friday. The Wall Street Journal cited Best Buy's claims as part of a piece on Walmart's advertising practices, pointing out that Best Buy was "compelled" to price-match Walmart's aggressive iPhone 5 discounts, leaving the big-box electronics retailer in the red.Both chains offer...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7073-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7073_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:40:15">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/08/best-buys-new-games-at-used-prices-promotion-starts-feud/</link><title>New games at used prices: Best Buy's Utah plan starts a feud</title><description>... it is surprising to see Best Buy make its new game prices competitive with GameStop's used game prices.In West Jordan, Utah, an eagle-eye Cheapassgamer reader snapped a picture of a sign at a local Best Buy. It said that Best Buy would price-match any used game from GameStop or GameCrazy with a new copy...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7073-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7073_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:42:40">http://arstechnica.com/security/2012/05/best-buy-collecting-email-passwords/</link><title>Best Buy's surprisingly insecure approach to new PC setup</title><description>... down" (over-aggressive change requirements often have this effect, for instance).Best Buy.... He had settled on an HP Windows 7 machine and was in the process of paying for it when a Best Buy... with the familiar Best Buy and Geek Squad logos, one side contained a new computer setup form, where you...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7073-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7073_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:45:42">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/08/best-buy-launching-huge-360-game-sale-ps3-next-week/</link><title>Best Buy launching huge 360 game sale, PS3 next week</title><description>...In the mood to spend some money? Best Buy is running a rather insane deal, where you get 50 percent off certain Xbox 360 titles by purchasing the first game at the full price, and the list of games that qualify for the deal is rather stunning. Some of the titles aren't even out yet, so if you...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7073-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7073_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:49:11">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/10/youtube-intros-links-to-buy-music-featured-in-videos/</link><title>YouTube intros links to buy music featured in videos</title><description>... using in the soundtrack? you may be able to find out, and even buy it directly from the page. Google... videos from EMI, for example, youll see links to buy the featured song on Amazon or iTunes. Google describes these buttons as click-to-buy links, which are nestled unobtrusively beneath the video...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>