<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7078">count in korean</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:37:51" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7078-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7078_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:37:52">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/02/casino-operators-issue-warning-over-iphone-card-counting-app/</link><title>Casino regulators issue alert over iPhone card-counting app</title><description>...An iPhone-based card-counting system recently turned up in a California Indian casino. This new application is causing a lot of fuss, and Nevada gaming regulators have issued a general alert about it, warning Las Vegas casinos about its potential use in gameplay.Want to count cards at a US casino? The consensus seems to be that "skilled players" can count cards all they want; it's...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7078-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7078_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:40:13">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2008/12/intel-to-challenge-korean-ftc-consumer-groups-lash-out/</link><title>Intel to challenge Korean FTC, consumer groups lash out</title><description>...Last June, the Korean Fair Trade Commission fined Intel approximately $19 million for what...-year investigation into Intels behavior; at the time Intel expressed disappointment with the Korean..., alleging that the Korean FTCs ruling was based on substantial factual and legal errors...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7078-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7078_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:40:42">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2014/04/suspected-n-korean-drone-plane-recovered-by-s-korean-military/</link><title>Suspected N. Korean “drone plane” recovered by S. Korean military</title><description>...Last year, North Korean state media reported that the countrys leader, Kim Jong Un, had overseen... Korea has recovered what may be part of the vaunted North Korean drone force after it crashed... technology.South Korean officials reported today that they had recovered an unmanned aircraft...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7078-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7078_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:43:25">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/01/overall-the-technology-in-north-korea-is-very-limited-right-now/</link><title>North Korean Internet stance will affect its “physical world,” “economic growth”</title><description>...Former Google CEO Eric Schmidt is back from a North Korean trip not everyone was thrilled about. Last night, he took to his Google+ page to post a few quick thoughts on the experienceleading with an unsurprising revelation."Overall, the technology in North Korea is very limited right now."Schmidt described a few quick problems he encountered during his trip (officially part of a delegat...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7078-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7078_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:45:26">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/03/networks-of-south-korean-banks-broadcasters-hit-in-cyber-attack/</link><title>Networks of South Korean banks, broadcasters hit in cyberattack</title><description>...The computer networks of three major South Korean banks and three television networks went offline... Korea, the government has said it's not ruling out the possibility. The South Korean military... against South Korean government and business networks.A spokesperson for South Korea's public...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7078-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7078_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:47:24">http://arstechnica.com/security/2013/04/north-korean-military-blamed-for-wiper-cyber-attacks/</link><title>North Korean military blamed for “wiper” cyber attacks against South Korea</title><description>...The South Korean government is pointing a finger toward Pyongyang in its assessment... of an anti-North Korean organization and South Korean broadcaster YTN. Forensic evidence from it pointed directly to North Korean involvement. Six computers located at North Korean IP addresses...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7078-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7078_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:50:14">http://arstechnica.com/security/2013/04/anonymous-hackers-take-control-of-north-korean-propaganda-sites/</link><title>Anonymous hackers take control of North Korean propaganda accounts</title><description>...A Twitter and Flickr account associated with a North Korean news agency has been taken...;s website and other North Korean websites, which appear to be offline.The Twitter and Flickr accounts represent Uriminzokkiri (meaning "Our Nation"), a North Korean news and propaganda site...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7078-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7078_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:53:49">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/02/north-korean-defector-fights-pyongyang-with-thumbdrive-laden-balloons/</link><title>North Korean defector fights Pyongyang with thumbdrive-laden balloons</title><description>...SAN FRANCISCOFor years, Park Sang Hak has fought the North Korean government with balloons.The long.... (The last is included so starving North Koreans can buy rice on the black market.) While the balloons... from the border.Speaking in a local South of Market coffee shop, the North Korean defector explained Monday morning...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7078-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7078_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:57:32">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/11/counting-photons-without-destroying-them/</link><title>Counting photons without destroying them</title><description>...Detecting photons is destructive. From telescope cameras through phosphorescent screens to detectors inside particle colliders, measuring and counting photons requires absorbing them, at which point... in a mirror is a product of all the light that bounced off. The mirror itself isn't counting...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7078-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7078_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:00:09">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2011/08/27000-south-korean-iphone-users-suing-apple-over-locationgate/</link><title>27,000 South Korean iPhone users suing Apple over "Locationgate"</title><description>...Following a recent victory against Apple over claims that iPhone location data collection violated user privacy, a South Korean law firm has nowlaunched a class-action lawsuit over the same location data issues. The firm is asking for 1 million won for each of the roughly 27,000 plaintiffs, which could put Apple on the hook for about US$25 million.In April of this year, security researchers Alasd...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>