<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7079">a-team theme music</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:02:54" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7079-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7079_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:02:55">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/03/pretty-penguin-five-great-themes-for-the-gnome-desktop/</link><title>Pretty penguin: five great themes for the GNOME desktop</title><description>... and a standard set of applications for Linuxhave an elaborate theme system that enables users... environment. Many custom GNOME themes are published in online galleries so that they can be downloaded..., which has become the de facto standard home of downloadable GNOME theming content.Although a wide...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7079-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7079_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:05:37">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/03/hands-on-a-close-look-at-ubuntus-new-non-brown-theme/</link><title>Hands-on: a close look at Ubuntu's new non-brown theme</title><description>... Linux distribution's traditional brown theming. The new theme, which was announced yesterday... Wednesday left a lot of questions unanswered. Fortunately, the new themes were rolled out to Ubuntu 10.04... some hands-on testing so that we could see how the new theme looks with a number of popular...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7079-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7079_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:08:24">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/11/unlock-hidden-windows-7-themes/</link><title>Windows 7 themes: how to unlock them or create your own</title><description>...Themes have been a part of Windows since at least Windows 95, and they're still with us... with a handful of themes, but it also lets you get more. In this guide, we're going to show you how to unlock themes that are already on your computer, remove themes that you've added, and get...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7079-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7079_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:10:16">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/03/canonicals-design-team-responds-to-theme-criticisms/</link><title>Canonical's design team responds to theme criticisms</title><description>...Canonical is burying Ubuntu's traditional brown theme and is adopting a new visual style for version 10.04, which is scheduled for release in April. The new theme was revealed last week as part... theme includes a richer color palette and a number of stylistic enhancements. The change...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7079-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7079_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:14:05">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/team-fortress-2-gets-scout-update-goes-half-price/</link><title>Team Fortress 2 gets Scout update, goes half price</title><description>...Valve is continuing its support for Team Fortress 2, this time with an update focused on the Scout class. This includes new achievements, weapons, and even a few maps. Additionally, Valve announced... interest and bringing in some new players to Team Fortress 2. As we have learned, discounts on Steam tend...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7079-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7079_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:17:14">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/05/trauma-team-review-melodrama-and-medicine-on-the-wii/</link><title>Trauma Team review: melodrama and medicine on the Wii</title><description>...The Trauma Center games deliver two things: fast-paced, tension-filled surgeries where steady hands and accuracy will get you higher rankings, and insane melodramatic storylines. Trauma Team.... Title Trauma Team Developer Atlus Publisher Atlus Price $39.99 Shop.Ars Platform Nintendo WiiThe game...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7079-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7079_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:18:47">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/05/report-teaser-trailer-for-next-team-ico-game-leaked/</link><title>Report: Teaser trailer for next Team Ico game leaked</title><description>...It's been a long time coming, but it looks like we may finally have some details on the upcoming project from Shadow of the Colossus and Ico developer Team Ico. The news comes via what appears... that looks very similar to past Team Ico games in terms of aesthetics. It's hard to glean just how...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7079-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7079_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:21:00">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/06/map-making-in-team-fortress-2-gets-a-little-easier/</link><title>Map making in Team Fortress 2 gets a little easier</title><description>...While Valve may be busy at work supporting and developing the sequel for Left 4 Dead, that doesn't mean that it has forgotten about its other big multiplayer shooter, Team Fortress 2. The developer has announced an update to the Source SDK, which will make the process of creating new maps much...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7079-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7079_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:21:57">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/10/ubisoft-and-adult-swim-team-up-to-deliver-music-to-gamers/</link><title>Ubisoft and Adult Swim team up to deliver music to gamers</title><description>...Ubisoft and Cartoon Networks Adult Swim are joining forces to provide a free downloadable music album to gamers. While this sounds interesting in its own right, the project (African Swim) becomes... able to getting to experience music from artists like Jozi, Gumshev and Maggz, players can actually...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7079-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7079_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:23:17">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/01/iphone-dev-team-releases-yellowsn0w-0-9-4-beta-unlock/</link><title>iPhone dev team releases yellowsn0w 0.9.4 beta unlock</title><description>... than a spanking fresh new iPhone unlock? As promised, the iPhone dev-team has delivered its iPhone 3G unlock... with the latest 2.2 firmware update from Apple. Its also the baseband and update that the dev team have been warning you not to upgrade to. It turns out that the team eventually managed to unlock...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>