<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7080">lord of the rings hobbits theme</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:27:10" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7080-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7080_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:27:11">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/12/ars-technicast-episode-17-deconstructing-the-hobbit/</link><title>Ars Technicast, Episode 17: Deconstructing The Hobbit</title><description>... material. In this episode of the Ars Technicast, we discuss the role The Hobbit played in Tolkiens grand mythology of Middle Earth, and how Peter Jacksons films have re-imagined The Lord of The Rings...The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey finally arrived a week ago. For fans of J.R.R. Tolkien, the new...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7080-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7080_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:30:30">http://arstechnica.com/staff/2012/12/a-tolkien-nerds-thoughts-on-the-hobbit-an-unexpected-journey/</link><title>A Tolkien nerd's thoughts on The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey</title><description>...I first read J.R.R. Tolkien's The Hobbit when I was no more than eight or nine years old.The Lord of the Rings trilogy followed when I wasn't much older than that. I continue to make a point of reading through all of the books (and their appendices, at least the ones that aren't concerned with Elvish grammar) at least once every couple of years or soeven making it through The Silma...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7080-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7080_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:34:08">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/01/lords-of-the-rings-a-look-at-tree-ring-science/</link><title>Lords of the rings: understanding tree ring science</title><description>...Ask any second grader what you can do with the rings on a tree, and they'll respond, "Learn the age of the tree!" They're not wrong, but dendrochronologythe dating of trees based on patterns in their ringsis more than just counting rings. The hundred year-old discipline has given scientists access to extraordinarily detailed records of climate and environmental conditions hund...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7080-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7080_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:37:08">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/12/the-first-hobbit-trailer-is-here-and-it-is-good/</link><title>The first Hobbit trailer is here, and it is good</title><description>... we didn't see with the Lord of the Rings books. In the Hobbit characters could be silly, fun, heroic, and selfish. That's a contrast to the characters in Lord of the Rings, who were portrayed...Peter Jackson's take on the Hobbit won't be hi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7080-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7080_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:40:50">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/06/the-lego-barad-dur-50000-pieces-two-months-of-construction-pure-awesomethe-lego-barad-dur-50000-pieces-2-months-to-build-pure-awesome/</link><title>The Lego Barad-dûr: 50,000 pieces, 2 months to build, pure awesome</title><description>... Lord of the Rings the first time and it was an instant point on my to-do list for the future, but our...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7080-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7080_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:43:32">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/12/on-the-hobbit-the-desolation-of-smaug-and-weaknesses-in-the-source-material/</link><title>On The Hobbit: The Desolation of Smaug and weaknesses in the source material</title><description>...Let me begin by saying that I didn't dislikeThe Hobbit: The Desolation of Smaug.This was emphaticallynot the case with last year'sAn Unexpected Journey, which has a whole pile of structural and thematic problems.Peter Jackson and crew took what could have been a reasonably watchable two-hour fantasy film and padded it out to three hours with interminable chase sequences, memorable-for-a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7080-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7080_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:47:44">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/03/lotr-game-rights-go-from-ea-to-warner-bros/</link><title>LotR game rights go from EA to Warner Bros.</title><description>...Electronic Arts' license of the Lord of the Rings franchise expired at the end of 2008, and now the rights are back at New Line. While EA has been publishing games based on Tolkien's seminal works for so many years that it's hard to think of a LotR game without the publisher's logo on it, Warner Bros. new outlook on video games makes it seem unlikely that it will be contractin...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7080-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7080_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:51:34">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/03/pretty-penguin-five-great-themes-for-the-gnome-desktop/</link><title>Pretty penguin: five great themes for the GNOME desktop</title><description>... and a standard set of applications for Linuxhave an elaborate theme system that enables users... environment. Many custom GNOME themes are published in online galleries so that they can be downloaded..., which has become the de facto standard home of downloadable GNOME theming content.Although a wide...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7080-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7080_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:52:21">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/03/hands-on-a-close-look-at-ubuntus-new-non-brown-theme/</link><title>Hands-on: a close look at Ubuntu's new non-brown theme</title><description>... Linux distribution's traditional brown theming. The new theme, which was announced yesterday... Wednesday left a lot of questions unanswered. Fortunately, the new themes were rolled out to Ubuntu 10.04... some hands-on testing so that we could see how the new theme looks with a number of popular...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7080-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7080_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:55:19">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/11/hacking-away-at-the-horrors-of-middle-earth-lotr-war-in-the-north-delivers/</link><title>Hacking away at the horrors of Middle Earth: LOTR: War in the North delivers</title><description>... you're tasked with destroying. The Lord of the Rings films featured some wonderful scenes.... If you're a fan of the Lord of the Rings movies, you're going to be in heaven fighting through...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>