<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7083">I'm on the road again</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:39:29" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7083-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7083_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:39:31">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/10/im-a-pc-and-windows-7-was-my-idea/</link><title>I'm a PC and Windows 7 was my idea</title><description>...Along with Windows 7's official worldwide debut today, Microsoft launched the accompanying ad campaign under the following slogan: "I'm a PC and Windows 7 was my idea." As you can see in the image, Times Square in New York is draped with huge advertisements for Windows 7. There are posters and banners everywhere, as Microsoft makes sure everyone knows that today is the day of ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7083-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7083_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:39:58">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/06/bumpy-road-interview/</link><title>Bumpy Road devs discuss making an arcade game about love</title><description>... took this principle to heart with Bumpy Road. Though automatic side-scrollers are near ubiquitous in the iOS app storefrom Canabalt to Robot Unicorn AttackBumpy Road feels like something different... about love.Unlike most games of this type, Bumpy Road isn't about running away from something...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7083-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7083_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:42:27">http://arstechnica.com/security/2013/10/silk-road-mastermind-unmasked-by-rookie-goofs-complaint-alleges/</link><title>FBI: Silk Road mastermind couldn’t even keep himself anonymous online</title><description>...What will get you in the end is sloppy opsec. Short for operations security, it encompasses a sprawling list of disciplines, including keeping PCs free of malware, encrypting e-mail and other communications, and placing an impenetrable firewall between public and personal identities.The latest high-profile criminal defendant to get a first-hand lesson in the perils of poor opsec is Ross William U...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7083-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7083_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:43:19">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/10/how-the-feds-busted-a-top-silk-road-seller/</link><title>How the feds busted a top Silk Road seller</title><description>... on the Silk Road, a clear indication of a crackdown on dealers using the notorious site. News..., arrested on October 2 and 3 respectively, are behind the NOD account on Silk Road... girlfriend.By February 2013, the UPS store had received a package for Aaron Thompson again. With a search...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7083-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7083_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:46:35">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/10/amid-silk-road-uncertainty-bitcoin-value-drops-over-20-in-3-hours/</link><title>Amid Silk Road uncertainty, Bitcoin value drops over 20% in 3 hours</title><description>... around 1:00pm CT, dropped again toward the $109.71/bitcoin rate, and rose back to the low...;s tangentially related to the currency. Silk Road, the sprawling online criminal enterprise that used bitcoins... linking Bitcoin value fluctuation with the Silk Road shutdown. The Bitcoin drop could as easily be due...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7083-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7083_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:47:39">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/10/silk-road-kingpin-shackled-in-court-pleads-for-time/</link><title>Silk Road kingpin, shackled in court, pleads for time</title><description>...SAN FRANCISCORoss Ulbricht, the 29-year-old alleged to have run the Silk Road online drug... laundering as well as soliciting the murder of another Silk Road user. Authorities said that Ulbricht was the mastermind behind the infamous Silk Road marketplace, which was shut down on Wednesday...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7083-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7083_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:49:39">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/03/fbi-believes-small-pennsylvania-hosting-company-is-connected-to-silk-road/</link><title>FBI believes small Pennsylvania hosting company is connected to Silk Road</title><description>... man whom federal prosecutors accuse of running a backup server on behalf of the Silk Road, the Tor...;I'm afraid that I'm not willing to comment about Silk Road,"Nadovich told Ars, adding... name was redacted, notes that the agency has analyzed the contents of the seized Silk Road...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7083-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7083_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:50:46">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/02/police-crack-down-on-silk-road-following-first-drug-dealer-conviction/</link><title>Police crack down on Silk Road following first drug dealer conviction</title><description>...An Australian drug dealer has become the first person to be convicted of a Silk Road-related crime..., and cocaine.People can buy goods from Silk Road only by connecting with the anonymizing Tor network and using... by security researchers at Carnegie Mellon University revealed that the Silk Road trades items worth 1.22...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7083-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7083_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:52:13">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/01/men-charged-with-scheme-to-sell-1-million-in-bitcoins-to-silk-road-users/</link><title>Men charged with scheme to sell $1 million in bitcoins to Silk Road users</title><description>... for use on Silk Road, the online emporium that allowed people to buy and sell illegal drugs... Road from 2011 to 2013, according to a criminal complaint unsealed Monday in federal court in Manhattan... worth of Bitcoin transactions that flowed over Silk Road, which was shut down in October...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7083-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7083_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:54:29">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/01/feds-ready-to-auction-off-25-million-in-silk-road-bitcoin/</link><title>Feds ready to auction off $25 million in Silk Road Bitcoin</title><description>... announced the forfeiture of 29,655 bitcoins that were seized from a Silk Road server during a raid... million when it was seized. The US Attorney's office also announced that the Silk Road website... and who is suspected of being the mastermind behind the Silk Road, has been in custody since federal agents...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>