<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7084">Burn after reading review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:55:25" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7084-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7084_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:55:28">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/10/burning-monkey-puzzle-lab-tetris-on-drugs/</link><title>Burning Monkey Puzzle Lab: Tetris on drugs</title><description>... to picturing the interactive experience of Freeverses new Burning Monkey Puzzle Lab for iPhone (iTunes link... pieces extinguish even more items and, when played properly, can rack up high scores. Design Burning... to release Tranquility, a relaxation utility, today or tomorrow. Three other games, Burning Monkey...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7084-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7084_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:57:43">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/05/reading-information-by-burning-it/</link><title>Reading information by burning it</title><description>...File this in the "useless but really cool" department. Scientists, inspired by the fact that DNA encodes information in its basic chemistry, pondered other systems that could function in an analogous manner. The system that they came up with is every science geek's dream: something that you set on fire and watch as it glows in different colors. The precise sequence of those colors...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7084-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7084_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:58:58">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/05/making-microsoft-nicer-through-patents/</link><title>Microsoft now all about cooperation? Yes, thanks to patents</title><description>...When Hernn Corts landed in Mexico in 1519, he was no less ambitious than Microsoft, but differences between the man and the monopolist were immediately apparent. Corts, for instance, burned his ships so that no retreat was possible, then marched through the interior of the country on an imperialistic orgy, massacred people in the marketplaces, overthrew an empire, and set himself up as the ruler....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7084-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7084_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:00:13">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/06/levar-burton-talks-reading-rainbow-from-tv-to-e-books-and-beyond/</link><title>LeVar Burton talks Reading Rainbow : from TV to e-books and beyond</title><description>..."The mission of Reading Rainbow has always been to use the prevailing technology of the day... force behind the old television classic Reading Rainbowtold Ars on the phone on Thursday. That conversation followed the successful launch of his new Reading Rainbow app for the iPad...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7084-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7084_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:03:01">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/04/genes-need-good-teachers-to-produce-reading-skills/</link><title>Genes need good teachers to produce reading skills</title><description>..., environment, and reading ability. The portion of the paper that reviews the current literature provides... portion of children's reading skills can be ascribed to genetic influencestypical twin studies... they create can have a strong influence on the development of reading ability. It would be very...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7084-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7084_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:04:25">http://arstechnica.com/business/2014/02/ken-burns-shows-how-apps-can-remix-great-works-of-media-for-fans/</link><title>Ken Burns shows how apps can remix great works of media for fans</title><description>...App DetailsDeveloper: Ken Burns Media, LLCPublisher: American Documentaries, IncPlatform: iOS 7... purchase.Links: Official website | AppleKen Burns has finally released an app. Titled simply "Ken Burns," the new free-to-try app collects hours of footage from over 20 of the man's famed...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7084-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7084_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:07:41">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/07/time-is-the-fire-in-which-we-burn-ars-reviews-singularity/</link><title>Time is the fire in which we burn: Ars reviews Singularity</title><description>... Shop.Ars Platform Xbox 360 (Reviewed), PlayStation 3, PCListen up, it's story timeYou'll find...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7084-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7084_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:09:12">http://arstechnica.com/staff/2013/07/why-i-hate-read-receipts/</link><title>Why I hate read receipts</title><description>...Few things on the Internet giveth and taketh away the way a read receipt does. An immediate read-and-response is immense validation, while a crucial message that has been read but not responded... workers did double duty as tracking numbers.That version of read receipts was more like a delivery...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7084-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7084_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:11:29">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/04/why-you-should-read-the-book-before-the-lights-go-out/</link><title>Why you should read the book Before the Lights Go Out</title><description>..., unforeseen side effects, and less-than-perfect solutions."The book is a fast and easy read... interesting. This carries over to the book, and it reads almost like a long-form blog post, which is a good... on varying fuels.In all, this is a great book, and one I recommend that pretty much everyone should read...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7084-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7084_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:14:56">http://arstechnica.com/staff/2010/12/year-in-review-2010s-most-popular-stories/</link><title>Year in review: 2010's most popular stories</title><description>...These are the most popularby pageviewsstories that ran on Ars Technica during 2010. We've split them into two categories: multipage features and reports. Without further ado:Multipage features10. Tentacular, tentacular!: Beware, mortals: Cthulhu has returned, and he's armed with bacon and an unhealthy obsession with geek brains. Battle your way through our first-ever interactive adventu...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>