<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7086">falsifying pictures 21st centurie</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:39:30" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7086-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7086_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:39:32">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/08/beardyman-captures-the-quiet-sounds-of-the-21st-century/</link><title>Beardyman captures the quiet sounds of the 21st century</title><description>...We live in a silent century. Though no less powerful than their pre-millennial ancestors, our post-millennial innovations are mostly intangible; even when they do occupy physical space, they but wobble neighboring air particles and scarcely make a sound.Compiling the "Sounds of the 21st Century" is a steep challenge, therefore, but one that legendary beatboxer Beardyman didn't shy...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7086-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7086_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:41:35">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/12/the-shards-bleeding-edge-anatomy-of-a-21st-century-skyscraper/</link><title>The Shard's bleeding edge: anatomy of a 21st century skyscraper</title><description>... the Shard, has compared its shape to "a 16th century pinnacle or the mast of a very tall ship... they plan to keep the Shard lean, green, and above all verticaland why skyscrapers are needed in the 21st...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7086-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7086_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:42:48">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/04/21st-century-access-to-19th-century-materials/</link><title>Archives digitize 19th century materials for 21st century access</title><description>..., has announced the launch of Nineteenth Century Collections Online, a multiyear global digitization... Archives.Nineteenth Century Collections OnlineThe Nineteenth Century Collections Online offers a host of material "from the 'long' nineteenth century (1789-1914) and beyond." These in...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7086-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7086_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:45:43">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/08/dozuki-will-drag-service-manuals-kicking-and-screaming-into-21st-century/</link><title>Dozuki will drag service manuals kicking, screaming into 21st century</title><description>... is very simple. "Service manuals are stuck in the 20th century. We're going to fix...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7086-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7086_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:48:27">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/10/legendary-pictures-looking-to-pick-up-epic-games/</link><title>Legendary Pictures looking to pick up Epic Games</title><description>...The world of film is coming ever closer to that of video games, as Variety is reporting that Legendary Pictures is in talks to purchase Gears of War developer Epic Games. The rumors come just a few weeks after Legendary boss Thomas Tull left game publisher Brash Entertainment, which he helped...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7086-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7086_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:51:26">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/10/the-21st-century-guide-to-platform-trolling-apple-edition/</link><title>The 21st century guide to platform trolling: Apple edition</title><description>...Though the glory days of platform contention may be behind us, there is plenty about today's computing landscape that's... sub-optimal, shall we say. Yesterday we looked at some of the many problems with the world of Windows: things that make the computing experience worse than it should be.Windows' number one competitor is, of course, Mac OS X (sorry penguins, maybe 2011 will be t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7086-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7086_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:55:01">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/10/the-21st-century-guide-to-platform-trolling-windows-sucks/</link><title>The 21st century guide to platform trolling: Windows edition</title><description>...It is an unfortunate truth that the glory days of platform trolling are behind us. Where once we had an enormous variety of targets with their many foiblesthe legendary user-friendliness and rich capabilities of MS DOS, Apple's infamous low prices, Windows NT's svelte size and minimal hardware demands, IBM's memorable and effective OS/2 marketing campaigns, BeOS's rich selecti...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7086-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7086_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:56:54">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/09/steam-comes-to-the-living-room-tv-with-big-picture-mode-beta/</link><title>Steam comes to the living room TV with Big Picture mode beta</title><description>..., rectangular picture icons designed to be viewed from a living room couch rather than a desk chair. Navigation in Big Picture mode is handled with a standard handheld controller (like that on the Xbox 360... and text-based communication, Big Picture mode also features a unique on-screen keyboard...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7086-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7086_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:00:30">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/12/ars-asks-what-video-games-will-still-be-widely-played-in-100-years/</link><title>Ars Asks: What video games will still be widely played in 100 years?</title><description>... could have the centuries-long impact of a board game like chess."Tough for chess to overtake League... one comes out with slightly better graphics. Chess has captivated us for centuries."Chess... for centuries. More recently, corporate-controlled games like Monopoly and Scrabble have stood the test...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7086-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7086_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:03:38">http://arstechnica.com/business/2010/04/last-year-printer-comparison-website/</link><title>Tweak your typeface, save money on toner</title><description>... for Microsoft Office, the site determined that Century Gothic actually saved the most ink or toner... to convince the University of Wisconsin-Green Bay to switch to Century Gothic for the bulk of its printing needs.The school's IT department has asked staff and faculty to use Century Gothic whenever...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>