<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7087">Jonathan Kreisberg discography</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:05:01" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7087-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7087_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:05:02">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/09/jonathan-coulton-interview/</link><title>Web 2.Rockstar: The robotic tale of Jonathan Coulton</title><description>... of, figuring out how to control their own careers. The first of these, Jonathan Coulton, has decided... This is a song about math, Jonathan Coulton told a huge crowd of fans at PAX 2007, and they erupted... into a career. Jonathan Coulton is now a full-time musician. Our intimate chat with the man himself...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7087-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7087_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:06:26">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/03/doing-science-jonathan-coulton-to-create-music-for-portal-2/</link><title>Doing science: Jonathan Coulton to create music for Portal 2</title><description>...Portal was something of a perfect storm. Game mechanics that felt new, a story that tied into the world of Half-Life, a length that didn't outstay its own welcome, and to really drive the point home the end credits featured the instantly memorable song "Still Alive" by Jonathan...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7087-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7087_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:08:12">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/06/post-10/</link><title>Jonathan Mak's Sound Shapes may be NGP's killer app</title><description>...Jonathan Mak was a busy man during the NGP preview event in Los Angeles. While higher profile games such as Uncharted were immediately impressive, word quickly spread to check out his rhythm game, and he found himself beset by the press. He was fine with it: the creator of Everyday Shooter was able...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7087-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7087_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:09:39">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/05/apple-designer-jonathan-ive-winced-over-some-apple-design-choices/</link><title>Apple designer Jonathan Ive "winced" over some Apple design choices</title><description>...Apple's prized product designer Jonathan ("Jony") Ive is a constant source of fascination among the pressdoubly so after the death of Appleco-founderSteve Jobs. Though Ive appears with relative frequency in news articles and documentaries, interest in his design philosophy has never...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7087-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7087_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:11:57">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/10/apple-posts-jonathan-ives-favorite-industrial-macbook-pr0n/</link><title>Apple posts Jonathan Ive's favorite industrial MacBook pr0n</title><description>...Sure you can watch a stream of Apples keynote event yesterday at which it refreshed the MacBook lineup and introduced a MacBook-only Cinema Display. But dont you want to see the good stuff? At Apples notebook event yesterday, Jonathan Ive, Apples Senior VP of Industrial Design, said of the new...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7087-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7087_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:16:03">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/03/getting-lost-in-jonathan-blows-the-witness/</link><title>Getting lost in Jonathan Blow's The Witness</title><description>... advice when I get stuck. So I was a bit surprised when Braid creator Jonathan Blow started... be the only tools the player needs to get through.Yeah... there's the loneliness. Jonathan...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7087-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7087_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:17:31">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/braid-finally-coming-to-the-pc-in-march/</link><title>Braid finally coming to the PC in March</title><description>...Last year Braid creator Jonathan Blow revealed that the PC version of his hit Xbox Live Arcade game was being delayed in an attempt to bypass the dreaded Holiday glut of games. Now we finally have a release date for the port, which will be coming out via three different online distributors.?I...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7087-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7087_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:19:52">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/06/genachowski-mcdowell-confirmed-two-more-to-go/</link><title>Genachowski, McDowell confirmed for FCC; two more to go</title><description>... Commissioner Jonathan Adelstein will leave the FCC. Adelstein is scheduled to run the United States Department...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7087-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7087_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:23:45">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/05/harvard-prof-to-chair-fccs-net-neutrality-advisory-committee/</link><title>Harvard prof to chair FCC's net neutrality advisory committee</title><description>...The Federal Communications Commission has named an Open Internet Advisory Committee to monitor and report on the effectiveness of the FCC's network neutrality regime. The committee will be chaired by Harvard law professor Jonathan Zittrain. According to a statement from FCC chairman Julius...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7087-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7087_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:26:33">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/04/ars-at-the-museum-the-art-of-video-games-at-the-smithsonian/</link><title>Ars at the Museum: The Art of Video Games at the Smithsonian</title><description>... for the film's CGA graphics. Jonathan GitlinThe exhibition actually opened a couple of weeks ago... with dry ice. Jonathan GitlinFast forward a couple of weeks (or skip through some cut scenes... to current consoles. Jonathan GitlinBathed in a cool blue light, the exhibit greets you with a projected...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>