<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7093">What do i need to go fly fishing?</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:49:09" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7093-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7093_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:49:10">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/05/flying-car-crashes-near-elementary-school-in-canada/</link><title>Flying car crashes near elementary school in Canada</title><description>...A flying car crashed near an elementary school in Vernon, British Columbia on Friday, according... is named Maverick, and CBC calls it the fifth-ever flying car in Canada. The Transportation Safety Board confirmed the crash, calling the vehicle an I-Tech Maverick SP Powered Parachute. The company...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7093-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7093_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:50:54">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/02/what-wed-do-in-a-perfect-world-to-fix-the-psp-go/</link><title>What we'd do (in a perfect world) to fix the PSP Go</title><description>... Network is a great service. The PSP Go? It needs work, and if Sony can't do what's necessary... needs to do the same thing. "We highly encourage Sony to make simultaneous digital releases... to a halt?Does the system even need to be saved?Anothe...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7093-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7093_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:54:53">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/01/doing-math-on-the-fly-birds-form-the-flying-v-for-efficiency/</link><title>Doing math on the fly, birds form the flying V for efficiency</title><description>... formation timed their movements differently to those flying in a single-file line, just as they need..., have an innate ability to do the required mathematics, quite literally, on the fly: judging the distance...Across the globe, hundreds of species of birds can be seen flying in V ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7093-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7093_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:56:27">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/08/ars-does-soylent-day-2-my-god-what-have-i-gotten-myself-into/</link><title>Ars does Soylent, Day 2: My God, what have I gotten myself into</title><description>...Day 1 recap: Like trench warfare in FranceI ended the previous entry saying that I was going to head out running, but that did not happen. As it got nearer to 7pm, I started feeling ominous rumblings in my bellythe kind that could either be the sign of some harmless gas or the harbinger of the poopocalypse. I stayed in, instead watching a couple of episodes of The Wire with my wife, who ate a fin...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7093-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7093_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:59:33">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/02/ask-ars-what-do-i-do-with-a-dead-ups/</link><title>Ask Ars: What do I do with a dead UPS?</title><description>... take. To submit your own question, see our helpful tips page. Question: My UPS is dead and I need to dispose of it. Is there any kind of special consideration here (is it dangerous?), or can I just dump..., so it needs to be disposed of properly. That's also true of cadmium, an ingredient...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7093-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7093_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:03:43">http://arstechnica.com/science/2008/12/wait-what-was-i-going-to-title-this-article/</link><title>Wait... what was I going to title this article?</title><description>...People forget. Whether it was something that happened 10 years ago or what you had for breakfast, we forget. Why we forget, especially in the short-term, is an open ended problem in experimental... amounts of time did better when asked what the sequence of characters was than their peers...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7093-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7093_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:04:16">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/01/have-iphone-will-fly-hands-on-with-the-ardrone-ready/</link><title>Have iPhone will fly: hands on with the AR.Drone</title><description>...Are you interested in something you can fly? A video game? A hacking project? The AR.Drone... notes. It doesn't really complete with the standard flying toys and models you'll find... make sure that it stays stable; I was able to walk up to it and give it a nice push to watch...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7093-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7093_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:07:05">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/04/fruit-flies-show-why-swatting-at-flies-is-often-fruitless/</link><title>Fruit flies show why swatting at flies is often fruitless</title><description>... slapped yourself and the table many times, yet the fly continues to taunt you?Flies impressive... flies can rapidly make banked turns, executing them far faster than their regular flight movements.To study fruit fly flying technique, they constructed a test environment with high-spe...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7093-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7093_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:08:18">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/06/what-to-expect-from-google-io-2012-tasty-android-treats-and-nexus-tablets/</link><title>What to expect from Google I/O 2012: tasty Android treats and Nexus tablets</title><description>... screen" app development in the I/O session list. Its possible that Google is going to show off... and Google TV boxes.Ars Technicas Ryan Paul and Dan Goodin are going to be at Google I/O this week to catch...Googles annual developer conference, called Google I/O, is set to begi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7093-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7093_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:10:04">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2014/03/information-overload-i-know-too-much-to-program-quickly-what-can-i-do/</link><title>Information overload: I know too much to program quickly. What can I do?</title><description>... note, I recently started doing the pomodoro technique and it has helped a lot. Instead of going... still happy with my choice, I love programming, and I consider myself good at what I do.Lately... so many different ways in which things c...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>