<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7094">calculate inertia sphere</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:11:37" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7094-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7094_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:11:38">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/11/cats-use-gravity-inertia-gecko-like-process-to-lap-up-cream/</link><title>Cats use gravity, inertia, gecko-like process to lap up cream</title><description>... of their tongue to pull water into their mouths from the surface. Once there, they exploit inertia... thanks to sheer inertia. Cats then take advantage of their head orientation and gravity to hold...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7094-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7094_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:13:05">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/02/at-long-last-ti-releases-graphing-calculator-for-the-ipad/</link><title>At long last, TI releases graphing calculator for the iPad</title><description>...Texas Instruments has brought its graphing calculator functionality to a more modern platform... calculatorand has cloud integration for teachers to share files with students.TIs graphing calculators... the graphing calculator functionality into devices that students are likely carrying around with them...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7094-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7094_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:14:05">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/11/remember-ti-84-calculators-theyre-finally-getting-color-screens/</link><title>Remember TI-84 calculators? They're finally getting color screens</title><description>... that most graphing calculators have, inexplicably, forgone for ages. But finally, Texas Instruments... of its TI-84 calculator, according to a post Friday at TechPoweredMath.Calculators... operating system.In February 2011, Texas Instruments released a new graphing calculator named the TI...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7094-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7094_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:17:51">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/12/portals-physics-engine-rebuilt-in-25kb-on-a-graphing-calculator/</link><title>Portal's physics engine rebuilt in 25KB—on a graphing calculator</title><description>..., from the ground up, onwait for ita graphing calculator. In a display that puts the old calculator versions... on TI-83/84 calculators, execute more than 16 kilobytes of code.When Marcolina set out to rebuild Portal on TIs graphing calculator platform, he was 17. Now, hes a 20-year-old game design major a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7094-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7094_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:19:52">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/03/how-nasa-got-an-android-handset-ready-to-go-into-space/</link><title>How NASA got an Android handset ready to go into space</title><description>...Its what science fiction dreams are made of: brightly colored, sphere-shaped robots that float above the ground, controlled by a tiny computer brain. But it isn't fiction:its the SPHERES... Gingerbread. (HET is a project at NASA's Ames Research Center that uses SPHERES, which stands...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7094-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7094_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:22:15">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/01/squeezing-a-circle-on-the-surface-of-a-sphere/</link><title>Squeezing a circle on the surface of a quantum sphere</title><description>... on a curved surfacethe surface of a sphere for instance. In this case, the effect of squeezing depends... of the joint polarization state sits on a very small sphere with a sharply curved surface. The researchers... the sphere. As the squeezing increases, it wraps further around, and also twists slightly. There comes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7094-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7094_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:23:30">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/12/why-ti-80-series-graphing-calculators-took-22-years-to-go-color/</link><title>A big evolutionary step for a mystifyingly arcane device</title><description>... graphing calculators with a color screen next year, in large part because graphing calculators are near... decades ago. Why did TI wait so long? And after waiting so long, why now?Graphing calculators... Instruments created its first graphing calculator, dubbed the TI-81, for use by students in high school...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7094-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7094_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:25:30">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/03/how-nonlocal-can-we-make-the-universe/</link><title>Calculating the universe's lack of locality</title><description>... we knew the quantum mechanics might well be nonlocal. Eventually, John Bell calculated how strongly.... Its authors calculate how strongly correlated two systems can be based purely on information theory. It turns...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7094-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7094_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:26:21">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/06/simulating-the-sounds-of-water/</link><title>Calculating the sounds of water</title><description>... more complex physical setups. Theyeventuallyplan to have these calculations complete in real time, allowing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7094-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7094_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:27:29">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/09/odin-sphere-devs-new-game-coming-next-year/</link><title>Odin Sphere dev's new game coming next year</title><description>... Sphere and Grim Grimoirenext project, but it looks like we will be seeing it some time next year... will have a lot in common with Odin Sphere, from the beautifully detailed 2D graphics, to the fast... methods of control, with one aimed at more casual fans. Odin Sphere was one of the best late...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>