<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7095">iron in water supply</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:29:22" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7095-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7095_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:29:23">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/08/himalayan-water-supply-gets-an-improved-outlook/</link><title>Himalayan water supply gets an improved outlook</title><description>... with headwaters that are fed by glacial melt high in the Himalayas.Those rivers supply water to a staggeringly... to their earlier results, the researchers found no decrease in total water supplied to either of the rivers... of Glacier National Park in the US into a sad irony, the loss of glacial ice can ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7095-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7095_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:30:10">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/06/history-of-water-availability-in-rockies-region-shows-trouble-ahead/</link><title>History of water availability in the Rockies shows trouble ahead</title><description>..., acts like a massive frozen water tower, providing a steady supply of water throughout the drier... that, as warming continues, the region will have to prepare, as they put it, for "water-supply reductions...Communities in the Rocky Mountain region of North America rely on snow...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7095-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7095_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:34:33">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/09/can-pumping-too-much-groundwater-raise-sea-level/</link><title>Can pumping too much groundwater raise sea level?</title><description>...The overuse of groundwater is a concern that looms over discussions of water supply in many regions around the world. Many groundwater aquifers are pumped more quickly than they can be replenished, meaning wells have to be drilled deeper and deeper to reach an ever-diminishing resource. The Ogallala Aquifer, which extends from Nebraska to Texas, is a prime example. There, groundwater irrigation h...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7095-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7095_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:35:40">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/02/reverse-alchemy-replacing-precious-platinum-with-ignoble-iron/</link><title>Reverse alchemy: replacing precious platinum with ignoble iron</title><description>... managed to substitute an iron-based one. They found that "in many examples, the new base-metal (iron) catalysts offer advantages in both activity and selectivity over currently employed precious.... In the presence of the iron catalyst and fairly mild conditions (barely above room temperature), 2000 ppm...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7095-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7095_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:38:03">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/06/adding-iron-is-like-giving-early-rna-enzymes-steroids/</link><title>Adding iron is like giving early RNA enzymes "steroids"</title><description>... shapes for catalysis. Changing that metal to iron could increase the types of reactions.... Once photosynthetic organisms appeared and started pumping out oxygen, that iron turned to rust... of the RNA backbone just one sugar flanked by two phosphate groups. They plunked a magnesium or an iron...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7095-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7095_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:38:35">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/08/water-going-going-gone/</link><title>Water: going, going, gone</title><description>...The availability of clean water is key to life, happiness, and prosperity. For those of us... of the world's population. When it comes to water resource management, things get tricky very quickly, as the "ownership" of water resources can be contentious. It is difficult to estimate...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7095-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7095_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:41:21">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/07/apple-to-replace-time-capsules-with-dodgy-power-supplies/</link><title>Apple to replace Time Capsules with dodgy power supplies</title><description>...Users with a Time Capsule that has a failing power supply will notice that it doesn't power on or will shut downwithout warningafter powering up. Apple has identified a range of Time Capsules... in this range exhibiting power supply problems, Apple will repair or replace it free of charge. If you...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7095-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7095_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:44:08">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/04/can-we-actually-taste-water-insects-can/</link><title>Can we actually taste water? Insects can</title><description>...Think back to the last glass of water you drank. Did you actually taste the water? Before you..., but you would be able to feel its presence in your mouth. In much the same way, we can feel the water we drink, it's not clear whether we actually taste anything beyond trace elements in the water...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7095-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7095_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:45:01">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/02/humanitys-water-footprint-sasquatch-is-thirsty/</link><title>Humanity's water footprint: US exports the most, uses the most per capita</title><description>...Most people are familiar with the concept of a "carbon footprint," and some even feel dutifully guilty about their own. "Water footprints" get a little less play. Even though we live on a blue planet (oddly named "Earth" by one of its continentally-biased inhabitants), water is still a precious resource that warrants conservation. After all, over 99 percent of that w...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7095-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7095_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:46:51">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/10/3d-printing-loosens-cgis-iron-grip-on-movie-special-effects/</link><title>3D printing loosens CGI’s iron grip on movie special effects</title><description>...;s use in Iron Man 2: the special effects studio scanned Robert Downey Jr.'s hands and printed models of his appendages to make a more comfortable version of his Iron Man suit. 3D printers...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>