<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7096">touchpad scroll dell latitude</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:50:34" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7096-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7096_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:50:36">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/01/dell-leaks-its-own-new-latitude-xt2-tablet/</link><title>Dell leaks its own new Latitude XT2 tablet</title><description>... fans with a buffed up line of its own brand, Dell has accidentally let slip some shots and specs for its new Latitude XT2 tablet PC. Details on the new XT2, which will replace the original XT, came...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7096-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7096_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:52:28">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/10/dell-locates-source-of-cat-pee-smell-in-laptops-after-four-months/</link><title>Dell locates source of cat pee smell in laptops after four months</title><description>...Dell users rose up mightily in June to tell the company that it was... shipping laptops that smelled like cat urine, according to the BBC. Four months later, Dell has finally figured out the the culprit: a palm rest.The computer in question was the Dell Latitude 6430u, which many users claimed...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7096-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7096_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:53:15">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/03/leaked-retailer-info-hp-touchpad-arriving-in-june-for-499/</link><title>Leaked retailer info: HP Touchpad arriving in June for $499</title><description>...HP revealed its upcoming Touchpad tablet during a press event last month. The 10-inch touch-enabled..., with different tiers based on storage capacity. A $499 price point at launch will help make the Touchpad... Touchpad will have a June launch. This is consistent with HP's previous statements...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7096-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7096_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:56:07">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/06/hp-touchpad-tablet-makes-surprise-appearance-at-tech-conference/</link><title>HP webOS TouchPad tablet makes surprise appearance at Computex</title><description>...HP's planned iPad killer, the HP TouchPad, popped up among the booths at the Computex show... for HP's devices, had a TouchPad on display at its booth at Computex. A SanDisk representative... one of the long sides of the TouchPad. The operating system looked pretty snappy overall, though...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7096-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7096_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:57:56">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/06/make-a-date-with-your-palm-hp-touchpad-coming-july-1/</link><title>Write it on your Palm: HP Touchpad coming July 1</title><description>...HP has announced the official launch date for its upcoming TouchPad tablet. The product will be available for purchase in the United States on July 1. Launches will follow in the UK, France, and Germany during the first week of July. Broader international availability will occur later this year.HP...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7096-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7096_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:01:17">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/08/elder-scrolls-vs-minecraft-dev-scrolls-is-our-word/</link><title>Elder Scrolls vs. Minecraft dev: "scrolls" is our word</title><description>...ZeniMax Media publishes a series of role-playing games called The Elder Scrolls, developed... behind Minecraft, is currently developing a collectible card-style game called Scrolls. Confused... that the developer has infringed upon The Elder Scrolls trademark.What's going onLast week...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7096-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7096_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:02:58">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/07/microsoft-apple-others-sued-over-touchpad-patent/</link><title>Microsoft, Apple, others sued over touchpad patent</title><description>... Tsera which claims to have invented the touchpad. The lawsuit, filed last week in the US District Court...; portable radio, voice recorder, or portable CD player are disclosed. A touchpad is mounted... of the touchpad. No immediate visual feedback is provided as a command pattern is traced, and the user does...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7096-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7096_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:05:41">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/07/more-major-dell-stakeholders-say-no-to-go-private-deal/</link><title>Update: More major Dell stakeholders say no to go-private deal</title><description>...As the vote approaches on Michael Dell's joint offer with Silver Lake Partners to take Dell... own 11.5 percent of Dell Inc's stock, will oppose the Dell/Silver Lake offer of $13.65... that voting block, Dell will need those who hold at least 42 percent of the remainder...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7096-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7096_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:08:48">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/01/dell-unveils-latitude-10-essentials-tablet-under-500-just-barely/</link><title>Dell unveils Latitude 10 “Essentials” tablet under $500 (just barely)</title><description>... of the Intel Atom-based Latitude 10 tablet Dell announced in October. It's designed with one thing... of the Latitude 10 Essentials configuration may be enough to spark some interest. And Dell has a lead...At CES today, Dell unveiled another entry in its Windows 8 tablet line a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7096-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7096_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:11:26">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/06/ars-hp-touchpad-review/</link><title>webOS takes on tablets: Ars reviews the HP TouchPad</title><description>...First announced back in February, the HP TouchPad looked like a powerful way to extend the rescued..., and their waiting has at last been rewarded: the TouchPad launches today with the much-improved webOS 3.0... options. The TouchPad delivers smooth and snappy performance on everything from games to Web browsing...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>