<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7098">tour moscow</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:15:25" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7098-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7098_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:15:27">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/07/moscow-metro-says-new-tracking-system-is-to-find-stolen-phones-no-one-believes-them/</link><title>Moscow Metro says new tracking system is to find stolen phones; no one believes them</title><description>...On Monday, a major Russian newspaper reported that Moscows metro system is planning what appears... phones.According to Izvestia (Google Translate), Andrey Mokhov, the operations chief of the Moscow Metro systems... to intercept the audio of voice calls.The Moscow Metro did not immediately respond to our request...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7098-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7098_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:17:02">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/06/with-wikileaks-help-snowden-lands-in-moscow-headed-on-to-democratic-nation/</link><title>With WikiLeaks’ help, Snowden lands in Moscow, headed on to “democratic nation”</title><description>... Hong Kong on a commercial flight, landed in Moscow, and was reportedly picked up by Venezuelan... the State Department in Washington, D.C., and the Ecuadorian Embassy in Moscow for confirmation... that Snowden is spending the night in Moscow before heading for Havana, Cuba. He will then continue...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7098-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7098_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:17:54">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/07/ecuador-president-snowden-cant-leave-moscow-airport-without-russias-ok/</link><title>Ecuador president: Snowden can’t leave Moscow airport without Russia’s OK</title><description>... transit zone in Moscows Sheremetyevo Airportseem to be stymying Ecuadors every effort to get Snowden...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7098-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7098_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:20:22">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/06/dragon-age-to-go-on-tour/</link><title>Dragon Age to go on tour</title><description>... to its fall release, the cooler it seems. Now, Bioware has announced that the game is going on tour around... on the tour will feature a lot of RPG products on display. Based on what we got to see of the game... style that everyone expects from a Bioware game. Here's the tour list: San Diego Comic-Con, July...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7098-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7098_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:23:02">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/06/guitar-hero-world-tour-full-band-90-via-amazon/</link><title>Guitar Hero: World Tour full band $90 via Amazon</title><description>...Guitar Hero: World Tour comes in a big, heavy box. There are multiple Hero games coming... Rock Band and Guitar Hero sale, and today Amazon is featuring Guitar Hero: World Tour as the deal... Tour drums beat the Rock Band drums hands down, but that's pure opinion. I prefer the Rock Band...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7098-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7098_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:24:07">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/12/the-eagles-land-in-guitar-hero-world-tour/</link><title>The Eagles land in Guitar Hero: World Tour</title><description>...Just in case Hotel California wasnt enough to satiate your desire for The Eagles, Activision has announced a new track pack that will be bringing three more classic rock tunes to Guitar Hero: World Tour. The new DLC joins the ranks of Nirvana and The Smashing Pumpkins, both of whom had similar...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7098-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7098_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:25:14">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/11/the-raconteurs-join-guitar-hero-world-tour/</link><title>The Raconteurs join Guitar Hero: World Tour line-up</title><description>...This time around it looks like Activision is actually going to fulfill its promise to consistently add new downloadable songs to Guitar Hero: World Tour. After releasing a Jimi Hendrix track pack last week, they are doing the same for the Jack White-fronted band The Raconteurs. The content pack...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7098-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7098_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:28:26">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/11/more-hendrix-songs-released-for-guitar-hero-world-tour/</link><title>More Hendrix songs released for Guitar Hero: World Tour</title><description>...Jimi Hendrix, the man Rolling Stone Magazine declared to be the greatest guitar player of all time, is adding more songs to Activisions newest Guitar Hero entry. Microsofts Major Nelson announced today that the original and greatest of axe men is coming to Guitar Hero: World Tour with an exclusive...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7098-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7098_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:30:17">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/10/guitar-hero-world-tour-launch-dlc-detailed/</link><title>Guitar Hero: World Tour launch DLC detailed</title><description>...One of the major selling points of Rock Band over Guitar Hero has been the games extensive library of downloadable content. With the upcoming GH: World Tour, Activision is hoping to change that by providing a steady stream of downloadable songs. In addition to the strong on-disc track list for GH...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7098-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7098_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:31:22">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/guitar-hero-world-tour-getting-stand-alone-instruments/</link><title>Guitar Hero: World Tour stand-alone drums, guitar ship</title><description>... instruments for Guitar Hero: World Tour without buying the game itself. Activision has finally announced... will be compatible with both World Tour and the upcoming Guitar Hero: Metallica. Unfortunately... firm believers that the World Tour drums are better quality than what you get with Rock Band 2...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>