<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7099">lecture manova</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:32:33" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7099-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7099_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:32:35">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/04/testing-students-during-video-lectures-improves-learning/</link><title>Testing students during video lectures improves learning</title><description>...;flipped" classroom model, where students take lectures through videos at their convenience and spend..., he did something similar. In the first experiment, he divided a 21-minute lecture into four segments... followed by tests on the subject matter of the lecture. The other half (the non-tested group) just...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7099-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7099_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:33:41">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/01/punched-up-lectures-hands-on-with-the-new-itunes-u-app-for-ios/</link><title>Punched up lectures: hands on with the new iTunes U app for iOS</title><description>... at Ars have already dabbled in listening to iTunes U lectures in the past, we were interested... the app.Once you download a few lectures that interest you, you can go back to your main "Library" to check out what you have. When you load up that particular lecture series, the app will tell...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7099-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7099_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:35:12">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/12/how-to-market-your-indie-games-ben-kucheras-lecture-at-run-jump-dev/</link><title>How to market your indie games: Ben Kuchera's lecture at Run Jump Dev</title><description>...There is a group of independent game developers called Run Jump Dev that meets in Lexington Kentucky of all placesto discuss their projects and share information and stories and stories about the games they're creating. Since I live in Cincinnati and love to support both local groups who game and independent developers as a whole, I jumped at the chance to speak to the group when they invite...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7099-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7099_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:36:34">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/01/stanford-offering-updated-iphone-dev-course-on-itunes-u/</link><title>Stanford offering updated iPhone dev course on iTunes U</title><description>...Like it did last year, Stanford University has posted the complete lecture and presentation slides...: it was downloaded from iTunes more than 4.4 million times last year. The latest series of lectures are updated... aspects of the classes," Julie Zelenski, a Stanford computer science lecturer, told The Loop.Unlike...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7099-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7099_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:38:15">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/02/study-listening-to-podcasts-better-than-going-to-lectures/</link><title>Study: class podcasts can lead to better grades</title><description>...Listening to podcasted versions of university lectures seems to be better for students than simply... students soaked up information, McKinney and her team gave a psychology lecture to 64 students. The students were then split into groups after the lecture, one group receiving printed slides...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7099-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7099_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:39:16">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/08/newest-youtube-user-to-fight-a-takedown-is-copyright-guru-lawrence-lessig/</link><title>Newest YouTube user to fight a takedown is copyright guru Lawrence Lessig</title><description>... lecture of Lessig's entitled "Open," they were mistaken. Lessig has teamed... in Lessig's lecture. According to the complaint, Lessig showed clips of different groups... and response' tradition of communication."The lecture was from 2010, but Lessig posted it in June...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7099-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7099_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:40:39">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/05/iphoneipod-touch-prescribed-to-mu-journalism-students/</link><title>iPhone/iPod touch prescribed to MU journalism students</title><description>... because of recent research suggesting that students who are able to re-listen to lectures later... Journalism School associate dean Brian Brooks told the Missourian late last week that lectures alone... more information by listening to a recording of a lecture another time.The "requirement" to buy...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7099-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7099_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:43:07">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/01/the-legends-speak-how-gdc-got-great-developers-to-look-back/</link><title>The legends speak: how GDC got great developers to look back</title><description>...The Game Developers Conference has always been a place to hear the best and brightest in the video game industry talk about their craft, but something special had to be done to celebrate the show's 25th year in operation. The show's organizers had an idea: why not book a series of lectures by the people who created some of the best and most influential games in the industry's histo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7099-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7099_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:44:32">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/02/lawrence-lessig-wins-damages-after-rights-holder-demands-youtube-takedown/</link><title>Lawrence Lessig sees compensation after rights holder’s YouTube takedown</title><description>...On Thursday, a settlement was reached between Creative Commons co-founder Lawerence Lessig and Liberation Media, an Australian music label that owns the rights to French band Phoenix' song Lisztomania.Last summer, Liberation had a video of one of Lessig's lectures (called "Open," which is embedded above) taken down when the company found that he had used video clips with Phoen...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7099-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7099_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:48:01">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/04/stanford-iphone-developer-course-available-free-via-itunes-u/</link><title>Stanford iPhone developer course available free via iTunes U</title><description>... curriculum and the innovation of our students."Videos of all the lectures, lead by Apple engineers... this week. The slides from the lectures will be available to download as well. The school notes...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>