<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7100">korean bbq san francisco review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:51:20" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7100-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7100_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:51:21">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/09/driver-san-francisco-developer-defends-ubisoft-drm-practices/</link><title>Driver: San Francisco developer calls Ubisoft DRM "quite morally correct"</title><description>...Ubisoft has come under quite a bit of fire for its PC ports, including the recent delayed, DRM-laden version of From Dust. Driver: San Francisco, published by Ubisoft and developed by Ubisoft... with piracy then we wouldn't need it."Driver: San Francisco will also be the first game...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7100-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7100_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:55:26">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/10/startups-aboard-icebreaker-ship-could-face-eviction-soon-san-francisco-says/</link><title>Startups aboard “Icebreaker” ship could face eviction soon, San Francisco says</title><description>...Right now, moored at Pier 50 in San Francisco, theres a converted Icelandic icebreaking cargo ferry that's been a startup incubator over the last two years. (It was first tricked out to be used as a residence.)In exchange for living and co-working space aboard the ship, companies give up a small equity stake (or pay money or in-kind labor for maintenance) to the ships owners, which include B...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7100-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7100_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:58:11">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/05/san-francisco-backtracks-on-cell-phone-radiation-bill/</link><title>San Francisco backtracks on cell phone radiation bill</title><description>... instead. So reports Friday's San Francisco Chronicle, which says that it's not just... Senator Mark Leno of San Francisco says he's going to propose a new version of a cell phone...The City of San Francisco's controversial cell phone radiation disclosure bill has...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7100-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7100_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:01:32">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/03/san-franciscos-bay-bridge-becomes-a-glowing-network-of-ethernet-enabled-leds/</link><title>San Francisco’s Bay Bridge becomes a glowing network of Ethernet-enabled LEDs</title><description>...SAN FRANCISCO, CAOn Tuesday evening at 9pm local time, a 1.8 mile western span of the San Francisco... section between San Francisco and neighboring Treasure Island will display a dazzling array of 25,000... take over.At a press conference a few hours before th...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7100-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7100_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:04:25">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/08/did-bart-pull-a-mubarak-in-san-francisco/</link><title>Scenes from an Anonymous protest: Did San Francisco's subway "pull a Mubarak"?</title><description>...You could call it a modest victory for civil liberties. A police unit for Bay Area Rapid Transit (BART) briefly shut the Civic Center subway station in San Francisco on Monday evening in response to a demonstration. But, unlike last week, it appears that BART declined to cut off mobile phone access, even as activists briefly held up the departure of an outgoing train.I happened to be at the stati...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7100-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7100_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:06:27">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/03/the-dazzling-glory-of-san-franciscos-25000-leds-now-on-video/</link><title>The dazzling glory of San Francisco's 25,000 LEDs—now on video</title><description>...As we reported earlier this week (both in written and pictorial form), a prominent section of the San Francisco-Oakland Bay Bridge has been transformed into a massive public art project called... section between San Francisco and neighboring Treasure Island will display a dazzling array of 25,000...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7100-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7100_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:08:05">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2014/04/reporter-i-was-assaulted-for-wearing-google-glass-in-san-francisco/</link><title>Reporter: “I was assaulted for wearing Google Glass” in San Francisco</title><description>...In the aftermath of Fridays protest in front of the San Francisco home of a Google lawyer... has taken place: in February 2014, a social media consultant claimed she was assaulted at a San Francisco... in choosing to assault someone based on their appearance as a way to preserve San ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7100-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7100_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:11:07">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/04/reporter-i-was-assaulted-for-wearing-google-glass-in-san-francisco/</link><title>Reporter: “I was assaulted for wearing Google Glass” in San Francisco</title><description>...In the aftermath of Fridays protest in front of the San Francisco home of a Google lawyer...: in February 2014, a social media consultant claimed she was assaulted at a San Francisco bar for having... someone based on their appearance as a way to preserve San Francisco's culture...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7100-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7100_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:13:54">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/03/activist-sues-san-francisco-pd-after-warrantless-search-of-his-phone/</link><title>Activist sues San Francisco PD after warrantless search of his phone</title><description>...A San Francisco activist, a local attorney, and the American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU... it illegal to camp in public places without permission. A spokesperson for the San Francisco Police... this week, charge San Francisco and its police department with vio...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7100-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7100_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:14:51">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/07/san-francisco-turns-its-back-on-apple-after-green-registry-pull-out/</link><title>San Francisco turns its back on Apple after green registry pull-out</title><description>...The City of San Francisco will no longer be buying Macs following Apple's withdrawal of its products from the eco-friendly EPEAT registry. Officials from San Francisco's Department...;s bottom line may end up being minimal.Still, the City of San Francisco has apparently alr...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>