<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7101">innodb versus myisam</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:15:53" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7101-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7101_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:15:55">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/04/versus-mode-comes-to-resident-evil-5-tomorrow/</link><title>Versus mode comes to Resident Evil 5 tomorrow</title><description>...The multiplayer versus update for Resident Evil 5 has been given an official date, with the for-pay... you $5 on the PlayStation and 400 Microsoft points on the 360."Versus allows up to four... or other secret characters, and choose from either one-on-one or two-versus-two team matches for either...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7101-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7101_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:17:47">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/05/build-versus-buy-one-companys-decision-to-go-it-alone/</link><title>Build versus buy: one company's decision to go it alone</title><description>.... But it wasn't an easy decision to make."Whenever you're doing a buy versus build analysis...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7101-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7101_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:21:03">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/09/the-eternal-antitrust-case-microsoft-versus-the-world/</link><title>The eternal antitrust case: Microsoft versus the world</title><description>..., because the Microsoft antitrust case has never really ended. Like the "Jarndyce versus Jarndyce" legal...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7101-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7101_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:24:44">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/03/resident-evil-5-versus-mode-coming-after-launch-for-5/</link><title>Resident Evil 5 Versus mode coming after launch for $5</title><description>...While Resident Evil 5 is designed to be played in co-op mode, Capcom has sent word that a Versus mode will be added to the game... for a price. While we have no date other than "post-launch... as Chris, Sheva or other secret characters, and choose from either one-on-one or two-versus-two team...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7101-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7101_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:25:37">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2011/02/iphone-versus-iphone-ars-puts-verizon-and-att-to-the-test/</link><title>iPhone versus iPhone: Ars puts Verizon and ATandT to the test</title><description>... tests.Phone callsThe obvious appeal of the Verizon iPhone (versus its ATT equivalent) is the network. Many...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7101-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7101_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:27:10">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/05/oracle-google-judge-asks-for-comment-on-eu-court-ruling/</link><title>Oracle v. Google judge asks for comment on EU court ruling</title><description>...The copyright phase of the Oracle v. Google trial is winding down. While the world waits for a jury verdict on the facts, the judge overseeing the case is wrestling with the complexities of the law. Oracle has argued that the "structure, sequence and organization" of the Java API is eligible for copyright protection, while Google disagrees.On Thursday, Judge William Alsup asked each par...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7101-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7101_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:30:26">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/04/vc-in-chinese-tech-firms-drops-by-84-in-q1-2012-versus-q1-2011/</link><title>VC in Chinese tech firms drops by 84% in Q1 2012 versus Q1 2011</title><description>...A new study by Thomson Reuters reveals that in Q1 2012, venture capital in Chinese tech companies fell by 84 percent compared to Q1 2011. The new data released on Monday shows that venture capital firms invested only $138.5 million in Chinese Internet companies versus $866.5 million in the same...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7101-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7101_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:31:48">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/07/the-long-struggle-vaccines-versus-malaria/</link><title>The long struggle: vaccines versus malaria</title><description>...After clean water, vaccines may have saved more lives than any other public health intervention. Eradication of malaria, a disease that may have killed more humans than any other single cause, likely requires a malaria vaccine. However, after nearly a century of research, todays only candidate might not pack enough immunological punch to win deployment. Sadly, there are no obvious successors. Goa...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7101-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7101_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:35:45">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/05/oracle-google-lawyers-spar-over-androids-dalvik-vm-as-patent-phase-begins/</link><title>Oracle, Google lawyers spar over Android's Dalvik VM as patent phase begins</title><description>...The second phase of the Oracle v. Google trial got into full swing today, following yesterday's verdict, which left Oracle with a partial and inconclusive victory over Google. The subject matter has moved from copyrights to patents, and the next phase of the trial will deal with the "virtual machines" that both Android and Java use to speed up their operations. In opening statement...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7101-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7101_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:39:28">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/03/batteries-whats-here-versus-what-we-need/</link><title>Batteries: What’s here versus what we need</title><description>...We mostly think of batteries in terms of gadgets like phones and laptops. Although we'd all love lighter weight, higher capacity, and faster charging for our gadgets, progress for this type of battery hasfor the most partalready made huge strides. The modern battery is largely keeping pace with our needs.But two other big potential users of batteriesthe electric grid and automobileshaven&amp;apo...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>