<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7102">vlc mac</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:40:17" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7102-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7102_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:40:18">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/07/vlc-10-officially-released/</link><title>VLC 1.0 officially released after more than 10 years of work</title><description>...The open source VLC Media Player finally reached version 1.0 on Tuesday. The new version, codenamed... in the development effort. VLC has attracted a tremendous community of contributors who continue to advance... out an already impressive set of features. VLC can be used for everything from serving up streaming video...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7102-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7102_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:41:16">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/04/videolan-looking-for-help-from-experienced-mac-os-x-devs/</link><title>VideoLAN looking for help from experienced Mac OS X devs</title><description>...If you're a Mac OS X developer with some free time and want to contribute to the most popular media player alternative for the platform, then the VideoLAN team is looking for you.The recent VLC update, 0.9.9, was designed to improve video performance on Intel-based Macs, as well as fix several...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7102-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7102_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:43:19">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/07/vlc-media-player-returns-to-the-ios-app-store-after-30-month-hiatus/</link><title>VLC media player returns to the iOS App Store after 30-month hiatus</title><description>...After disappearing the better part of three years ago, the VLC media player app for iOS has made... from the Web.A version of VLC created by the company Applidium first made its debut on the App Store back in November 2010, but it was pulled in January 2011 due to a licensing dispute. All versions of VLC...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7102-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7102_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:47:26">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/11/the-vlc-ios-license-dispute-and-how-it-could-spread-to-android/</link><title>The VLC-iOS license dispute and how it could spread to Android</title><description>...Video fanatics were thrilled when an iOS version of VLC made its way to the App Store recently... like they do with the (ever-popular) VLC desktop clients. That may not last forever, though: a wrench has now been thrown into the mix by one of the many VLC code contributors, leading to a complex...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7102-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7102_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:50:13">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2011/01/vlc-for-ios-vanishes-2-months-after-eruption-of-gpl-dispute/</link><title>VLC for iOS vanishes 2 months after eruption of GPL dispute</title><description>...It's official: the iOS version of VLC has been yanked from the App Store. Though Apple... to a licensing dispute that started more than two months ago. The iOS version of VLC was not developed... for free. However, one of the programmers who contributed to the original VLC code, Rmi Denis...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7102-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7102_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:53:53">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/11/week-in-apple-macbook-air-review-ars-ipad-app-vlc-drama-and-more/</link><title>Week in Apple: MacBook Air review, Ars iPad app, VLC drama, and more</title><description>...: a new lawsuit over the iPhone 3G, conflicts over VLC licensing for iOS, the impending release of iOS... crippling the devices in order to boost sales for the iPhone 4. The VLC-iOS license dispute and how it could spread to Android: There's drama going on behind closed doorsand in publicover VLC...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7102-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7102_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:58:18">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/09/hands-on-with-vlc-movie-player-for-ipad/</link><title>Hands on with VLC Movie-Player for iPad</title><description>... miss is the volume boost of desktop VLC. ITunes on both the Mac and the iPad have whisperingly low... any file? Thanks to VLC for the iPad, there is.VLC is a port of the popular and excellent desktop... version of VLC is simpler than the desktop version, and quite a lot prettier. To get movies...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7102-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7102_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:59:33">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2014/01/apple-execs-badmouth-touchscreens-os-convergence-on-the-macs-30th-birthday/</link><title>Apple execs badmouth touchscreens, OS convergence on the Mac’s 30th birthday</title><description>... about where the Mac has been and where it's going.An incredible amount of thought and creativity went into the original Mac metaphor, said Tribble. So there are some extremely strong threads of DNA... themthat the Mac should be easily approachable and learnable by just looking at it, that it should bend...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7102-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7102_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:01:44">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/12/ifixit-tears-the-2013-mac-pro-asunder-finds-an-actually-repairable-mac/</link><title>iFixit tears the 2013 Mac Pro asunder, finds an actually repairable Mac</title><description>..., or proprietary connectors on everything, it's been a long time since a Mac, iPhone, or iPad received anything but faint praise from iFixit.That changed today when iFixit tore the new Mac Pro apart... easy to repair and upgrade (for a Mac).Enlarge / The RAM and SSD are both dead simple to replace...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7102-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7102_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:02:23">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/11/apple-tells-fan-to-be-patient-about-mac-mini/</link><title>Apple tells fan to "be patient" about Mac mini</title><description>...Rumors of the possible demise of the Mac mini have been swirling around the Internet for a while..., who was so concerned that the company might kill the Mac mini that he e-mailed an Apple executive and received a phone call suggesting that the Mac mini may not be down for the count just yet. After a string...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>