<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7103">cystic fibrosis treatment</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:05:46" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7103-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7103_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:05:47">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/04/why-snake-oil-sells/</link><title>Why snake oil cures sell</title><description>.... Many alternative treatments, from homeopathy to a variety of herbal remedies, have been shown... treatment decisions spread. This has allowed them to show that ineffective treatments are often... or may not be efficacious, but regardless of that, I will have, in effect, demonstrated that treatment...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7103-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7103_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:06:43">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/08/addicted-to-the-internet-14500-please-for-first-us-rehab/</link><title>Addicted to the Internet? $14,500, please, at first US rehab</title><description>... treatment center designed to treat it has opened its doors. The Heavensfield Retreat Center has launched a program called reSTART located in Fall City, WA, which offers a 45-day treatment program.... This is in addition to psychiatric assessments, medical treatment, scholastic tutoring, and career guidance...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7103-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7103_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:07:42">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/02/set-objective-medical-standards-get-sued/</link><title>Set objective medical standards, get sued</title><description>... medical organization's attempts at formulating treatment standards for Lyme disease has been run off... of sophisticated tests for its presence and successful treatment with antibiotics. A subset of patients, however... that chronic Lyme disease is a real medical phenomenon, and maintains its own treatment guidelines...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7103-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7103_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:10:13">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/02/ibms-supercomputer-jeopardy-was-too-easy-time-to-cure-cancer/</link><title>IBM’s supercomputer: Jeopardy was too easy, time to cure cancer</title><description>...: curing cancer. Watson has spent the last year parsing data on cancer treatments from the Sloan... index. The results Watson returns are recommendations on treatment, in descending order..., Watson stacks treatments in the order of likelihood that theyll succeed. But the results...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7103-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7103_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:11:38">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/07/compounds-coax-hiv-out-of-hiding-so-it-can-be-eliminated/</link><title>Compounds coax HIV out of hiding so it can be eliminated</title><description>... addition to current treatments, which cannot eradicate these dormant viruses.Current HIV treatment... treatment, too, because it binds to protein kinase C better than prostratin. But there are several... in animals. They hope these new compounds could be used as part of a treatment that eliminates all HIV...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7103-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7103_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:14:02">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/02/six-month-treatment-limits-problems-with-peanut-allergies/</link><title>Six-month treatment limits problems with peanut allergies</title><description>... of the study, half the children were given this treatment, the other half a placebo. By the end.... In a second round, the authors gave the controls the chance to receive the treatment; 91 percent..., and most participants rated the treatment as improving the quality of their lives.The Lancet, 2014. DOI...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7103-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7103_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:14:48">http://arstechnica.com/business/2011/09/microsoft-office-likely-to-get-the-metro-treatment/</link><title>Microsoft Office likely to get the Metro treatment</title><description>... the Metro treatment. In a call with financial analysts Wednesday, Sinofsky was asked if Microsoft will use...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7103-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7103_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:17:32">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/03/a-treatment-for-white-nose-syndrome/</link><title>Possible treatment for bat white nose syndrome</title><description>.... Were going for a stopgap," said Boyles. The origins of WNS are still unknown, and no other treatment...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7103-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7103_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:18:42">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/12/insulin-pill-may-soon-be-a-reality-for-diabetes-treatment/</link><title>Insulin pill may soon be a reality for diabetes treatment</title><description>... treatment, nearly a quarter of all diabetes patients depend on insulin injections. Estimated annual...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7103-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7103_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:19:23">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/03/early-treatment-sometimes-lets-the-body-keep-hiv-in-check/</link><title>Early treatment sometimes lets the body keep HIV in check</title><description>..., came a report that early treatment with antivirals has allowed one individual to keep an HIV infection limited for extended periods of time without treatment. Now, a report in PLOS pathogens suggests... fourteen individuals who started antiviral treatment less than two months after first infection...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>