<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7105">dark knight rises dvd</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:40:06" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7105-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7105_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:40:08">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/05/eternal-darkness-creator-seeking-crowdfunding-for-spiritual-sequel/</link><title>Eternal Darkness creator seeking crowdfunding for spiritual sequel</title><description>...It's been almost 11 years since Eternal Darkness: Sanity's Requiem became the first M-rated game published by Nintendo, but to this day fans talk reverently about the GameCube cult classic's rich mythos and mind-bending "insanity effects." Now, Eternal Darkness director Dennis Dyack is trying to bring that magic back with plans to attract crowdfunding for a spiritual succ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7105-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7105_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:41:51">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/04/addictive-but-accesible-ars-explores-free-to-play-co-op-rpg-spiral-knights/</link><title>Addictive but accessible: free-to-play, co-op RPG Spiral Knights</title><description>... games continues to rise, and Spiral Knights is proof of this. It's fun, addictive... of, including camps filled with NPCs to chat with. Spiral Knights mac*, pc Release Date:now MSRP:Free Official site * = platform reviewed Spiral Knights plays like a very simplified action RPG. You can attack...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7105-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7105_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:46:11">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/09/20-steam-jedi-knight-collection-not-fit-for-modern-systems/</link><title>$20 Steam Jedi Knight Collection not fit for modern systems</title><description>...On Steam, you can purchase a $20 collection of Jedi Knight titles, including Star Wars Jedi Knight: Jedi Academy, Star Wars Jedi Knight II: Jedi Outcast, Star Wars Jedi Knight: Dark Forces II, Star Wars Jedi Knight: Mysteries of the Sith, and Star Wars: Dark Forces. That's a pretty awesome deal, right? It would be, if all the games worked on modern systems.From the slickdeals forum, here is...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7105-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7105_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:49:20">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/03/sega-details-free-to-play-mmo-spiral-knights-ars-readers-can-play-early/</link><title>Sega details free-to-play MMO Spiral Knights , Ars readers can play early</title><description>... submarine and has worked on browser-based games like Puzzle Piratesto create Spiral Knights... early.While it's an MMO, Spiral Knights also has a large focus on co-op, action RPG-style play... crafting, and guilds. Take a look at the game in action: Spiral Knights Spiral Knights is expected...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7105-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7105_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:51:57">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/02/knights-contract-starts-with-a-good-idea-descends-into-frustration/</link><title>Knight's Contract : loading screens with a side of combat</title><description>...... the case is not made.The idea of a knight who can't be killed guarding a witch with magical powers...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7105-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7105_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:53:56">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/09/batman-the-brave-and-the-bold-wii-is-a-lighter-dark-knight/</link><title>Batman: the Brave and the Bold Wii is a lighter Dark Knight</title><description>... it becomes a fresh way to fight the forces of evil as a (slightly less) Dark Knight. WayForward may...Batman is an always an interesting character, but the most recent takes on the Caped Crusader have been almost oppressively dark. Go back and read the comics that took place before Year...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7105-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7105_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:56:35">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/10/batman-arkham-origins-review-the-dark-knight-repeats/</link><title>Batman: Arkham Origins review: The Dark Knight repeats</title><description>... because it was so enjoyable.The Dark Knight GlitchesI'd be remiss here if I didn't mention the significant technical...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7105-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7105_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:58:00">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/03/stop-innovating-please-kaleidescape-loses-dvd-ripping-case/</link><title>Stop innovating, please: Kaleidescape loses DVD ripping case</title><description>... media servers, violated the terms of its DVD licensing agreement by allowing consumers to rip DVDs. The DVD Copy Control Association sets rules that all manufacturers of DVD players must follow. The organization objected to the DVD-ripping functionality of Kaleidescape's products and went...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7105-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7105_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:59:26">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/01/white-knight-chronicles-coming-to-north-america/</link><title>White Knight Chronicles confirmed for North America</title><description>...Japanese gamers have been enjoying the Level 5 developed RPG White Knight Chronicles since December 25, but until now we were never quite sure whether or not the title would make its way... denied either. With Final Fantasy XIII going multiplatform, White Knight Chronicles is the only big...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7105-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7105_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:00:04">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/12/dark-knight-blu-ray-scratches-surface-of-bd-live-potential/</link><title>Dark Knight Blu-ray scratches surface of BD-Live potential</title><description>...The Dark Knight was a huge theatrical release, and Warner Bros. is hoping its just as large a success on DVD and Blu-ray. The disc release is special for Warner as well: this is the first Blu-ray disc the studio has released that supports all the BD-Live extras available from players that support...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>