<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7106">active learning survey</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:03:59" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7106-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7106_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:04:00">http://arstechnica.com/staff/2010/06/love-us-hate-us-take-our-quick-reader-survey-and-be-heard/</link><title>Want to help steer the good ship Ars Technica? Take our quick survey</title><description>...Editor's note: I'm bumping this survey call again. We have nearly 6,000 responses so far... of surveys around here. We routinely ask you for feedback in surveys because it's one of three big... below.Rock the survey....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7106-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7106_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:04:31">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/04/testing-students-during-video-lectures-improves-learning/</link><title>Testing students during video lectures improves learning</title><description>... the time in class delving into issues they don't understand.But are they really improving learning... learning compared to classroom learning, but more rigorous studies were needed. After all, ease of access to the learning material comes with a bundle of distractions only a single click away...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7106-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7106_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:05:35">http://arstechnica.com/staff/2013/01/the-great-ars-survey-the-results-are-in/</link><title>The great Ars survey: The results are in</title><description>...Earlier this year we asked you, esteemed readers, to take our most recent survey and share your..., reader comments, and feedback from our peers in the industry, but we particularly value our surveys because so many of you are generous with your time. This year, nearly 17,000 people took the survey...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7106-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7106_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:07:32">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/06/samsung-galaxy-s-4-active-is-official-and-ready-when-you-are/</link><title>Samsung Galaxy S 4 Active is official and ready when you are</title><description>... that the Samsung Galaxy S 4 Active is official. Samsung confirmed the existence of the device today in a press... differences in hardware, however; the Galaxy S 4 Active features an LCD TFT rather than an Super... for adventure it really is, the Galaxy S 4 Active received an Ingress Protection factor of 67...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7106-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7106_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:08:48">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/08/learning-in-your-sleep-can-really-stink/</link><title>Learning in your sleep can really stink</title><description>..., they focused on two sensory systems, hearing and smell, that we know are active while a person is asleep..., and found something a bit odd. Once learned, an association was equally strong in both REM and non-REM sleep. But when it was learned it had a curious effect: associations learned during REM sleep...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7106-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7106_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:09:41">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/03/what-scientists-really-think-about-animal-research/</link><title>What scientists really think about animal research</title><description>... practices.About 30 percent of US scientists surveyed knew someone who had been negatively affected by animal rights activism; this percentage was slightly higher in the UK and slightly lower in the rest of the world. Activism ranges from complaints and protests to outright threats and physical attacks. In 2009...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7106-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7106_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:10:52">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/06/pre-orders-for-the-samsung-galaxy-s-4-active-begin-tomorrow-at-att/</link><title>Pre-orders for the Samsung Galaxy S 4 Active begin tomorrow at ATandT</title><description>... handset will soon be available at ATT. The company announced that it will carry the Galaxy S 4 Active... water without touching the screen. The Galaxy S 4 Active also features an LCD TFT rather than an Super AMOLED display.The Active will also support both LTE and 3G HSPA+.We expect to hear...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7106-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7106_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:12:13">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/02/survey-tries-quantifying-ipad-hype-suggests-interest-waning/</link><title>Survey tries quantifying iPad hype, suggests interest waning</title><description>..."iPad hoopla" has passed, according toa survey by electronics shopping site Retrevo... they were confident they would buy one after finding out the product's details.Retrevo did similar surveys... and after. The week prior to Apple's big media event, 26 percent of those surveyed said they knew...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7106-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7106_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:12:52">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/03/wireless-survey-91-of-americans-have-cell-phones/</link><title>Wireless survey: 91% of Americans use cell phones</title><description>... of its semiannual US wireless industry survey for the last half of 2009. Even in the face... to grow as a vast majority of the US population is using a mobile phone.The survey of wireless... of overall wireless services revenue and up 26 percent year-over-year.The survey revealed that 257 million...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7106-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7106_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:15:33">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/03/survey-macs-cost-notably-less-to-support-than-windows-pcs/</link><title>Survey: Macs cost notably less to support than Windows PCs</title><description>... believed to have a lower total cost of ownership (TCO) due to lower support costs. A recent survey... it easier to integrate Macs in Windows-centric IT deployments, surveyed IT admins from companies... and developers (especially cross-platform developers).Apple has historically done little to actively develop...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>