<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7107">grimm episodes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:18:13" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7107-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7107_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:18:15">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/10/no-edits-comic-feature/</link><title>Grimm Season 2 launches with strong episode</title><description>... different than what previous episodes have presented. Instead of Grimm simply corrupting...Here at Ars, weve been fans of American McGees Grimm ever since Ben got to play around with a preview build of the first episode. So far, weve actually been pretty impressed with the games weve...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7107-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7107_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:20:55">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/04/star-wars-episode-vii-charges-ahead-now-reportedly-with-peter-mayhew/</link><title>Star Wars: Episode VII charges ahead, now reportedly with Peter Mayhew</title><description>... Mayhew will be playing the part of Chewbacca in Disney's upcoming Star Wars: Episode VII. Mayhew... that Episode VII will be set after Return of the Jedithirty five years after, in fact. Nailing...'ll have to wait a year and a half to find out: Episode VII istargeting a US release around...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7107-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7107_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:23:49">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/10/half-life-2-episode-3-may-not-see-release-until-2010/</link><title>Half-Life 2: Episode 3 may not see release until 2010</title><description>...With Half-Life 2: Episode 2 having been released just last year, its a safe bet that we wont be seeing Gordon Freeman in a new game anytime soon. But just long will we have to wait? Well, according to Doug Lombardi, Valves VP or marketing, it will be quite a while. The next time you play as Gordon will be longer than the distance between Half-Life 2 to Episode One, and Episode One to Episode Two,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7107-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7107_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:24:38">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/08/fable-iii-announced-fable-ii-goes-episodic/</link><title>Fable III announced, Fable II goes episodic</title><description>... more interactive adventure elements."Fable II, meanwhile, will be coming to Xbox Live in an episodic format. The first episode, set to be released on September 29, will be free, while players will have to pay for subsequent episodes. No pricing has been announced as of yet, but the digital version...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7107-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7107_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:28:27">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/12/penny-arcade-episode-2-on-ps3-has-game-ending-glitch-patch-incoming/</link><title>Penny Arcade: Episode 2 on PS3 has glitch; patch incoming</title><description>...PlayStation 3 owners were brought up-to-date last week when Hot Head Games released the second episode of Penny Arcade Adventures: On the Rain Slick Precipice of Darkness. But, if you decided to pick it up, you may want to hold off on completing it, as the title features a game-ending glitch...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7107-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7107_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:29:58">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/11/star-wars-episode-vii-gets-an-official-release-date-december-18-2015/</link><title>Star Wars: Episode VII gets an official release date: December 18, 2015</title><description>...The time that I rode in the Millennium Falcon with Kyle Orland, Jonathan Gitlin, and Eric Bangeman. Lucasfilm / Aurich LawsonLock your S-foils in attack position: Lucasfilm has announcedthat Star Wars: Episode VII will be arriving in theaters in time for Christmas 2015.The official dateDecember 18...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7107-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7107_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:31:46">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/10/empire-strikes-back-cowriter-takes-over-script-for-star-wars-episode-vii/</link><title>Empire Strikes Back cowriter joins Abrams on Star Wars: Episode VII script</title><description>...: Episode VIIalongside JJ Abrams. Commenting on the switch at StarWars.com, Lucasfilm President Kathleen... slated to handle Episode VII, is no longer involved. Arndt boasted an award-winning background... withSkyfall, Dark Knight Rises,andInceptionin his resume.According to thesite, shooting for Episode...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7107-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7107_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:32:17">http://arstechnica.com/ars-podcast/2012/04/ars-technicast-episode-1-the-singularity/</link><title>Ars Technicast, Episode 1: "The Singularity"</title><description>...Welcome to the debut episode of the Ars Technicast, where we bring you the latest in the worlds of computing, technology, science, and everything in between. On this weeks show, our host, Senior... Technicast, Episode 1, "The Singularity"...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7107-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7107_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:33:18">http://arstechnica.com/ars-podcast/2012/11/ars-technicast-episode-15-read-any-darwin-lately/</link><title>Ars Technicast, Episode 15: Read any Darwin lately?</title><description>... age, but many people have never even read it. In this episode of the Ars Technicast, Editor in Chief... Editor Cesar Torres in a discussion about Darwins book. In this episode we talk about how the book... ways in which it could be discussed as a piece of literature.ListenArs Technicast, Episode 15 : Read...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7107-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7107_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:34:47">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/03/sega-not-planning-more-sonic-4-after-upcoming-episode-2/</link><title>Sega "not planning" more Sonic 4 after upcoming Episode 2</title><description>..., downloadable episodes, the company was careful not to say just how many episodes it planned to release... recently told Digital Spy the team is "currently not planning to release another episode," after the second.Sonic 4's first episode got mixed reviews (including a glowing write up from...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>