<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7108">renting car seattle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:37:32" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7108-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7108_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:37:33">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/12/seattle-announces-its-own-gigabit-internet-service/</link><title>Seattle announces its own gigabit Internet service</title><description>... speed.On Thursday, Seattle Mayor Mike McGinn announcedthe city reached an agreement with Gigabit... underused fiber. Seattle abandoned its plan for a municipal network last summer. A connected city... with a demonstration fiber project in twelve Seattle neighborhoods and includes wireless methods to deploy...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7108-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7108_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:40:03">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/06/gigabit-seattle-priced-at-80-per-month-just-over-what-google-fiber-costs/</link><title>Gigabit Seattle priced at $80 per month, just over what Google Fiber costs</title><description>...Last year, Seattle decided to jointhegigabit Internet party. Gigabit Seattle has just announced its pricing, and it looks a lot like Google Fibers offerings.The company said Monday... installation charge with one-year contractGigabit Seattle is a partnership between Gigabit Squared...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7108-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7108_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:41:47">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/08/my-house-is-for-rent-adventures-in-scam-baiting/</link><title>"My house is for rent?" Adventures in online scam baiting</title><description>... to see the home for rent that was advertised on craigslist. Can I take a look around?"This might be a normal thing to hear if you had actually advertised your house for rent on craigslist... purchased. He asked the woman where she had learned that his house was for rent; she told him...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7108-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7108_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:42:56">http://arstechnica.com/business/2014/01/gigabit-project-in-seattle-reportedly-dead-leaves-trail-of-unpaid-bills/</link><title>Gigabit project in Seattle reportedly dead, leaves trail of unpaid bills</title><description>...The Gigabit Squared project to bring fiber Internet to Seattle is reportedly dead, with the company... to Seattle neighborhoods in partnership with Gigabit Squared is the small companys unpaid bill for $52,250," theSeattle Timeswrote today. "Erin Devoto, Seattles chief technology officer, said...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7108-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7108_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:43:53">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/10/love-gigabit-seattle-comcast-has-donated-lots-to-the-guy-now-trying-to-slow-it/</link><title>Love Gigabit Seattle? Comcast has donated lots to promoter’s rival (Updated)</title><description>... of the world.Sure, there are a few bright spots of gigabit nationwide, including Seattle, which announced its service nearly a year ago. Seattle Mayor Mike McGinn pushed for Gigabit Seattle, a partnership...-Seattle). The mayoral election is set for Tuesday, November 5.Murray, the Post adds, "has com...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7108-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7108_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:46:35">http://arstechnica.com/security/2013/06/after-burglaries-mystery-car-unlocking-device-has-police-stumped/</link><title>After burglaries, mystery car unlocking device has police stumped</title><description>... silently down a deserted residential street in Long Beach, California. Each one goes up to a car in the area, takes out a small electronic device, and pulls on the passenger side car handle. The first man tries a car in the street. It doesn't open, and he walks on. The other two men try...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7108-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7108_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:49:17">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/02/interview-what-driving-will-be-like-in-five-to-ten-years/</link><title>Drive-by-wireless: why the future of cars is P2P mesh, 4G cellular, and the cloud</title><description>... or multicore processors have anything to do with cars, but you'd be wrong. They have everything... Hushyar, a former senior VP at ATT and current CEO of Telemetria, makers of the DashTop in-car compute appliance. In this fascinating interview, we talk about the ultimate evolution of not just the car...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7108-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7108_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:50:34">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2014/03/bloodhound-ssc/</link><title>Bloodhound SSC: How do you build a car capable of 1,000mph?</title><description>...Human beings achieved many 'firsts' in the 20th century. We climbed the planet's highest mountains, dived its deepest undersea trench, flew over it faster than the speed of sound, and even escaped it altogether in order to visit the moon. Beyond visiting Mars, it may feel like there are no more milestones left to reach. Yet people are still trying to push the envelope, even if they...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7108-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7108_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:51:38">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/03/video-ipad-is-the-brain-for-self-driving-car/</link><title>Video: iPad is the brain for self-driving car</title><description>...Self-driving cars are quickly changing from a staple of sci-fi movies to reality in recent years. But not all self-driving cars are implemented the same way. One such variation has been developed...;s auto-driving capabilities.Oxford's iPad car aims to be a middle-of-the-road solution between...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7108-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7108_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:54:30">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/09/robot-cars-now-officially-legal-in-california/</link><title>Robot cars now officially legal in California</title><description>... to legalize and regulate autonomous cars.Google, of course, has already developed a fleet of a dozen cars... at the event. "I expect that self-driving cars will be far safer than human-driven cars."Nevada became the first state earlier this year to regulate autonomous cars, and the Los Angeles T...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>