<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7109">best place to eat pho in new york</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:57:22" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7109-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7109_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:57:25">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/08/new-york-financial-regulator-hits-22-bitcoin-related-companies-with-subpoenas/</link><title>New York financial regulator hits 22 Bitcoin-related companies with subpoenas</title><description>...Late last week, the New York Department of Financial Services, the states banking regulator,sent 22 subpoenas to Bitcoin-related companies, according to a source familiar with the matter.The full list includes BitInstant, BitPay, Coinbase, CoinLab, Coinsetter, and Dwolla, as well as investors Andreessen Horowitz, Google Ventures, and Winklevoss Capital Management (whichclaims to own one percent o...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7109-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7109_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:58:50">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/09/new-york-will-install-91-text-stops-in-hopes-that-people-will-lol-l8er/</link><title>New York to create 91 roadside “Text Stops” in hopes that you’ll lol l8er</title><description>...Yesterday, New York Governor Andrew Cuomo announced a new initiative to stop drivers from texting on the roadturn rest areas into Text Stops and put up signage that lets people know how many miles they'll have to hold off on tweeting that witty tweet.91 rest stops, Park-n-Ride facilities, and parking areas along the New York State Thruway and State Highways will now become special texting zo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7109-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7109_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:01:23">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/02/tesla-says-it-lost-hundreds-of-orders-after-new-york-times-controversy/</link><title>Tesla says it lost “hundreds” of orders after New York Times controversy</title><description>...Swanky car company Tesla recently engaged in some very public barb-trading with The New York Times... as the Times bad reporting."We did actually get a lot of cancellations as a result of The New York Times... to The New York Times article. There were prob...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7109-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7109_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:03:37">http://arstechnica.com/business/2011/12/spammers-take-control-of-new-york-times-e-mail-list/</link><title>New York Times mistakenly spams 8 million people</title><description>...UPDATE: Just after we posted the story below, New York Times reporters confirmed that the e-mail...: The New York Times has some confused customers on its hands after spammers apparently took control... system is overwhelmed by calls.The New York Times confirme...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7109-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7109_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:04:51">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/05/new-york-legislation-would-ban-anonymous-online-speech/</link><title>New York legislation would ban anonymous online speech</title><description>...Did you hear the one about New York state lawmakers who forgot about the First Amendment in the name of combating cyberbullying and baseless political attacks?"Proposed legislation in both chambers would require New York-based websites, such as blogs and newspapers, to remove any comments posted on his or her website by an anonymous poster unless such anonymous poster agrees to attach his or...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7109-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7109_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:05:40">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/10/uber-decides-to-pull-the-plug-on-its-new-york-taxi-service/</link><title>Uber decides to pull the plug on its New York taxi service</title><description>... that it would be halting its month-long partnership with existing New York yellow cab drivers. Ubers black car and UberX services remain unaffected. But the New York Taxi and Limousine Commission has indicated... after Uber Taxilaunched, New York authorities t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7109-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7109_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:08:24">http://arstechnica.com/security/2013/01/chinese-hackers-attacked-new-york-times-computers-for-four-months/</link><title>Chinese hackers attacked New York Times computers for four months</title><description>...The New York Times reports that its internal network wasattackedby Chinese hackers over the last four months. The e-mail accounts of several reporters who worked on a story critical of the family of Chinese prime ministerWen Jiabaowere infiltrated, and the passwords of every single New York Times employee were stolen. However, there is no evidence that information about sources for the stories on...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7109-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7109_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:09:34">http://arstechnica.com/business/2010/01/ny-times-to-spend-the-year-erecting-a-partial-paywall/</link><title>New York Times to spend 2010 erecting a partial paywall</title><description>...Like many publications with one foot in the digital world, one foot in print, The New York Times...;t be put in place until a year from now, in January of 2011. The Times' own coverage... that will be targeted by the new billing system. The intent is for the new charges to creat...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7109-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7109_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:10:14">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/03/new-york-times-time-going-with-html5-video-for-ipad-too/</link><title>Et tu? New York Times, Time going with HTML5 video for iPad</title><description>... clients, the New York Times and Time Inc., are participating launch partners, meaning that these two..., and other features over the next year.With such major names as the New York Times and Time on board, it's pretty...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7109-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7109_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:10:58">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/10/is-new-york-city-an-anti-white-space-town/</link><title>Is New York City an anti-white space town?</title><description>...The New York City Council heard testimony about the dangers and prospects of unlicensed white space devices on Tuesday. Speakers pro and con discussed the question of whether allowing unlicensed applications to tap into unused TV channels would pose a threat to the wireless microphone systems that Broadway production companies depend on. As Ars readers know, this debate normally rages at the Fede...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>