<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7110">civil engineering jobs pennsylvania</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:13:04" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7110-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7110_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:13:05">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/12/pennsylvania-study-rejects-video-game-legislation/</link><title>Pennsylvania study rejects video game legislation</title><description>...After over a year of research, the results of a Pennsylvania study looking into the effect... who was a social scientist. My main job was to discuss violent video game research (pros and cons). In addition...). Of course this report will only have an impact on the state of Pennsylvania, meanwhile places like...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7110-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7110_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:13:57">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/07/engineer-warned-jobs-of-potential-iphone-4-antenna-issues/</link><title>Engineer warned Jobs of potential iPhone 4 antenna issues</title><description>... that the iPhone 4 suffers from an antenna design flaw, and a new report by Bloomberg News reveals that Steve Jobs was warnedearly in the design phase by a top engineer that the antenna design could lead to dropped calls.Steve Jobs highlighted the iPhone 4 antenna design as "brilliant engineering" during...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7110-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7110_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:16:16">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/12/civilization-v-patch-smartens-up-ai-cleans-up-mechanics/</link><title>Civilization V patch smartens up AI, cleans up mechanics</title><description>...Civilization V has recevied a patch today, as announced on Firaxis's forums. The patch... for various city buildings. We gave Civilization V a favorable review and remain fans, but a number..., for example, has often emerged as an intolerant and ruthless warmonger. For a version of Civilization...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7110-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7110_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:17:06">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/09/the-history-of-civilization-20-years-of-wonders/</link><title>The history of Civilization : 20 years of Wonders</title><description>...The Civilization series spans nearly 20 years, several consoles, and innumerable hours of gameplay... in on its release date, Ars takes a look back at the evolution of Civilization, and how it captured our... In the beginning, there was, counterintuitively, Civilization. Montezuma began a long and storied reign...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7110-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7110_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:20:12">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/05/pre-columbian-americas-enjoyed-water-pressure/</link><title>Pre-Columbian Americas enjoyed water pressure</title><description>...Until recently, it was thought that hydrodynamic systems used to provide water pressure were brought to the new world by Spanish explorers. A new discovery in the Mayan city of Palenque appears to demonstrate that pre-Columbian civilizations enjoyed the benefits of positive water pressure long...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7110-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7110_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:23:35">http://arstechnica.com/staff/2013/08/announcing-arsjobs-our-new-jobs-board/</link><title>Announcing Ars/Jobs, our new jobs board</title><description>... recruitment network of jobs sites and search engines, Ars/Jobs is the most optimized tech jobs tool... for job seekers, we launched our first jobs board several years ago. Today, ArsTechnica is proud to announce the launch of Ars/Jobs, o...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7110-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7110_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:25:58">http://arstechnica.com/security/2008/10/your-privacy-is-an-illusion-uk-attacks-civil-liberties/</link><title>Your privacy is an illusion: UK attacks civil liberties</title><description>... perspective. Coming from civil servants, thats harsh criticism indeed. Passport, please Knowing... could be an indication of a broader rejection of greater government intrusion. For the good of our civil liberties...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7110-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7110_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:27:19">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/06/review-gods-kings-is-an-essential-civilization-expansion/</link><title>Review: Gods and Kings is an essential Civilization expansion</title><description>...When it comes to expansions, the Civilization series seems to be trending in the opposite direction... Civilization remained un-expanded, and the expansions for the second title merely amounted to optional collections of scenarios and a disastrous multiplayer versionthe Civilization II experience...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7110-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7110_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:27:58">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/09/statecraft-as-entertainment-ars-reviews-civilization-v/</link><title>Statecraft as entertainment: Ars reviews Civilization V</title><description>... its predecessors, Civilization Vis a turn-based strategy game that takes place in the historical world. You select a civilization from the 18 available to play, including old standbys like the English... more than a settler for company. Civilization V DeveloperFiraxis Publisher2K Games Price$49.99 Shop.Ars PlatformPC...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7110-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7110_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:29:45">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/04/firaxis-takes-civilization-to-the-star-with-beyond-earth-announcement/</link><title>Firaxis takes Civilization to the stars with Beyond Earth announcement [Updated]</title><description>..., the speculation among those in the know quickly converged on the obvious: Civilization VI. While we did get a new Civilization announcement today, the specific direction was far from expected. Instead, the next entry in the Civilization series is going to outer space with Civilization: Beyond Earth.As...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>