<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7111">what is the starting salary for a recruiter</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:31:09" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7111-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7111_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:31:14">http://arstechnica.com/business/2010/06/workers-need-education-to-stay-ahead-of-it-curve/</link><title>More IT means lower salaries for uneducated workers</title><description>... salary, according to a research paper published this week. A study on the education level of workers... that IT has actually depressed the salaries of many less-educated workers. The authors of the paper suggest... did find that IT seemed to have beneficial effects to some degree on all workers' salaries...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7111-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7111_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:32:39">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/08/how-what-what-in-the-butt-made-fair-use-easier-to-claim/</link><title>How "What What (In the Butt)" unintentionally bolstered "fair use"</title><description>...Wisconsin, state of my birth, I salute you for turning out federal judges like J.P. Stadtmueller. Stadtmueller is the man who waded into the swampland of fair use, South Park, and "What What (In the Butt)" to deliver a July 6 order that may break new judicial territory by citing South Park episode "Osama bin Laden Has Farty Pants" in its footnotes. And Stadtmueller has the pro...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7111-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7111_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:35:42">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/01/help-ive-got-windows-8-and-i-miss-my-start-menu/</link><title>Help! I've got Windows 8 and I miss my Start menu!</title><description>... at $4.99 per PC. I can't really see the appeal. If a Windows 7 Start menu is what you want... users divided. The chief complaints are that Windows 8 has no Start button and that it has no Start menu, only the (full-screen, Metro-styled) Start screen. Secondary to these is the c...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7111-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7111_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:36:57">http://arstechnica.com/business/2008/10/google-monetizes-start-page-vocal-minority-gets-vocal/</link><title>Google monetizes start page, vocal minority gets vocal</title><description>... money with it. Despite what appears to be a vocal minority that is unhappy with the changes, thats what Google may have finally been able to do with the redesign of its popular iGoogle start page... desktops. But the new iGoogle may be exactly what the start page needed to take the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7111-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7111_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:38:25">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/05/yo-dawg-we-heard-you-like-start-buttons-so-we-put-one-in-your-mouse/</link><title>Yo dawg, we heard you like Start buttons, so we put one on your mouse</title><description>...Windows 8 haters, rejoice. Microsoft has heard your cries and has brought back the Start button.But... mice contain, yup, a Windows logoed Start button.Enlarge / The Sculpt Touch Mouse. The blue bit... you to the Start screen. The mouse connects to your PC using Bluetooth. It will cost $39.95...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7111-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7111_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:41:05">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/05/youth-and-veteran-groups-protest-virtual-army-centers/</link><title>Youth and veteran groups protest virtual army centers</title><description>... over the weekend, rallying against the center's apparent effort to recruit soldiers through..., and for the use of electronic entertainment to aid in recruiting efforts. "The Army Experience Center... has resorted to such a deceiving recruiting strategy."Ars hasexplored the use of video games...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7111-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7111_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:42:21">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/08/start-menu-on-lenovo-windows-8-pcs-will-nag-you-to-install-apps/</link><title>“Start menu” on Lenovo Windows 8 PCs will nag you to install apps</title><description>...Windows users looking for something resembling the classic Start Menu that was stripped out of Windows 8 don't have to look too far. Several apps that roughly recreate the Start Menu's functionality can be downloaded and installed easily enough.But some PC manufacturers are making Start...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7111-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7111_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:43:39">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/09/study-self-fulfilling-prophecy-drives-gender-wage-gap/</link><title>Study: "self-fulfilling prophecy" drives gender wage gap</title><description>... salary differences may result in part from workers own expectations of gender roles. The study breaks... those with gender-specific differences in employment and salary. Its structured so that its key points... of Youth (NLSY), run by the US Bureau of Labor Statistics. The panel started with over 12,000 individuals...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7111-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7111_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:47:01">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/08/parallels-puts-start-menu-back-in-windows-8-virtual-machines/</link><title>Parallels puts Start menu back in Windows 8 virtual machines and Mac dock</title><description>...The newest version of Parallels Desktop brings a Windows 7-style Start menu and button to Windows... 7-style view by installing the Start8 and ModernMix add-ons. Start8 brings back the Start menu... available as a single download in the virtual machine's settings.The Start menu is available both...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7111-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7111_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:47:39">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/11/gamestop-to-start-selling-dlc-in-store-wait-what/</link><title>GameStop to start selling DLC in store... wait, what?</title><description>... DLC itself.According to a report from Variety, the retailer will start selling digital content in its stores starting next year, and it already has backing from Sony and Microsoft. The new service...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>