<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7118">part time jobs texas city</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:53:37" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7118-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7118_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:53:40">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/10/time-warner-att-want-kansas-city-to-give-them-google-fiber-style-deal/</link><title>Time Warner, ATandT want Kansas City to give them Google Fiber-style deal</title><description>... negotiating position. Time Warner Cable is currently in talks with Kansas City, Missouri, to provide...Google Fibers pending rollout in Kansas City has certainly drawn the attention of jealous geeks... on in the past, Kansas City has rolled out the digital red carpet for Google: giving rights of way...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7118-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7118_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:55:27">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/05/texas-bans-most-private-drone-use-fearing-spying/</link><title>Texas bans (most) private drone use, fearing spying</title><description>... was for meant for law enforcement, not private citizen surveillance.Drones used by Texas cities...-City Times, The bill was apparently created in response to People for the Ethical Treatment...;s also been discussed at the state and national level. Now the Texas legislature has pass...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7118-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7118_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:58:04">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/09/tesla-sets-its-sights-on-texas-with-more-supercharger-station-openings/</link><title>Tesla sets its sights on Texas with more Supercharger station openings</title><description>...Electric car manufacturer Tesla Motors is responding to legal barriers in Texas by doing the proverbial double-down move. Rather than retreat and lick the wounds from its lost battle with the 2013 Texas legislature, the company is investing millions in building five Supercharger stations to link together Austin, San Antonio, Dallas/Fort Worth, and Houstonthe "Texas Triangle."The state&amp;a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7118-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7118_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:00:09">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/10/steve-jobs-was-a-noticer-that-could-be-harsh-at-times-sensitive-at-others/</link><title>Steve Jobs was a "noticer" who could be harsh at times, sensitive at others</title><description>...Plenty of ink has been spilled since former Apple CEO Steve Jobs passed away almost one year ago...: Jobs regretted not having life-saving cancer surgery earlier. He waslivid over Android's purported copying of iOS. And Jobs was often driven to tears at what could seem like the drop of a hat.And...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7118-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7118_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:02:47">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/06/report-steve-jobs-recovered-set-for-timely-return-to-apple/</link><title>Report: Steve Jobs recovered, set for timely return to Apple</title><description>...Apple CEO Steve Jobs is reportedly on track to return to Apple full-time later this month, right on schedule. Insiders speaking to The Wall Street Journal claim that Jobs' recovery is "coming along" and that Apple's directors have been receiving weekly updates since Jobs took leave in January. Whether or not we'll see him at next week's WWDC keynote, however, remains...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7118-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7118_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:05:26">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/01/texas-where-science-and-history-have-become-ideological-battlegrounds/</link><title>Texas, where science and history have become ideological battlegrounds</title><description>...Some of the most important decisions that influence the public's knowledge aren't made by scientific societies and they don't take place in Washington DC. For the most part, they're made in the capitals of each state, as each has its own standards for what students leaving its public schools should know. Those standards set lesson plans and help decide which textbooks are acce...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7118-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7118_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:07:19">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/04/spacex-decides-to-build-a-lil-old-commercial-spaceport-in-texas/</link><title>SpaceX considering a new 'Commercial Cape Canaveral' in Texas</title><description>... Impact Study for the construction of a new spaceport in Cameron County, Texas, on the Gulf and very near the northern border of Mexico. The site could make Texas a powerhouse in commercial space.The... at Canaveral for the Falcon 9. It's unknown at this time whether SpaceX is still interested...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7118-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7118_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:09:24">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/02/texas-school-board-searching-for-another-side-to-theory-of-evolution/</link><title>Texas school board searching for “another side” to theory of evolution</title><description>...We recently reviewed the documentary The Revisionaries, which chronicles the actions of the Texas.... However, it now looks like his successor intends to carry on his legacy.This week, the Texas... she saw.Barbara Cargill testifies before the Texas Senate. Cargill's complaint is that the material...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7118-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7118_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:11:08">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/03/texas-proposes-one-of-nations-most-sweeping-mobile-privacy-laws/</link><title>Texas proposes one of nation’s “most sweeping” mobile privacy laws</title><description>...Privacy experts say that a pair of new mobile privacy bills recently introduced in Texas are among... warrantless powers to not only track suspects in real-time based on their phone data, but also to access... providers. The Texas bill would require just that. In addition, the Texas bill would also require...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7118-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7118_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:12:05">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/09/texas-still-seeing-attempts-to-limit-evolution-in-school-textbooks/</link><title>Texas still seeing attempts to limit evolution in school textbooks</title><description>... unscientific.)The Texas Freedom Network, which advocates for separation of church and state (among... Academy of Science's strong support of the theory of evolution. At the same time, this is a theory... was not a mechanism of evolution and that one standard definition of evolution (change over time) was invalid...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>