<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7119">chocolate photo</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:13:28" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7119-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7119_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:13:29">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/08/deleting-zombie-photos-from-iphoto/</link><title>Deleting zombie photos from iPhoto</title><description>...Recently I noticed when I delete photos from the iPhoto trash, iPhoto doesn't necessarily... photos that I need to get rid of.But as I noticed, sometimes iPhoto doesn't delete photos when you... point though).So, after a little tinkering, here's how to get rid of those unwanted photos...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7119-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7119_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:15:33">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/02/macworldiworld-2013-in-photos-on-and-off-the-show-floor/</link><title>Macworld/iWorld 2013 in photos: On and off the show floor</title><description>... that network from a computer and have the photos transferred instantly over-the-airuseful for digital.... A digital photo gallery displayed art made by Mac and iOS users throughout the world. Jacqui Cheng... Rodney Another shot of the panel from another angle. Thanks to all the Ars readers who sent in photos...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7119-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7119_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:18:36">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2008/10/1080p-digital-photo-viewer-puts-family-pics-on-your-big-screen/</link><title>1080p digital photo viewer puts family pics on your big screen</title><description>...PIE United has announced what it claims to be the worlds first HDMI 1080p digital photo viewer. The device allows users to view digital photos and video on a big screen 1080p HDTV directly from a memory card. Some newer digital cameras have HDMI outallowing you to look at photos or watch video...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7119-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7119_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:19:08">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/02/fix-reportedly-coming-for-ios-photo-uploading-loophole/</link><title>Fix reportedly coming for iOS photo uploading loophole</title><description>...A loophole within iOS that allows developers to surreptitiously upload users' photos... databasethey also have access to your photos, music, movies, calendars, and more with their associated... permission for the app to access a particular kind of information, such as photos with location data...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7119-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7119_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:20:44">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/06/photo-gallery-thin-macbook-pro-with-retina-display/</link><title>Photo gallery: thin MacBook Pro with retina display</title><description>... gathered around to take photos and examine the new machine. We, of course, were among... the wedge-shaped MacBook Air. As you can see from the photos, it looks like a classic MacBook Pro...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7119-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7119_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:24:23">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/08/windows-live-photos-tops-a-billion-pictures-in-seven-months/</link><title>Windows Live Photos tops a billion pictures in seven months</title><description>...Windows Live Photos, a seven-month old web service for uploading and sharing photos, recently broke... for Windows Live Photos: one billion photos uploaded! This is a significant part of the more than seven billion photos posted on Windows Live today (most of which were uploaded befo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7119-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7119_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:27:51">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/02/nearly-3-years-later-deleted-facebook-photos-are-still-online/</link><title>Over 3 years later, "deleted" Facebook photos are still online</title><description>...Facebook is still working on deleting photos from its servers in a timely manner nearly three years.... In the meantime, photos that users thought they "deleted" from the social network months or even years ago remain accessible via direct link. The problem: "deleted" photos never go awayWhen...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7119-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7119_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:30:53">http://arstechnica.com/business/2010/10/facebook-may-be-making-strides/</link><title>"Deleted" Facebook photos still not deleted: a followup</title><description>... more than a year ago examining whether photos really disappear from social network servers when you delete them...; photos online. We decided to revisit the issue recently when readers continued to point out that our deleted photos from that article were still online more than 16 months later. Indeed, this old...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7119-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7119_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:34:30">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/03/snap-a-few-photos-win-20000/</link><title>Snap a few photos, win $20,000</title><description>...;the most lucrative and influential international student photo contest in the world," has begun...) can submit their three best photos (without an entry fee) in one of three categories: Nature..., all expenses paid, to the annual Microsoft Pro Photo Summit. Microsoft claims that past winners...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7119-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7119_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:38:11">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/03/leaving-editing-geotagging-flagging-behind-in-windows-8-photos/</link><title>Windows 8 Photos app brings "fast and fluid" to picture management</title><description>... a tablet-like experience. The Photos app gives users fluid, near-instantaneous access to your pictures..., and others that are included don't work evenly across the app.When you pull up Photos from the Metro... a short login process, and after you've given the program your credentials, the home Photos...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>