<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7120">tortellini pasta salad</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:39:51" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7120-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7120_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:39:52">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/08/x-ray-pulsars-boil-nuclear-pasta-to-keep-spinning/</link><title>X-Ray pulsars boil “nuclear pasta” to keep spinning</title><description>... the nuclear pasta region. It got that name because it is thought to consist of ordered regions..., and density of the star affect the ordering of its constituents.This pasta has a distinctive property... currents in the pasta region, which provides an intermediate step in converting magnetic energy...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7120-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7120_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:41:15">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/04/the-price-gouging-premiums-of-time-warner-cables-data-caps/</link><title>The price-gouging premiums of Time Warner Cable's data caps</title><description>... to lunch with a friend, do you split the bill in half if he gets the steak and you have a salad.... But TWC's steak/salad analogy breaks down when it's crafted more accurately. The real question is whether you would even have lunch with a friend at a restaurant that charged $45 for a salad and $200...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7120-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7120_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:42:51">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/09/why-are-we-idiots-about-taking-care-of-our-health/</link><title>Why are we idiots about taking care of our health?</title><description>... the salad bar. Or do whatever is necessary to reduce their health risks.It doesn't work that way.... Placing the healthier choices at salad bars closer to the edges gets more people to select them...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7120-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7120_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:44:13">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/10/avast-new-hacks-could-steer-ships-into-pirates-grasp/</link><title>Avast! New hacks could steer ships into pirates’ grasp</title><description>.... Marco Balduzzi and Kyle Wilhoit, along with independent security researcher Alessandro Pasta...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7120-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7120_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:46:18">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/05/french-court-gives-youtube-a-victory-in-copyright-infringement-case/</link><title>French court gives YouTube a victory in copyright infringement case</title><description>... Picking a Wild Salad video, and content owner RumbleFish had the video taken down.Copyright holders like...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7120-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7120_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:48:56">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/03/microsoft-patent-points-to-head-mounted-laser-based-display-technology/</link><title>Microsoft patent points to head-mounted, laser-based display technology</title><description>... could become a thing of the pastas long as your coffee table is well out of the way.Again...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7120-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7120_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:49:57">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/09/starfox-64-3d-brings-a-classic-back-in-fine-form/</link><title>StarFox 64 3D brings a classic back in fine form</title><description>...Nintendo has a reputation of living in the pasta reputation that has been well earned. The company's first-party games are almost always worth playing, but they also trade heavily on nostalgia. StarFox 64 3D may be the second game that I would consider a must-have on the Nintendo 3DS, and like...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7120-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7120_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:52:22">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/10/self-appointed-guardians-of-tv-decency-fall-on-hard-times/</link><title>Self-appointed guardians of TV decency fall on hard times</title><description>...It appears that the decency group that targets dirty tweeters, naughty Android apps, and anything else that gets between its Victorian cross hairs is having a rough patch. The New York Times reports that the Parents Television Council's salad days are over. The recession has caught...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7120-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7120_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:54:48">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/01/verizon-metered-billing-much-fairer-than-all-you-can-eat/</link><title>Verizon: metered billing much fairer than all-you-can-eat</title><description>...;s meal was subsidized by the vegetarians on staff, who grazed the salad bar and downed fried polenta...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7120-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7120_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:57:34">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/10/forget-apples-a-tomato-a-day-is-what-might-keep-the-oncologist-away/</link><title>Genetically modified tomatoes can keep cancer at bay</title><description>... to take bioactive compounds in a pill, it might be more fun and appetizing to decorate salads...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>