<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7121">who is the man in the m&amp;m commercial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:58:40" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7121-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7121_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:58:41">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/12/dvr-commercial-skipping-50-or-97-depends-on-whom-you-ask/</link><title>DVR commercial skipping: 50% or 70%? Depends on whom you ask</title><description>... clearly bad for business because they make it easier to skip commercials, but consumers love them... commercials than homes without the devices. According to one ABC exec, speaking recently at a television conference in New York that we attended, fewer people skip commercials than used to. Plus, DVR owners...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7121-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7121_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:00:52">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/10/chelsea-manning-speaks-from-prison-for-the-first-time-rejects-pacifist-label/</link><title>Chelsea Manning speaks from prison for the first time, rejects “pacifist” label</title><description>...In her first public statement since being sentenced to 35 years in prison, Chelsea Manning (formerly known as Bradley Manning) says that she rejects being called a pacifist.Manning recently received... it, Manning wrote on Tuesday. In fact, I first found out about the award when I began receiving mail...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7121-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7121_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:01:38">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/05/alliant-techsystems-surprises-with-a-commercial-rocket/</link><title>Alliant Techsystems surprises with a manned rocket</title><description>... be amortized into ATK's launch prices, giving them a big advantage. NASA is even paying to man-rate..., developing nations that want a space program, International Space Station servicing, and commercial cargo.... In short, Alliant Techsystems has surprised many of us with a formidable new entrant into the commercial...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7121-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7121_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:03:25">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/02/inside-the-isle-of-mans-1month-unlimited-music-plan/</link><title>Inside the Isle of Man's</title><description>...Last month, the Isle of Man announced that it was going to try its governmental hand at addressing... became clear during the conversation. The first is that, for Berry and the government of Man, the dive... in music or not. The grand planThe Isle of Man is a crown protectorate, a position that keeps it separate...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7121-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7121_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:05:56">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/11/judge-denies-foxs-request-to-stop-dishs-commercial-skipping-service/</link><title>Judge denies Fox's request to stop Dish's commercial-skipping service</title><description>...A federal judge refused to issue a preliminary injunction in a case pitting the Dish satellite network against the Fox media empire. The dispute is over the legality of Dish's Hopper DVRs, especially its "AutoHop" feature. That automatically detects and skips over commercials. Fox...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7121-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7121_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:08:30">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/12/army-releases-2010-chat-log-between-manning-and-assange/</link><title>Army releases 2010 chat log between Manning and Assange</title><description>... chat logs from 2010 between former intelligence analyst Chelsea Manning (formerly known as Bradley Manning) and Wikileaks founder Julian Assange. After handing over a massive trove of diplomatic cables and other videos to Wikileaks, Manning was convicted in July 2013 of espionage, theft...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7121-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7121_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:10:30">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/11/bradley-manning-finally-fesses-up-over-wikileaks/</link><title>Bradley Manning finally fesses up over WikiLeaks...</title><description>...Bradley Manning, the US Army Private First Class accused of leaking classified documents... Meade, Maryland.To be clear, Manning has not pled guilty or not guilty in the case, where.... But this marks the first time Manning has offered to accept formal responsibility for leaking government...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7121-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7121_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:11:58">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/02/manning-shocked-by-the-bloodlust-went-with-wikileaks/</link><title>Manning, shocked by “the bloodlust,” went with WikiLeaks</title><description>...Over the course of two hours in a military courtroom today, Bradley Manning explained whyand... were not part of a plea bargain; Manning still faces trial in June on the most serious charges, such as "aiding the enemy."The Guardian's Ed Pilkington sets the scene:Manning was flanked...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7121-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7121_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:14:47">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/01/dont-touch-the-dvr-commercials-help-us-enjoy-the-show-more/</link><title>Don't touch the DVR: commercials help us enjoy the show more</title><description>... of the Journal of Consumer Research, which has published a study on how viewers respond to commercial breaks... and/or software that lets them skip the commercials, indicating an abiding dislike for the interruptions, it turns out that theyd probably enjoy the program more with the commercials in place. The authors...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7121-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7121_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:17:49">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/12/calm-act-passed-will-quiet-loud-tv-commercials-within-a-year/</link><title>CALM Act passed, will quiet loud TV commercials within a year</title><description>..., at least Democrats and Republicans can agree on one thing: TV commercials are too damned loud. After approval by the House, the Commercial Advertisement Loudness Mitigation (CALM) Act is now...;s (D-CA) bill will require commercials to be at the same decibel levels as programs during...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>