<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7122">horse dog pics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:20:06" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7122-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7122_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:20:07">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/03/domesticating-the-horse/</link><title>Domesticating the horse</title><description>... at the domestication of the horse. The authors show that the horse is likely to have been domesticated... to identify its paeleolithic origins. The horse is no different, but in this case, the changes are not so radical that we cannot trace the horse lineage. In fact, one key way to distinguish early...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7122-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7122_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:22:54">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/01/transmissible-cancer-is-a-time-capsule-from-the-earliest-dogs/</link><title>Transmissible cancer is a time capsule from the earliest dogs</title><description>...Innumerable cases of cancer arise each year throughout the animal kingdom. As far as we're aware, that cancer has only twice outlived the animal in which it originated by spreading to new hosts. One of these forms of cancerstrikes the Tasmanian Deviland appears to have evolved within the last few hundred years. The second circulates among dogs,and its origin has been harder to pin down.Now,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7122-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7122_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:24:19">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/04/popcap-introduces-indie-label-4th-and-battery-unpleasant-horse/</link><title>PopCap introduces "indie label" 4th and Battery, Unpleasant Horse</title><description>... to hone their chops." Unpleasant Horse These games are being described as short films, or B... horse that sports wings and advances through the game by destroying small birds and landing on more pleasant horses from above. Landing atop other horses enables the player to force them earthward...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7122-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7122_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:27:29">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/05/where-did-dogs-come-from-it-turns-out-we-dont-really-know/</link><title>Where did dogs come from? It turns out we don't really know</title><description>...Dogs were the very first creatures that humans domesticated, and their remains have been found..., archeological, and historic evidence to argue that the history of domestic dogs is such a mess.... The source of domesticated dogs, the gray wolf, historically ranged across all of North America, Europe...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7122-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7122_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:28:24">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/12/clerk-dogs-brings-video-store-guy-into-your-home/</link><title>Clerk Dogs brings video store guy into your home</title><description>... want to watch. The idea behind Clerk Dogs is simple: improve upon current movie recommendations... the site, though, Clerk Dogs simply asks for users to type the name of a movie they love to get started... the recommendation breadcrumb trail that Clerk Dogs clerks have generated, but mash it allows users...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7122-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7122_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:29:18">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/03/ubisoft-teases-may-27-release-date-for-watch-dogs/</link><title>Ubisoft teases May 27 release date for Watch Dogs [Updated]</title><description>...Almost two years after it was first revealed publicly, Ubisoft's open-world, tech-driven spy game Watch Dogs will hit on May 27, the company announced today.The release date appears at the end of a new, story-focused trailer that first appeared on Xbox.com; it was later released...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7122-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7122_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:30:11">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/02/ubisoft-fighting-fraudulent-abandonment-order-for-watch-dogs-trademark/</link><title>Ubisoft fighting fraudulent abandonment order for Watch Dogs trademark</title><description>...Ubisoft has filed a petition with the US Patent and Trademark Office fighting what it says is a fraudulent request to abandon its trademark on the upcoming game Watch Dogs.The issue started this weekend, when the USPTO received and filed a "request for Express Abandonment" on one of six Watch Dogs trademarks assigned to Ubisoft. The request covered "Game software and electronic gam...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7122-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7122_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:32:17">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/10/watch-dogs-release-pushed-back-from-november-into-q2-2014-or-later/</link><title>Watch Dogs release pushed back from November into Q2 2014 or later</title><description>... techno-spying game Watch Dogs, publisher Ubisoft has announced that the title has been delayed... players even more exceptional experiences."The development team behind Watch Dogs went...;s Creedand Watch Dogs will no longer be actively fighting for gamers' holiday-season open-world dollars...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7122-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7122_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:32:48">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/06/ubisoft-shooter-watch_dogs-punishes-our-interconnected-society/</link><title>Ubisoft shooter Watch Dogs punishes our interconnected society</title><description>...Ubisoft's upcoming game Watch Dogs closed out the company's press conference at E3 Monday...; minds. Amid the company's off-color jokes, the preview of Watch Dogs (which has been two years... properties.In Watch Dogs, the player is a character who is able to see data collected by various...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7122-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7122_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:35:03">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/06/ellen-page-thinks-naughty-dog-ripped-off-her-likeness-for-the-last-of-us/</link><title>Ellen Page thinks Naughty Dog “ripped off” her likeness for The Last of Us</title><description>... she is, and she's lashing out publicly at developer Naughty Dog for "ripping off" her likeness... that the uncanny valley effect tends to mask tiny differences in similar faces.Naughty Dog... her too," he added.We've reached out to Sony and Naughty Dog for further comment....</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>