<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7123">raleigh bike</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:35:43" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7123-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7123_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:35:44">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2010/08/bike-sharing-to-a-new-level-the-tech-behind-social-bikes/</link><title>Taking bike sharing to a new level: the tech behind Social Bikes</title><description>...Car-sharing services are becoming increasingly popular in the US, particularly in urban areas where it's more convenient and cost-efficient to borrow a car instead of owning one. However, for many urban dwellers and visitors, a car can still be impractical for getting from one place to the nextparking, traffic, and other concerns come into play. Enter bike-sharing services, which are slowly...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7123-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7123_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:37:57">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/03/can-larry-and-sergey-gaylord-lure-google-fiber-to-raleigh/</link><title>Can "Larry and Sergey Gaylord" lure Google fiber to Raleigh?</title><description>... a pro in operation, look no further than Raleigh, North Carolina city councilman Bonner Gaylord... with caveats: the twins must be boys, and Google must come to Raleigh. One wonders if even 1Gbps fiber...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7123-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7123_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:38:59">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/04/north-carolina-cities-mobilize-against-anti-muni-broadband-bill/</link><title>North Carolina cities mobilize against anti-muni broadband bill</title><description>..., Greensboro, Raleigh, Momeyer, Asheville, Rockingham, and Bladenville.All oppose House of Representatives.... Interestingly, the city of Raleigh, which has also passed a statement against the bill, is partially...;s legislative mailing address is in Raleigh. Avila told local press that the legislation would protect...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7123-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7123_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:39:57">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/04/moving-bikes-stay-uprightbut-not-for-the-reasons-we-thought/</link><title>Moving bikes stay upright—but not for the reasons we thought</title><description>..., you never forget how to do. As it turns out, bikes make that easy on us. If a typical bicycle... the gyroscopic and the negative trail factors, and the bike would still be stable as long... out and built a bike with a counter-rotating wheel to get rid of gyroscopic effects, as well as a negligible...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7123-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7123_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:42:33">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/11/kickstarter-frankencar-combines-solar-panels-with-bike-pedals/</link><title>Kickstarter “Frankencar” combines solar panels with bike pedals</title><description>...-off from a wall outlet, or the power of your own two feet. The vehicle is still classified as a bike... about which vehicle to take out for short trips. Bikes are efficient and environmentally friendly...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7123-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7123_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:43:37">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/08/tweets-contribute-to-charging-driver-with-murder-in-fatal-bike-accident/</link><title>Tweets contribute to charging driver with murder in fatal bike accident</title><description>...An 18-year-old man from Pleasanton, California has seen charges against him increased from vehicular manslaughter to murder due in part to some tweets in which he bragged about his reckless driving. The man, Cody Hall, is being held in an Alameda county jail without bail, waiting for a trial.On June 9, according to the San Francisco Chronicle, Hall was allegedly driving 83 mph in a 40 mph zone an...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7123-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7123_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:44:11">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/12/google-delays-its-1gbps-fiber-announcement/</link><title>Google delays its 1Gbps fiber announcement</title><description>... changed its name to Google, Kansas, while a Raleigh, North Carolina city council member offered to name his unborn twins Sergey and Larry Gaylord if Raleigh got the nod.In today's announcement...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7123-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7123_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:45:23">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/05/new-york-bicycle-hire-works-like-london-and-paris-but-more-expensive/</link><title>New York bicycle hire works like London and Paris, but more expensive</title><description>... its syllable-count may in part explain the propensity of Londoners to refer to the things as Boris bikes after the Mayor who saw them in). It comes as no surprise, then, that New York's Citi Bikes... bikes, New York's 10,000 and Paris' 18,000 see their schemes comfortably into the top four...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7123-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7123_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:46:44">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/12/time-warner-cable-tv-goes-blurry-in-presence-of-verizon-lte-phones/</link><title>Time Warner Cable TV goes blurry in presence of Verizon LTE phones</title><description>...In Raleigh, North Carolina, customers of Time Warner Cable are seeing blurry, pixelated TV when Verizon LTE phones are used in the same room.A report by WRAL in Raleigh says that "Time Warner...: After publication, Time Warner told us the following: "It's limited to the Raleigh market and WRAL...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7123-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7123_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:47:57">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/10/the-gyrobike-wants-to-save-children-from-scrapes-at-a-price/</link><title>The gyrobike wants to save children from scrapes, at a price</title><description>...The art of teaching your child to ride a bike hasn't changed in... well, ever, really. You get... bike riders will be able to stay upright once one of the battery-powered wheel is attached to their bike. The technology was actually created as a tool to ride a unicycle. "We quickly realized...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>