<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7125">psychological effects of obesity in children</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:13:50" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7125-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7125_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:13:51">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/09/lasker-awards-go-to-biologists-for-work-on-obesity-blindness/</link><title>Lasker Awards go to biologists for work on obesity, blindness</title><description>... on the more clearly effective macular degeneration treatment. Obesity and genetics The Medical Research award went... significant strides in understanding the biology of obesity, and another who turned our knowledge.... They're effective to a degree, but none of them have been outright cures, and mos...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7125-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7125_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:16:20">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/05/parents-have-gastric-bypass-childrens-dna-may-receive-the-benefits/</link><title>Parents have gastric bypass; children’s DNA may receive the benefits</title><description>...Gastric bypass surgeries would, at first glance, seem to tackle the problems of obesity through... than its impact on obesity.New research shows that the effects may go beyond the patients themselves..., and it reveals that the children also see changes in how their bodies handle fats and sugars (as well...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7125-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7125_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:17:03">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/09/toddlers-learn-about-entropy-from-messy-bedrooms/</link><title>Toddlers recognize entropy from messy bedrooms</title><description>... can knock them down. A new study in PNAS last week showed that children as young as one year old... that cannot.In these experiments, children were shown an image or video featuring either an animate object... out. Then, the children were shown the aftermath of the convergence: either an ordered set of blocks...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7125-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7125_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:19:47">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/harmonix-brings-rock-band-to-children-in-need/</link><title>Harmonix brings Rock Band to children in need</title><description>.... The deal will help bring the music game to seriously ill children around the country,Were honored to work with Starlight, which has an amazing tradition of offering support to seriously ill children... are designed to allow the children a chance to get out and relax, spending time with friends...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7125-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7125_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:23:14">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/07/gnomon-photo-tour-how-artists-get-into-video-games/</link><title>Gnomon School of Visual Effects: training the next generation of effects artists</title><description>... in the special effects industry would be in the best position to train others working... of Visual Effects so special.Gnomon has stayed in the same facility since it began, and art... from some of the biggest names in all the areas of special effects design and art. Reading the rsums of the people either...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7125-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7125_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:25:47">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/07/forget-titanic-women-and-children-rarely-first-off-sinking-ships/</link><title>Forget Titanic : Women and children rarely first off sinking ships</title><description>.... The ship's captain ordered that women and children be allowed to evacuate first, and his officers..., the Lusitania sank so quickly that there wasn't time to organize an evacuation, and women and children... that, in contrast to the Titanic, the crew generally does the best, and children the worst. Women started out ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7125-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7125_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:28:21">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/02/no-fix-for-mass-effect-2-text-issue-could-have-been-avoided/</link><title>No fix for Mass Effect 2 text; issue could have been avoided</title><description>...? We had readers contacting us to talk about their problems reading the text in Mass Effect 2...;We understand that on some standard definition TVs the smallest text in Mass Effect 2... this issue does affect a small portion of SDTV owners, we are unable to resolve it for Mass Effect 2...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7125-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7125_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:30:54">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/01/mass-effect-2-to-get-one-more-dlc-release-turns-off-news-network/</link><title>Mass Effect 2 to get one more DLC release, turns off news network</title><description>...Mass Effect 2's Cerberus Network, a service that provided story background for off-screen... one more DLC package coming to players before the release of Mass Effect 3\. The Cerberus Daily News... Effect 3, which is due out sometime this coming holiday season for the Xbox 360, PS3, and PC...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7125-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7125_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:32:01">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/08/ios-devs-pay-50000-for-collecting-childrens-info-in-apps/</link><title>iOS devs pay $50,000 for collecting children's info in apps</title><description>...The parent company ofBroken Thumbs Appsa prominent iOS app maker responsible for games like Zombie Duck Hunt, Truth or Dare, and Emily's Dress Uphas today settled with the Federal Trade Commission over its apparent collection of children's personal data in its iPhone and iPod touch apps. Though the FTC has gone after other companies for similar violations, this case is the first focused...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7125-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7125_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:32:42">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/11/understanding-the-other-race-effect/</link><title>"They all look alike": Understanding the "other race effect"</title><description>.... This phenomenon, called the other race effect, was first written about nearly a century ago (and supported... in the response decreases the second time; this effect is called repetition suppression. A particular... different Western Caucasian faces. The same effect was seen in East Asians; the neural signal showed...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>