<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7126">alicia keys brand new me lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:35:17" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7126-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7126_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:35:18">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/10/lyrics-site-liveuniverse-slammed-with-6-6-million-copyright-judgment/</link><title>Lyrics site LiveUniverse slammed with $6.6 million copyright judgment</title><description>...Several years after music publishers began pursuing websites that published lyrics on the Web... LiveUniverse makes it crystal clear: hosting an unauthorized lyrics site can get you in serious legal... by a Los Angeles federal judge this week for running a lyrics site that didn't pay for a license...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7126-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7126_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:38:29">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/09/google-now-one-of-the-top-10-most-valuable-brands/</link><title>Google now one of the top 10 most valuable brands</title><description>... from 2007. Interbrand notes that one of the most important new factors driving brand value across... to compete. The key to success, in good times and bad, is understanding how your brand creates value....Interbrand has concluded its study of this years top brands and released its a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7126-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7126_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:39:19">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/09/microsoft-takes-bronze-in-most-valuable-brand-report/</link><title>Microsoft remains third most valuable brand, Apple in top 20</title><description>...BusinessWeek's 2009 report on the 100 Best Global Brands is based on data collected during... dropping four percent from a brand value of $59,007 million to $56,647 million. This is the first year..., finally making it into the top 20 and increasing its brand value by 12 percent, from $13,724 million...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7126-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7126_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:41:55">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/02/surprise-apple-brands-top-social-media-index/</link><title>Surprise: Apple brands top "social media index"</title><description>... with their consumers" using "social media," has identified the top 100 social brands of 2008. It probably comes as no surprise to Infinite Loop readers that Apple and its brands show.... What this essentially means is that the company tracks the brands that users of Twitter, Flickr...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7126-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7126_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:43:43">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2011/01/fool-me-twice-iphone-users-burned-again-with-new-alarm-bug/</link><title>Fool me twice: iPhone users burned again with new alarm bug</title><description>...Happy 2011! As many of you may have already noticed, Apple tried to help you ring in the new year.... But how long until the next one?Like the Daylight Saving Time bug before it, the New Year bug was first exposed by our friends in New Zealand, who discovered that their non-repeating alarm clocks...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7126-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7126_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:45:16">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/11/pages-arrive-on-google-giving-businesses-a-reason-to-care/</link><title>Businesses can now participate on Google+ with brand "pages"</title><description>... businesses and brands to join its homegrown social network. The new feature closely resembles.... Any group, business, band, or brand will be able to create a page as a sort of profile. Individuals... it doesn't yet work for all pages.The new pages features joins other recent upgrades...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7126-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7126_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:46:57">http://arstechnica.com/security/2012/09/adobe-to-revoke-crypto-key-abused-to-sign-5000-malware-apps/</link><title>Adobe to revoke crypto key abused to sign malware apps (corrected)</title><description>...Adobe is revoking a cryptographic key used to confirm the authenticity of its applications... for valid Adobe software," officials wrote. The private key associated with the code... that was signed by the Adobe key was called pwdump7 v7.1. It "extracts password hashes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7126-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7126_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:48:29">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/08/users-treat-criticism-of-favorite-brands-as-threat-to-self-image/</link><title>Fanbois treat criticism of favorite brands as threat to self-image</title><description>... of Illinois, you may instead be defending yourself because you view criticisms of your favorite brand... of Consumer Psychology, examines the strength of consumer-brand relationships, concluding that those who have more knowledge of and experience with a brand are more personally impacted by incidents...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7126-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7126_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:50:01">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/12/bittorrent-serverless-chat-replaces-usernames-with-crypto-keys/</link><title>BitTorrent serverless chat replaces usernames with crypto keys</title><description>...BitTorrent, Inc. is developing a serverless instant messaging system that relies on public key... but with cryptographic key pairs.The company, which develops the BitTorrent peer-to-peer protocol... identity is a cryptographic key pair. To everyone on the BitTorrent Chat network at large, you ARE your...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7126-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7126_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:53:14">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/07/will-your-employer-get-sued-for-your-security-screw-ups/</link><title>So sue me: are lawyers really the key to computer security?</title><description>... management's heart is in it.This is a key advantage of using liability as the centerpiece...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>