<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7128">where to donate clothes in nyc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:12:14" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7128-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7128_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:12:15">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/04/how-to-donate-online-to-charities-supporting-boston-bombing-victims-and-first-responders/</link><title>How to donate online to charities supporting Boston bombing victims and first responders</title><description>... advisespeople to donate their money only to known, reputable organizations.Any Ars readers who want... (Donors also can text REDCROSS to 90999 to make a $10 donation.)The One FundAmericas Fund - Boston...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7128-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7128_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:14:07">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/12/bigmapple-other-nyc-apps-load-up-on-location-data-online/</link><title>BigMapple, other NYC apps load up on location data online</title><description>... without forcing them to switch to yet another new service.Thanks to the NYC BigApps competition..., with prizes that total up to $20,000. Public voting for the contest is now open (NYC BigApps...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7128-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7128_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:15:05">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/05/silicon-valley-donations-to-obama-reach-record-levels/</link><title>Silicon Valley donations to Obama reach record levels</title><description>... donation to Romney, and then a combined $700 to Rick Perry in September.And Steve Wozniak, the Apple...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7128-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7128_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:17:36">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/12/wikipedias-new-plea-for-donations-stirs-skepticism/</link><title>Wikipedia's new plea for donations stirs skepticism</title><description>... has mixed things up by replacing it recently with a personal plea for donations. Wales appeal has triggered...) and that all of its content is free. He says that donations help the organization cover the increasing cost of bandwidth... donation requests and turn to the ad-based revenue model that supports many other sites that ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7128-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7128_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:18:43">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/02/wikileaks-struggling-to-make-ends-meet-begs-for-donations/</link><title>WikiLeaks, struggling to make ends meet, begs for donations</title><description>... necessary" to keep the site going, and is begging for donations lest it be stuck offline...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7128-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7128_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:19:46">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/01/2012-childs-play-drive-ends-with-record-of-over-28700-in-donations/</link><title>2012 Child's Play drive ends with record of over $28,700 in donations</title><description>... Fundraising total:$28,713.52Number of individual donations: 454Average donation: $63.25Median donation: $20Most common donation: $5 (86 donations)Top single donation: $5,000 (!)Donations of $1,000 or more: 4Donations of $100 or more: 43D...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7128-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7128_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:22:02">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/10/love-gigabit-seattle-comcast-has-donated-lots-to-the-guy-now-trying-to-slow-it/</link><title>Love Gigabit Seattle? Comcast has donated lots to promoter’s rival (Updated)</title><description>... were donations for Murrays earlier state senate campaign.Locally in Washington State, where Comcast... on the city's gigabit project and the Comcast donations, and we have posted it at the bottom..., theWashington Postreports that Comcast has been donating money to McGinns rival, state Sen. Ed Murray...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7128-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7128_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:24:52">http://arstechnica.com/security/2010/01/fbi-warns-of-haiti-donation-scams-advises-legit-ways-to-help/</link><title>Online scammers try to hijack Haiti donation bandwagon</title><description>... out spam soliciting donations that will go anywhere but Haiti. Scammers pop up anytime something... such as the Haiti quakes, though, have the added benefit of concerned citizens wanting to donate moneyindeed... donation sites and ended up sending their money to those with ill intentions instead of charities...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7128-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7128_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:25:37">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/07/where-the-wild-lawyers-are-knocking-sequels-off-kickstarter/</link><title>Where the Wild Lawyers Are: knocking sequels off Kickstarter</title><description>...A London writer and illustrator who wanted to create a sequel to Where the Wild Things Are, one of the most famous children's books of all time, have had their idea shot down due to a copyright... from within the UK, where we had taken specific legal advice and confirmed that we are not infringing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7128-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7128_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:28:09">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2011/03/apple-stores-accepting-old-ipad-donations-for-teach-for-america/</link><title>Apple Stores accepting old iPad donations for Teach for America</title><description>...), but have no plans to resell? Apple may have a solution for you: the company has begun promoting a new donation... for donation. Retail employees will give the iPads to Teach for America, which subsequently... for America is a 501(c)(3) corporation, so if you need an extra incentive to donate your iPad...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>