<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7129">avg home edition</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:30:55" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7129-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7129_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:30:56">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2008/11/avg-incorrectly-flags-user32-dll-in-windows-xp-sp2sp3/</link><title>AVG incorrectly flags user32.dll in Windows XP SP2/SP3</title><description>...After a Sunday virus definition update, AVGs antivirus software began to mistakenly warn users... to have been affected (users who have moved to Vista can apparently breathe a sigh of relief). Both AVG 7.5 or 8.0 was affected by the flawed definition file. Complaints started to flood the AVG forums and the security...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7129-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7129_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:32:39">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/12/sonys-home-juggles-free-speech-with-hate-speech/</link><title>Sony's Home juggles free speech, hate speech</title><description>...Sonys Home has had a rocky start. Server issues, lack of compelling content, and a somewhat hostile... its discrimination, Michael Marsh, a gamer who wanted to set up a gay/straight alliance in Home, told..., which contains the word Hell. This points to a larger problem that Home will be forced to deal...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7129-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7129_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:36:02">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/12/hands-on-with-sodium-one-not-quite-the-evolution-home-needs/</link><title>Hands-on with Sodium One: not quite the evolution Home needs</title><description>...After over a year of existence, PlayStation Home is still struggling to find its place. Despite a wealth of game-themed spaces and even an alternate reality game, there isn't much to do while in Home, something that's been a problem for the service from the very beginning. Enter Sodium One. The curiously named Home space is being billed by Sony as the "next evolutionary step"...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7129-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7129_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:37:34">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/warhawk-invades-home-goes-on-sale/</link><title>Warhawk invades Home, goes on sale</title><description>...Sony has announced that it will be adding yet another game-related space to PlayStation Home later today, with the Warhawk Command Center. This new area will not only look like the game that it's based on, but will also give users the ability to plan strategies for upcoming Warhawk battles.In addition to various monitors that display high scores and gameplay tips, the area also includes a ne...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7129-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7129_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:38:53">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/01/slap-happy-sam-playstation-home/</link><title>Slap Happy Sam makes PlayStation Home fun, Conspiracy falters</title><description>...Ever since the release of Home, Sony has experimented with various ways to entice users to enter... of mini-games. Now Sony is attempting something different: releasing Home games crafted by actual..., but not any more interesting. This is an action-style game set in Home, and as such it doesn't play...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7129-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7129_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:41:40">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/11/worth-the-money-the-gaming-collectors-edition-trend/</link><title>Worth the money? The gaming collector's edition trend</title><description>... in the numberand sizeof collector's editions available. At times it seems that nearly every game... Riley from the NPD group to find out."Limited and Collector's editions of games have seen... in addition to giving consumers choice by offering several different SKUs to select from, special editions...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7129-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7129_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:44:55">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/07/windows-home-server-is-dead-but-we-shouldnt-mourn-it/</link><title>Windows Home Server is dead, but we shouldn't mourn it</title><description>... four Windows Server versions, the Enterprise, Small Business Server, and HPC editions... Home Server. This too is being left behind. The current version, Windows Home Server 2011... features or upgrades.Naturally, Windows Home Server's die-hard band of advocates is annoyed...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7129-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7129_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:48:26">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/12/sony-home-will-become-a-system-seller/</link><title>Sony: Home will become a system seller</title><description>...After what feels like forever, Sonys Home service has finally launched for the PlayStation 3. Unfortunately, in its current open beta form, Home has received somewhat of a lukewarm reception thanks... for the service and expects that one day, Home will be a major selling point for the struggling PS3...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7129-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7129_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:49:39">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2014/01/the-battle-for-the-home-why-nest-is-really-googles-new-smart-home-division/</link><title>The battle for the home: Why Nest is really Google’s new smart home division</title><description>...Guess who's now the leader in the connected-home space? Google's 3.2 billion dollar... of the connected home. With the dust settled and news of the acquisition sinking in, it's time to take a look at what Google might have in store for the company.Google's Smart Home DivisionOne...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7129-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7129_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:51:47">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/08/gone-home-review-where-the-heart-is/</link><title>Gone Home review: Where the heart is</title><description>... and script of Gone Home came in the form of a movie, the result might be received as a competent film... at the difficulties of growing up gay.But Gone Home isn't a movie. You control it with a mouse... of story-only gamelast year's Dear Esther springs immediately to mindyet Gone Home has already carved...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>