<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7131">golf games</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:13:56" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7131-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7131_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:13:57">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/10/wiiware-and-virtual-console-monday-shining-midnight-golf-edition/</link><title>WiiWare and Virtual Console Monday: Shining Midnight Golf edition</title><description>...I guess weve been spoiled these past few weeks, as the WiiWare and Virtual Console line-ups have continued to give us great game after great game. But all good things must come to an end, though there are still a few titles to get excited about this week. WiiWare Midnight Bowling (GameLoft, 1-4 players, Rated E, 800 Wii points) If there is one thing the Wii needs, its a bowling game. Its not like...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7131-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7131_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:15:32">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/11/xbox-one-game-extravaganza-hands-on-with-10-launch-exclusives/</link><title>Xbox One game extravaganza: Hands-on with 10 launch exclusives</title><description>... will be pretty familiar to anyone who's played a golf game, and despite the cartoonish characters...When game publishers offer the opportunity to preview an upcoming game at some elaborate event... every Xbox One-exclusive game in the console's launch lineup, though, I dec...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7131-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7131_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:16:43">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/03/sackboy-comes-to-hot-shots-golf-a-dozen-people-are-excited/</link><title>Sackboy comes to Hot Shots Golf, a dozen people are excited</title><description>...Hot Shots Golf: Out of Bounds is one of the more enjoyable PS3 games that it seems no one talks about. It's a shame too, the game is a very fun and addictive take on golf.You can read our original review for more info.Owners of the game will get a fun bonus tomorrow: Sackboy will be hitting...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7131-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7131_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:18:54">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/04/tiger-woods-on-the-wii-comes-with-disc-golf-video/</link><title>Tiger Woods on the Wii comes with disc-golf (video)</title><description>...Tiger Woods PGA Tour 10 is going to be one of the first games bundled with the Wii MotionPlus, and it's the game that has many of us excited about the technology. A trailer for the title shows off the ability to play disc golf using the peripheral, and the video gives you a good idea of just...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7131-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7131_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:20:16">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/03/keeping-golf-courses-clean-with-recycled-sewage/</link><title>Keeping golf courses clean with recycled sewage</title><description>... for a pastime I (attempt to) enjoy: golf. According to a UN estimate, golf courses around the world use 2.5... Nevada is home to 53 golf courses, many of them high-end. Courses such as these are expected... of using lower quality, recycled water, possibly including some forms of sewage. The golf course...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7131-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7131_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:21:55">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/05/week-in-gaming-guitar-hero-repair-star-wars-psp-go/</link><title>Week in gaming: Guitar Hero repair, Star Wars, PSP GO!</title><description>...This week in gaming we have the man who created a great guide to help fix your Guitar Hero...;s success at retail. Let's see what the world of gaming was talking about during the week.Writer...: When an independent game developer found its latest game on the torrent sites, it had a pleasantly...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7131-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7131_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:23:10">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/10/google-enters-gaming-with-adsense-for-games/</link><title>Google enters gaming with AdSense for Games</title><description>...In-game advertising has long been a hot button issue among gamers. They can be intrusive and often downright annoying. But development isnt getting any cheaper, so in-game ads arent going anywhere... AdSense for Games. Like the original AdSense, this service will include text, photo, and video...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7131-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7131_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:25:12">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/07/ars-technicast-episode-5-retro-gaming/</link><title>Ars Technicast, Episode 5 - Retro gaming</title><description>...This week were dedicating our show to retro gaming. As we discuss the games of our youth, we discover that were still in love with many of those early games. Gaming editor Kyle Orland joins Senior... was only allowed to have one console at a time), the games we played at arcades, and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7131-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7131_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:26:20">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/10/bermudas-golf-courses-sit-on-land-thats-partly-an-african-import/</link><title>Bermuda's golf courses sit on land that's (partly) an African import</title><description>... can find them just beneath the grass of Bermudas beautiful golf coursesa little earth that caught...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7131-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7131_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:28:19">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/week-in-gaming-halo-wars-price-drops-and-ea-focuses-on-the-wii/</link><title>Week in gaming: Halo Wars, price drops, and EA loves the Wii</title><description>... had to say goodbye to long-time contributor Frank Caron. Thankfully, there was a ton of gaming news this week... of the past seven days.Playing video games linked to breast-feeding, not crime Frustrated with the way that mainstream media continually links violent crime to games, our own Ben Kuchera did a little...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>