<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7133">museum of natural history</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:54:13" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7133-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7133_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:54:14">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/01/writings-of-natural-selection-co-discoverer-alfred-russel-wallace-go-online/</link><title>Writings of natural selection co-discoverer Alfred Russel Wallace go online</title><description>... of their names on the cover.A hundred years after his death, the Natural History Museum (NHM) is hoping... History Museumis one of many institutions that believes it should be.The reason why is simple: ask the average person in the street who discovered natural selection, they will ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7133-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7133_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:55:44">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/02/science-online-at-the-american-museum-of-natural-history-tackles-social-media-for-science/</link><title>Ars and nature.com at the American Museum of Natural History: good stuff</title><description>... with the American Museum of Natural History toorganizea special program entitled "Beyond a Trend... journalists to the museum staffhave adopted social media to reach the public more effectively...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7133-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7133_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:57:50">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/02/the-exosuit-a-wearable-submarine-for-visiting-deep-water/</link><title>The “Exosuit”: A wearable submarine for visiting deep water</title><description>... at the American Museum of Natural History on Thursday. Dubbed the "Exosuit," the system lets humans... of the ocean. According to Michael Lombardi, dive safety officer at the American Museum of Natural History..., they will also get to image them wit...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7133-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7133_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:00:38">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/02/organizing-a-museum-can-take-a-lesson-from-design-and-digital-media/</link><title>Organizing a museum can take a lesson from design and digital media</title><description>... Story)that Fiona Romeo, head of design and digital media at the National Maritime Museum (NMM... Staghow could museum curation follow on from stop-motion animation?Romeo has been working in museums... as a story skeptic as far as museum exhibits were concerned. "Museums arguabl...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7133-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7133_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:01:30">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/06/early-apple-documents-posted-to-computer-history-museum-site/</link><title>Early Apple documents posted to Computer History Museum site</title><description>...A couple of documents giving insight into Apple's early days are making the rounds today thanks to The Computer History Museum (CHM) in Mountain View, California. Apple's Preliminary Macintosh Business Plan and Preliminary Confidential Offering Memorandum have both been posted to the museum's website, donated by Dan Kottke and Mike Markkula.According to the CHM, the Preliminary Mac...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7133-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7133_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:04:27">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/10/spacewar-the-first-2d-top-down-shooter-turns-50/</link><title>Spacewar! , the first 2D top-down shooter, turns 50</title><description>... cafeteria. Now I play Angry Birds on my Android phone, but the Computer History Museum in Mountain View... video games: Spacewar! Spacewar! at the Computer History Museum First conceived by a crew of developers... formative editions are the focus of the Computer History Museum'...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7133-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7133_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:05:24">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/02/a-visual-tour-of-the-creation-museum/</link><title>A visual tour of the Creation Museum</title><description>... tickets, Nate and I headed into the Main Hall. It felt like walking into any natural history museum until... viewpoint. Exhibits displayed the kind of things you'd expect to see in any natural history museum, again accompanied by text you wouldnot expect ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7133-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7133_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:08:22">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/03/private-collector-builds-apple-pop-up-museum-to-tell-the-story-of-apple/</link><title>Private collector builds Apple Pop-Up Museum to “tell the story of Apple”</title><description>... its own history museum, but the project got killed when Steve Jobs returned to the company in 1997... selection of early Apple documentation available to the public, at the Computer History Museum...Apple may not open its own museum anytime soon, but that's not stopping enthusi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7133-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7133_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:11:55">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/06/a-trip-through-gaming-history-the-videogame-history-museum-at-e3/</link><title>A trip through gaming history: the Videogame History Museum at E3</title><description>..., software, and collectibles put together by the Videogame History Museum. Even if the next big high.... Andrew Cunningham Large portions of the Videogame History Museum's sprawling booth.... Andrew Cunningham Large portions of the Videogame History Museum's sprawling booth...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7133-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7133_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:15:07">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/07/fracked-pennsylvania-shale-could-be-naturally-leaky/</link><title>Fracked Pennsylvania shale could be naturally leaky</title><description>...Hydraulic fracturingfrackingfor natural gas has revolutionized the energy industry in many places... there. In nature, however, its usually true that to consider something to be impossible... natural gas production wells in parts of Pennsylvania and New York. While that suggested the water...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>