<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7134">history of yoga</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:17:40" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7134-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7134_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:17:41">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/10/hands-on-with-the-lenovo-yoga-tablet-a-lopsided-design-and-18-hour-runtime/</link><title>Hands on with the Lenovo Yoga Tablet: lopsided design and 18 hour runtime</title><description>...Lenovo held a media event in New York today where it announced the Yoga Tablet, an oddly designed..., which Lenovo says should give the tablet 18 hours of battery life.The Yoga Tablet is very much a budget device...: the Yoga Tablet is coated in a silver flake plastic that looks like something from a 90s Radio Shack shelf...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7134-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7134_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:18:23">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/11/a-good-ultrabook-a-bad-tablet-the-lenovo-ideapad-yoga-13-review/</link><title>A good Ultrabook, a bad tablet: the Lenovo IdeaPad Yoga 13 review</title><description>... with screens that slide or fold down over the keyboard.Lenovo's IdeaPad Yoga 13 is something... qualityEnlarge / In laptop mode, the Yoga is practically indistinguishable from a standard Ultrabook. Note both... CunninghamSpecs at a glance: Lenovo IdeaPad Yoga 13Screen1600900 at 13.3" (138ppi)OSWindows 8...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7134-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7134_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:21:11">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/01/lenovos-ideapad-yoga-can-do-downward-dog/</link><title>Lenovo's IdeaPad Yoga can do downward dog</title><description>..., the IdeaPad Yoga, has a display that can fold all the way back into a tablet-like form factor. IdeaPad YogaThe Yoga wasnt so much announced as teased at the beginning of CES, with a set of photos showing... i7 processor.The hinge on the Yoga is flexible (obviously), but stiff enough that we could fold...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7134-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7134_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:22:07">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2014/03/lenovo-yoga-2-pro-review-you-say-you-want-resolution/</link><title>Lenovo Yoga 2 Pro review: You say you want resolution</title><description>...The Yoga 2 Pro has a knack for bending and folding. The first thing youll notice about Lenovos...: Lenovo Yoga 2 ProSCREEN32001800 at 13.3" (276 ppi)OSWindows 8.1 64-bitCPU1.6GHz Intel Core... the second iteration of the Yoga Pro line brings more to the portable party.Most notably, the new Yoga...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7134-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7134_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:24:53">http://arstechnica.com/science/2008/11/new-exhibit-blends-art-history-and-science/</link><title>New exhibit blends art, history, and science</title><description>...The Huntington Library opened a permanent exhibit on November 1st that masterfully displays the roots of modern science, going back as far as the first century, to Ptolemys model of the heavens. Ars took a firsthand look at the new Dibner Hall of the History of Science during its press preview...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7134-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7134_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:27:30">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/04/a-history-of-the-amiga-part-9-the-demo-scene/</link><title>A history of the Amiga, part 8: The demo scene</title><description>... with a long and storied history, produced a 64k intro ironically called The Scene is Dead... to mention. While at first glance the demo scene might seem to be a part of history, its continued...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7134-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7134_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:29:48">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/04/from-touch-displays-to-the-surface-a-brief-history-of-touchscreen-technology/</link><title>From touch displays to the Surface: A brief history of touchscreen technology</title><description>... in the history of touchscreen technology.Android and iOS users should thank to E.A. Johnson... iDevices anyway?) But history did not end with 2011, either. We'll also discuss how...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7134-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7134_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:32:13">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/01/scienceonline-09-history-art-and-science/</link><title>ScienceOnline 09: History, art, and science</title><description>... and the History of Science." Outside of science, engineering, and tech related things, I have always enjoyed learning about history, and the history of science, engineering, and mathematics has always drawn me...: "Why is the history of science so important?" In mainstream culture, where sc...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7134-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7134_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:35:12">http://arstechnica.com/security/2010/02/browser-history-hijack-social-networks-lost-anonymity/</link><title>Browser history hijack + social networks = lost anonymity</title><description>...Simply joining a few groups at social networking sites may reveal enough information for hackers to personally identify you, according to some recent computer science research. In a paper that will be presented at a security conference later this year, an international team of academics describes how they were able to build membership sets using information that social networking sites make avail...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7134-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7134_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:38:49">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/09/the-complicated-truth-behind-scientific-findings/</link><title>The complicated history of simple scientific facts</title><description>... it as a fact, and write science articles assuming that it is one.A full history, or pronouncements...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>