<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7135">Ahmed Dogan assassination</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:40:42" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7135-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7135_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:40:43">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/06/e3-assassins-creed-2-gets-november-release-date/</link><title>Assassin's Creed 2 gets November release date</title><description>...While it's been no secret that Assassin's Creed 2 is in the works, little has been known about the game until now. At the Ubisoft press conference, a new trailer was shown and Ubi has announced an official release date for the title.At the conference yesterday, a new trailer for the sequel to Assassin's Creed showcased the 15th Century Venice setting and Altair's replacement, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7135-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7135_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:43:36">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/08/together-we-kill-first-look-at-assassins-creed-brotherhood/</link><title>Together we kill: first look at Assassin's Creed Brotherhood</title><description>... assassins.After his exploits in the previous game, Ezio has become somewhat of a hero amongst the assassin... assassins, instead you can summon them to lend a hand. They're sort of an evolved version.... It was incredibly cool. However, I was told that it would take quite a bit of time to get your assassins...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7135-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7135_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:44:18">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/10/hiding-in-the-shadows-hands-on-with-assassins-creed-multiplayer/</link><title>Hiding in the shadows: hands-on with Assassin's Creed multiplayer</title><description>... of creating the feeling of being an assassin, a feeling that can often be lost in the complex single-player...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7135-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7135_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:46:03">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/11/assassins-creed-revelations-review-climbing-up-the-walls/</link><title>Assassin's Creed Revelations review: the upside of yearly releases</title><description>... war between an ancient order of assassins and the Knights Templar stayed. And this is where it gets a little tough to explain. Backstoryor lack thereofIn the first game, you played as shamed assassin..., an Italian assassin. They tie together through Desmond Miles, a twenty-something bartender kidnapped...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7135-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7135_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:47:11">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/11/more-successor-than-sequel-hands-on-with-assassins-creed-2/</link><title>More successor than sequel: hands on with Assassin's Creed 2</title><description>... in the lower right corner of the screen was littered with things to do: from optional assassinations...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7135-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7135_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:49:14">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/02/ubisoft-details-drm/</link><title>Official explanation of controversial Assassin's Creed 2 DRM</title><description>...Ubisoft has long had some controversial ideas about how DRM should be used, but when PC Gamer was given a review copy of Assassin's Creed 2 on the PC it seemed as if the reality was going to be much worse than what opponents to DRM had feared: the game requires an always-on 'Net connection and constant communication with the home server. If your connection is dropped, the game kicks you...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7135-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7135_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:50:55">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/08/acr-preview/</link><title>When in doubt, use a bomb: Assassin's Creed Revelations first look</title><description>... becoming a master assassin, which took place before the events of the first game.With its now annual...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7135-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7135_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:51:32">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/11/2007s-assassins-creed-was-a/</link><title>Sweeter the second time: Ars reviews Assassin's Creed 2</title><description>...-living lifestyle as he takes up the role of assassin in order to exact revenge for his family... learning new abilities. Untrained as an assassin, Ezio learns as the game progresses, and so does... for most of the game, ranging from new assassinations to improved climbing abilities.Many of the new skills...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7135-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7135_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:53:30">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/03/rumor-ubisoft-pirates-own-soundtrack-for-assassins-creed-brotherhood-pc/</link><title>Did Ubisoft pirate its own soundtrack for Assassin's Creed: Brotherhood PC?</title><description>...Assassin's Creed: Brotherhood is finally coming to the PC later this month, after hitting consoles last November. To make amends, the publisher is releasing a digital deluxe version of the game, complete with a wide range of extras, including a copy of the game's soundtrack. The problem? It looks like that soundtrack may actually be a torrented version.As one Reddit user discovered afte...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7135-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7135_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:53:56">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/04/sci-fi-author-sues-ubisoft-over-assassins-creed-copyright-infringement/</link><title>Sci-fi author sues Ubisoft over Assassin's Creed copyright infringement</title><description>... to the series' sci-fi-meets-historical-assassinations plotline.The book even makes reference to using the Link for assassination attempts, though the specific targets of those assassinations don't seem... 290:"If John Wilkes Booth fathered a child after he assassinated Lincoln, and we found...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>