<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7136">Soccer trick</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:56:01" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7136-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7136_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:56:02">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/12/sega-soccer-slam-returns-as-an-xbox-original-on-the-360/</link><title>Sega Soccer Slam returns as an Xbox original on the 360</title><description>... that Sega Soccer Slam never sold in huge numbers, but I loved my copy, and it became a huge hit at parties whenever I pulled it out. An over the top, violent, and cartoonish take on the sport of the soccer... and deceptively deep gameplay shouldnt think twice about picking up Soccer Slam. IGN also gushed. I really hope...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7136-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7136_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:57:22">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/03/nintendo-details-excitebots-trick-racing/</link><title>Nintendo details Excitebots: Trick Racing</title><description>... will depend on a combination of the tricks you pull off and where you finish in the actual... with Mario Kart Wii. Excitebots: Trick Racing will be hitting the Nintendo Wii on April 20....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7136-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7136_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:00:06">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/12/app-store-lessons-bad-karma-tricks/</link><title>App Store lessons: bad Karma tricks</title><description>...Nothing says lame attempt to get noticed more than including the names of popular products in your App Store description to raise your search profile. When users search for those names, up pops your application like a poor, unloved relative who shows up at family reunions, gets drunk, and tries to go home with the family silver. At Tapbots, Paul Haddad noticed that unrelated applications were pop...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7136-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7136_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:02:14">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/12/xbox-marketplace-update-soccer-slam-edition/</link><title>Xbox Marketplace Update: Soccer Slam edition</title><description>...)GraphSpacer (200 MP)Word Soup (400 MP)Tower Revolution (400 MP)Xbox OriginalsSega Soccer Slam (1200 MP... into Soccer Slam this week. The game features everything thats great about arcade sports games...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7136-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7136_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:02:53">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/04/wii-excitebots-is-missing-next-gen-features-still-fun/</link><title>Wii Excitebots is missing next-gen features, still fun</title><description>.... That's where Excitebots: Trick Racing comes in. Why settle for fun when you can be insane? Title Excitebots: Trick Racing Developer Monster Games Inc. Publisher Nintendo Price $39.99, $49.99... a soccer ball into the goal, or you can glide off cliffs and rescue butterflies... all while racing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7136-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7136_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:04:38">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/04/this-week-in-game-releases-april-20-26-2009/</link><title>This week in game releases: April 20-26, 2009</title><description>...Pick of the week: Excitebots - Trick Racing (Wii)If you thought last week was slow in terms of new... to launch title Excite Truck, Excitebots: Trick Racing swaps road vehicles for animal-themed cars... the controller in circles to boost off certain obstacles. Yes, it makes you look silly. WiiExcitebots: Trick...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7136-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7136_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:08:18">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/06/buzzfeed-sued-for-3-6-million-over-fairly-boring-soccer-photo/</link><title>BuzzFeed sued for $3.6 million over fairly boring soccer photo</title><description>...An Idaho photographer has sued the social media site Buzzfeed for $3.6 million. The lawsuit says the site is liable for damages, not just for publishing the photographer's photo of a female soccer player heading a ball back in 2010 but for every one of the dozensof sites that ran the photo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7136-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7136_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:11:20">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/12/microsoft-wants-your-windows-7-tips-tricks/</link><title>Microsoft wants your Windows 7 tips and tricks</title><description>...Microsoft is trying to tap into the Windows tweaking community. The Microsoft TechNet Magazine is relaunching its popular Tip of the Day feature, starting with a look at the best tips and tricks for Windows 7, but instead of writing these tips and tricks itself, Microsoft is reaching out to its users. The Windows tweaking community is huge, and apparently Microsoft wants to embrace it a little mo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7136-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7136_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:13:57">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/04/magic-tricks-on-dsiware-stabbing-pirates-on-wiiware-yawn/</link><title>Magic tricks on DSiWare, stabbing pirates on WiiWare, yawn</title><description>... some magic tricks you can play with your DS.WiiWare Party Fun Pirate (TOMY Corporation, 1-4 players, Rated...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7136-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7136_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:16:34">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/10/weird-kindle-tricks-screensavers-screenshots-and-games/</link><title>Weird Kindle tricks: screensavers, screenshots, and games</title><description>... know about. These tips and tricks may not radically change your Kindle experience, but they range... favorite Kindle tips and tricks?...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>