<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7137">Cat movies</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:17:39" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7137-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7137_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:17:40">http://arstechnica.com/business/2014/03/this-is-londons-first-cat-cafe-lady-dinahs-cat-emporium/</link><title>This is London’s first cat cafe, Lady Dinah’s Cat Emporium</title><description>...Lady Dinah's Cat Emporium opens this weekend, so it seemed only right that I stopped... and serving staff.Between the front entrance and the cats themselves there are three doors. Between... towels. An attendant lays down the ground rules for how not to handle cats (don't fuss them...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7137-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7137_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:20:20">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/06/what-does-your-cat-do-when-youre-not-around/</link><title>What does your cat do when you’re not around?</title><description>...Even though we domesticated them over 9,000 years ago, house cats remain a bit of an anomaly... we probably shouldnt. Those of us who keep our house cats indoors have a pretty good idea of what they get up to all day. But those free-roaming cats keep an air of mystery. Just what do they get...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7137-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7137_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:22:43">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/12/earliest-evidence-of-cat-domestication-found-in-china/</link><title>Earliest evidence of cat domestication found in China</title><description>...There has been much debate about how cats went from hunting in the wild to being a much-loved pet; we know little about their domestication. Now researchers have found the earliest case of cat... have happened.The oldest record of a cats association with humans comes from Cyprus where, about 9,500 years...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7137-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7137_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:24:58">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/01/a-dream-come-true-become-a-cat-with-catlateral-damage/</link><title>A dream come true: Become a cat with Catlateral Damage</title><description>...First-person simulators are cool. Cats are cool. Indie title Catlateral Damage brings together these two cool things to make something even cooler: a cat simulator. You're a cat trapped... you live the cat experience first-hand. Punch and swipe things with your paws, sending them tumbling...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7137-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7137_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:26:18">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/05/warner-brothers-sued-for-unauthorized-use-of-two-feline-internet-memes/</link><title>Warner Brothers sued for unauthorized use of Nyan Cat and Keyboard Cat</title><description>... in the lawsuit.Keyboard Cat is a YouTube video uploaded in 2007. It shows a man's cat supposedly playing music on a keyboard. Nyan Cat is featured in an extremely irritating video that was uploaded to YouTube in 2011. As the complaint describes it, Nyan Cat is "a character with a cat's face...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7137-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7137_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:27:59">http://arstechnica.com/science/2008/12/stealthy-strides-are-less-efficient-how-cats-walk/</link><title>Stealthy strides are less efficient: how cats walk</title><description>...Cats and dogs, dogs and cats. Mankinds best friends can be a little polarizing, with cat people..., examines the way in which cats walk. That might sound like a pretty simple thing... this last bit). Cats, on the other hand, arent specialized for walking long distances. Instead...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7137-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7137_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:29:30">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/02/my-life-as-a-cat-an-hour-with-terry-cavanaghs-chatchat-mmo/</link><title>My life as a cat: an hour with Terry Cavanagh's ChatChat MMO</title><description>...The instructions underneath VVVVVV creator Terry Cavanagh's new browser-based MMO ChatChat simply read: "be a cat." These instructions also describe a dream I held between the ages of 5 and 7, so I'm eager to finally see if my dreams were realistic. Below is a short, diary-style description of my first hour as a cat.Warning: The following story contains major spoilers for what...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7137-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7137_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:31:10">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/03/demographics-cat-map-plots-locations-names-and-colors-of-london-felines/</link><title>DeMOGraphics: Cat Map plots locations, names, and colors of London felines</title><description>...TheZoological Society of London(ZSL) has launched an initiative to collect data about the cats of London into a map. It's called, perhaps unsurprisingly, Cat Map.Cat Map invites mog owners..., as "ginger".ZSL is keen to find out how many and what sort of cats live in London. The data...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7137-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7137_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:31:45">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/11/cats-use-gravity-inertia-gecko-like-process-to-lap-up-cream/</link><title>Cats use gravity, inertia, gecko-like process to lap up cream</title><description>...The way cats drink water turns out to be a more complex process than we thought, according... video of cats drinking water, they found that cats are, among other things, using only the tip... that cats would take advantage of the grain of their tongue that serves them so well in grooming...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7137-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7137_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:33:38">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/10/dell-locates-source-of-cat-pee-smell-in-laptops-after-four-months/</link><title>Dell locates source of cat pee smell in laptops after four months</title><description>... that smelled like cat urine, according to the BBC. Four months later, Dell has finally figured... smelled like "cat pee. Many seemed to think the smell was coming from inside the keyboard, so Dell... of cat pee was strong in these laptops.Dell announced late Tuesday that the palm rest turned...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>