<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7141">Cambridge must do</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:27:48" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7141-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7141_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:27:49">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/10/xbla-pc-orcs-must-die-adds-third-person-action-to-tower-defense/</link><title>XBLA, PC Orcs Must Die adds third-person action to tower defense</title><description>... to protect. When things begin to go wrong, there's very little you can do about it except reload your... more. This is why Orcs Must Die is such a breath of fresh air: the game puts you into the actual dungeons... is in the dungeon while all this is going on, so you must run from place to place to set your traps, and you...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7141-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7141_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:29:29">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/06/what-you-can-do-when-junk-apps-invade-the-app-storewhat-nintendo-must-do-to-make-the-3ds-a-must-have/</link><title>What Nintendo must do to make the 3DS a must-have</title><description>... goliath should do to make the 3DS a must-buy. Connect digital purchases to your account, not your... so far for Kinectthat screams "must buy"? It's getting sad that all this new technology..., that's going to make us want the system.What are your thoughts? What does Nintendo have to do...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7141-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7141_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:30:18">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/07/review-orcs-must-die-2-encourages-you-to-share-your-tower-defending/</link><title>Review: Orcs Must Die 2 encourages you to share your tower defending</title><description>... Orcs Must Die went a long way toward fixing this problem by adding a bit of direct, third-person combat... after Orcs Must Dies initial release, Orcs Must Die 2 does its best to extend this original concept... style.Half the fun of Orcs Must Die 2 is coming up with ways to combine these traps and weapons ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7141-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7141_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:32:10">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/03/get-it-done-with-gnome-do-081/</link><title>Get it done with GNOME Do 0.8.1</title><description>...GNOME Do is an open source launcher utility for the Linux desktop that offers a minimalistic, task... version, 0.8.1, was released on Friday.GNOME Do was originally modeled after Quicksilver, a similar... so that it can be used very quickly.GNOME Do is highly extensible and provides a plugin framework that can be used...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7141-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7141_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:34:46">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/02/in-search-of-a-proper-to-do-application-for-android/</link><title>In search of a proper to-do application for Android</title><description>... sort of functionality. I had forgotten to look into downloading a to-do application that would allow... to that same specialty store.So I went to the Google Play store in search of a few to-do lists and task..., those in need of a quick way to leave a note can do so with one tap from the main screen. For power...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7141-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7141_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:36:02">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/02/can-do-not-track-tame-the-webs-cookie-monsters/</link><title>Can Do Not Track starve the Web's Cookie Monster?</title><description>... a "Do Not Track" button on their browsers. While a good step toward broader Web privacy...: we must rely on advertisers to police themselves and on browser makers to implement functionality... in Apple's Safari browser in order to serve up advertising cookies shows the need for a system like Do...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7141-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7141_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:38:21">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/06/ie-10s-do-not-track-default-dies-quick-death/</link><title>IE 10′s "Do Not Track" default dies quick death</title><description>...Well, that didnt take long.The latest proposed draft of the Do Not Track specification published Wednesday requires that users must choose to turn on the anti-behavioral tracking feature in their browsers and software.Microsoft IE 10, which the company announced last week, will have Do Not Track...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7141-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7141_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:39:20">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/09/do-not-track-support-added-to-chrome-arriving-by-the-end-of-the-year/</link><title>Do Not Track support added to Chrome, arriving by the end of the year</title><description>... for the "Do Not Track" Web privacy feature yesterday. The feature will make its way through... they visit that they do not wish for third parties to record their online activity. The feature has been controversial due to Microsoft's Do Not Track implementation in Internet Explorer 10. Redmond...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7141-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7141_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:40:28">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2011/02/do-not-track-arrives-in-firefox-beta-ad-industry-not-on-board-yet/</link><title>Do Not Track arrives in Firefox beta, ad industry not on board yet</title><description>... also adds support for a "Do Not Track" setting.The implications of behavioral advertising... and Mozilla last month, the downside of introducing a new Do Not Track mechanism is that won't actually... the feature through the Firefox user interface, but doing so could potentially help to encourage...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7141-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7141_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:43:31">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/02/white-house-announces-new-privacy-bill-of-rights-do-not-track-agreement/</link><title>White House announces new privacy "Bill of Rights," Do Not Track agreement</title><description>...: the completion of an industry agreement on "Do Not Track" technology for behavior-based web... Trade Commission. The "Do Not Track" agreement is a first step toward that model. Signed..., Yahoo, Microsoft, and AOL, the agreement will lead to the adoption of Do Not Track features integrated...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>