<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7142">Amsterdam museums</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:45:36" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7142-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7142_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:45:37">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/02/organizing-a-museum-can-take-a-lesson-from-design-and-digital-media/</link><title>Organizing a museum can take a lesson from design and digital media</title><description>... Story)that Fiona Romeo, head of design and digital media at the National Maritime Museum (NMM... Staghow could museum curation follow on from stop-motion animation?Romeo has been working in museums... as a story skeptic as far as museum exhibits were concerned. "Museums arguabl...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7142-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7142_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:47:18">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/02/a-visual-tour-of-the-creation-museum/</link><title>A visual tour of the Creation Museum</title><description>... in Genesis and the Creation Museum. The morning after the debate, we headed back over to the Creation Museum to take in the sights and to further investigate some of the things that caught our eye in our... narrative in Genesis 1-2, walking through the Creation Museum can be unsettling. There are fossils...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7142-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7142_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:49:53">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/03/private-collector-builds-apple-pop-up-museum-to-tell-the-story-of-apple/</link><title>Private collector builds Apple Pop-Up Museum to “tell the story of Apple”</title><description>...Apple may not open its own museum anytime soon, but that's not stopping enthusiasts... Lonnie Mimms to put together a museum-quality exhibit based on Mimms' extensive... and stardom." And so the two teamed together to create the Apple Pop-Up Museum, which will be part...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7142-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7142_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:51:34">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/04/gallery-apple-pop-up-museum-and-vintage-computer-festival-southwest/</link><title>Gallery: Apple Pop-Up museum and Vintage Computer Festival Southeast</title><description>...Were you in Atlanta last weekend to visit the Apple Pop-Up Museum as part of the Vintage Computer... Societyand one member in particular, Lonnie Mimmsthe VCFSE and Apple Pop-Up Museum saw more than 1,100 visitors when it opened on April 20 and 21.We wrote about the museum and the VCFSE last month...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7142-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7142_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:52:55">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/03/how-amsterdam-was-wired-for-open-access-fiber/</link><title>How Amsterdam was wired for open access fiber</title><description>...The city of Amsterdam has been involved for several years in building Citynet, a partnership between the city and two private investors to wire 40,000 Amsterdam buildings with fiber. And it's not just fiber, it's open access fiberany ISP can sign up to use the infrastructure and deliver ultra-fast Internet access.In 2008, the European Union ruled that the city's involvement in the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7142-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7142_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:55:16">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/08/crawly-but-not-necessarily-creepy-spiders-invade-manhattan/</link><title>Crawly, but not necessarily creepy: spiders invade Manhattan</title><description>... go anywhere near the American Museum of Natural History in New York. Not only are spiders... quantities of insects. That makes them a major source of pest control.Enlarge / Museum staff show..., a projection system is used to let one of the museum employees do live demos, ranging from the shed...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7142-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7142_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:57:53">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/01/writings-of-natural-selection-co-discoverer-alfred-russel-wallace-go-online/</link><title>Writings of natural selection co-discoverer Alfred Russel Wallace go online</title><description>... of their names on the cover.A hundred years after his death, the Natural History Museum (NHM) is hoping... and transcribed by museum volunteers and staff, and can be freely read and downloaded.Who was Alfred Wallace...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7142-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7142_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:58:35">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/10/spacewar-the-first-2d-top-down-shooter-turns-50/</link><title>Spacewar! , the first 2D top-down shooter, turns 50</title><description>... cafeteria. Now I play Angry Birds on my Android phone, but the Computer History Museum in Mountain View... video games: Spacewar! Spacewar! at the Computer History Museum First conceived by a crew of developers... in a long line of computers that focused on interactivity and affordability," the museum exhibit...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7142-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7142_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:00:43">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2014/04/samsung-opens-a-self-obsessed-innovation-museum-in-korea/</link><title>Samsung opens a self-obsessed “Innovation Museum” in Korea</title><description>...Samsung has traditionally been thought of as a "fast follower"a company that often copies innovations from its competitors and gets them to market quickly. Lately, though, the company has been working hard to try to position itself as more than just a copycat. In March, Samsung launched design.samsung.com, a design-focused site highlighting products the company is particularly proud of....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7142-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7142_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:02:19">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/04/ars-at-the-museum-the-art-of-video-games-at-the-smithsonian/</link><title>Ars at the Museum: The Art of Video Games at the Smithsonian</title><description>... at the Smithsonian American Art Museum, here in Washington, DC. As Ars' local correspondent and sometime museum reviewer, I braved the crowds and went to check out how one of the nation's premiere art museums dealt with our digital pastime.A screening of Tron at the exhibit's opening weekend...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>