<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7143">from dusseldorf to washington dc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:04:49" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7143-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7143_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:04:50">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/12/dc-city-council-passes-law-legitimizing-uber-car-service/</link><title>DC City Council passes law legitimizing Uber car service</title><description>... the country, scored a big victory on Tuesday as the DC City Council passed legislation..., though its drivers will be required to submit trip data back to the DC Taxicab Commission... Uber is now on firm legal footing in DC, it is still facing legal challenges elsewhere...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7143-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7143_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:06:32">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/07/one-day-after-dc-polices-reasonable-camera-policy-phones-still-taken/</link><title>One day after DC police's reasonable camera policy, phone still taken</title><description>...On July 20, just 24 hours after a new camera policywas enacted by the Metropolitan Police Department of Washington, DCyou guessed itthe cops still took a guys phone. The new policy forbids the confiscation of cameras and cameraphones, and disallows police from ordering citizens to stop filming...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7143-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7143_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:09:19">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/02/consumers-for-paper-options-wants-the-government-to-push-more-paper/</link><title>“Consumers for Paper Options” wants the government to push more paper</title><description>...According to a new profile in the Washington Post, a four-year-old lobbying group calling itself Consumers for Paper Options turns out to be an astroturfing group funded by the Envelope Manufacturers..., its executive director is John Runyon, a veteran DC lobbyist.The Social Security Administration...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7143-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7143_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:11:00">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/01/dcs-cto-prepares-for-data-onslaught-on-inauguration-eve/</link><title>DC's CTO prepares for data onslaught on inauguration eve</title><description>...As President-elect Barack Obama prepares to take the oath of office in Washington, DCand political junkies flood into the city for their chance to catch a glimpse of history in the makingthe citys..., is a more somber CES: CES Government, where Washington, DCs tech technocrats fly thousands of miles...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7143-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7143_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:11:49">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/02/washington-post-launches-photosynth-series/</link><title>Washington Post launches Photosynth series</title><description>...The Washington Post's Web site has launched its first Photosynth series on Washington-area monuments and museums, becoming the first to digitally take users inside the historic D.C. landmarks. The series kicked off yesterday on President Lincoln's birthday, with a virtual tour of the Lincoln Memorial that includes a 360 degree view and the ability to zoom in close enough to see the smal...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7143-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7143_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:13:55">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/01/fcc-blasts-verizon-for-911-outages-during-summer-2012-storm/</link><title>FCC blasts Verizon for 911 outages during summer 2012 storm</title><description>... of 911 calls failed to connect.The storm, which hit the Washington DC metro area and parts of West...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7143-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7143_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:16:16">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/02/apple-submitting-fourth-plan-for-georgetown-apple-store/</link><title>Apple submitting fourth plan for Georgetown Apple Store</title><description>...There are a few Apple Stores surrounding Washington, D.C., but even though the Apple Store concept has been around for a while, there isn't actually an Apple Store inside D.C. itself. As you might expect, Apple is trying to change that, and the Washington Post has the details...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7143-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7143_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:17:50">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2008/10/washington-dc-latest-to-drop-microsoft-for-web-apps/</link><title>Washington DC latest to drop Microsoft for web apps</title><description>...Washington D.C. has joined 500,000+ businesses and organizations in moving its communication and productivity tools into the cloud. Vivek Kundra, CTO for the District, signed an agreement with Google... of communication and productivity tools. Washington D.C. is a not-insignificant win for Google...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7143-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7143_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:19:50">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/07/washington-residents-to-be-able-to-register-to-vote-via-facebook/</link><title>Washington State will enable voter registration via Facebook</title><description>...The State of Washington says that early next week it will become the first state in the nation... (a Washington company, naturally) will provide a new interface to let voters access the MyVote system.Today, Washington and 12 other states, including Utah, California, Connecticut, Indiana, counties in Nevada...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7143-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7143_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:20:28">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/04/washington-state-slams-t-mobile-for-deceptive-no-contract-ads/</link><title>Washington state slams T-Mobile for “deceptive ‘No-Contract’” ads</title><description>... out the remainder of the contract or return the phoneas stated in T-Mobiles company policy. But the Washington... by the rules, Bob Ferguson, Washingtons attorney general said in a statement on Thursday. My office...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>