<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7144">can headphones cause hearing loss</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:22:30" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7144-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7144_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:22:31">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/12/dismissal-of-ipod-hearing-loss-lawsuit-upheld-on-appeal/</link><title>Dismissal of iPod hearing loss lawsuit upheld on appeal</title><description>... the lawsuit against Apple, even though none of them had actually suffered any hearing loss... hearing loss. Further, the court also ruled that since the named plaintiffs did not suffer... Apple won't necessarily protect anyone from hearing loss, but limit...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7144-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7144_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:23:45">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/09/crank-that-ipod-hearing-loss-rates-lower-than-thought/</link><title>Crank that iPod: hearing loss rates lower than thought</title><description>... in a manner that wouldn't cause hearing loss, but debates about whether music players need lower default... from hearing loss thanks to loud music may be much lower than previously believed, according to a new... that conventional hearing tests are produc...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7144-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7144_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:24:58">http://arstechnica.com/security/2008/10/employees-not-it-responsible-for-most-corporate-data-loss/</link><title>Employees, not hackers, cause most corporate data loss</title><description>...Earlier this summer, we covered a report suggesting that the majority of corporate data loss comes... of corporate data losses this past year were due to hackers. Unfortunately, the good news mostly ends there. Negligent employees are far and away the largest cause of data breaches, but IT managers...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7144-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7144_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:27:34">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2010/02/2-live-crew-with-kids-in-the-room-airdrive-heaphones-review/</link><title>2 Live Crew with kids in the room: Airdrive headphones review</title><description>...Many headphones seek to make their mark by cutting you off from the rest of the world. Canalphones block out ambient noise and allow you to focus purely on the sounds you're hearing from your laptop, iPod, or other music device. The Airdrives go in a different direction, bringing you the sound from your device while allowing you to continue to hear what's going on around you.It's a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7144-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7144_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:28:53">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/10/eu-reminds-us-to-lose-the-distraction-turn-the-volume-down/</link><title>EU reminds us to lose the distraction, turn the volume down</title><description>...There was a time when I cranked out writing projects with a pair of headphones on, hard rock blasting directly into my auditory canal. The music created an odd sort of sonic mental insulation from the world around me that could be useful for tuning out roommates, spouses, the loud whispering couple in the library, or the chatty women at the coffee shop. But were there any long-time side effects f...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7144-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7144_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:29:46">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/06/man-creates-invisible-headphones-by-implanting-magnets-into-his-ears/</link><title>Man creates “invisible headphones” by implanting magnets into his ears</title><description>...A man has implanted magnets into his ears to use as invisible headphones in a remarkable example... can hear conversations across a room. Having a mic hooked up to it and routed through my phone... that allows you to hear through walls. That might be my next implant actually."He also plans...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7144-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7144_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:31:49">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/12/apples-new-in-ear-headphones-set-to-ship-in-about-a-week/</link><title>Apple's new in-ear headphones set to ship in about a week</title><description>...Just yesterday, there were gripes about Apples long-awaited, big-pimpin new in-ear headphones... are now being accepted via the Apple Store online, and the headphones are expected to ship in seven to 10 days. Rumor has it that the headphones had to go back to the drawing board because Steve Jobs...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7144-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7144_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:34:57">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/11/apple-rumored-to-ready-wireless-headphones-for-ios-devices/</link><title>Apple rumored to ready wireless headphones for iOS devices</title><description>...Apple appears to have purchased Wi-Gear, the company behind the iMuffs line of Bluetooth headphones designed for the iPod and iPhone. According to a source speaking to 9to5 Mac, the company plans to leverage the acquisition to develop its own stereo Bluetooth headphones for iPhones, iPads, and even...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7144-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7144_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:37:53">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2010/05/you-didnt-need-to-hear-the-fire-alarm-able-planet-nc300/</link><title>You didn't need to hear the fire alarm: Able Planet NC300s</title><description>...The last set of headphones from Able Planet we looked at aimed to make sounds clearer at a lower... of technology, it can be slightly disconcerting.The headphones work as advertised. The television in the same room as my gaming all but disappeared, and I couldn't hear my wife asking me to make dinner...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7144-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7144_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:39:52">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/04/apple-to-replace-problematic-headphones-with-inline-remote/</link><title>Apple to replace problematic headphones with inline remote</title><description>..., Apple has identified a potential defect in the inline remotes that may cause this problem and has a new program for replacing defective headphones free of charge.The problem mainly affects the Apple Headphones with Remote than came with iPod shuffles made between February 2009 and February 2010...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>