<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7146">why do leaves fall</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:58:37" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7146-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7146_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:58:38">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/02/explaining-tree-leaf-size-using-physics/</link><title>Explaining the size of tree leaves using physics</title><description>..., physics now offers an explanation for why tall trees have such, ahem, tiny leaves.Before we get to the trees and their pitifully small leaves, let's take a quick look at the sort of arguments and insights that physics offers biologists. For instance, it can help you determine why the smallest...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7146-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7146_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:01:16">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2011/04/safari-to-gain-do-not-track-support-in-lion/</link><title>Safari to join "Do Not Track" crowd, leaving Google behind</title><description>...Apple is officially hopping on the "Do Not Track" train, adding support for special opt... set and forget.Mozilla made the first step in building broad browser support for "Do... on "Do Not Track." However, Mozilla noted recently that the AP News Registry...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7146-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7146_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:03:08">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/01/leave-home-a-coming-of-age-shooter/</link><title>Leave Home a coming of age... shooter?</title><description>...We stumbled upon Leave Home on the Xbox Live Indie Gaming Channel after hearing about it via word... in a few minutes, but the game changes depending on how well or poorly you do, adopting a modular..., leaving homeit's a pretty personal game to me. I thought it'd be interesting to translate...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7146-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7146_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:05:45">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/08/nothing-but-the-soylent-were-trying-1-full-week-of-the-meal-substitute/</link><title>Nothing but the Soylent: We’re trying 1 full week of the meal substitute</title><description>... in September.But what does it taste like? How does it make you feel? What does it do to your, you know, um, poop...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7146-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7146_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:07:13">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/12/cloudy-with-a-chance-of-leaves-reducing-climate-uncertainty/</link><title>Cloudy with a chance of leaves: reducing climate uncertainty</title><description>... the plants can do with existing leaves. As a result, the authors argue, plants will respond by growing more leaves, provided they're not starved for water and nitrogen. And, they argue, lots.... In other words, knowing a model does clouds right for a decade doesn't tell us whether it'll do...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7146-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7146_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:09:44">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/01/ask-ars-why-will-apples-do-not-disturb-bug-fix-itself-next-week/</link><title>Ask Ars: Why will Apple's Do Not Disturb bug fix itself next week?</title><description>... were left wondering: what's causing this bug, and why will it fix itself on January 7? That's what we're here to answer.Q: What's causing Apple's Do Not Disturb bug and why...Those of us using Apple's new Do Not Disturb (DND) feature under iOS 6 were met...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7146-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7146_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:12:00">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/02/in-search-of-a-proper-to-do-application-for-android/</link><title>In search of a proper to-do application for Android</title><description>..., those in need of a quick way to leave a note can do so with one tap from the main screen. For power... sort of functionality. I had forgotten to look into downloading a to-do application that would allow... to that same specialty store.So I went to the Google Play store in search of a few to-do lists and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7146-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7146_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:15:02">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/03/get-it-done-with-gnome-do-081/</link><title>Get it done with GNOME Do 0.8.1</title><description>...GNOME Do is an open source launcher utility for the Linux desktop that offers a minimalistic, task... version, 0.8.1, was released on Friday.GNOME Do was originally modeled after Quicksilver, a similar... so that it can be used very quickly.GNOME Do is highly extensible and provides a plugin framework that can be used...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7146-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7146_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:15:58">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/02/can-do-not-track-tame-the-webs-cookie-monsters/</link><title>Can Do Not Track starve the Web's Cookie Monster?</title><description>...Last week, the White House announced a new Internet privacy agreement with the companies serving nearly 90 percent of "online behavioral advertisements," theoretically forcing the likes of Google, Yahoo, Microsoft, and AOL to stop monitoring the Web-surfing habits of users who click a "Do Not Track" button on their browsers. While a good step toward broader Web privacy protect...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7146-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7146_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:17:47">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/09/do-not-track-support-added-to-chrome-arriving-by-the-end-of-the-year/</link><title>Do Not Track support added to Chrome, arriving by the end of the year</title><description>... for the "Do Not Track" Web privacy feature yesterday. The feature will make its way through... they visit that they do not wish for third parties to record their online activity. The feature has been controversial due to Microsoft's Do Not Track implementation in Internet Explorer 10. Redmond...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>