<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7147">breast cancer review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:18:31" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7147-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7147_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:18:32">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/11/judges-refuses-to-block-lawsuit-over-patenting-genetic-tests/</link><title>Judge refuses to block lawsuit over patenting genetic tests</title><description>... variants associated with breast cancer. The suit targeted Myriad Genetics, which licenses... families that have high incidences of breast and ovarian cancer. The University patented the use... the specter of breast cancer, but also for the future course of bio...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7147-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7147_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:20:02">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/10/mapping-the-mutations-of-twelve-major-cancer-types/</link><title>Mapping the mutations of twelve major cancer types</title><description>... cluster. For example, the work identified five distinct breast cancer clusters, each driven..., like 94.6 percent of ovarian cancers and one of the breast cancer clusters.Although these tumor types... for cancer, none has emerged. This is primarily because eve...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7147-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7147_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:21:10">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/07/appeals-court-overrules-lower-court-upholds-breast-cancer-gene-test/</link><title>Appeals Court overrules lower court, upholds breast cancer gene test</title><description>...A bit over two years ago, a large collection of interested parties joined together with the ACLU to challenge a practice that had become business as usual: the patenting of human genes. The group filed a suit that targeted a specific set of patents: those used by Myriad Genetics to control the market for tests of the BRCA breast cancer genes. In a surprise result, the judge overseeing the case is...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7147-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7147_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:23:33">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/08/breathalyzer-developed-that-detects-lung-cancer/</link><title>Breathalyzer developed that detects lung cancer</title><description>...; the method is simple, noninvasive, portable, and affordable. Diagnosing diseases like lung cancer... and 40 people who had been diagnosed with lung cancer, but have not received treatment yet... levels in the lung cancer patients.The team devised a sensor system made from nine chemiresistors...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7147-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7147_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:25:46">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/03/decision-over-breast-cancer-tests-hammers-gene-patents/</link><title>Gene patents may not survive breast cancer test ruling</title><description>... that covered tests for mutations in the BRCA genes, which predispose their carriers to breast and ovarian cancers (the US Patent and Trademark Office was also sued, for good measure). Just about everyone... to cancer. Myriad claimed that the Prometheus decision applies to its patents; this indicated that a common...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7147-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7147_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:28:11">http://arstechnica.com/science/2008/10/unnatural-killers-engineering-immune-cells-to-kill-cancer/</link><title>Unnatural killers: engineering immune cells to kill cancer</title><description>... for use against metastatic breast cancer that binds to the protein, and other groups... rid of cancers before they become problems. For example, a number of studies show that organ transplant recipients, who undergo long-term immunosuppression, have higher rates of cancers. Researchers...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7147-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7147_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:29:56">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/01/programming-cancer-vaccines-in-your-body/</link><title>Revving up the immune system to fight cancer</title><description>...A cancer vaccination may eventually come in the form of a small implant that goes under the skin... polymer that contains cancer antigens and a collection of immune-system activating components... cells in situ." They envision treating a multitude of tumors and infectious diseases, from breast...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7147-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7147_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:30:59">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/06/cancer-as-a-biofilm/</link><title>Do biofilms make for better cancer models?</title><description>.... Not the most pleasant thought. Nature Reviews Cancer, 2011, DOI: 10.1038/nrc3039... cancer research in a new initiative from the NIH: bringing in a bunch of people who haven't been working on cancer and see if they can offer some new insights. On the face of it, this sounds...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7147-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7147_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:33:54">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/08/ambry-hits-back-at-myriads-bad-faith-enforcement-of-breast-cancer-gene-patents/</link><title>Ambry hits back at Myriad’s “bad faith enforcement” of breast cancer gene patents</title><description>...For many years, all testing of the BRCA1 and BRCA2 genes in the US was under control of one company: Myriad Genetics of Utah. But many expected that monopoly to be over when the Supreme Court ruled 9-0 that Myriad can't claim patent rights to those genes. In fact, the court ruled, such "isolated" DNA sequences can't get patents at allalthough a lab-made form of the gene called...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7147-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7147_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:36:33">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/11/for-redheads-skin-cancer-may-be-in-the-genes/</link><title>For redheads, skin cancer may be in the genes</title><description>... with the fact that even these safeguards may not be enough to protect me from skin cancer. New research... than eumelanin. Weve long known that redheads are at a high risk of sun-induced skin cancer... incidence of melanoma in those with fair skin, even in the absence of cancer-causing UV exposure.To...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>