<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7152">haskell hash string</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:47:23" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7152-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7152_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:47:24">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/07/the-fruits-of-string-theory-the-shape-of-inner-space/</link><title>The fruits of string theory: The Shape of Inner Space</title><description>.... In the intervening decade, the basic ideas of string theorythat the Universe is potentially made... experimental test to directly probe for the existence of these tiny strings, many within... is that, in order to pursue the study of string theory, entire fields of mathematics have been revolutionized...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7152-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7152_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:48:05">http://arstechnica.com/security/2013/03/cisco-switches-to-weaker-hashing-scheme-passwords-cracked-wide-open/</link><title>Cisco switches to weaker hashing scheme, passwords cracked wide open</title><description>...Password cracking experts have reversed a secret cryptographic formula recently added to Cisco devices. Ironically, the encryption type 4 algorithm leaves users considerably more susceptible to password cracking than an older alternative, even though the new routine was intended to enhance protections already in place.It turns out that Cisco's new method for converting passwords into one-way...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7152-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7152_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:49:59">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/07/from-string-theory-mathematics-to-high-t-superconductivity/</link><title>From string theory mathematics to high-T superconductivity</title><description>... at the non-obvious connections that exist between string theory in a hyperboloid spacetime and high... University in the Netherlands, looks at the possibility of using the mathematics of string theory... this critical region of quantum phase space, the authors attempt to borrow a technique from the string...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7152-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7152_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:52:10">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/06/whats-next-string-theory-test-or-data-saying-dont-bother/</link><title>What's next: string theory test or data saying don't bother?</title><description>... current iterations of string theory. Given that Brian Greene, one of the festival organizers, is a noted proponent of string theory, you might expect the presentation to be one-sided; Greene himself... some perspective on strings by pointing out that the extra dimensions they vibrate through are so small...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7152-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7152_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:54:36">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/12/lhc-spots-no-black-holes-eliminates-some-versions-of-string-theory/</link><title>LHC spots no black holes, eliminates some versions of string theory</title><description>... of some forms of string theory. If this form of the theory were right, the LHC should... is notably absent. String theory is an attempt to deal with the fact that the two major theories... of string theorythe paper calls it the ADD model because Arkani-Hamed, Dimopoulos, and Dvali...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7152-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7152_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:57:16">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/11/how-is-lazy-evaluation-in-haskell-useful/</link><title>How is “lazy evaluation” in Haskell useful?</title><description>... when and where an expression will be evaluated?Related: "Is Haskell worth learning?"Answer.... But this is not actually the case. Lazy languages like Haskell make it a point to be referentially transparent, i.e. making sure that the order in which expressions are evaluated will never affect their result. In Haskell...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7152-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7152_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:00:01">http://arstechnica.com/security/2008/11/nist-crowdsources-crypto-with-algorithm-competition/</link><title>NIST crowdsources crypto with SHA-3 algorithm competition</title><description>... the successor of SHA-2 by 2012. Hash functions generate unique digest strings that can serve... a new secure hashing algorithm, and the contest will end Friday, by which time the agency hopes... some previous standard hashing functions including MD5 and SHA-0, and studies have also demonstrated...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7152-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7152_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:01:10">http://arstechnica.com/security/2012/06/flame-wields-rare-collision-crypto-attack/</link><title>Flame malware wielded rare "collision" crypto attack against Microsoft</title><description>... when exploiting decades-old hashing functions. To pull it off, researchers had to wield the power of 200... files into ciphertext that can never be converted back to their original form. These hash functions... a unique string of ciphertext. The ability for someone to find a collision, in which two different...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7152-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7152_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:03:19">http://arstechnica.com/security/2013/10/how-the-bible-and-youtube-are-fueling-the-next-frontier-of-password-cracking/</link><title>How the Bible and YouTube are fueling the next frontier of password cracking</title><description>... of the more than 860,000 password hashes cracked, his attempts to decipher the remaining 40 percent were failing.The... used to generate the one-way hashes. When the output of a guessed word matched one of the leaked Stratfor hashes, Young would have successfully cracked another password. (Security professionals call...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7152-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7152_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:03:55">http://arstechnica.com/security/2013/07/got-an-account-on-a-site-like-github-hackers-may-know-your-e-mail-address/</link><title>Got an account on a site like Github? Hackers may know your e-mail address</title><description>...LAS VEGASIf you have an account on Github, StackExchange, or any one of countless other sites, there's a good chance hackers can identify the e-mail address you used to register it. That's because Gravatar, a behind-the-scenes service that says it works with millions of sites, broadcasts the information using cryptography that in many cases is trivial to crack.People have been warning a...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>