<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7153">pig latin help</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:06:13" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7153-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7153_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:06:15">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/05/hunting-feral-pigs-at-night-with-drones/</link><title>Hunting feral hogs. At night. With drones.</title><description>..., pig-hunting drone the Dehogaflier. The drone itself runs around $10,000 with all the gear attached...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7153-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7153_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:07:05">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/02/microsoft-no-change-to-custom-support-prices-this-year/</link><title>Microsoft: no change to custom support prices this year</title><description>...ZDNet has spotted a note on the Microsoft Help and Support website that announces Microsoft will keep its legacy support pricing at 2008 levels for Custom Support Agreements through the rest of this year, apparently to help customers control costs during the recession. "The global economic...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7153-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7153_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:08:22">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/10/domain-extensions-go-global-goodbye-com-welcome/</link><title>Say hello to .??? as domain names go truly global</title><description>... a plethora of non-Latin characters to be used in domain name extensions and opening more doors to Internet..., and more. Previously, ICANN allowed the registration of domain names with non-Latin charactersso, for example, http://clintecker??????????.combut the extension had to remain in Latin characters. Now...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7153-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7153_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:08:59">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/08/ars-does-soylent-day-1-embrace-the-chalky-weird-sweetness/</link><title>Ars does Soylent, day 1: Embrace the chalky weird sweetness</title><description>... feel quite normal. The brief bout of nausea from breakfast is gone, and the second helping goes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7153-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7153_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:10:41">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/03/the-week-in-science-faces-fears-of-exploding-pigs/</link><title>The week in science faces fears of exploding pigs</title><description>... archaeology: A new technology is helping archeologists map the environments around excavations sites...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7153-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7153_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:11:58">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/02/pig-msra-came-from-humans-evolved-via-farm-drugs/</link><title>"Pig MRSA" came from humans, evolved via farm drugs</title><description>... all did for a living, and received the answer that they were all pig farmers. So they checked the pigs, and the pigs were carrying the MRSA strain as well. And if a new MRSA strain in humans was odd, then a MRSA strain in pigs was very oddbecause swine have their own varieties of staph...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7153-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7153_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:12:56">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/11/glitch-the-battle-to-build-a-massive-multiplayer-game-without-combat/</link><title>Butterfly milking and pig nibbling: building the strange world of Glitch</title><description>... watch them farming and then step in to help them out. Stewart Butterfield in his office at Tiny Speck..., the player can interact with almost every object in the world. Pigs can be patted or nibbled; just...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7153-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7153_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:14:21">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2010/07/iphones-not-king-pig-verizon-3g-phone-users-snarf-most-data/</link><title>iPhone not king pig: Verizon 3G phone users gobble most data</title><description>... encourage users to look into such solutions, as it would help users cut down on data overages...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7153-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7153_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:16:03">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/09/you-get-dirty-and-the-pigs-are-happy-ars-reviews-dirt-2/</link><title>You get dirty and the pigs are happy: a review of Dirt 2</title><description>... some of the tension, it also helps to keep the interest of players who might have rage-quit after a particularly...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7153-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7153_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:16:53">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/01/assisted-gps/</link><title>Inside assisted GPS: helping GPS help you</title><description>...Location, location, location The Global Positioning Satellite (GPS) system can help you find... a bit much from what is fundamentally 1990s-era technology. Fortunately, theres help. Assisted GPS... waiting on their part, either. Typically, AGPS systems help a GPS figure out where the satellite signals...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>