<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7154">stones satisfaction</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:17:42" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7154-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7154_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:17:44">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/02/meet-evan-stone-p2p-pirate-hunter/</link><title>Meet Evan Stone, P2P pirate hunter</title><description>...Evan Stone is not the devil; indeed, the antipiracy lawyer sees himself on the side of the angels... of water."From his office in Denton, Texas, Stone needed only six months to make himself... in gay porn. In August, he sued 113. In September, Stone went after 670. October brought a case...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7154-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7154_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:19:17">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/04/apple-14-points-ahead-of-dell-in-new-satisfaction-survey/</link><title>Apple 14 points ahead of Dell in new satisfaction survey</title><description>...Apple once again wears the crown in consumer satisfaction, according to the latest data..., Apple's strength in customer satisfaction is nothing new, as the company has consistently dominated the rankings for many years. In the latest American Customer Satisfaction Index from November...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7154-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7154_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:22:01">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/11/google-settles-rosetta-stone-lawsuit-its-last-major-dispute-over-adwords/</link><title>Google settles Rosetta Stone lawsuit, its last major dispute over AdWords</title><description>... to key advertisements to their names, which are protected trademarks. Rosetta Stone... on confidential terms.Rosetta Stone argued the ads keyed to its name were confusing consumers... as Rosetta Stone pointed them out.The case was appealed, and a muddledruling came out of the US Court...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7154-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7154_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:24:57">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/10/review-find-hidden-objects-with-stone-of-destiny-on-iphone/</link><title>Review: Find hidden objects with Stone of Destiny on iPhone</title><description>...When the Stone of Destiny first debuted on App Store for ten bucks, I passed it by. A few weeks... feelings. The iPhone isnt exactly the best platform to be playing find-the-object, and yet Stone of Destiny delivers enough game to be worth that dollar. About the Game Stone of Destiny has a basic...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7154-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7154_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:27:33">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/09/sanctioned-p2p-lawyer-fined-10000-for-staggering-chutzpah/</link><title>Sanctioned: P2P lawyer fined $10,000 for "staggering chutzpah"</title><description>...A federal judge has fined Texas lawyer Evan Stone $10,000 for sending out subpoenas and then... the judge's permission.In September 2010, Stone brought suit on behalf of Mick Haig Productions... had turned over their information to Stone, information generally obtainable only by subpoena.The...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7154-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7154_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:29:03">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/07/copyright-troll-10000-sanctions-upheld-by-appeals-court-are-bullst/</link><title>Copyright troll: $10,000 sanctions upheld by appeals court are "bulls**t"</title><description>... people are singing the praises of Evan Stone, a Denton, Texas attorney that the Electronic Frontier... sanctions (PDF) against Stone on Thursday for having issued 670 unauthorized subpoenas to the ISPs... copies of a German porn film, Der Gute Onkel (The Good Uncle). Stone represented the films producer...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7154-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7154_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:29:49">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/04/survey-iphone-ranks-highest-among-smartphone-buyers/</link><title>Survey: iPhone ranks highest among smartphone buyers</title><description>...Apple is tops when it comes to consumer satisfaction among smartphone manufacturers, according to the latest J.D. Power and Associates 2009 Wireless Consumer Smartphone Customer Satisfaction Study and the 2009 Wireless Traditional Mobile Phone Satisfaction Study. Apple managed to score a 791...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7154-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7154_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:31:31">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/09/playstation-store-update-1/</link><title>PlayStation Store Update: Can't get no satisfaction edition</title><description>... with the release of GH5, and it includes the following Rolling Stones songs:"I'm Free (Live)""Prodigal Son (Live)"(I Can't Get No) Satisfaction (Live)""Under My Thumb (Live)""You Gotta Move (Live)"The Rolling Stones Live Track Pack ($8.99)Meanwhile Rock...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7154-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7154_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:32:12">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/10/iphone-tops-personal-business-satisfaction-rankings/</link><title>iPhone tops personal, business satisfaction rankings</title><description>...Apple has taken the lead in both the personal and business categories of J.D. Power and Associates' latest mobile phone satisfaction study. The firm announced its second set of study results for 2009 on Thursday, noting that satisfaction among all phone owners has gone up since just six months ago. Apple in particular has managed to come out even further ahead, even in a category where it is...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7154-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7154_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:33:42">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/02/50-million-more-for-twitter-piles-on-pressure-to-profit/</link><title>$50 million more for Twitter piles on pressure to profit</title><description>...Twitter, the microblogging service that is spreading like wildfire, has secured over $50 million in its third round of funding. Strangely, the company was not even looking for the money, but news of such a large sum is placing even more pressure on Twitter's plans to begin generating revenue. The service has become everything to everyonea microblogging platform, a customer service hub, a rep...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>