<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7155">ted talk mooc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:35:11" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7155-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7155_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:35:12">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/06/first-ever-government-sponsored-ted-talks-given-last-night/</link><title>First ever government-sponsored TED Talks given yesterday</title><description>...Secretary of State Hillary Clinton announced a new program at the State Department, the Global Partnership Initiative, earlier this year. The initiative seeks to increase partnerships between the public and private sectors to help solve a number of pressing global issues. One of the first fruits of the Global Partnership Initiative was a series of TED Talks, dubbed TED@State, held yesterday after...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7155-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7155_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:35:48">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/03/ted-moves-toward-the-classroom-with-the-launch-of-ted-ed/</link><title>TED moves toward the classroom with the launch of TED-Ed</title><description>... opportunity, she told Ars, TED Talks are of course 15 minute lectures, and while sure, oratory...The TED organization rolled out its education initiative today. So far, TED-Ed consists primarily of a YouTube channel with, as TED-Ed curator Chris Anderson describes it in a blog post,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7155-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7155_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:38:22">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/03/the-nsa-invited-to-ted-takes-a-swipe-at-snowden/</link><title>The NSA, invited to TED, takes a swipe at Snowden</title><description>...Two days after Snowden made a surprising appearance at TED in Vancouver, the conference is giving... in an interview with TED curator Chris Anderson, which was reported by Wired UK, Forbes, and the BBC, among... was no whistleblower, Ledgett emphasized."There were some kernels of truth in [Snowden's TED...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7155-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7155_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:41:21">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/07/hands-on-ted-books-ios-app-officially-released-with-some-fixes/</link><title>Hands-on: TED Books iOS app "officially" released with some fixes</title><description>...When we first did a hands-on with the new TED Books app for iOS two weeks ago, I had a fair amount... versus non-downloaded books.The TED team apparently took our criticisms to heartor at least... to the TED Books app's "official" launch, so I thought I'd take another look...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7155-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7155_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:44:14">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/03/john-hodgman-and-rob-reid-talk-year-zero-aliens-and-the-riaa/</link><title>John Hodgman and Rob Reid talk Year Zero, Aliens, and the RIAA</title><description>...Rob Reid made quite the splash with his humorous/serious TED talk on Copyright Math. Hearing it calls for a more detailed explanation of the numbers he used, and Reid has laid it all bare.Reid isnt done with the music industry, either. Ars has learned some new details about Reids debut novel, Year...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7155-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7155_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:45:51">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/07/hands-on-with-ted-books-for-ios-discoverability-is-good-polish-needed/</link><title>Hands-on with TED Books for iOS: discoverability is good, polish needed</title><description>...TED Talk videos have an almost cult-like following among the geek crowd, but many of the topics...;s why TED launched TED Books at the beginning of last year as a way to both capitalize on the popularity of its TED talks, and offer viewers a way to read more ab...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7155-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7155_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:47:02">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/10/2009-iphone-tech-talk-dates-and-cities-announced/</link><title>2009 iPhone Tech Talk dates and cities announced</title><description>... be coming to you with its own series of iPhone Tech Talks to take place through the end of 2009... of Apple's developer program, the talks are free. The Tech Talks aren't newApple had a world tour...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7155-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7155_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:48:33">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/09/google-talk-creates-awkward-moments-with-misdirected-messages/</link><title>Update: Google Talk creates awkward moments with misdirected messages</title><description>...Google has acknowledged a problem with its Talk service that misrouted messages from users...;identified an issue with Google Talk messages sent between 22:00 PST and 01:30 PST. Any messages sent... Talk or Hangouts chat with one user to be sent to another random person on the sender's Talk...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7155-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7155_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:50:51">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/10/apple-kicks-off-iphone-tech-talk-world-tour-later-this-month/</link><title>Apple kicks off iPhone Tech Talk World Tour later this month</title><description>...The Apple Developer Connection has just announced dates and times for an iPhone Tech Talk World... as possible. Don Briggs, developer of iLEVELi, says, I attended a Cocoa Tech Talk a few years agoit was a Good Thing, definitely. Based on that experience, I recommend the iPhone Tech Talk. If you...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7155-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7155_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:51:43">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/03/snowden-big-revelations-to-come-reporting-them-is-not-a-crime/</link><title>Snowden: Big revelations to come, reporting them is not a crime</title><description>...Edward Snowden made a surprise appearance on the TED stage in Vancouver todayusing a Beam telepresence robot from "somewhere in Russia."Snowden, in his second remote talk in eight days after an appearance at SXSW Interactive in Texas, urged online businesses to encrypt their websites...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>