<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7168">fabric glue</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:23:00" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7168-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7168_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:23:01">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/11/yahoo-introduces-glue-visual-search/</link><title>Yahoo introduces "Glue" visual search</title><description>...Yesterday, Yahoo introduced its Yahoo! Glue service to the United States. Glue works by aggregating... it was a big hit, according to Yahoo. Yahoo Glue combines multiple search results ontoa single visual page Glue has a strong flavor of Kosmix and Mahalo, so this is hardly a new idea. The presentation used...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7168-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7168_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:24:17">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/12/an-accelerometer-so-good-that-only-quantum-mechanics-limits-it/</link><title>An accelerometer so good that only quantum mechanics limits it</title><description>... compromise, however, is also due to fabrication limitations. A recent paper in Nature Photonics shows that clever fabrication can result in an accelerometer that is both fast and sensitive.An accelerometer... (silicon nitride) is a great material for making tiny optical components. The researchers fabricated...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7168-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7168_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:25:54">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/03/electrons-may-be-the-glue-in-cuprate-superconductors/</link><title>Electrons may be the glue in cuprate superconductors</title><description>... excitations are the glue binding Cooper pairs together. However, being able to state that it is electrons...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7168-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7168_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:27:40">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/09/using-ultraviolet-light-to-fabricate-thin-flexible-electronics/</link><title>Using ultraviolet light to fabricate thin flexible electronics</title><description>... metallic and oxygen atoms) are very efficient, and happen to be transparent. However, fabricating... behavior.This UV-based photochemistry method of metal oxide semiconductor fabrication is potentially very... for annealing, which may allow the fabrication of inexpensive, flexible, transparent electronic devices.Nature...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7168-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7168_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:28:25">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/06/graphene-meets-silicon-with-conventional-fab-techniques/</link><title>Graphene meets silicon with conventional fab techniques</title><description>... of etching circuits, and that has been one of the difficulties preventing easy fabrication... is the method used to integrate the graphene FET into a circuit using conventional fabrication techniques...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7168-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7168_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:30:08">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/11/ars-and-the-world-science-festival-want-our-readers-to-explore-the-fabric-of-the-universe/</link><title>World Science Festival wants Ars readers to explore the Fabric of the Universe</title><description>...Brian Greene is a theoretical physicist and co-founder of the World Science Festival. In his spare time, Greene also writes books and hosts television shows intended to bring modern physics to a popular audience. His latest effort in that regard is called The Fabric of the Cosmos, and he's going to be launching it with a live QA session on Wednesday night. The session will feature Greene, st...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7168-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7168_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:31:57">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/11/weird-science-gets-its-kicks-huffing-glue-from-old-books/</link><title>Weird Science gets its kicks huffing glue from old books</title><description>...Sniffing the glue of old books: Lots of people speak fondly of the distinct aroma of libraries, both personal and private. It turns out they might not be imagining it. Researchers have done a wholesale identification of the volatile chemicals released by books and performed multivariate analysis...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7168-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7168_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:33:01">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/01/carbon-nanotubes-bind-to-fabric-to-make-wearable-electronics/</link><title>Carbon nanotube dye may put a capacitor in your shorts</title><description>...? That may eventually be possible, thanks to a carbon nanotube-based ink that can turn many common fabrics... up in a clothing store near you anytime soon, however, as ensuring that the fabrics only direct... with the fabric. This allows the flexible carbon nanotubes to wrap around the fibers in very high volumes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7168-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7168_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:34:03">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/08/five-things-radically-changing-what-enterprise-means/</link><title>Five things radically changing what “enterprise” means</title><description>.../ESCON connectors when plugging into mainframes or an isolated Fibre Channel fabric for standard... off of its own fabric and onto a data center's Ethernet network thanks to encapsulation schemes... and networking onto one set of Ethernet wires. Companies like Cisco make unified fabric switches that handle...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7168-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7168_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 07:38:46">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/05/duke-nukem-forever-was-the-glue-that-kept-us-together/</link><title>Duke Nukem Forever was the glue that held us together</title><description>...It's hard to remember how old I wasand I'm not going to date myself by tryingbut I was lost in a computer game. The title was Duke Nukem 3D, and every day I'd rush home from school, dial into a friend's computer, and we'd play against each other for hours on end. The weapons and tactics were fiendish: placing laser trip mines into the teleporter so my opponent would blind...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>