<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7173"> severed spinal cord</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:15:27" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7173-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7173_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:15:28">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/11/unlike-rodents-primates-can-grow-new-spinal-nerve-connections/</link><title>Unlike rodents, primates can grow new spinal nerve connections</title><description>... to 5-8 year old rhesus monkeys (Macaca mulatta), which involves severing one side of the spinal cord... that the mammalian spinal cord can extensively recover from partial, but not complete, injury. Although the general consensus has been that the axonal projections, which connect t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7173-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7173_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:16:12">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/07/researchers-restore-lung-function-after-spinal-damage/</link><title>Enzyme and graft combo restores lung function after spinal injury</title><description>...Until the last few decades, it was generally thought that damage to the spinal cord was permanent, as the nerves within our vertebrae stubbornly resist regrowing severed connections after injuries. But a number of studies have helped us understand why exactly it is that the nerves refuse to grow, raising the prospect that we could use this knowledge to intervene and help repair damage to the spin...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7173-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7173_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:17:25">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/08/hbo-cuts-the-cord-brings-streaming-only-service-to-europe/</link><title>HBO cuts the cord, brings streaming-only service to Europe</title><description>...An HBO streaming service that does not require an associated cable subscription is coming in mid-October, according to Variety. The rollout is confined to only a few European countries, but it's an embrace from Time Warner to cord-cutters that non-HBO customers have long sought. The service...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7173-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7173_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:19:25">http://arstechnica.com/business/2011/07/fox-challenges-cord-cutters-by-sticking-online-shows-behind-paywall/</link><title>Fox challenges cord-cutters by sticking TV shows behind paywall</title><description>... that cord-cutting is going to be a problem," Hopkins said. The networks have long feared a small... that cord-cutters represent less than three percent of those who watched TV online in 2009... subscriptions around so they can watch live sports. So, while cord-cutting may be en vogue among Internet...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7173-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7173_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:22:33">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2008/10/ubuntu-community-manager-releases-cc-licensed-metal-album/</link><title>Ubuntu community manager releases CC-licensed metal album</title><description>... is part of his solo project, called Severed Fifth, which he intends to use as a springboard for testing..., which consists of eight tracks, is available for free in OGG and MP3 formats from the Severed Fifth web site... some questions about his vision for Severed Fifth. Bacon hopes that his music will inspire listeners...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7173-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7173_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:23:59">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/05/ready-alternatives-ready-alternatives-indicate-tv-ownership-is-poised-for-declinemean-tv-ownership-is-poised-for-decline/</link><title>Ready alternatives indicate TV ownership is poised for decline</title><description>... consumption and may not rely on the TV as much as they once did.According to Nielsen, several... altogether. (This group is usually known as the "cord-cutters," which is a different group.... We wouldn't be surprised, though, if those who had already cut the cord to their cable or satellite...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7173-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7173_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:26:06">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/10/logitech-to-cut-the-cord-on-your-mic-this-december/</link><title>Logitech to cut the cord on your mic this December</title><description>... a microphone. If you have an insatiable need to get rid of all your cords, this may be worth your...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7173-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7173_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:28:36">http://arstechnica.com/business/2010/09/sports-are-what-keep-people-from-cutting-the-cord/</link><title>Live sports keep people from cutting cable cord</title><description>...Cord-cutters are no threat to the subscription TV industry as long as sports fans are around. BTIG analyst Richard Greenfield conducted a survey of 1,200 multichannel TV subscribers and found that only a tiny percentage were likely to ditch their cable or satellite TV subscriptions in favor...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7173-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7173_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:29:49">http://arstechnica.com/business/2010/04/cable-cord-cutters-grow-but-barriers-still-exist-for-most/</link><title>Cable cord-cutters grow, but barriers still exist for most</title><description>... said that cord-cutters currently represent less than three percent of people who watch full TV shows...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7173-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7173_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:30:58">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2010/11/google-tries-calming-fears-of-jittery-tv-networks/</link><title>Google tries calming fears of jittery TV networks</title><description>...Google is trying to calm the fears of TV execs by disavowing cord-cutters. The company says it doesn't believe that cord-cutting is a real phenomenon, adding that traditional TV is still where... content to users." It appears to be true that cord-cutters (those who ditch their cable...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>