<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7174">seal team 6</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:32:10" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7174-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7174_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:32:11">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/06/tekken-6-to-offer-penny-arcade-skins-fight-sticks/</link><title>Tekken 6 to offer Penny Arcade skins, fight sticks</title><description>...Are you a Tekken fan? Are you ready to drop some serious money on your favorite fighting game? Namco Bandai has just sent final details on the packages available with Tekken 6, and there is some impressive stuff going on here. Custom Penny-Arcade art? Oh yes. Arcade sticks? Those too. Let's take a look.First, you'll be able to buy the game for the regular $60 price, but if you want to s...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7174-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7174_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:34:28">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/05/apple-hints-at-ios-6-as-part-of-icloud-beta-preparations/</link><title>Apple hints at iOS 6 as part of iCloud beta preparations</title><description>...;s Web interface.The additions to iCloud are apparently being tested for release as part of iOS 6...://beta.icloud.com, first sign in to iCloud with the iOS 6 Beta." To our knowledge, Apple has not yet seeded iOS 6 to registered third-party developers, but is almost guaranteed to be testing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7174-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7174_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:36:22">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/01/resident-evil-6-announced-for-release-this-fall/</link><title>Zombie President: Resident Evil 6 announced for November 2012</title><description>...Resident Evil 6 is in development and on the way, Capcom announced today in a press release... all over again."Resident Evil 6 is set for release on November 20 of this year on XBox 360... for your viewing pleasure. Resident Evil 6 trailer...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7174-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7174_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:37:21">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/team-fortress-2-gets-scout-update-goes-half-price/</link><title>Team Fortress 2 gets Scout update, goes half price</title><description>...Valve is continuing its support for Team Fortress 2, this time with an update focused on the Scout class. This includes new achievements, weapons, and even a few maps. Additionally, Valve announced... interest and bringing in some new players to Team Fortress 2. As we have learned, discounts on Steam tend...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7174-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7174_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:39:12">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/05/trauma-team-review-melodrama-and-medicine-on-the-wii/</link><title>Trauma Team review: melodrama and medicine on the Wii</title><description>...The Trauma Center games deliver two things: fast-paced, tension-filled surgeries where steady hands and accuracy will get you higher rankings, and insane melodramatic storylines. Trauma Team.... Title Trauma Team Developer Atlus Publisher Atlus Price $39.99 Shop.Ars Platform Nintendo WiiThe game...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7174-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7174_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:40:54">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/05/report-teaser-trailer-for-next-team-ico-game-leaked/</link><title>Report: Teaser trailer for next Team Ico game leaked</title><description>...It's been a long time coming, but it looks like we may finally have some details on the upcoming project from Shadow of the Colossus and Ico developer Team Ico. The news comes via what appears... that looks very similar to past Team Ico games in terms of aesthetics. It's hard to glean just how...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7174-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7174_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:44:01">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/06/map-making-in-team-fortress-2-gets-a-little-easier/</link><title>Map making in Team Fortress 2 gets a little easier</title><description>...While Valve may be busy at work supporting and developing the sequel for Left 4 Dead, that doesn't mean that it has forgotten about its other big multiplayer shooter, Team Fortress 2. The developer has announced an update to the Source SDK, which will make the process of creating new maps much...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7174-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7174_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:44:52">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/10/the-latest-virtualization-showdown-parallels-desktop-9-vs-vmware-fusion-6/</link><title>The latest virtualization showdown—Parallels Desktop 9 vs. VMware Fusion 6</title><description>.... Fusion 4 showdownSept. 2010: Parallels 6 reviewNov. 2009: Fusion 3 reviewWe'll start... that's growing increasingly loud at Parallels.New VMware Fusion 6 featuresAside from Windows 8.1... make version 6 of Fusion a tempting update. As in Parallels Desktop, VMware is advertising better...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7174-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7174_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:45:55">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/01/iphone-dev-team-releases-yellowsn0w-0-9-4-beta-unlock/</link><title>iPhone dev team releases yellowsn0w 0.9.4 beta unlock</title><description>... than a spanking fresh new iPhone unlock? As promised, the iPhone dev-team has delivered its iPhone 3G unlock... with the latest 2.2 firmware update from Apple. Its also the baseband and update that the dev team have been warning you not to upgrade to. It turns out that the team eventually managed to unlock...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7174-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7174_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 08:47:22">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/12/scouts-xbox-360-getting-love-with-team-fortress-2-patch/</link><title>Scouts, Xbox 360 getting love with Team Fortress 2 patch</title><description>...Valve is continuing to support their lighthearted shooter Team Fortress 2, this time with an update intended to rebalance the Engineer and the Spy. Additionally, the developer has outlined its future plans, which include a new class update. The upcoming update includes the following changes...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>