<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7176"> weather in nyc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:03:30" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7176-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7176_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:03:34">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/01/forecasting-space-weather-and-its-economic-impact/</link><title>Forecasting space weather and its economic impact</title><description>... weather and the challenges that it can pose to mans adventures on Earth and in the heavens. That report that resulted from the workshopSevere Space Weather EventsUnderstanding Societal and Economic.... Space weather had an even greater impact in 1989, when a geomagnetic storm knocked out power...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7176-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7176_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:05:41">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/12/bigmapple-other-nyc-apps-load-up-on-location-data-online/</link><title>BigMapple, other NYC apps load up on location data online</title><description>... without forcing them to switch to yet another new service.Thanks to the NYC BigApps competition..., with prizes that total up to $20,000. Public voting for the contest is now open (NYC BigApps...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7176-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7176_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:07:16">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/06/cold-weather-events-to-persist-as-planet-warms/</link><title>Cold weather events to persist as planet warms</title><description>... Research Letters takes a look at how cold weather events are expected to change in a warming climate... on a more general conclusion: we'll still need to be prepared to deal with cold weather events... the continuation of regional extreme cold weather events. Geophysical Research Letters, 2011. DOI...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7176-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7176_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:09:52">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/02/understanding-extreme-weather-in-an-era-of-climate-change/</link><title>Understanding extreme weather in an era of climate change</title><description>...The US has clearly seen some pretty extreme weather events over the last year. These events... of the American Association for the Advancement of Science hosted a session on US weather extremes... of the most dramatic weather events, hurricane intensity is going up, although the numbers...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7176-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7176_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:11:34">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/04/see-the-front-lines-of-pandemic-virus-war-thanks-to-the-weather-channel/</link><title>See the front lines of pandemic virus war—thanks to The Weather Channel? [Updated]</title><description>... not really the drill. If you watch Virus Hunters on The Weather Channel starting this week, youll learn... producer with Weather Films. When theres someone who knows bats are infected with a disease that humans...;VirusHuntersdebuts in the next few weeks, and it'll run on The Weather Channel while also being...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7176-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7176_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:12:11">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/12/like-factories-tornadoes-wind-down-on-weekends/</link><title>Weather fronts of the world unite: tornadoes demand the weekend off</title><description>...One of the classic sci-fi doomsday machines is the weather manipulator. What better way to bend the world to your will than taking control of the weather? It seems, however, that labor regulations... of weather phenomena, including rainfall, lightning, and storm heights. Its called the weekend effect...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7176-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7176_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:14:33">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/10/watch-out-weather-balloons-big-wireless-wants-your-spectrum/</link><title>Watch out weather balloons: big wireless wants your spectrum</title><description>...? Now they're going after the frequencies used to guide weather balloons. "Last spring..., and 1675-1710MHz used largely by the National Ocean and Atmospheric Administration for weather satellites and balloons.Ouch. I love weather balloons. And the NOAA has the coolest ones. Bolstered by Spectra...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7176-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7176_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:16:48">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/01/weather-so-severe-it-generates-antimatter/</link><title>Weather so severe it generates antimatter</title><description>...It turns out thunderstorms pack a much bigger punch than most people think. In the mid-1990s, we found that lightning and the associated electric field above a thunderstorm can be strong enough to produce a gamma ray blast detectable from space. These terrestrial gamma-ray flashes (TGFs) are believed to occur all over the world at a rate of about 500 per day. Researchers usingNASA's Fermi Ga...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7176-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7176_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:17:17">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/02/science-online-at-the-american-museum-of-natural-history-tackles-social-media-for-science/</link><title>Ars and nature.com at the American Museum of Natural History: good stuff</title><description>... Science Online NYC. We're pleased to announce that, in February, we'll also be working... Online NYC events have featured a very active discussion with the audience. The event will take... of Minerals and Gems. You can sign up at the announcement page linked above. If youre not in NYC...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7176-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7176_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:18:38">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/05/shuttle-monitoring-radar-can-watch-raindrops-in-a-cloud/</link><title>Shuttle-monitoring radar can watch raindrops in a cloud</title><description>...Turn on the Weather Channel, and you might see storm-tracking images from your friendly local Doppler radar system. Although your average storm front is quite large, this technology... we can? For one thing, a better understanding of cloud dynamics will lead to more accurate weather...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>