<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7180">blink reflex</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:16:30" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7180-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7180_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:16:31">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2014/01/google-plans-to-dump-adobe-css-tech-to-make-blink-fast-not-rich/</link><title>Google plans to dump Adobe CSS tech to make Blink fast, not rich</title><description>...Google's mission for 2014 is to make its Blink rendering engine faster and lighter on mobile platforms. To do this, it's planning not simply to improve the Blink code. The company... is also supported by Blink contributor Opera, with Opera CTO Hkon Wium Lie arguing that Regions doesn't...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7180-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7180_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:18:48">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2014/01/chrome-rendering-engine-will-get-faster-lighter-and-better-offline-in-2014/</link><title>Chrome rendering engine will get faster, lighter, and better offline in 2014</title><description>... WebKit rendering engine to a new, Google-backed (but still open-source) engine called Blink. Reasons... Google Groups post by Google software engineer Eric Seidel shows just what the Blink team...,"in part because Web engines (e.g. Blink) are not nearly as good on performance-constrained...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7180-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7180_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:20:38">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/04/does-webkit-face-a-troubled-future-now-that-google-is-gone/</link><title>Does WebKit face a troubled future now that Google is gone?</title><description>...Now that Google is going its own way and developing its rendering engine independently of the WebKit project, both sides of the split are starting the work of removing all the things they don't actually need.This is already causing some tensions among WebKit users and Web developers, as it could lead to the removal of technology that they use or technology that is in the process of being sta...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7180-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7180_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:22:05">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/09/why-super-hexagon-should-be-your-next-ios-gaming-addiction/</link><title>Why Super Hexagon should be your next iOS gaming addiction</title><description>... through them start to emerge automatically, at the reflexive level of muscle memory.You'll need to sharpen those reflexes as far as they'll go, because even at its easiest levels Super Hexagon... of friends and strangers.Yes, Super Hexagon is just a basic test of visual acuity and reflexes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7180-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7180_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:24:06">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/05/opera-15-provides-a-mish-mash-of-opera-features-and-the-chrome-interface/</link><title>Opera 15 provides a mish-mash of Opera features and the Chrome interface</title><description>... to use the WebKit-derived Blink engine. We're still in the early days, with the browser missing... was always a concern. WebKit doesn't have that problem and Blink shouldn't either... its users of the same.Update: Amended post to note that Opera 15 is Blink-based, rather than WebKit-based....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7180-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7180_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:26:14">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/01/week-in-tech-blinking-lights-laying-your-own-fiber/</link><title>Week in tech: blinking lights, laying your own fiber</title><description>...The evolution of computer displays: We've come a long way since the days of blinking lights and teletypes. Ars surveys the history of computer displays from the very early days.Tale of the trench: what if your subdivision laid its own fiber?: A community-owned fiber network might sound like...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7180-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7180_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:28:29">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/04/nbp-unleash-the-dogs-of-policy/</link><title>Don't blink: Hard-charging FCC turns broadband plan into action</title><description>.... Here's the schedule. Don't blink and don't sneeze.Q2: April to JuneAny day now the FCC...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7180-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7180_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:30:32">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2008/09/secret-acta-treaty-emerges-blinking-into-the-sunlight/</link><title>Secret ACTA treaty emerges blinking into the sunlight</title><description>...At a public meeting this Monday, ACTA negotiators at last stepped into the spotlight and took questions about both the treaty and the drafting process. The treaty isnt about going after iPods at the border, but it still has the potential for plenty of mischief. Short on specifics The much-maligned, drafted-in-secret, Anti-Counterfeiting Trade Agreement, is an odd beast. Its being drafted by a gro...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7180-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7180_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:31:37">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/07/android-4-3-teardown-reveals-small-blink-and-youll-miss-them-changes/</link><title>Android 4.3 teardown reveals small, blink-and-you’ll-miss-them changes</title><description>...Over the weekend, the intrepid software tinkerers over at Android Police pickedapart last week's Android 4.3 leak. The screenshots were initially published on SamMobilewithout much context, but Android Police has managed to identify some of the expected new features.Android 4.3 is only a minor update, but it may make a big difference for end users. As we picked out from the leaked screenshot...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7180-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7180_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:32:07">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/08/dangerous-lasers-homebrew-spectroscopy-and-webcam-hacking/</link><title>Achtung! Test safety of laser pointers with paper cups, webcam</title><description>... produced drops. As the visible light intensity drops, the laser is less likely to set off a blink reflex...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>