<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7185">constitution of italy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:29:42" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7185-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7185_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:29:43">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/07/italy-threatens-apple-with-potential-ban-over-warranty-dispute/</link><title>Italy threatens Apple with potential ban over warranty dispute</title><description>...Italy's Antitrust Authority is officially taking Apple to task over the company's alleged failure to offer two-year warranties on its products under Italian law. The authority confirmed on Tuesday that it had opened proceedings against Apple, which will potentially face fines of up to $378,000 or even be suspended from selling its products in Italy if the company doesn't meet the c...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7185-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7185_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:30:19">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/04/italy-blocks-27-sites-suspected-of-aiding-file-sharing/</link><title>Italy blocks 27 sites suspected of aiding file-sharing</title><description>...Italian authorities have recently ordered that two dozen file-sharing websites be blocked in Italy, the largest such move since American authorities seized over 80 domain names in 2010.The blockagewhich occurred at the DNS level and can be routed aroundwas ordered (Google Translate) by the Public...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7185-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7185_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:32:03">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/09/congressional-report-adds-italy-switzerland-to-piracy-watchlist/</link><title>Congressional report adds Italy, Switzerland (!) to piracy watchlist</title><description>... the list, but there are two new additions: Italy and Switzerland. Canada and Spain remained on the list... and make our services as accountable and transparent as they can possibly be."Meanwhile, Italy...-sharing. The new report laments that in Italy, "there has not been a sufficient legislative...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7185-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7185_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:33:54">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2008/11/google-execs-may-face-judge-in-italy-over-teen-violence-vid/</link><title>Google execs may face judge in Italy over teen violence vid</title><description>...When Internet video hosts get dragged into the court room, chances are good theyre getting sued for something related to copyrighted material. But rumors have persisted since July that Google execs might get hauled before a judge in Italy to answer to charges of defamation for a video that briefly...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7185-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7185_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:34:48">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/01/following-fine-in-italy-belgian-group-sues-apple-for-warranty-practices/</link><title>Following fine in Italy, Belgian group sues Apple for warranty practices</title><description>... after Apple was fined by regulators in Italy. This time, it's a Belgian consumer group called... in Italy at the end of 2011. The basic gist is that EU law specifies that buyers should receive a warranty... and implies they must purchase AppleCare in order to get it. This is why Italy sued Apple for allegedly...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7185-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7185_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:35:53">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/06/viral-nature-of-the-internet-means-only-family-can-release-autopsy-photos/</link><title>"Viral nature of the Internet" means only family can release autopsy photos</title><description>... Marsh's due process constitutional rights when Coulter made photocopies of 16 images... are given out by family members, this ruling is the first that says it is also a constitutional... that a clear precedent for the violation of constitutional rights had not been established...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7185-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7185_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:37:12">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/04/suit-challenging-drone-strikes-that-killed-americans-16-year-old-boy-is-tossed/</link><title>Suit challenging drone strikes that killed Americans, 16-year-old boy is tossed [Updated]</title><description>... for Constitutional Rights, exposed the administration's unmanned "targeted killing" program...-of-its-kind lawsuit alleged violations of international human rights and the US Constitution, arguing... from any battlefield, is profoundly at odds with the Constitution," Hina Shamsi, director...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7185-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7185_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:38:29">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/02/italy-preparing-to-hold-youtube-others-liable-for-uploads/</link><title>Italy preparing to hold YouTube, others liable for uploads</title><description>... traditional broadcasters, but Italy has been the democracy that has gone furthest in that direction..., but the government insists that the new rules are meant to bring Italy into compliance with a separate EU directive on video content. Such moves always raise concern in Italy that the motivations may...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7185-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7185_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:40:14">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/03/doj-sec-investigating-microsoft-over-bribery-claims/</link><title>DoJ, SEC investigating Microsoft over bribery claims</title><description>... to government officials in China, Romania, and Italy to secure software contracts, the Wall Street Journal... resellers and the Ministry of Communications. In Italy, the company's dealings with customer...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7185-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7185_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:43:14">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2008/11/eff-kentucky-domain-seizures-flawed-on-many-levels/</link><title>EFF: Kentucky domain seizures flawed on many levels</title><description>... and nations, leaving it on the wrong side of the Constitution. Under the Commerce Clause..., for example, to access a site that is lawful in Nevada. Beyond the Constitution, the seizure...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>