<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7189">judiciary act 1789</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:43:05" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7189-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7189_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:43:07">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/05/blacklists-ahoy-protect-ip-act-sails-on-to-senate-floor/</link><title>Blacklists, ahoy! PROTECT IP Act sails on to Senate floor</title><description>...The Senate Judiciary Committee this morning unanimously approved the PROTECT IP Act by a voice vote... by the Senate Judiciary Committee, but Sen. Ron Wyden (D-OR) put a hold on the bill when it came..., when the PROTECT IP Act was introduced, Wyden said it would be "hard to consider legislation...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7189-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7189_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:44:27">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/06/its-hard-to-imagine-a/</link><title>Are the feds torturing the Patriot Act for location data?</title><description>...It's hard to imagine a Senator making a blunter statement than Sen. Ron Wyden (D-OR) made in the heat of the Patriot Act reauthorization fight last month: "When the American people find out how their government has secretly interpreted the Patriot Act," he said, "they will be stunned and they will be angry." Wyden is in a position to know. As a member of the Senate Intell...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7189-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7189_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:45:14">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/07/senate-introduces-revised-version-of-the-cybersecurity-act-of-2012/</link><title>Senate introduces revised version of the Cybersecurity Act of 2012</title><description>... Act of 2012 (PDF) today, hoping to revitalize lagging support for the bill, especially among Republicans. The act, which was first introduced in February of 2012, calls for the creation of a council... a claim to "enhancing cybersecurity" in its own way).The revised version of the act makes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7189-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7189_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:46:09">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/07/dozens-of-law-professors-protect-ip-act-is-unconstitutional/</link><title>Dozens of law professors: PROTECT IP Act is unconstitutional</title><description>...An ideologically diverse group of 90 law professors has signed a letter opposing the PROTECT IP Act..., but also by libertarians like Post and Glenn "Instapundit" Reynolds."The Act would allow courts... industries," the professors write. "Passage of the Act will compromise our ability to defend...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7189-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7189_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:47:30">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/03/what-ever-happened-to-the-call-home-act/</link><title>Whatever happened to the Call Home Act?</title><description>...Its passage in December of 2006 was hailed by the Senatethe Call Home Act, subtitled "A bill... that the Call Home Act has done US military abroad much good. One critic has called the law "intentionally... with their husbands and sons meant everything to them.As authorized by the Call Home Act, the FCC...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7189-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7189_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:48:18">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/10/calm-act-plans-to-put-loud-tv-commercials-to-sleep/</link><title>CALM Act plans to put loud TV commercials to sleep</title><description>... Act pass, the FCC would have a year to put together its own regulatory framework for TV volume...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7189-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7189_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:50:08">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/02/patriot-act-author-absent-reform-well-halt-bulk-metadata-program-renewal/</link><title>Patriot Act author: Absent reform, we’ll halt bulk metadata program renewal</title><description>...In a Congressional committee hearing, the author of the Patriot Act threatened to orchestrate a movement to not reauthorize the controversial post-9/11 law.In a session of the House Judiciary... this committee acts and acts soon, I fear we will lose valuable counterterrorism tools along...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7189-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7189_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:50:43">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/06/as-senators-defend-mass-surveillance-effs-foia-lawsuit-still-awaits/</link><title>As Senators defend mass-surveillance, Patriot Act FOIA lawsuit still awaits</title><description>... out how their government has secretly interpreted the Patriot Act, they will be stunned... the Patriot Act was being interpreted to allow mass spying.Today Udall told his hometown paper... authorized by the "business records" provision of the Patriot Act. "Therefore, it is lawful...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7189-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7189_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:52:02">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/08/protect-ip-act-would-cost-taxpayers-47-million-private-sector-much-more/</link><title>PROTECT IP Act would cost taxpayers $47 million, private sector much more</title><description>...The Congressional Budget Office has released a new estimate of the cost of the PROTECT IP Act... to the private sector. The Unfunded Mandates Reform Act requires the CBO to estimate whether proposed... of large-scale Internet censorship infrastructure mandated by the PROTECT IP Act, so it's hard...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7189-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7189_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:53:53">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/05/sen-ron-wyden-to-place-a-hold-on-the-protect-ip-act/</link><title>Sen. Ron Wyden places a "hold" on the PROTECT IP Act</title><description>...The office of Sen. Ron Wyden (D-OR) tells Ars that the just-passed-out-of-committee PROTECT IP Act..., he's at it again after the PROTECT IP Act failed to incorporate enough of his desired changes.A... analysis of the Protect IP Act, or PIPA, I am compelled to draw the same conclusion. I understand...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>