<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7200">uss stennis</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:10:41" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7200-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7200_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:10:42">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/12/enterprise-to-dock-with-u-s-s-ars-openforum-tonight/</link><title>Enterprise to dock with U.S.S. Ars OpenForum tonight</title><description>...One could say that Christmas has come early to the Ars Technica Community. Tonight the Ars Technica OpenForum will undergo its first major migration in quite some time, but before you get anxious, let me tell you what this change is all about. Were migrating to Eve for Enterprise, which is a more scalable, robust, and sturdy implementation of our current forum platform, Eve. It will look and feel...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7200-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7200_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:12:27">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/05/watch-out-maverick-navy-drones-practicing-their-carrier-landings/</link><title>Watch out Maverick: Navy drones practicing their carrier landings</title><description>... the stage for the X-48B to go to sea for flight testing aboard the aircraft carrier USS George H. W... aboard the battleship USS Iowa (BB-61) as a forward spotter for naval gunfire (tests... when Iraqi troops on Fallaka Island surrendered to a Pioneer flown off the USS Wisconsin (BB-64...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7200-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7200_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:14:50">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/10/the-navys-newest-warship-is-powered-by-linux/</link><title>The Navy’s newest warship is powered by Linux</title><description>...When the USS Zumwalt (DDG 1000) puts to sea later this year, it will be different... at the heart of the Zumwalt and are preparing to do the same for the next ship in line, the USS Michael... of the Zumwalt will have more in common with the fictional starship USS Enterprise's bridge...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7200-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7200_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:16:43">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/09/after-20-year-absence-star-trek-returns-to-the-world-of-pinball/</link><title>After 20-year absence, Star Trek returns to the world of pinball</title><description>... through the images does reveal that the USS Vengeance at the top of the playfield is mounted on a spring... a wizard mode. USS Vengeance toy details. Details of various parts of the playfield and toys....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7200-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7200_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:17:29">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/11/star-trek-comes-with-itunes-exclusive-extras-but-bilks-fans/</link><title>Star Trek comes with iTunes-exclusive extras, but bilks fans</title><description>... at the original crew of the USS Enterprise through a new lens, as well as Score, which shows how composer...;s editions that come with different USS Enterprise modelsthey're like getting a toy and a movie...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7200-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7200_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:18:39">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/12/national-archives-wwii-records-digitized/</link><title>Browsing the past: National Archives' WWII records digitized</title><description>... named USS Hornet, so I expected a rich trove of images to be returned when hornet was used... of action reports from submarines, including one in which the crew of the USS Dace were commended...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7200-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7200_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:19:33">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2014/04/navy-will-test-seafaring-firefighting-robots/</link><title>Navy will test seafaring, firefighting robots</title><description>... fire can get out of control quickly. A fire, set deliberately aboard the submarine USS Miami...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7200-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7200_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:20:25">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/08/court-ruling-that-nsa-spying-violated-4th-amendment-remains-secret/</link><title>Court ruling that NSA spying violated 4th Amendment remains secret</title><description>... secret. Decisions handed down by the USs Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Court (FISC) are classified...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7200-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7200_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:21:21">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/01/fedora-11-codenamed-leonidas-will-kick-bad-guys-into-pit/</link><title>Fedora 11 codenamed Leonidas, will kick bad guys into pit</title><description>... developers failed to realize, however, is that the USS Leonidas was a derelict vessel that the Union...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7200-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7200_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:22:05">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2014/04/navy-prepares-to-take-rail-gun-to-sea/</link><title>Navy prepares to take railgun to sea</title><description>... System (LaWS), which will beput to sea aboard the USS Ponce late this summer, the Office of Naval...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>