<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7207">earthquake</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:55:44" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7207-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7207_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:55:45">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/10/can-humans-cause-an-earthquake/</link><title>Can humans cause an earthquake?</title><description>...One of the things people often wonder about earthquakes is whether human activity can play a role... to a bigger question: could we actively trigger small earthquakes to prevent the big, damaging ones..., lowering the stress threshold necessary to trigger an earthquake just enough for one to occur.The story...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7207-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7207_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:57:59">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/04/surprising-indonesian-earthquakes-set-record/</link><title>Surprising Indonesian earthquakes set record</title><description>...A pair of massive earthquakes that occurred earlier today off the coast of Indonesia, reminiscent... minimal damage. The earthquakes were extremely unusual, setting a new record for strike-slip faultsvertical faults where the blocks slide horizontally past each other. Most major earthquakes occur on ramp...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7207-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7207_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:59:37">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/03/milkshakes-unusual-earthquakes-in-wisconsin/</link><title>Milkshakes: unusual earthquakes strike Wisconsin</title><description>... out, and there were no reports of industrial accidents, either. Thoughts naturally turned to earthquakes, even though Wisconsin... a magnitude 1.5 earthquake in the seismic records from March 20th began circulating. Such small earthquakes... of seismometers were able to detect the earthquake in Clintonvil...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7207-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7207_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:01:59">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/07/can-fracking-cause-bigger-more-frequent-earthquakes/</link><title>Can fracking cause bigger, more frequent earthquakes?</title><description>... from the planet, can cause earthquakes. New reports that look at American fracking, deep waste-water... regulatory framework to deal with them.The most striking indication of human-induced earthquakes is provided by the graph below, which shows the cumulative number of earthquakes in the central and eastern US...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7207-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7207_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:02:39">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/09/mineral-transformation-may-trigger-deep-earthquakes/</link><title>Mineral transformation may trigger deep earthquakes</title><description>... that suggested something unexpected. The only way to make sense of the data was if an earthquake occurred hundreds of kilometers beneath the Earths surface.Since Turners observations, deep earthquakes... earthquakes do not have immediate consequences for humans. But they hold clues about destructive quakes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7207-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7207_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:05:02">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/02/earthquakes-booms-big-enough-to-be-detected-from-orbit/</link><title>Earthquakes’ booms big enough to be detected from orbit</title><description>... out to be small earthquakes. While it was an unusual story, its actually not that uncommon of an occurrence.Early... continued, off and on, for about five months. The mystery didnt last long, as the earthquakes....)In total, 105 earthquakes were detected, with a couple as large as magnitude 4.0. For most of them...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7207-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7207_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:06:33">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/06/japanese-earthquake-literally-made-waves-in-norway/</link><title>Japanese earthquake literally made waves in Norway</title><description>...During an earthquake, its the area near the epicenter that sustains the greatest damage, though... by the earthquake actually travels around the globeseveral times, in factas the planet, in essence, rings like a struck bell. The bigger the earthquake, the louder it rings. And the magnitude 9.0 quake...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7207-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7207_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:08:16">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/04/apple-donating-money-devices-to-earthquake-victims-in-china/</link><title>Apple donating money, devices to earthquake victims in China</title><description>...Apple has donated 50 million yuan (about $8 million) to earthquake victims in the Sichuan region of China, and the company offered condolences on the front page of its Chinese website on Monday...;At this difficult time, our hearts are with the victims of the Sichuan earthquake. Aside from the cash...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7207-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7207_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:09:42">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/04/monitoring-earthquakes-from-space/</link><title>Monitoring earthquakes from space</title><description>...Large earthquakes occur when a fault ruptures. While the fault and the earthquake epicenter are often deep below the earth's surface, the ground above the fault moves a little too. This movement is very slight, but it is possible to measure it with high precision GPS instruments, or with satellites. Following the magnitude 6.3 earthquake that struck LAquila in central Italy on April 6th, the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7207-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7207_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:11:02">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/12/cluster-of-80-magnitude-earthquakes-doesnt-indicate-earth-is-more-active/</link><title>Cluster of &gt;8.0-magnitude earthquakes doesn't indicate Earth is more active</title><description>...The past few years have seen an unusual number of epically large earthquakes, with severalin... whether large earthquakes cluster and, if they do, whether we should be getting nervous... earthquake above magnitude 7.0 that occurred between 1900 and 2011. To eliminate aftershocks and local...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>