<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7209">crab dip appetizer</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:22:19" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7209-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7209_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:22:20">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/04/computer-built-using-swarms-of-soldier-crabs/</link><title>Computer modeled using swarms of soldier crabs</title><description>... have essentially built a billiard ball computer using soldier crabs(PDF). In their report, they demonstrate that "swarms of soldier crabs can implement logical gates when placed in a geometrically constrained environment."Soldier crabs or Mictyris guinotae live in flat lagoons and form huge...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7209-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7209_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:23:36">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/12/transparent-crab-shell-holds-the-secret-to-bendable-screens/</link><title>Transparent crab shell holds the secret to bendable screens</title><description>... University took an entire (dead) crab, and treated its body to a brew of acids and chemicals. Hydrochloric... and pigments.This left a crab shell made entirely of translucent chitin. Chitin is a long-chain polymer...), and the team ended up with a perfect, ghostly recreation of a crab, only now completely see-through.Buoyed...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7209-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7209_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:24:12">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/02/a-neutron-star-thats-a-fast-particle-accelerator-may-lie-at-the-heart-of-the-crab-nebula/</link><title>A neutron star that's a fast particle accelerator may lie at the heart of the Crab Nebula</title><description>...The Crab Nebula (also designated M1 or NGC 1952) is visible through small telescopes... visible in 1054 CE. A pulsar was found in the center of the Crab in 1968. This rapidly rotating neutron.... During that mapping, it became apparent that the Crab pulsar is one of the brightest sources of gamma...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7209-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7209_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:25:14">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/01/crab-nebula-gets-erratic-with-gamma-ray-outbursts/</link><title>Crab Nebula gets erratic with gamma-ray outbursts</title><description>...The Crab Nebula is the result of a supernova observed by Chinese astronomers in 1064, making it one of the more recent remnants available to study. Its core contains a rapidly spinning pulsar... they could generate a field strong enough to push electrons around at these energies. "The Crab Nebula...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7209-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7209_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:27:08">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/05/weird-science/</link><title>Weird Science looks for vacancies at the hermit crab hotel</title><description>...They may still be crabs, but they're not hermits: This is a fascinating bit of social behavior that I had no idea existed. For hermit crabs, decent shells are a scarce commodity, and they've evolved a social means of optimizing shell occupancy that researchers have termed a vacancy chain. This new observational study describes two types of vacancy chains, synchronous and asynchronous. T...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7209-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7209_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:29:10">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/10/crab-nebulas-neutron-star-is-pulsing-with-gamma-rays/</link><title>Crab nebula's neutron star is pulsing with gamma rays</title><description>...In 1054, a supernova went off in our galactic neighborhood and was recorded in a number of historical accounts. Today, the remnants of that blast form the spectacular Crab Nebula shown above. Buried within it is a rapidly rotating neutron star, which we can detect by its pulsed emissions. Now, researchers have used a rather unusual telescopeone that incorporates our own planet into the opticsto c...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7209-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7209_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:29:51">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/10/latest-changewave-survey-shows-dip-in-apple-purchases/</link><title>Latest ChangeWave survey shows dip in Apple purchases</title><description>... from ChangeWave Research that shows a dip in Apple purchases in the past three months, in addition... for desktops. Despite the dip, director of research Paul Carton is quick to point out that the purchase... are at their lowest level of 2008. The dip seems to be part of an overall trend towards lower levels...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7209-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7209_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:32:18">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/04/gartner-tablet-hype-fueling-worldwide-dip-in-pc-sales/</link><title>Gartner: tablet hype fueling worldwide dip in PC sales</title><description>...Worldwide PC sales experienced an unexpected year-over-year decline for the first quarter, according to market research firm Gartner's preliminary sales figures for early 2011. Gartner attributes the 1.1 percent dip in unit shipmentsthe first decline in six consecutive quarters since...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7209-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7209_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:34:13">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/04/march-video-game-sales-hurt-badly-by-late-easter/</link><title>"Late" Easter leads to 17 percent dip in game revenues</title><description>...The NPD report for March has been released, and last month was a rare slow period in game sales, although we're warned not to take the 17 percent dip too seriously. "While it might be tempting to jump to the conclusion that the sky is starting to fall on the video games industry given...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7209-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7209_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:35:49">http://arstechnica.com/business/2010/01/youtube-dipping-its-toe-into-rentals-but-users-may-balk/</link><title>YouTube dipping its toe into rentals, but users may balk</title><description>...YouTube is finally jumping into the movie rental business after months of rumors, though it's starting slow. YouTube will begin offering five films from the 2009 and 2010 Sundance Film Festivals starting Friday of this week, and the company is hoping that the test will attract more movie studios to its new venture. That could prove difficult, though, as recent history shows that users aren&amp;a...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>