<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7211">punctuation guide</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:48:52" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7211-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7211_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:48:52">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2008/12/ultimate-road-warrior-guide-2008/</link><title>The Ars Technica Ultimate Road Warrior Guide</title><description>... to the Internet. But thats where this community-driven guide comes in. We turned to the Ars staff... in the guide as a reference point for 3G broadband. A lesser-known but solid brand is Millenicom... batteryRichardSolo$69.99 RichardSolo Power SliderIncase $99.95IncasePicking the right netbook: a mini-guide...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7211-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7211_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:51:04">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/12/ars-technica-system-guide-december-2012/</link><title>Ars Technica System Guide: December 2012</title><description>..., performance jumps up throughout all three System Guide boxes. Performance benefits are huge... (Piledriver) grace the System Guide. Updated graphics card architectures from Nvidia (Kepler) and AMD...;ll focus more on the tangible benefits for the System Guide: better overall performance...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7211-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7211_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:53:14">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/12/ars-technica-system-guide-december-2011/</link><title>Ars Technica system guide: December 2011</title><description>...;re here to sort them out.The bottom line remains the same as it always doesthe System Guide builds get faster and cheaper.System Guide BasicsThe traditional Budget Box ($), Hot Rod ($$), and God Box... in previous guides as: "God wouldn't be a glutton.")Each box comes with a full set...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7211-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7211_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:54:13">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/04/ars-technica-system-guide-gaming-boxes-april-2013/</link><title>Ars Technica System Guide: Gaming Boxes</title><description>...The main Ars System Guide is great for what it isan updated, step-by-step look at the best.... And if our System Guide build got much bigger, it might notever get published.In particular... shift. There's where the newest System Guide comes in. Meet the special Gaming Boxes.The goal...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7211-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7211_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:55:02">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/12/2011-gadget-gift-guide/</link><title>Ars Technica's 2011 holiday gift guide extravaganza</title><description>...Every holiday session, millions of geeks suffer at the hands of poorly thought-out gifts: USB flash drives in Hello Kitty shapes. T-shirts that detect Wi-Fi signals. Your second, third, and fourth copies of Arkham City.No more, friends. This year, buy the tech-savvy friends and family in your life something they actually wantor something they don't know they want until you, insightful person...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7211-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7211_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:55:57">http://arstechnica.com/staff/2009/03/find-ars-system-guides-easier/</link><title>Find Ars System Guides easier</title><description>.... How it works is pretty simple, each of those buttons in the masthead of the Guides section of the site will always link to the most recent system guide containing that box.Most of the time we put... eventually point to different articles. The HTPC guide, as is usual, will most likely continue to stand...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7211-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7211_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:56:50">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2008/11/staff-gift-guide-2008/</link><title>Ars Staff Gift Guide 2008</title><description>... guide. This year it came out so huge another group of picks would have been overwhelming. Never ones... my gift guide entries [and then edit out his stupid comments later -ed]! So it only seems right to kick off this staff edition of our annual gift guide with my favorite time saver/addiction. Keurig...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7211-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7211_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:58:03">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/08/week-in-tech-system-guide-supercomputers-trading-stocks-and-more/</link><title>Week in tech: System Guide, supercomputers trading stocks, and more</title><description>... market.The Ars System Guide is back, this time with our special gaming edition. If you're looking...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7211-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7211_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:59:40">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/11/ars-technica-system-guide-november-2013/</link><title>Ars Technica System Guide: November 2013</title><description>... Guide.As for the rest of the computing industry, at least as far as the System Guide is concerned... to focus more on the tangible benefits for the System Guide: better overall performance and performance... system.System Guide fundamentalsThe main Ars System Guide is a three-system affair...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7211-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7211_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:00:36">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/07/ars-technica-system-guide-july-2013/</link><title>Ars Technica System Guide: July 2013</title><description>...Compared to the massive, across the board shakeups seen in some updates, this iteration of the System Guide looks pretty straightforward. The new System Guide accounts for a significant jump in graphics performance and the continuing evolution of faster CPUs, but the effects are limited.Small but significant product changes add up, though, and enough of them mean an updated System Guide. It'...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>