<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7215">squamous cell carcinoma</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:45:17" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7215-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7215_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:45:18">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/01/acid-bath-turns-cells-from-any-tissue-into-stem-cells/</link><title>Acid bath turns cells from any tissue into stem cells</title><description>...The development of human embryonic stem cells, which have the ability to form any cell in the body, may enable us to repair tissues damaged by injury or disease. Initially, these cells... developed a combination of genes that could reprogram most cells into an embryonic-like state. That worked...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7215-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7215_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:46:27">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/05/printable-a3-sized-solar-cells-hit-a-new-milestone-in-green-energy/</link><title>Printable A3-sized solar cells hit a new milestone in green energy</title><description>... have brought us one step closer to that reality.Researchers from the Victorian Organic Solar Cell Consortium (VICOSC) developed a printer that can print 10 meters (about 33 feet) of flexible solar cells a minute. Unlike traditional silicon solar cells, printed solar cells are made using organic semi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7215-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7215_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:47:16">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/04/distributing-single-cells-on-a-microwell-plate-using-gravity/</link><title>Distributing single cells using gravity</title><description>...Ever since HeLa cells were mass produced to help medical researchers test the safety and efficacy of the polio vaccine, cell biology has become more and more about scale and speed. Ideally, researchers want to take control of single cells, direct them to individual experiments, and observe...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7215-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7215_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:48:04">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/10/nobel-prize-for-the-heart-of-cell-signaling/</link><title>Nobel prize for the heart of cell signaling</title><description>... worked on a group of biochemicals called G-protein-coupled receptors.These receptors sit in the cell-membrane and allow small molecules outside the cell to manipulate the response of the cell. G-proteins play a role in vision, smell, mood regulation, and the immune system. They also help control cell...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7215-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7215_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:49:46">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/11/end-of-the-line-for-ibms-cell/</link><title>End of the line for IBM's Cell</title><description>... that the Cell processor has reached the end of the line. Turek then put a more positive spin on the news by stating the obvious truth that heterogeneous multiprocessors, of which Cell was the first mass-market... concepts and ideas will live on in the company's product line. By many metrics, Cell...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7215-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7215_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:50:21">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/02/questions-arise-about-stem-cell-breakthrough/</link><title>Questions arise about stem cell breakthrough</title><description>... simple technique that could convert just about any cell to a stem cell using a brief time in acidic... in mice. That individual pointed out that the cells behave unlike any others we knowthey... any cells, which provides lots of time for something to go wrong. Even the researchers who've...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7215-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7215_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:51:13">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/08/stem-cells-turned-into-cancer-killing-immune-cells/</link><title>Stem cells turned into cancer-killing immune cells</title><description>... is also able to identify cells that have gone bad inside the body. Even though cancer cells look a lot like normal ones, immune cells can often tell the differenceenough that people who receive long-term... has its limits, or cancer wouldn't be a problem.Cancer cells evolve ways to avoid detection or...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7215-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7215_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:52:06">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/10/riots-lead-mozambique-to-ban-cell-phone-anonymity/</link><title>Riots lead Mozambique to ban cell phone anonymity</title><description>...Mozambique has more than six million cell phone users, many of them using the cheap prepaid models...;s cell phones can be used anonymously, something the government is suddenly determined to stop. A new rule gives cell phone users two months to register their names and numbers with the government...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7215-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7215_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:53:41">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/05/senators-call-for-end-of-anonymous-prepaid-cell-phones/</link><title>Senators call for end to anonymous, prepaid cell phones</title><description>... prepaid cell phone to purchase the Nissan Pathfinder and M-88 fireworks used in the bomb attempt. The case sparked new calls to regulate prepaid cell phones in order to provide more accountability... manager."In 2009," said the Schumer/Cornyn announcement, "[prepaid cell phones...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7215-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7215_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:55:43">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/07/blue-cells-of-death-mark-the-end-of-a-worms-life/</link><title>Blue cells of death mark the end of a worm’s life</title><description>... have known for many years that cells can die in two ways. Necrosis occurs when either the cells machinery breaks down with age or exposure to trauma damages the cell beyond repair. Apoptosis is a programmed process triggered on demand, by which even healthy cells can undergo a series of changes resulting...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>