<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7216">salmonella</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:56:35" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7216-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7216_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:56:36">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/09/salmonella-causes-then-feeds-off-gut-inflammation/</link><title>Salmonella causes, then feeds off gut inflammation</title><description>...If youve ever had the misfortune to experience salmonella poisoning, you are familiar with symptoms... published a few years ago linked severe intestinal inflammation with improved growth of Salmonella... of Salmonella Typhimurium in samples that contain rival microbes.This led the authors to ask...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7216-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7216_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:57:57">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/09/cows-cleared-of-charges-in-salmonella-epidemic-new-suspects-named/</link><title>Cows cleared of charges in salmonella epidemic; new suspects named</title><description>... resistant Salmonella. While livestock have been assumed to be a main source of antibiotic-resistant... more for treatments.An antibiotic resistant strain of Salmonella became a global epidemic in the 1990s. Infection...-genome sequencing of Salmonella samples that were collected over a 22-year period. This detailed level...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7216-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7216_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:59:31">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/01/immune-cells-inadvertently-help-bacteria-form-persistent-infections/</link><title>Immune cells inadvertently help bacteria form persistent infections</title><description>..., Sophie Helaine and her colleagues demonstrated that when mice are infected with Salmonella... a technique she called fluorescent dilution. She engineered Salmonella cells to express a fluorescent... Salmonella persistence. In addition to these external conditions, about 14 Salmonella genetic elements...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7216-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7216_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:01:53">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/02/oral-delivery-of-a-ribozyme-via-engineered-salmonella-reduces-viral-load/</link><title>Meet the newest virus fighter: Salmonella</title><description>... Liu at UC Berkeley made a modified strain of Salmonella to deliver interfering RNA exactly where... so is not fully understood. Some low-activity Salmonella strains are safe for humans: the vaccine against typhoid fever that has been used since the 1980s is based on an attenuated Salmonella strain. The bacteria...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7216-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7216_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:02:21">http://arstechnica.com/science/2008/12/clearing-my-in-box-a-bullet-post/</link><title>Clearing my inbox: a bullet post</title><description>... in space! A study of gene regulation and protein expression in spacefaring Salmonella...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7216-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7216_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:05:03">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/01/parasitic-wasp-larvae-clean-house-by-sanitizing-cockroaches/</link><title>Parasitic wasp larvae clean house by sanitizing cockroaches</title><description>... that harbor and transmit some pretty nasty pathogens like Salmonella, E. coli, and the eggs of various...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7216-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7216_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:07:02">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/05/hands-on-with-microsofts-new-search-to-bing-or-not-to-bing/</link><title>To Bing or not to Bing? Hands on with Microsoft's new search</title><description>... Pox, Allergies, or Salmonella will give you more information, be it symptoms or remedies. Microsoft...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>