<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7217">who was lincolns vice president</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:08:25" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7217-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7217_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:08:26">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/09/apple-hires-former-newton-designer-to-head-product-marketing/</link><title>Apple hires former Newton designer to head product marketing</title><description>...Lots of folks have left Apple and gone on to other successful careers, and occasionallylike Steve Jobs himselfthey come back to work for the iconic computing company. That is the case of Michael Tchao, a former Newton designer, who has recently been named vice president of product marketing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7217-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7217_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:09:20">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/03/rubin-out-pichai-in-as-googles-new-senior-vice-president-of-android/</link><title>Rubin out, Pichai in as Google’s new senior vice president of Android</title><description>...Google announced that Sundar Pichai has been instated as senior vice president of Android at Google. He'll take over the role from former Senior Vice President of Mobile and Digital Content Andy Rubin.The pace of innovation has never been greater, and Android is the most used mobile operating...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7217-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7217_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:11:12">http://arstechnica.com/staff/2012/09/presidents-and-would-be-presidents-cant-resist-meddling-with-nasa/</link><title>Presidents—and would-be presidents—can't resist meddling with NASA</title><description>...;s plans for NASA would be if he is elected, other than to say that President Obama "has failed... of the 1970s. Carter is one of the few presidents in the last 50 years to not really care much... to low earth orbit for years, the first President Bush proposed that the struggling agency take...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7217-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7217_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:11:51">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/01/did-president-obama-just-order-the-government-to-study-video-game-violence/</link><title>Did President Obama just order the government to study video game violence?</title><description>...All afternoon, my little corner of the Internet has been blowing up with tweets, links, and e-mail messages regarding President Obama's unprovoked and unnecessary attack on video games. The general consensus, judging from headlines and social networking sound bites, is that the president is singling out video games as a scapegoat, taking the side of politicians and lobbyists trying to sidest...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7217-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7217_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:14:14">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/01/new-president-means-new-look-features-for-whitehouse-gov/</link><title>New president means new look, features for whitehouse.gov (Updated)</title><description>...As Barack Obama was sworn in as the 44th President of the United States this morning, WhiteHouse.gov saw its own changes applied almost immediately. Featuring an all-new design, the new site touts... is also a primary focus for the site, as President Obamas executive orders and proclamations will be published...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7217-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7217_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:15:36">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/04/if-president-obama-wanted-the-nsa-to-quit-storing-phone-metadata-hed-act-now/</link><title>If President Obama wanted the NSA to quit storing phone metadata, he’d act now</title><description>...President Barack Obama says he wants Congress to adopt legislation that would end the National... only with new court's order.Ultimately, congressional action will be necessary even if the president signs an executive order on the issue. Future presidents are not bound by former presidential...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7217-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7217_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:16:31">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2008/11/the-first-blackberry-president/</link><title>The first BlackBerry president?</title><description>... in cabinet meetings, the overwhelming demands on a presidents attention make this impractical. Let his aides attend to the blinkenlights and pass on what its actually vital for the president to deal... the executive branch over warrantless wiretapping, drawn from his book about the Cheney vice...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7217-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7217_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:17:13">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/01/microsoft-promotes-bob-muglia-to-president/</link><title>Microsoft promotes Bob Muglia to president</title><description>...After working for 21 years for Microsoft, Bob Muglia has been promoted from vice president to president of Microsofts Server and Tools Business (STB), which generated some US$13 billion in FY08, or about 20 percent of the companys total revenue. He is now among the two other Microsoft presidents...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7217-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7217_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:18:31">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/04/cispa-veto-recommended-by-white-house-bills-authors-defend-it/</link><title>CISPA veto recommended by White House, bill's authors defend it</title><description>...Not a fan of CISPA? Fear not. President Barack Obama isnt either.A Wednesday e-mail released by the Office of Management and Budget made very clear that should the bill reach the presidents desk... stated herein, if H.R. 3523 were presented to the President, his senior advisors would recommend...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7217-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7217_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:19:16">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/07/sinofsky-promoted-to-president-of-windows-division/</link><title>Sinofsky promoted to president of Windows division</title><description>...Microsoft has promoted Steven Sinofsky to president of the Windows division. Sinofsky previously... at the software giant. He will become the sixth Microsoft executive to hold a title of president... to President of the Windows Division. Windows 7 is receiving terrific feedback from customers...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>