<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7218">edward kennedy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:21:14" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7218-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7218_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:21:15">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/08/edward-snowden-leaves-airport-gets-one-year-asylum-in-russia/</link><title>Edward Snowden leaves airport, gets one-year asylum in Russia</title><description>...Edward Snowden has been granted one-year temporary asylum in Russia and reportedly left the Moscow airport he's been staying in since June 23.Snowden was in Sheremetyevo International Airport..., confirmed on Twitter that "Edward Snowden was granted temporary asylum in Russia for a year...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7218-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7218_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:22:49">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/04/edward-snowden-and-journalist-laura-poitras-awarded-truth-telling-prize/</link><title>Edward Snowden and journalist Laura Poitras awarded truth-telling prize</title><description>...The 2014 Ridenhour Prize for Truth-Telling was awarded Monday to Edward Snowden and Laura Poitras. The award, named for the Vietnam veteran who helped uncover the My Lai Massacre and later became... recipients, the awards committee explained:We have selected Edward Snowden and Laura Poitras...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7218-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7218_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:23:42">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/11/rock-band-tracks-dead-kennedys-mission-of-burma/</link><title>Rock Band tracks: Dead Kennedys, Mission of Burma</title><description>... Kennedys and Mission Of Burma. Lets take a peek: Dead KennedysCalifornia Uber AllesHoliday... have been clamouring for the Dead Kennedys, so there will likely be a night of... interesting...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7218-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7218_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:24:38">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/08/street-view-goes-indoors-for-kennedy-space-centers-50th/</link><title>Street View goes indoors for Kennedy Space Center's 50th</title><description>...Fans of US space exploration can now get an insider's view of Kennedy Space Center without... Operations Center at Kennedy, Google has worked with NASA to capture some of the significant locations... a nice view of how Kennedy has grown up over the years....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7218-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7218_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:25:43">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/01/buffy-vs-edward-remix-unfairly-removed-by-lionsgate/</link><title>“Buffy vs Edward” remix unfairly removed by Lionsgate</title><description>... vs Edward: Twilight Remixed to YouTube. The work is an example of fair use, transformative... that Buffy vs Edward and other noncommercial videos would suffer significantly because of blurring... notification from YouTube saying that my Buffy vs Edward remix had matched third party content owned...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7218-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7218_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:27:25">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/07/bolivia-joins-the-party-also-grants-asylum-for-edward-snowden/</link><title>Bolivia joins the party, also grants asylum for Edward Snowden</title><description>...In a move that is sure to rankle the United States, Bolivian President Evo Morales has declared that he will grant Edward Snowden asylum in his South American homeland.That now brings the total number of countries willing to accept the famed NSA leaker to three, after Venezuela and Nicaraguastepped...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7218-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7218_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:29:19">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/08/launch-pads-runways-facilities-nasas-grand-shuttle-sell-off-continues/</link><title>Launch pads, runways, facilities: NASA’s grand shuttle sell-off continues</title><description>...Earlier this week, NASA announced that two commercial space companies have placed bids on one of the mobile launch platforms at the Kennedy Space Center in Florida. The platform is one of three... being divested is the shuttle runway and Shuttle Landing Facility at the Kennedy Space Center...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7218-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7218_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:30:21">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/06/more-snowden-leaks-reveal-uk-surveillance-on-2009-g20-summit-attendees/</link><title>More Snowden leaks reveal UK surveillance on 2009 G20 summit attendees</title><description>...The impact of Edward Snowden's leaked information now extends beyond the NSA. Today,The Guardianreportedthataccording to documents uncovered by Snowdenforeign politicians and officials who attended the 2009 G20 summit in London had their calls intercepted and computers monitored by the host...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7218-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7218_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:31:58">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/12/nsa-should-stop-undermining-encryption-standards-obama-panel-says/</link><title>NSA should stop undermining encryption standards, Obama panel says</title><description>...A presidential advisory committee today recommended that the US government stop any efforts to undermine encryption standards or attack commercial software.The panel's report (full text at Whitehouse.gov) comes in response to the National Security Agency leaks of Edward Snowden and makes 46...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7218-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7218_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:32:43">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/01/buffy-vs-edward-remix-is-back-online-but-no-fallout-for-lionsgate/</link><title>“Buffy vs Edward” remix is back online, but no fallout for Lionsgate</title><description>...Jonathan McIntosh's widely watched remix entitled "Buffy vs Edward" has been on YouTube for years, and in that time it racked up more than 3 million views and became a "poster boy" for why remixes needed to be protected from overreaching copyright law in the digital age.In October, his video was the object of a takedown from Lionsgate. McIntosh wrote about his saga earlie...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>