<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7219">honda insight</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:34:09" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7219-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7219_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:34:10">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/08/new-probe-to-provide-insight-into-mars-interior/</link><title>New probe to provide InSight into Mars' interior</title><description>...Mars is set to play host to another robot. The InSight (Interior Exploration using Seismic..., InSight is a stationary scientific platform, based largely on the highly successful Phoenix probe... better than our home world, revealing new insights into the formation and evolution of terrestrial...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7219-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7219_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:34:45">http://arstechnica.com/science/2008/11/further-insights-into-the-origins-of-cosmic-rays/</link><title>Further insights into the origins of cosmic rays</title><description>...) would be built somewhere high in the mountains of Mexico and would provide greater insights into high...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7219-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7219_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:37:20">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/12/online-buzz-key-to-creating-long-term-game-revenue/</link><title>Online buzz key to creating long-term game revenue</title><description>..., according to a new report from Wisconsin-based new media company Networked Insights, topping... that Networked Insights calls interactions. The interactions measurement is equivalent to buzz, or how much the gaming community is talking about and playing a given game. Source: Networked Insights...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7219-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7219_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:39:26">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/10/the-fifth-estate-come-for-the-cumberbatch-not-wikileaks-insight/</link><title>The Fifth Estate : Come for the Cumberbatch, not WikiLeaks insight</title><description>...If you like movies, The Fifth Estateis for you. The latest in a string of WikiLeaks-related films opens on October 18, and it has all the makings of classic, sugar-candy Hollywood: there's the top-line lead (Benedict Cumberbatch, who has played Khan, Sherlock,and nowAssange), some dramatic liberties with history in the name of drama (Russian spies pre-Manning, a dramatic border crossing that...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7219-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7219_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:41:12">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/04/angling-to-develop-for-google-glass-google-gives-some-insight/</link><title>Angling to develop for Google Glass? Google gives some insight</title><description>...If youre looking for a taste of what it will be like to develop for Google Glass, the company posted a video demonstrating the hardware and a little bit of the API on Thursday. Timothy Jordan, a senior developer advocate at Google, gave a talk at SXSW in early March that lasted just shy of an hour and gave a look into the platform.Google Glass bears more similarity to the Web than the Android mob...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7219-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7219_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:43:06">http://arstechnica.com/business/2010/03/five-insights-into-the-behaviors-of-social-media-users/</link><title>Five insights into the behaviors of social media users</title><description>...We do a decent amount of social media coverage here at Ars, but not everything that happens with Facebook, Twitter, and the like is worth its own story. Sometimes, though, we happen across things that make us say "huh, that's interesting." It turns out there are a lot of things we thought we knew about social media users, but not all of them are true. Here are a few tidbits we gath...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7219-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7219_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:44:41">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/12/verizon-seeks-customers-to-spam-with-mobile-marketing-forever/</link><title>Verizon seeks customers to spam with mobile marketing forever</title><description>...Verizon is starting to contact customers this week about allowing the telecom to sell their dataincluding location, browsing information, and mobile app usageto third-party marketers in exchange for coupons. The company promises one coupon up front, with the potential for e-mails, texts, snail mail, or mobile ads with more offers based on the data collected.The program is called Verizon Selects a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7219-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7219_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:46:14">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/03/researchers-trap-antihydrogen-for-insight-into-our-matter-dominated-universe/</link><title>Researchers trap antihydrogen for insight into our matter-dominated universe</title><description>...How different are matter and antimatter? This is a question that gets at the heart of modern particle physics and early-universe cosmology. The objects of everyday experience are made of ordinary matter. While some natural process produce limited amounts of antimatter, every known star and galaxy appears to be matter-based.If matter and antimatter are physical mirrors of each other, then an atom ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7219-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7219_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:47:31">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2014/02/ars-goes-to-the-chicago-auto-show/</link><title>Ars goes to the Chicago Auto Show</title><description>... 200 miles or so of range. Eric Bangeman A hybrid Honda Insight. Eric Bangeman A Honda Civic running... says this race car can hit 186mph. Eric Bangeman This No. 25 Snapple Honda will be driven by Marco Andretti in the 2014 IndyCar competition. Eric Bangeman Honda and Andretti Autosp...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7219-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7219_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:48:51">http://arstechnica.com/features/2012/10/my-car-is-becoming-smarter-than-me/</link><title>My car is smarter than me—and I get better gas mileage for it</title><description>.... We had to wait another two years for hybridization to reach this side of the Pacific though. Honda, not Toyota, was first with their highly aerodynamic Insight. You may even be surprised to find out we reviewed the Insight at Ars way back then. Its unfamiliar looks drew crowds and prompted Will Ryu...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>