<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7221">what is mittelschmerz</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:01:55" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7221-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7221_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:01:56">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/08/how-what-what-in-the-butt-made-fair-use-easier-to-claim/</link><title>How "What What (In the Butt)" unintentionally bolstered "fair use"</title><description>...Wisconsin, state of my birth, I salute you for turning out federal judges like J.P. Stadtmueller. Stadtmueller is the man who waded into the swampland of fair use, South Park, and "What What (In the Butt)" to deliver a July 6 order that may break new judicial territory by citing South Park episode "Osama bin Laden Has Farty Pants" in its footnotes. And Stadtmueller has the pro...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7221-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7221_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:03:14">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/06/christ-what-an-asshole-is-only-001-of-new-yorker-caption-contest-subs/</link><title>"Christ, what an asshole" is only .001% of New Yorker caption contest subs</title><description>..."Christ, what an asshole" seems a fitting caption for nearly every New Yorker cartoon, and yet it's only been submitted 27 times out of well over 1.5 million entries in the magazine's caption contest. We've found one place the Internet's trolls haven't managed to permeate.The "CWAA" revelation dates all the way back to February 2006, from a blog post b...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7221-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7221_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:04:58">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/09/noted-smut-rag-the-new-yorker-banned-from-facebook-for-obscene-cartoon/</link><title>Noted smut rag The New Yorker banned from Facebook for obscene cartoon</title><description>..., as it's one of many where the catchall caption "Christ, what an asshole" fits...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7221-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7221_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:06:07">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/09/will-the-wii-u-win-u-back-share-your-thoughts/</link><title>Will the Wii U win u back?</title><description>... asking you, Ars readers, what would it take to get you interested in purchasing the Wii U...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7221-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7221_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:07:35">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/08/ars-does-soylent-day-2-my-god-what-have-i-gotten-myself-into/</link><title>Ars does Soylent, Day 2: My God, what have I gotten myself into</title><description>...Day 1 recap: Like trench warfare in FranceI ended the previous entry saying that I was going to head out running, but that did not happen. As it got nearer to 7pm, I started feeling ominous rumblings in my bellythe kind that could either be the sign of some harmless gas or the harbinger of the poopocalypse. I stayed in, instead watching a couple of episodes of The Wire with my wife, who ate a fin...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7221-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7221_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:09:06">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/09/how-one-game-developer-is-making-the-pirate-bay-work-for-him/</link><title>How one game developer is making The Pirate Bay work for him</title><description>... whatever they want in return. Further, the pay-what-you-want sale is being actively promoted..., dozens of artists have been featured as part of The Promo Bay, which is what the site calls... to other pay-what-you-want download efforts like The Humble Indie Bundle, which quickly made...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7221-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7221_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:11:15">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/03/the-next-reason-to-put-down-the-pipe-pot-kills-gaming-skill/</link><title>The next reason to put down the pipe: pot kills gaming skill</title><description>...The use of marijuana has been linked to many terrible things in the media, including hitting small kids with your car when getting take out food. The government's newest argument for you to put down the joint? Getting high kills your video game skills."Getting high affects your brain in ways that may directly influence your gaming ability, many of the skills required for winning a backg...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7221-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7221_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:13:02">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2014/01/ces-2014-what-we-saw-what-we-loved-and-what-well-remember/</link><title>CES 2014: What we saw, what we loved, and what we’ll remember</title><description>... up with different opinions and takeaways from the show. Here's what each of the Ars CES crew got...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7221-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7221_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:14:04">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/03/playstation-move/</link><title>PlayStation Move: what we hate, what we love</title><description>... and demos, and they all looked uncomfortably similar to what we've already played on the Nintendo... by buttons in a square pattern. It can be tricky to figure out what buttons to hit by responding... it's clear that's what Sony has done. Nintendo of America's Reggie Fils-Aime...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7221-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7221_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:16:03">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/03/batteries-whats-here-versus-what-we-need/</link><title>Batteries: What’s here versus what we need</title><description>...We mostly think of batteries in terms of gadgets like phones and laptops. Although we'd all love lighter weight, higher capacity, and faster charging for our gadgets, progress for this type of battery hasfor the most partalready made huge strides. The modern battery is largely keeping pace with our needs.But two other big potential users of batteriesthe electric grid and automobileshaven&amp;apo...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>