<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7222">route 666</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:18:25" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7222-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7222_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:18:26">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/11/understanding-the-internets-insecure-routing-infrastructure/</link><title>Understanding the Internet's insecure routing infrastructure</title><description>...As an incident that we reported on last week shows, the Internet routing system isn't... into Internet routing. Routing is based on autonomous systems (ASes) exchanging prefixes (ranges of IP... or falsified information, and there are routing databases where ASes can register this information...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7222-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7222_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:19:34">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/11/666-chip-why-a-texas-student-thinks-her-school-id-is-the-mark-of-the-beast/</link><title>666 chip? Why a Texas student thinks her school ID is the “Mark of the Beast”</title><description>... more mysterious.666The number 666 has pervaded popular culture over the centuries. Sci-fi author Robert..., and there fell to reading, and then to supper, and to bed."But the 666 of Revelation is most likely... that 666 is a reference to the Roman Emperor Nero. Nern kaisar, Greek for Nero Caesar, adds...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7222-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7222_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:20:59">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/08/researchers-craft-algorithm-to-turn-mesh-networking-green/</link><title>Researchers craft algorithm to turn mesh networking green</title><description>... of individual users. Mesh networks currently require a routing algorithm to route traffic from a given...;s equipment. Currently, these routing algorithms tend to focus on two things: minimizing the number... capacity isn't being strained. To try to do better, they designed a mesh network and routing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7222-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7222_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:22:18">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/03/routing-light-with-a-single-atom/</link><title>Routing light with a single atom for quantum computing</title><description>... requires some method to route photons to different locations. This is not actually a huge problem, provided that the routing is not part of the computationwe define the paths through a computer or network... to implement a quantum "if" statement, which requires some form of dynamic routing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7222-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7222_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:24:02">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2011/06/e-mail-service-through-icloud-stops-when-5gb-limit-is-reached/</link><title>iCloud stops routing Apple e-mail when 5GB limit is reached</title><description>... to have? But because e-mail is being routed through the same virtual space that can only hold... for customers with a larger, more active setup of devices. Another possible solution would be to route...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7222-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7222_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:25:22">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/11/amd-avoiding-larrabee-route-on-road-to-cpugpu-fusion/</link><title>AMD avoiding Larrabee route on road to CPU/GPU "Fusion"</title><description>... the Larrabee route, and replace the GPU with a pool of small x86 cores. Obviously, you have to expose... the Larrabee route (i.e., multiple small, independent, x86 cores with lots of vector hardware...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7222-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7222_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:26:23">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/10/cogent-picks-peering-fight-with-zombie-sprint/</link><title>Cogent picks peering fight with "zombie" Sprint</title><description>...As of thursday afternoon, customers of Cogent Communications are no longer able to reach Sprint customersand the other way around. The reason: Sprint severed its connection with Cogent. Cogent is a large, but not huge, wholesale Internet Service Provider that connects large web destinations, business, government agencies, and universities to the Internet. Sprint is also in this business, and also...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7222-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7222_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:27:09">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/01/understanding-bufferbloat-and-the-network-buffer-arms-race/</link><title>Understanding bufferbloat and the network buffer arms race</title><description>...If a little salt makes food taste better, then a lot must make it taste great, right? This logic is often applied in the digital domain, too. (My pet peeve is that TV shows and DVDs keep getting darker and darker.) In a similar vein, networks used to buffer a little data, but these buffers have been getting larger and larger and are now getting so big they are actually reducing performance. Long-...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7222-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7222_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:29:08">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/02/the-route-to-a-kindle-owners-heart-goes-through-the-wallet/</link><title>The route to a Kindle owner's heart goes through the wallet</title><description>...A customer satisfaction survey of Kindle Fire owners shows that while the vast majority are satisfied with their purchase, it is mainly the low price fueling their happiness. ChangeWave Research asked a sample of new Kindle Fire owners how they were enjoying their device so far; slightly more than half reported being "very satisfied," and 59 percent said the $199 price of the Kindle Fir...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7222-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7222_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:29:49">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/07/plants-vs-zombies-en-route-to-more-systems/</link><title>Plants vs. Zombies en route to more systems</title><description>...Plants vs. Zombies is still taking up way too much of our time around the Ars Technica offices, so the news that the game is making its way to other platforms is somewhat bittersweet. Yes, it's good to share the love, but do we really want more ways to play it? Probably not. Let's take a look at what PopCap's PR guy extraordinaire said to Kombo.com."I don't know the exact...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>