<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7230">council bluffs</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:55:26" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7230-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7230_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:55:27">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/02/kansas-google-fiber-you-want-ip-video-with-that/</link><title>Is Google planning to offer IP video to Kansas City?</title><description>...Does Google want to provide some kind of IP video service for the people of Kansas City, Kansas and Kansas City, Missouri? We've heard the rumors. Here's another hint that they may be true after all: the Federal Communications Commission has received and reviewed an application from Google Fiber for a fixed satellite, receive-only earth station to be located in Council Bluffs, Iowaabout...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7230-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7230_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:56:18">http://arstechnica.com/security/2014/02/security-certification-group-ec-councils-website-defaced-with-snowden-passport/</link><title>Security certification group EC-Council’s website defaced with Snowden passport</title><description>...Enlarge / A screencap of the defaced EC-Council page. The website for EC-Council, an International Council of E-Commerce Consultants, was defacedon Sunday evening. The hacker, who went by Eugene... of breaking into the site.Eugene Belford wrote on the EC-Council homepage, Defaced again? Yep, good job...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7230-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7230_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:56:50">http://arstechnica.com/business/2010/10/whistleblower-says-parents-television-council-is-beyond-repair/</link><title>Whistleblower: Parents Television Council is "beyond repair"</title><description>...The Parents Television Council was not pleased with our update on the decency group's financial decline and internal troubles. "Dear @ MatthewLasar - pretty lousy piece you wrote about the PTC," the organization's public relations guy Dan Isett tweeted me. Sorry, but it summarized a New York Times exposthat was, well, kind of worrisome. But apparently not disturbing enough for...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7230-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7230_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:58:05">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/10/oracle-wants-libreoffice-members-to-leave-ooo-council/</link><title>Oracle wants LibreOffice members to leave OOo council</title><description>... an OOo community council meeting last week, council chair Louis Saurez-Potts told the TDF members who also sit on the OOo community council that their participation in both organizations constituted...; he told TDF members during a council meeting that took place on an IRC channel. "If the TDF...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7230-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7230_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:59:37">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/11/norwegian-market-council-case-against-apple-progressing/</link><title>Norwegian Market Council case against Apple progressing</title><description>... and its legality under Norwegian law. Formal proceedings against Apple by the Norwegian Market Council... will continue to the Market Council unless Steve Jobs has a complete change of heart or the company decides..., to be followed by a trial in the spring or early summer of 2009. If the matter progresses and the Council...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7230-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7230_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:01:44">http://arstechnica.com/business/2010/11/ptc-broadcast-profanity-on-tv-out-of-control/</link><title>PTC: bleeped broadcast expletives on the rise</title><description>...The Parents Television Council has released a new report claiming that foul talk of every shape, size, and odor is all but taking over broadcast television. "These huge increases in harsh profanity should come as no surprise, given the Second Circuit Court's ruling last Julya ruling...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7230-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7230_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:02:34">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/01/wanted-better-fcc-indecency-complaint-statistics/</link><title>Wanted: Better FCC indecency complaint stats</title><description>... the Parents Television Council. Its time for the FCC to more fully disclose the nature of these complaints...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7230-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7230_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:04:32">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/11/presidents-tech-council-plays-sad-trombone-for-federal-cyber-security/</link><title>President’s tech council plays sad trombone for federal cybersecurity</title><description>...The President's Council of Advisors on Science and Technology (PCAST) released a report... attack, the council advised, the government "needs to lead by example and accelerate its efforts... of Windows, Linux, and MacOS. The council also recommended adoption across government offices...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7230-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7230_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:06:02">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/12/dc-city-council-passes-law-legitimizing-uber-car-service/</link><title>DC City Council passes law legitimizing Uber car service</title><description>...Uber, the smartphone-based car service that has been shaking up taxicab and limosine markets around the country, scored a big victory on Tuesday as the DC City Council passed legislation that officially recognizes "digital dispatch" car services. The new law comes just months after Uber...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7230-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7230_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:08:07">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/12/us-national-research-council-wants-abrupt-climate-change-warning-system/</link><title>US National Research Council wants abrupt climate change warning system</title><description>...Yesterday, the National Research Council (a branch of the US' National Academies of Science) released a report in which it called for the creation of an early warning system that would let us know when we're approaching tipping points in the climate.While talk of climate tipping points...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>