<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7234">347 ford engines</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:51:53" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7234-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7234_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:51:54">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2014/02/ford-exec-no-deal-with-blackberry-for-next-sync-yet/</link><title>Ford exec: No deal with BlackBerry for next Sync yet</title><description>...Earlier this week, Bloomberg reported that Ford had ousted Microsoft as its platform provider... Pim van der Jagt, managing director of the Ford Research Center in Aachen, Germany.Van der Jagt said that while Ford was not married with Microsoft, the automaker is still evaluating its needs...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7234-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7234_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:53:35">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2014/02/ford-drops-microsoft-will-use-blackberrys-realtime-os-for-next-sync/</link><title>Ford drops Microsoft, will use BlackBerry’s real-time OS for next Sync</title><description>...Ford Motor Company has done a lot over the last few years to turn its Sync in-car infotainment... engine for its next release, dropping Microsoft as its embedded operating system partner in favor of BlackBerry.Bloomberg News reports that Ford will switch to BlackBerrys QNX Neutrino real-time...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7234-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7234_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:55:28">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/05/ford-breaks-1-million-mark-for-vehicles-with-microsoft-sync/</link><title>Ford breaks 1 million mark for vehicles with Microsoft Sync</title><description>...Ford recently noticed that it was about to sell the 1 millionth vehicle with Microsoft Sync... as a present. Microsoft CEO Steve Ballmer's father is a 30-year Ford veteran, so the decision... was casually tipped off. As pictured above, Ford CEO Alan Mulally took the opportunity to hand...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7234-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7234_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:56:53">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/08/fords-plug-in-hybrids-will-talk-to-electrical-grid/</link><title>Ford's plug-in hybrids will talk to electrical grid</title><description>... technologies, and Ford is not about to be left behind. On Tuesday, it announced the development of a control... a touchscreen in the car's dashboard, and works with other Ford technologies like SYNC, SmartGauge with EcoGuide, and Ford Work Solutions. Integral to the success of this system is the cooperation...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7234-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7234_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:59:13">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/01/ford-applink-opens-floodgates-to-in-car-ios-android-and-blackberry-apps/</link><title>Ford AppLink opens floodgates to in-car iOS, Android, and BlackBerry apps</title><description>...;s John Eliss, global technologist for connected services. Ford has been leading the way in networking its cars and encouraging app developers to give Ford vehicles an edge in the increasingly technology... connectivity found in Ford dashboards. With the free SDK kits available, they're the first...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7234-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7234_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:00:17">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/03/an-old-hope-lucas-says-hamill-fisher-and-ford-set-for-star-wars-vii/</link><title>An Old Hope: Lucas says Hamill, Fisher, and Ford set for Star Wars VII</title><description>..., and Harrison "Han Solo" Ford appear set to reprise their roles in the upcomingJJ Abrams..., Hamill will be 62 in September, and Ford is already in his 70s. All three stars have kept active... in many Batman-related projects, and Ford is currently filming the upcoming Ender's Game movie...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7234-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7234_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:01:51">http://arstechnica.com/features/2012/10/more-bang-less-buck-how-car-engines-now-go-further-on-less/</link><title>More bang, less buck: How car engine tech does more with less</title><description>... would have a volumetric efficiency of 100 percent. In practice, most engines have a much lower figure.The Ford F-150 EcoBoost engine being put through a torture test. Ford Motor CompanyCar engines have to operate under... to the new EcoBoost engines, especiall...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7234-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7234_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:03:46">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/04/feasibility-of-nanosensors-for-monitoring-infrastructure/</link><title>Monitoring infrastructure with embedded nanosensors</title><description>...All engineering productschemical plants, bridges, buildings, oil rigs, you name itcome with some sort of fixed lifetime. It may be very long, but no (reasonable) engineer expects their designs to last forever. Tracking how well a structure is holding up relative to its design lifetime, however...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7234-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7234_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:05:28">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/11/what-the-ruckthe-physics-of-a-bump-in-a-rug/</link><title>What the ruck?—The physics of a bump in a rug</title><description>...One of the things that drew me to science and engineering when I was younger was a desire...;s really tough.)Engineering often goes further, using idealized systems, but modifying or mixing them..., engineers need to know what level of accuracy and exactness is neededor whether a correlation read off...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7234-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7234_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:06:28">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/04/exclusive-a-behind-the-scenes-look-at-facebook-release-engineering/</link><title>Exclusive: a behind-the-scenes look at Facebook release engineering</title><description>... to second largest website in the world. But few know the equally intriguing story about the engine... as the company's release engineers rolled out the new "timeline" feature for brand.... During my two days at Facebook, I learned about the important role that release engineering...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>