<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7235">silicone roof coatings</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:07:16" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7235-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7235_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:07:17">http://arstechnica.com/science/2008/10/smart-coating-releases-inhibitor-on-demand-to-stop-corrosion/</link><title>Smart coating releases inhibitor on-demand to stop corrosion</title><description>..., and cured) was used to form a passive barrier coating containing silicon and zirconium oxides and resin... against, inspecting for, and repairing corrosion is immense. As such, the corrosion resistant coatings industry, which includes everything from simple spray paint to complex and durable coatings...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7235-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7235_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:08:12">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/08/girl-gaming-company/</link><title>Silicon Sisters: gamer women for women gamers</title><description>...Are women getting what they want from video games? Although they are playing games in large numbers, few companies are trying to appeal to women, and most of those that do merely release pink controllers or stereotypically "girlie" games. Silicon Sisters wants to help change that, with the first "female owned and operated video game company," operating out of Vancouver.We got...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7235-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7235_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:09:46">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/06/graphene-meets-silicon-with-conventional-fab-techniques/</link><title>Graphene meets silicon with conventional fab techniques</title><description>... reminiscent of chicken wire, has some unusual properties, one of which may allow it to replace silicon... mobilitythe speed at which electrons move through the material is over 100 times greater than silicon. However...;s Science demonstrates graphene integrated circuitry printed on silicon wafers. The authors...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7235-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7235_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:11:57">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/09/thanks-to-budget-cuts-silicon-valley-patent-office-wont-open/</link><title>Budget cuts mean Silicon Valley patent office won’t open anytime soon</title><description>... will be that agency's plan to open an office in Silicon Valley in the near future, according to a Sunday report by The Associated Press. The Silicon Valley office was an idea that has been suggested for years... has no permanent site selected. In the long term, a full satellite office is still planned for the Silicon...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7235-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7235_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:13:27">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/03/moving-beyond-silicon-to-break-the-megahertz-barrier/</link><title>Moving beyond silicon to break the MegaHertz barrier</title><description>...We're rapidly closing in on a decade since the first desktop processors cleared the 3GHz mark, but in a stunning break from earlier progress, the clock speed of the top processors has stayed roughly in the same neighborhood since. Meanwhile, the feature shrinks that have at least added additional processing cores to the hardware are edging up to the limits of photolithography technology. Wit...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7235-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7235_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:14:18">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/09/silicon-circuits-that-dissolve-when-wet-made-for-smart-medical-implants/</link><title>Silicon circuits that dissolve when wet made for smart medical implants</title><description>...New silicon-containing circuits dissolve when wet. Dissolvable electronic devices might be useful..., for example. Silicon-based circuits in the device will stay in the body indefinitely.Scientists have built... semiconductors dont carry charge as well as their silicon counterparts. While its possible to build...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7235-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7235_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:15:23">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2010/07/the-future-of-electronics-is-frickin-hybrid-silicon-lasers/</link><title>Intel: the future of electronics is a hybrid silicon "laser device"</title><description>... with light by creating a stable, 50Gbps link between two devices using fiber optics. Dubbed "silicon... Barbara to develop hybrid silicon lasers. Using a unique process to bond indium phosphide to silicon along with carefully etched gratings in formed silicon waveguides, designers are able to create...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7235-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7235_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:17:06">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/05/epic-awarded-nearly-4-5-million-in-silicon-knights-lawsuit/</link><title>Epic awarded nearly $4.5 million in Silicon Knights lawsuit</title><description>... Silicon Knights for over five years has finally been resolved, with Epic winning $4.45 million... Silicon Knights had "breached the license agreement, misappropriated Epic's trade secrets, and infringed Epic's copyrights in the Unreal Engine 3 code."Silicon Knights first filed suit...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7235-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7235_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:19:00">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/01/amd-intel-nvidia-our-silicon-will-power-future-smart-tvs/</link><title>AMD, Intel, NVIDIA: our silicon will power future "smart" TVs</title><description>... of the TV silicon will ramp up very quickly," Koehnders told Ars. "We aren't sure what...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7235-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7235_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:19:52">http://arstechnica.com/science/2008/11/watch-out-for-seal-coated-parking-lots/</link><title>Watch out for sealant-coated parking lots</title><description>...Sealants used to coat parking lots to prevent cracking could be a serious environmental and health concern. Back in 2005, scientists first noticed that seal-coated parking lots in Austin, Texas... than those in lots that werent coated. Many compounds in the mixture of PAHs are known...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>