<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7241">flight simulators</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:19:11" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7241-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7241_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:19:12">http://arstechnica.com/security/2009/05/hackers-crack-flight-sim-community-site-ruin-it-for-everyone/</link><title>Hackers crack flight sim community site, ruin it for everyone</title><description>...A website for flight simulator enthusiasts, originally launched in 1996, has been essentially "destroyed" by the shenanigans of hackers. Avsim had become an important resource for flight sim users over the last 13 years, but the site has been completely shut downafter hackers essentially...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7241-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7241_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:21:00">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/07/microsoft-halts-further-development-on-free-to-play-flight/</link><title>Microsoft halts further development on free-to-play Flight</title><description>...The first free-to-play entry in Microsoft's venerable Flight Simulator franchise is reaching an ignominious end just a few months after its initial release. Microsoft has announced that it is halting further development on Microsoft Flight and reassigning some staff members at the Vancouver studio that developed it.Flight, which launched in February, will continue to be available as a free d...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7241-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7241_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:22:00">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/03/goat-simulator-preview-goat-of-the-year/</link><title>Goat Simulator preview: Goat of the year</title><description>... animal gaming genre: Goat Simulator. (No relation to the recently announced Bear Simulator... Goat Simulator, hyperbole is much of the point. The game began as a tech-demo lark to poke fun at the rising trend of weirdly serious Simulator games, including Euro Truck Simulator and Agr...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7241-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7241_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:22:57">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/01/report-massive-cuts-at-microsoft-flight-sim-studio/</link><title>Report: Massive cuts at Microsoft Flight Sim studio</title><description>... behind Microsoft Flight Simulator, has reportedly seen some very large-scale layoffs, which may even include the entire Flight Sim team. The franchise is one of the longest running game series in existence, with the first game, Flight Simulator 1.0, released in 1982 and the most rec...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7241-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7241_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:24:06">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/09/il-2-sturmovik-ww2-history-and-gaming-ftw/</link><title>IL-2 Sturmovik : WW2 realism and gaming FTW</title><description>...When it comes to WW2 flight simulators, the IL-2 Sturmovick franchise has managed to win some serious respect since it launched in 2001, earning a reputation for solid action with a high degree of realism. Up until now, though, the games has been only available on PC; IL-2 Sturmovik: Birds of Prey marks the first time an entry in the series has been available for consoles. Thankfully, the foray o...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7241-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7241_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:25:12">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/09/google-brings-flight-search-into-the-jet-age/</link><title>Google brings flight search into the Jet Age</title><description>...Google debuted its long awaited flight search Tuesday, achieving Concorde-like speed in returning... ITA Software for $700 million in April, can be found directly at Google.com/flights, or in its usual results when a user types in a query such as flights from lax to atl.Googles purchase of ITA...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7241-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7241_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:25:54">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/08/age-of-empires-microsoft-flight-are-back-with-trailers/</link><title>Age of Empires , Microsoft Flight return, with trailers</title><description>...Microsoft is showing a newfound enthusiasm for its Games for Windows brand, and has announced the return of two major franchises: Age of Empires and Microsoft Flight Simulator. Of course, the "Simulator" bit has been removed, so now it's just Flight. Let's take a look at the trailers, and discuss what little we know about these games.Does anyone else get a Battlefield Heroes v...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7241-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7241_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:27:12">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/04/simulating-materials-using-a-quantum-computer-made-of-cold-atoms/</link><title>An analog quantum computer made of cold atoms used to simulate electrons' spins</title><description>... be by using another quantum system. A promising new experiment demonstrates the simulation of hundreds of spins, using atoms as the simulation device.In a crystal lattice, electron spins may interact... more than 30 atoms, but it won't be practical to simulate thousands of atoms...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7241-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7241_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:28:42">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/04/ea-rolling-out-major-simcity-simulation-changes-today/</link><title>EA rolling out major SimCity simulation changes today</title><description>... of the game's simulation. EA is making an effort to address some of those simulation problems... options.But many of the most important fixes tweak the way the underlying game simulation works. Among...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7241-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7241_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:30:03">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/03/spacexs-reusable-rocket-completes-short-controlled-flight/</link><title>SpaceX’s reusable rocket completes short, controlled flight</title><description>.... The Grasshopper test platform completed its flight last Thursday, a step towards the company's plan... seconds, and then began its descent back to Earth. This is Grasshoppers fourth such flight (ithas... none are currently in use by any space program.SpaceX's Grasshopper: fourth flight set to music...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>