<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7242">hague convention</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:31:27" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7242-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7242_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:31:28">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/01/sizable-leipzig-game-convention-canned-for-2009/</link><title>Sizable Leipzig Game Convention canned for 2009</title><description>... Game Convention seemed to be one of the only main industry-run shows that has enjoyed stability. The sizable European convention has been growing steadily over the years and has had great support... that the 2009 Games Convention has been canceled. This announcement follows a banner year for the convention...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7242-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7242_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:32:35">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/11/rare-to-change-the-conventional-thinking-of-gaming/</link><title>Rare to "change the conventional thinking" of gaming</title><description>... doing, as it has vowed to change the conventional thinking of games and entertainment. Mark... to change conventional thinking of games and entertainment, Betteridge continued. I dont see us fighting...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7242-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7242_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:34:13">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/06/graphene-meets-silicon-with-conventional-fab-techniques/</link><title>Graphene meets silicon with conventional fab techniques</title><description>... direction). This is a desirable property, as conventional semiconductor-based devices typically show severe... is the method used to integrate the graphene FET into a circuit using conventional fabrication techniques...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7242-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7242_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:36:23">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2014/01/trustycon-security-counter-convention-planned-for-rsa-refusniks/</link><title>“TrustyCon” security counter-convention planned for RSA refusniks</title><description>... from the Moscone Convention Center. To add fuel to this dissenting fire, TrustyCon has already picked...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7242-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7242_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:36:51">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/07/half-minute-hero-arrives-on-xbla/</link><title>Half-Minute Hero on XBLA perverts RPG conventions</title><description>..., and the game takes any opportunity it can to poke fun at Japanese RPG conventions, such as fetch quests...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7242-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7242_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:37:49">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2011/08/apple-hoping-dutch-court-will-give-samsung-major-eu-wide-smackdown/</link><title>Apple hoping Dutch court will give Samsung major EU-wide smackdown</title><description>... is an important one, as an injunction from The Hague district court could stop Samsung's smartphones...; patent.Apple is asking The Hague for a strict EU-wide ban on manufacturing, stocking, importing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7242-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7242_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:39:36">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/08/gaymercon-wants-to-provide-a-safe-place-for-lgbtq-gamers/</link><title>GaymerCon wants to provide a "safe place" for LGBTQ gamers</title><description>... and tech convention with a focus on LGBT geek culture" is set to take place next August in San... important for us to feel everyone has a space at this convention." She added that she hopes women..., there will be protestors outside our convention, there will be people who picket us, throw things at us, say...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7242-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7242_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:40:22">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/05/bears-beets-battlestar-galactica-ars-visits-comicpalooza-2013/</link><title>Bears, beets, Battlestar Galactica : Ars visits Comicpalooza 2013</title><description>...We spent most of Saturday morning and afternoon at Comicpalooza 2013 at the George R. Brown convention center in Houston. Of particular interest to us this year was the fact that Comicpalooza was sharing floor space with Galacticon III; if there's one bunch of folks that this author...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7242-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7242_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:41:31">http://arstechnica.com/business/2010/09/monsters-defies-sci-fi-horror-conventions-to-tell-invasion-story/</link><title>Monsters defies sci-fi, horror conventions to tell invasion story</title><description>... is a science fiction movie with a little bit of horror, but the conventions of the genres...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7242-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7242_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:42:22">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/08/pictures-of-nvidia-tegra-tab-point-to-more-conventional-tegra-4-tablet/</link><title>Pictures of Nvidia “Tegra Tab” point to more conventional Tegra 4 tablet</title><description>...Especially in the last year, Nvidia has displayed a desire to augment its traditional chipmaking efforts with hardware of its own. This desire has surfaced in the form of server products like the Nvidia Gridand in gadgets like the oft-delayed, price-cut Shield gaming tablet. Leaked images of yet another piece of Nvidia hardware suggest that the company's next hardware effort may be something...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>