<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7249">largest alligator on record</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:52:36" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7249-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7249_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:52:38">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/03/gta-iv-records-most-money-largest-cast-biggest-budget/</link><title>GTA IV records: fast cash, biggest budget, largest cast</title><description>...Last year's Grand Theft Auto IV was a big game. You knew that. But what you might not know is that developer Rockstar spent and made faster cash on it than anything else, according to Guinness World Records. In addition to being the "most controversial" video game, Rockstar burned a record $100 million on GTA IV, "smashing the previous production record of $70 million set by S...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7249-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7249_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:53:12">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/03/majority-of-doctors-opposed-to-full-access-to-your-own-electronic-records/</link><title>Majority of doctors opposed to full access to your own electronic records</title><description>... records, you might think doctors and other caregivers would embrace transparency for patients... believe that patients should have full access to their own medical records via electronic means... to patients. So, despite the fact that we have rights to review and amend our records, doctors dont want...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7249-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7249_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:54:18">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/03/55-hours-81m-points-and-the-fall-of-missile-commands-30-year-old-record/</link><title>56 hours, 81m points, and the fall of Missile Command ’s 30-year-old-record</title><description>..., a challenger rose up and dethroned the 30-year-old record live on Twitch.tv. Victor Sandberg, aka Twitch user... play and his previous attempts at the record. Before this most recent event, Sandberg's best... than tournament settings forMissile Command, as the two records are kept separately. (Tournament...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7249-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7249_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:55:52">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2008/11/all-cell-records-are-equal-but-some-are-more-equal-than-others/</link><title>All cell records are equal, but some are more equal than others</title><description>... records for one of Barack Obamas cell phone accounts. Commenter Big Pink Bunny wondered: Would there be such a fuss if these people accessed Johnny D from Tuscaloosas records? Which is the right... the security breach here actually violated any criminal statutes (assuming the records werent passed...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7249-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7249_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:57:53">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/12/att-accused-of-violating-privacy-law-with-sale-of-phone-records-to-cia/</link><title>ATandT accused of violating privacy law with sale of phone records to CIA</title><description>... violated a privacy rule in the Communications Act by selling phone records to the Central Intelligence Agency (CIA).A report last month said that "ATT has turned over international calling records... against government collection of calling records. Previously, privacy advocates have tried to shut...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7249-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7249_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:59:57">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/06/analysis-right-to-record-cops-extends-to-private-settings/</link><title>Analysis: you can record cops, even in private</title><description>...In the past year, two different appeals courts have ruled that recording the actions of police... that the right to record the actions of law enforcement is also protected by the Constitution's due process... to two ways that a right to record interactions with law enforcement officials is implicated...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7249-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7249_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:00:30">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/01/2012-childs-play-drive-ends-with-record-of-over-28700-in-donations/</link><title>2012 Child's Play drive ends with record of over $28,700 in donations</title><description>... that I might come up embarrassingly short of last year's record $26,000 charity haul. Luckily...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7249-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7249_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:02:07">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2008/10/microsoft-healthvault-scores-with-aetna-e-records-pact/</link><title>Microsoft HealthVault scores with Aetna e-records pact</title><description>...Microsoft is working hard to spur the adoption of its personal health record platform, HealthVault..., its online health record platform, and this partnership is bound to help drive that. Portability of medical records is important; if you move from one doctor to another, youd like to hope that all of your...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7249-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7249_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:03:14">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/11/scotus-leaves-in-place-ruling-that-protects-right-to-record-police/</link><title>SCOTUS leaves in place ruling that protects right to record police</title><description>... ruling that the First Amendment protects a right to record the actions of police officers... ruled in May that "the act of making an audio or audiovisual recording is necessarily included... to disseminate the resulting recording." But Judge Richard Posner dissented. During oral arguments...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7249-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7249_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:03:57">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/04/state-privacy-laws-may-undercut-electronic-medical-records/</link><title>State privacy laws may undercut electronic medical records</title><description>...The US government has now adopted a policy of fostering the adoption of electronic medical records... standards for the security of those records. These two goalsprivacy and security of these records... offered the records of 200,000 patients for sale on Craigslist, while hospitals have seen their own...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>