<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7250">collagen vascular disease</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:04:51" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7250-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7250_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:04:52">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/12/diseases-thrive-where-biodiversity-is-low/</link><title>Diseases thrive where biodiversity is low</title><description>... disease transmission among the species left? The answeras it nearly always is to complex scientific... established diseases, transmission rates in communities depend heavily on the level of species richness...-end" hosts that wont (or cant) transmit the disease. Additionally, since there is more heterospecific...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7250-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7250_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:06:39">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/03/crowdsourcing-the-cloud-to-find-cures-for-rare-and-orphaned-diseases/</link><title>Crowdsourcing the cloud to find cures for rare and “orphaned” diseases</title><description>..., called SETI@Home, has inspireda nonprofit to find treatments for diseases that pharmaceutical companies... cures for diseases such as AIDS (with the Scripps Research Institute's FightAIDS@Home project..., (such as a virus or mutated enzyme) associated with a disease and a candidate drug molecule. These...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7250-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7250_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:07:20">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/07/mutation-limits-alzheimers-disease-other-cognitive-decline/</link><title>Mutation limits Alzheimer's disease, other cognitive decline</title><description>...Most people who live long enough undergo a gradual decline in their mental abilities. For those who suffer from Alzheimer's disease, however, the decline is radical; in some genetic forms of the disease, it can even strike middle-aged victims. This has led many to conclude that Alzheimer's pathology is distinct from that of age-related decline. But a new study has found a single mutatio...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7250-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7250_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:09:26">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/07/two-successful-gene-therapy-trials-block-inherited-diseases-in-humans/</link><title>Two successful gene therapy trials block inherited diseases in humans</title><description>... they inherited from their parents. But more serious genetic flaws can cause debilitating disease. Now, Italian researchers have come up with a way of treating one such inherited disease and reversing another... inherited disease that affects around 1 in 40,000 people.Engineered stem cellsMLD usually manifests...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7250-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7250_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:10:44">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/03/weird-science-venereal-diseases-picky-about-circumcision/</link><title>Weird science: venereal diseases picky about circumcision</title><description>... a bit challenging when the species is nearly as old as writing. Not all venereal diseases care whether...-up process, the authors screened for a variety of additional sexually transmitted diseases. It turns...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7250-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7250_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:12:27">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/06/protein-from-sushi-snack-may-help-detect-liver-diseases/</link><title>Protein from sushi snack may help detect liver diseases</title><description>.... Levels of bilirubin have been used for decades to assess liver health and diagnose diseases...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7250-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7250_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:13:22">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/07/linus-torvalds-microsoft-hatred-is-a-disease/</link><title>Linus Torvalds: "Microsoft hatred is a disease"</title><description>... is a disease. I believe in open development, and that very much involves not just making the source open...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7250-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7250_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:14:44">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/04/using-nonobvious-organisms-to-study-human-genetic-diseases/</link><title>Using nonobvious organisms to study human genetic diseases</title><description>... to follow development. A new method of choosing suitable models for human disease based... phenologs, the researchers first clustered all the genes implicated in a human disease. They then culled... chance. Even if a phenotype seems completely unrelated to a disease, the fact that they're...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7250-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7250_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:15:41">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/06/for-some-amphibians-habitat-loss-can-save-lives/</link><title>For wide-ranging amphibians, habitat loss can limit disease</title><description>... the spread of a deadly disease in some amphibians. Chytridiomycosis, a disease caused by the fungus..., and has caused the extinctions of about 200 frog species. To examine the relationship between this disease... for higher disease transmission rates between species; infections may not spread as quickly...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7250-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7250_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:16:24">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/02/malaria-deaths-drop-but-disease-may-be-more-lethal-than-we-thought/</link><title>Malaria deaths drop, but disease may be more lethal than we thought</title><description>...The success of efforts that target polio have raised hopes that it could be the next human disease to be eradicated within the decade. But that's not the only disease that public health... on the disease, as all estimates of deaths due to malaria indicate it has been going down since about 2005...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>