<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7258">swahili dishes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:34:13" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7258-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7258_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:34:16">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/09/dish-network-told-to-fork-over-another-200-million-to-tivo/</link><title>DISH Network told to fork over another $200 million to TiVo</title><description>...If it feels like the DISH vs. TiVo patent infringement case has been going on for ages, that's because it hasat least in relation to the Internet's attention span. DISH has already been hit.... The judge in the case found that DISH was in contempt of court for refusing to abide by a permanent...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7258-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7258_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:35:45">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/04/dish-bids-25-5-billion-for-sprint-nextel/</link><title>Dish bids $25.5 billion for Sprint-Nextel</title><description>...If nothing else, Dishs billionaire chairman, Charlie Ergen, is tenacious.On Monday, the satellite... Softbank.In January 2013, Dish made an unsolicited offer to acquire the struggling Clearwire... to Sprint. So Dish instead decided to go whole hog and make an unsolicited bid for Sprint."The Dish...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7258-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7258_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:36:42">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/12/dish-may-outbid-sprint-for-t-mobile-become-fourth-major-carrier/</link><title>Dish may outbid Sprint for T-Mobile, become fourth major carrier</title><description>...Days after Sprint was revealed to be considering a purchase of T-Mobile US, satellite provider Dish... the Department of Justice and the Federal Communications Commission. A Dish purchase of T-Mobile... to the matter.""Dish Network Corp, which lost out to Japanese telecoms giant Softbank...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7258-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7258_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:37:30">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/11/judge-denies-foxs-request-to-stop-dishs-commercial-skipping-service/</link><title>Judge denies Fox's request to stop Dish's commercial-skipping service</title><description>...A federal judge refused to issue a preliminary injunction in a case pitting the Dish satellite... argues that Dish has a "clear goal of violating copyrights and destroying the fundamental...;s request for a preliminary injunction. That means Dish will be allowed to continue marketing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7258-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7258_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:39:11">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/05/desperate-to-become-a-wireless-broadband-player-dish-ups-bid-for-clearwire/</link><title>Desperate to become a wireless broadband player, Dish ups bid for Clearwire</title><description>...Folks, were in a good old-fashioned bidding war! Dish has now upped its own bid for Clearwire... higher than Dishs own previous offer of $3.30. Both companies are after Clearwires significant spectrum holdings. Dishs new bid, at present valuation, is worth around $6.5 billion.As weve noted previously...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7258-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7258_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:41:03">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/12/decision-on-possible-new-lte-network-from-dish-coming-soon-fcc-says/</link><title>Decision on possible new LTE network from Dish coming soon, FCC says</title><description>...Those that follow play-by-play coverage of spectrum sales may know that Dish owns a prime chunk... in New York, Verizons CEO Lowell McAdam said that Dishs holdings were too small potatoes...; McAdam told the conference on Tuesday, as quoted by Reuters.Earlier this week, Dish announced...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7258-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7258_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:41:55">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/12/dish-gets-fcc-approval-to-build-next-generation-lte-network/</link><title>Dish gets FCC approval to build next-generation LTE network</title><description>...Dish Network has gotten approval from the Federal Communications Commission to build a cellular network on spectrum previously allocated to satellite services. Dish has said it plans to build an LTE... noted that Dish "could have built a mobile network without the FCC rule changes. But those handsets...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7258-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7258_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:42:32">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/01/out-of-nowhere-dish-makes-offer-to-fully-acquire-clearwire/</link><title>Out of nowhere, Dish makes offer to fully acquire Clearwire</title><description>... the two telcos who have been partners for years.Now though, Dish has made an unsolicited offer... at approximately $4.8 billion.The Dish Proposal is only a preliminary indication of interest and is subject... arrangements being requested by DISH (some of which, as currently proposed, may not be permitted...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7258-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7258_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:43:31">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/02/fox-blasts-newest-dish-hopper-in-court-wants-it-off-the-market/</link><title>Fox blasts newest Dish Hopper in court, wants it off the market</title><description>...The ad-skipping technology featured in the Dish Hopper DVR has won accolades and also inspired... right away, but was denied; now the issue is up on appeal.At the CES convention this year, Dish unveiled its next-generation Dish Hopper with Sling. The device allows users to move content they've...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7258-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7258_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:45:05">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2008/10/out-of-options-dish-finally-pays-tivo-104-million-judgment/</link><title>Out of options, DISH finally pays TiVo $104 million judgment</title><description>...DISH Network parent EchoStar has announced that it plans to pay $104 million to TiVo as part of a long-running legal dispute. DISH and EchoStar have reassured customers, however, that their DVRs... lawsuit against EchoStar in 2006, in which TiVo alleged that DISH infringed upon proprietary TiVo...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>