<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7259">radish root</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:45:41" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7259-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7259_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:45:42">http://arstechnica.com/security/2010/07/dns-root-zone-finally-signed-but-security-battle-not-over/</link><title>DNS root zone finally signed, but security battle not over</title><description>...Yesterday, the DNS root zone was signed. This is an important step in the deployment of DNSSEC..., looking up www.arstechnica.com means talking to a nameserver that knows about the "root," then... TLDs because the root wasn't signed. To get around this limitation, people experimenting...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7259-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7259_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:46:30">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/03/future-versions-of-cyanogenmod-wont-enable-root-by-default/</link><title>Future versions of CyanogenMod won't enable root by default</title><description>... superuser privilege level. Although rooting opens up sophisticated capabilities that wouldn't... comfortable enabling root access by default in their ROM. Future versions of CyanogenMod, starting with version 9, will not enable root by default. It will still be available as an option for users...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7259-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7259_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:47:19">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/03/china-censorship-leaks-outside-great-firewall-via-root-server/</link><title>China censorship leaks outside Great Firewall via root server</title><description>...On Wednesday, someone from the Chilean domain registry .cl noticed that one of the DNS root servers..., and twitter.com. Normally, root servers only provide a pointer to the correct set of Top Level Domain serversin this case, the .com servers operated by Verisign. But here, the "I" root server...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7259-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7259_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:48:06">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/02/howto-root-a-nook-color-to-transform-it-into-an-android-tablet/</link><title>How to root a Nook Color to transform it into an Android tablet</title><description>... on the Nook ColorThere are two different approaches to turning the Nook Color into a tablet: you can root... to the Nook Color in the long-term, but basic rooting is more practical for users who want a day-to-day tablet, right now. The rest of this article will focus on how to root and enhance the standard...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7259-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7259_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:49:07">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/10/square-enix-chaos-rings-port-wont-work-on-your-rooted-android/</link><title>Square Enix Chaos Rings port won't work on your rooted Android</title><description>...For hacker-minded Android users, being able to root a device with new firmware is a way to get more capability out of their hardware. But for users planning to buy Chaos Rings, a rooted device... puts it, "this game cannot be played on rooted devices." Chaos Rings drew accoladeswhen...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7259-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7259_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:49:47">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/05/google-blocks-android-movie-rentals-from-rooted-devices/</link><title>Google blocks Android movie rentals from rooted devices, blames DRM</title><description>... as one of its primary benefits, is blocking access to its new Android movie rental service to rooted Android... the root account, users can introduce software components that have been extracted from other Android..., rooting still allows users access to Google's services, including the Android Market. However, Google...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7259-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7259_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:50:34">http://arstechnica.com/security/2013/05/critical-linux-vulnerability-imperils-users-even-after-silent-fix/</link><title>Critical Linux vulnerability imperils users, even after “silent” fix</title><description>... or a Web applicationcan also use the bug to escalate their privileges to root. The flaw affects...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7259-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7259_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:51:33">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/04/better-safe-than-sorry-five-backup-apps-to-consider-for-your-android-device/</link><title>Better safe than sorry: five backup apps to consider for your Android device</title><description>... the most and offered what wed want from a backup suite for our non-rooted devices. If you have any suggestions...-popular Titanium Backup for rooted users comes Titanium Media Sync, which offers some very...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7259-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7259_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:52:17">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/04/how-to-create-near-infinite-clones-of-your-favorite-tomato-or-any-plant/</link><title>How to create near-infinite clones of your favorite tomato (or any) plant</title><description>... we would experiment with a weekend feature on cloning plants to get things started.How to root a tomato... it sounds likea piece of an existing plant that you cut off. No roots, no nothing. Just a piece of a plant... that has been cut off? I had to cut this plant from its roots because it was too close...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7259-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7259_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:54:52">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/12/htc-has-released-a-tool/</link><title>HTC releases tool to unlock bootloaders on its devices</title><description>... on its Android devices, preventing users from rooting them to install custom operating system builds...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>