<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7260">iowa girls high school basketball</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:56:18" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7260-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7260_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:56:20">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/03/march-madness-edit-of-ncaa-basketball-exclusive-to-xbox-live/</link><title>March Madness edit of NCAA Basketball exclusive to XBox Live</title><description>..., and will feature all the schools from this year's NCAA Division I Mens Basketball Championship... you'll be able to download a special edition of NCAA Basketball called NCAA Basketball 09: March... with updated ratings," EA explained. "NCAA Basketball 09: March ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7260-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7260_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:57:36">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/02/microsoft-and-girl-scouts-take-on-online-safety/</link><title>Microsoft and Girl Scouts take on online safety</title><description>...Seattle Tech Report discovered that Microsoft has teamed up with Girl Scouts of the USA to create LMK ("let me know"), an online safety website for girls. There is a version for teenagers... cyberbullying, predators, and social networking. It's a girl-for-girl tech campaign that also gives...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7260-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7260_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:59:19">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/01/female-teachers-math-anxiety-influences-female-students/</link><title>Female teachers transmit math anxiety to female students</title><description>... that when elementary school teachers, who are primarily female, displayed a high level of anxiety... midwestern school district, as well as the math achievement of their students (52 boys and 65 girls.... There was also no discrepancy between the math performance of boys and girls. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7260-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7260_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:00:49">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/06/iowa-city-to-ban-not-only-red-light-cameras-but-drones-license-plate-readers-too/</link><title>Iowa City to ban red-light cameras, drones, and license plate readers too</title><description>...On Tuesday evening, Iowa City is scheduled to hold the first reading (PDF) of what is likely... by a citizen group (andrepresented by the American Civil Liberties Union of Iowa) that originally began as a referendum on red light cameras. Iowa City is the only municipality in the state that allows...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7260-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7260_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:02:16">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/03/puzzle-quest-gets-a-makeover-in-mean-girls-the-videogame/</link><title>Puzzle Quest gets a makeover in Mean Girls the videogame</title><description>... Mean Girls. The game.Yes, this is a game based on the 2004 teen comedy starring Lindsay Lohan. But don't let the high school setting fool you, this game is pure Puzzle Quest. You get quests... elements. The original game, Challenge of the Warlords, tackled high fantasy, while the recently released...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7260-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7260_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:04:16">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/11/iowa-funds-200-per-user-app-to-stop-teen-texting-and-driving/</link><title>Iowa funds $200-per-user app to stop teen texting and driving</title><description>...Iowas Department of Transportation has awarded a contract to develop an app that will prevent... to the state.Aegis Mobility is adopting its TeenSafer property for Iowas TXTL8R" program... months.The app will technically be usable by anyone of any age, but Iowa intends to foot the bill of $4 per...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7260-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7260_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:05:47">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/11/texas-school-districts-rfid-tracking-of-students-goes-to-court/</link><title>Texas school district's RFID tracking of students goes to court</title><description>...A Texas high school sophomore has filed suitagainst San Antonio's Northside Independent School District, seeking to block her expulsion for refusing to wear a radio frequency identification badge in school. The girl and her parents are claiming the policy is a violation of her First Amendment rights, citing religious beliefs as the reason she has refused to wear the badge.Northside began iss...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7260-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7260_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:06:26">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/11/ten-boys-arrested-for-child-porn-distribution-connected-to-snapchat/</link><title>Ten boys arrested for child porn distribution connected to Snapchat</title><description>... investigators and dozens of officers have been pursuing the case ever since a staff member at a high school... pornography, thanks to photos obtained via Snapchat.CTV reports that the boys allegedly lured seven girls... as bait. What the girls apparently did not know (or trusted would not happen) is that ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7260-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7260_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:07:03">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/01/simpsons-powerpuff-girls-porn-nets-jail-time-for-australian/</link><title>Simpsons, Powerpuff Girls porn nets jail time for Australian</title><description>...We'll just come right out and say it: some people are into cartoon porn. Heck, even if you're not "into" it, you may have accidentally happened upon it just by running an innocent Google Image Search with SafeSearch turned off (guilty as charged). If you live in Australia, however, you may want to take extra care that your porn stash doesn't contain cartoon imagery of chi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7260-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7260_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:08:30">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/05/schools-cant-stop-wondering-what-students-are-up-to-on-facebook/</link><title>Schools can't stop wondering what students do on Facebook</title><description>...It's graduation season, which means that students, teachers, and administrators alike are all thinking about one thing: Facebook.Schools around the globe have a fascination withindeed, sometimes a fixation onthe social networking site and what their students are getting up to online. Questions about the appropriate response to student material on social networking sites have existed for year...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>