<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7263">hospital acquired pneumonia</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:32:20" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7263-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7263_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:32:21">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/06/hospitals-can-save-money-just-sorting-their-trash/</link><title>Hospitals can save money just sorting their trash</title><description>... by rethinking the supply of surgical tools. Many hospitals acquire surgical equipment in pre-packed...A report recently published in the Canadian Medical Association Journal suggests that hospitals... waste, which is estimated to cost eight times more to process. This alone can result in a hospital...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7263-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7263_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:33:50">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2008/11/panasonic-reveals-a-toughbook-for-the-hospital/</link><title>Panasonic reveals a Toughbook for the hospital</title><description>... (hospital-acquired infections) are a serious problem that may lead to longer hospital stays. This sort... about a crappy Dell) and urinated on (all of that was in just one night). So a hospital can be a tough...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7263-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7263_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:35:04">http://arstechnica.com/security/2012/10/hospitals-computer-hardware-also-suffers-from-infection/</link><title>Hospitals' computer hardware also suffers from infection</title><description>...Drug-resistant bacteria aren't the only pernicious bugs that hospitals need to worry about. MIT's Technology Review reports that hospitals' computerized equipmentsuch as patient monitoring systems, MRI scanners, and nuclear medicine systemsis dangerously vulnerable to malware...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7263-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7263_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:36:32">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/12/report-to-hospitals-give-residents-more-sleep/</link><title>Report to hospitals: Give residents more sleep</title><description>..., many teaching hospitals are sure to be up in arms. The report estimates the new guidelines could add...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7263-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7263_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:38:08">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/07/what-the-ashcroft-hospital-showdown-on-nsa-spying-was-all-about/</link><title>What the Ashcroft “Hospital Showdown” on NSA spying was all about</title><description>... in a hospital bed. Acting attorney general James Comeynow President Obamas nominee to head the FBIwas... that it was illegal. This prompted White House counsel Alberto Gonzales to rush to Ashcrofts hospital room... because the NSA did not actually acquire communications until specific communications were selected...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7263-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7263_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:39:43">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/06/hospital-confirms-steve-jobs-liver-transplant/</link><title>Hospital confirms Steve Jobs liver transplant</title><description>...The Methodist University Hospital in Tennessee confirmed today via press release that Steve Jobs indeed received a liver transplant at Methodist University Hospital Transplant Institute... (the liver is responsible for this function).The hospital now claims that Jobs is "recovering well...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7263-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7263_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:40:58">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/05/fcc-approves-spectrum-changes-for-sprint-and-hospitals/</link><title>FCC approves spectrum changes for Sprint and hospitals</title><description>.... Possibly more importantly, the government agency also gave hospitals a slice of spectrum... also approved a second set of spectrum-use rules, regulating the 2360-2400 MHz band for use in hospitals... have also been used to transmit patient data wirelessly) having this spectrum set aside for hospitals will further...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7263-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7263_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:41:38">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/04/healthcare-records-google-gets-pharmacies-ms-hospitals/</link><title>Healthcare records: Google gets pharmacies, MS hospitals</title><description>... that a major hospital, New York Presbyterian, will roll out online patient access to their records. The hospital system, formed by the merger of the teaching hospitals of Cornell and Columbia, is the first... to access these records online is probably especially significant in the case of these hospitals...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7263-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7263_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:42:13">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/03/microsoft-broadband-stimulus-should-help-hospital-schools/</link><title>Microsoft: broadband stimulus should help schools, hospitals</title><description>... on taxpayers investment in broadband."The answer: "Connecting schools, libraries and hospitals...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7263-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7263_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:42:50">http://arstechnica.com/security/2013/02/were-going-to-blow-up-your-boiler-critical-bug-threatens-hospital-systems/</link><title>We’re going to blow up your boiler: Critical bug threatens hospital systems</title><description>... large chillers used by hospitals and other facilities. Attackers could also exploit the bug to gain... installations, hospitals, and other mission-critical facilities. Tests the pair performed on a small sample... Hospital in the UK.Security experts have long argued that the convenience often comes at the price...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>