<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7274">detroit riot</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:45:04" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7274-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7274_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:45:05">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/12/riot-reverses-course-says-pro-league-of-legends-players-can-stream-other-games-after-all/</link><title>Riot reverses course, says pro League of Legends players can stream other games after all</title><description>... and disbelief from much of the community.In response to the backlash, Riot Games has backed down. e-sports... advantage, by trying to pay LCS teams and players to play competing games on stream. Riot sought to end...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7274-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7274_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:46:01">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/wiiware-and-virtual-console-monday-riots-and-chaos-edition/</link><title>WiiWare and Virtual Console Monday: Riots and chaos edition</title><description>... Points? Read on to find out.WiiWareSnowboard Riot (Hudson Entertainment, 1-4 Players, Rated E, 1000... about. But that aside, Snowboard Riot looks like it could be good for some multiplayer fun. Anyone...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7274-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7274_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:46:47">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/05/using-science-to-reform-toxic-player-behavior-in-league-of-legends/</link><title>Using science to reform toxic player behavior in League of Legends</title><description>...Riot Games founders and League of Legends creators Brandon Beck and Marc Merrill have encountered... players wasnt an acceptable solution for their game. Riot Games began experimenting... initiative, Riot introduced "the Tribunal" to League of Legends in May of 2011. The Tribunal...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7274-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7274_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:48:09">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/01/ford-applink-opens-floodgates-to-in-car-ios-android-and-blackberry-apps/</link><title>Ford AppLink opens floodgates to in-car iOS, Android, and BlackBerry apps</title><description>...-obsessed motor industry. So Wired.co.uk travelled to Detroit for the North American International Auto...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7274-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7274_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:49:31">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/09/foxconn-worker-riot-closes-factory/</link><title>Foxconn worker riot closes factory</title><description>... morning, Foxconn released a statement indicating that the riot started as a personal disagreement between... that the riots were started not by a fight between workers in off-campus housing, but instead... back plate. TUAW speculates that the riots were in no small part caused by the recent long iPhone 5...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7274-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7274_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:50:19">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/03/hidden-treasure-league-of-legends/</link><title>Hidden treasure: League of Legends</title><description>...Stepping into my hands-on with Riot Games' League of Legends, I wasn't entirely sure what to expect. I hadn't really heard much about it other than that it was an RTS/RPG game... that the game featured differences in environment and character models. I was informed that Riot had developed...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7274-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7274_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:51:15">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/12/sext-instagram-account-incites-riot/</link><title>Sext Instagram account incites riot</title><description>... Snapchat Sluts (NSFW). No rioting has resulted from Snapchat Sluts because, according to its curator...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7274-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7274_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:52:04">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/10/riots-lead-mozambique-to-ban-cell-phone-anonymity/</link><title>Riots lead Mozambique to ban cell phone anonymity</title><description>..., all thanks to some recent rioting.Back in September, the capitol city of Maputo was rocked by riots... parliament heard different versions of what happened, with some arguing that the riots... cell phones, something seen during the riots, but the government says it's more about stopping...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7274-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7274_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:52:45">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/10/to-pay-off-webcam-spies-detroit-kid-pawns-100k-in-family-jewels-for-1500/</link><title>To pay off webcam spies, Detroit kid pawns $100k in family jewels for $1,500</title><description>... took place up the road in Detroit. And she was right.The actual RAT attack in question doesn't..., who told the police.Hernandez and his mother both spoke to FOX Detroit about the case, and the video...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7274-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7274_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:54:12">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/12/riot-tells-pro-league-of-legends-players-they-cant-stream-competing-games/</link><title>Riot tells pro League of Legends players they can’t stream competing games</title><description>...League of Legends developer Riot has unleashed something of a bombshell on the pro-gaming community.... Riot has done a lot to promote the game as an e-sport. In addition to organizing LCS, Riot... streaming to tens of thousands of fans, this is a valuable resource that Riot is undermining.Unsurprisingly...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>