<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7293">basil recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:17:48" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7293-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7293_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:17:48">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/12/handy-lets-you-get-handsy-with-youtube-recipes-without-making-a-mess/</link><title>Handy lets you get handsy with YouTube recipes without making a mess</title><description>...If you've ever tried to follow a recipe online while cooking simultaneously, you'll know... Peasto Fritatta" recipe. It worked very well on Chrome on a Mac, although it didn't work... restricted to operating recipe videos. At the moment it is only compatible with Google Chrome (although...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7293-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7293_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:19:07">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/11/gamers-create-recipes-for-protein-folding-algorithms/</link><title>Gamers create recipes for protein-folding algorithms</title><description>...Chemically, the proteins that run most of a cell's functions are little more than a string of amino acids. Their ability to perform structural and catalytic functions is primarily dependent upon the fact that, when in solution, that string adopts a complex, three-dimensional shape. Understanding how that three-dimensional structure forms has been a serious challenge; even if you know the ord...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7293-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7293_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:21:07">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/08/science-academies-hand-climate-change-body-a-recipe-for-reform/</link><title>Science academies hand climate change body a recipe for reform</title><description>...In the wake of a few high-profile errors found in the most recent Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change assessment report, the organization asked the InterAcademy Council, a coalition of national science organizations, to examine its structure and procedures in order to identify potential weaknesses. The IAC's report came in today, and it more or less indicates that the IPCC has been a v...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7293-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7293_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:22:25">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/05/command-line-made-easy-five-simple-recipes-for-grep/</link><title>Command line made easy: five simple recipes for grep</title><description>...The grep command is regarded as one of the most essential building blocks of command line automation. It is a search tool that can be used to perform basic text filtering and processing tasks on files and streams. Although it is deceptively simple, it can sometimes take the challenge out of finding the proverbial needle in a haystack. In this article, I'm going to show you several examples o...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7293-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7293_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:23:05">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/08/cooking-with-the-ipad-which-apps-offer-the-best-experience/</link><title>Cooking with the iPad: which apps offer the best experience?</title><description>...Cooking: if you're not doing it very often, you should start. But you're probably not here to listen to me preach to you about the health, budget, and culinary enjoyment benefits of cooking for yourself. If you do cook, you may be interested in our latest app showdown. And if you don't, well, I've got nothin'.Many of us whocook on a regular basis have run into an odd prob...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7293-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7293_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:24:06">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/12/ipad-cooking-app-showdown-holiday-week-edition/</link><title>iPad cooking app showdown: holiday week edition</title><description>... it. Because of its magazine format, each issue comes with an article and recipes to go along with it. The articles had tappable links to the corresponding recipes and vice versa; I liked how the articles/recipes weren't crammed onto one view. Each article has a header image that starts in black...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7293-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7293_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:26:20">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/01/nothing-to-celebrate-on-public-domain-day-2010-in-the-us/</link><title>Nothing to celebrate on Public Domain Day 2010 in the US</title><description>... readers ever wanted open access to William Basil Worsfold's 1893 work A Visit To Java...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7293-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7293_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:27:18">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2008/09/microsoft-launches-food-related-website-delish/</link><title>Microsoft launches food-related website Delish</title><description>... with MSN, we developed Delish.com to go way beyond a typical recipe site. We are confident... game has begun. Delish.com currently offers thousands of recipes, how-to articles, photo galleries... and pop culture as it relates to food. The site even has RSS feeds (Recipes Menus has my attention...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7293-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7293_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:28:46">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/05/weekend-arts-humphry-slocombe-ice-cream-book-shares-simple-secrets/</link><title>Weekend Ar(t)s: Humphry Slocombe Ice Cream Book shares simple secrets</title><description>... of their favorite recipes and compiled them into the inaugural Humphry Slocombe Ice Cream Book. Finally... recipes that could be completed with nothing more than a bottom-level Cuisinart ice cream maker.... The related author's note only emphasizes this further: "It's true. These recipes are idiot...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7293-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7293_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:29:46">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/11/week-in-science-climate-change-and-climate-confusion/</link><title>Week in science: climate change and climate confusion</title><description>... be accompanied by seismic monitoring.Gamers create recipes for protein-folding algorithms: The people behind the protein folding game FoldIt let their users share protein folding recipes, which enabled them to quickly evolve a recipe that could outperform one that was being developed in a research lab.Russia...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>