<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7299">row row row your boat lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:22:06" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7299-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7299_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:22:08">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/08/saints-row-4-review-saint-misbehavin/</link><title>Saint's Row 4 review: Saint Misbehavin’</title><description>... Date: August 20, 2013Links: SaintsRow.comAfter an hour of playing the video game Saint's Row 4... enters the room when dad utters the words "Saint's Row."Little Caleb squeals... as violent and titillating as Saint's Row, one that has always competed with Grand Theft Auto...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7299-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7299_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:23:30">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/11/saints-row-3-is-the-gta-clone-that-worships-at-the-altar-of-fun/</link><title>Saints Row 3 is the GTA -clone that worships at the altar of fun</title><description>... up your play time and try a little bit of what the game has to offer. When Saints Row goes...Grand Theft Auto satirizes our violent culture, and Saints Row 3 began as a way to rip off Grand... franchise, but Saints Row: The Third went all in with the idea that it was satirizing a video game series...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7299-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7299_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:24:06">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/08/do-not-buy-the-1000000-saints-row-iv-bundle/</link><title>Do not buy the $1,000,000 Saints Row IV bundle</title><description>... craziness that is the $1,000,000 Saints Row IV Super Dangerous Wad Wad Edition (aka the Million Dollar...'d think that bundling all these extravagances together would get you more bang for your million... (when there was some vagueness, we went with the most expensive feasible option we could find):Saints Row IV Commander...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7299-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7299_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:25:36">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/12/voilition-opts-for-steam-only-drm-with-saints-row-2/</link><title>Voilition opts for Steam-only DRM with Saints Row 2</title><description>... for the upcoming PC release of Saints Row 2\. Volition Community moderator V-Singular discussed the decision... version and the retail version of Saints Row 2\. If you have a retail version, Steam is only going...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7299-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7299_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:27:14">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/03/itunes-81-hits-the-streets-along-with-front-row-update/</link><title>iTunes 8.1 hits the streets along with Front Row Update</title><description>... feature page:The iTunes DJ feature automatically picks songs from your entire library or from a specific... with the release of iTunes 8.1, Apple also pushed out Front Row Update 2.1.7. The Software Update description says that the update merely brings iTunes 8.1 compatibility to Front Row, so there's likely...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7299-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7299_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:28:40">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/02/apples-front-row-gains-hulu-netflix-streaming-via-plug-in/</link><title>Apple's Front Row gains Hulu, Netflix streaming via plug-in</title><description>...Front Row, the redheaded stepchild media center version of an Apple TV built into every Mac... of iTunes and your other media.After a simple installer places a file called frUnderstudy.frappliance.... It works by pulling RSS feeds from your Hulu and Netflix accounts, so you will have to sign in to each...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7299-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7299_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:29:19">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/12/deltas-3mbps-in-flight-wifi-is-gogo-on-first-seven-planes/</link><title>Delta's 3Mbps in-flight WiFi is Go(go) on first seven planes</title><description>..., lighter equipment paired with less antenna drag). A competitor, Row 44, is testing its service with Alaska Airlines and Southwest Airlines; Row 44 uses satellite-backed access...). In practice, this is likely 2Mbps over 700Kbps. Row 44 claims far higher speeds, in the tens of Mbps, due...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7299-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7299_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:30:56">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/12/thq-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-will-continue-to-operate/</link><title>THQ files for Chapter 11 bankruptcy, will continue to operate</title><description>...Struggling video game publisher THQ announced it has filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy, but it will continue to operate as it moves forward with an effort to sell its studios and assets.The publisher of franchises including Saints Row, Red Faction, and Company of Heroes has entered into a "stalking horse bidder" agreement with Clearlake Capital Group. THQ will sell seemingly all its asset...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7299-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7299_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:32:21">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/03/fortune-names-apple-most-admired-two-years-in-a-row/</link><title>Fortune names Apple "most admired" two years in a row</title><description>... for the second year in a row," according to the magazine.In what we can only describe as an inexplicable... year in a row....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7299-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7299_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:33:04">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/11/thq-response/</link><title>THQ explains studio closings, focusing on fewer titles</title><description>... and Saints Row, and maybe even create some interesting new intellectual properties....</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>