<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7303">what causes itchy feet</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:06:41" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7303-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7303_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:06:42">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/10/sticky-mushroom-feet-fail-last-but-fail-fast/</link><title>Sticky mushroom feet fail last, but fail fast</title><description>... of adhesion is different for flat and mushroom-shaped feet. But although there was some speculation..., that is.To investigate the way that adhesion fails, scientists created artificial mushroom feet and filmed the unsticking process. Initially, they filmed the feet unsticking at 5,400 frames per second...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7303-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7303_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:07:51">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/03/just-cause-2-beautiful-stupidity/</link><title>Just Cause 2 on the PC is beautiful stupidity</title><description>...The first twenty minutes or so of Just Cause 2 are laughably bad. The voice acting is cringe inducing, the story doesn't exactly seem inspired, and the action is stilted as you try to get a feel for the controls. It's one of the worst openings for a good game in recent memory. The good news is thatJust Cause 2 gets good. It gets really good.The game plays like every bad impulse Michael...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7303-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7303_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:08:29">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/08/how-what-what-in-the-butt-made-fair-use-easier-to-claim/</link><title>How "What What (In the Butt)" unintentionally bolstered "fair use"</title><description>...Wisconsin, state of my birth, I salute you for turning out federal judges like J.P. Stadtmueller. Stadtmueller is the man who waded into the swampland of fair use, South Park, and "What What (In the Butt)" to deliver a July 6 order that may break new judicial territory by citing South Park episode "Osama bin Laden Has Farty Pants" in its footnotes. And Stadtmueller has the pro...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7303-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7303_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:09:35">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/06/paradise-and-explosions-just-cause-2-at-e3/</link><title>Paradise and explosions: Just Cause 2 at E3</title><description>...Just Cause was one of those games that people seemed to either love or hate when it was first...;s amazing how, thanks to the grappling hook, the gameplay is so adaptable; this is what Bionic... leaping from vehicle to vehicle, shooting out tires (which causes the cars to flip spectacularly...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7303-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7303_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:10:13">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/09/unofficial-multiplayer-mod-for-just-cause-2-causes-hilarity-riot/</link><title>Unofficial multiplayer mod for Just Cause 2 causes hilarity, riot</title><description>... but awesomely functional multiplayer modification for Just Cause 2, the sandbox game which lets... one. However, the Just Cause 2 engine is accessible enough that a concerted reverse-engineering effort... which this weekend is undergoing another of its periodic open public beta tests.And what a public test...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7303-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7303_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:10:57">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/06/christ-what-an-asshole-is-only-001-of-new-yorker-caption-contest-subs/</link><title>"Christ, what an asshole" is only .001% of New Yorker caption contest subs</title><description>..."Christ, what an asshole" seems a fitting caption for nearly every New Yorker cartoon, and yet it's only been submitted 27 times out of well over 1.5 million entries in the magazine's caption contest. We've found one place the Internet's trolls haven't managed to permeate.The "CWAA" revelation dates all the way back to February 2006, from a blog post b...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7303-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7303_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:12:19">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/02/these-feet-were-made-for-walking-upright-and-long-distances/</link><title>These feet were made for walking: upright and long distances</title><description>... of footprints found at Ileret, Kenya gives anthropologists a clear view of what our ancestors feet looked like... of motion is quite energy-efficient, it is not what our muscular-skeletal system is best suited... of anatomical changes; our feet,knees, hip, spine, and even our skull all had to change to ac...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7303-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7303_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:13:04">http://arstechnica.com/business/2011/06/in-flight-internet-the-view-from-35000-feet-and-three-years/</link><title>In-flight Internet: the view from 35,000 feet and three years</title><description>...In-flight Internet access has had its up and downs, and, yes, this article will have its share of aviation-related puns. An aborted launch by Boeing in 2004 seemed to ground the idea, but a second attempt in 2008 has remained aloft. Each day, nearly 1,100 planestotaling 4,000 flights carrying an average of 500,000 passengersply their way over America while carrying WiFi gear from Aircell. Meanwhi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7303-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7303_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:13:43">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/03/apple-dragging-its-feet-on-itunes-dolby-51-issue/</link><title>Apple dragging its feet on iTunes Dolby 5.1 issue</title><description>..., although the Apple TV isn't affected. So far, the most likely cause is some type of encoding issue that causes the 5.1-channel track to break when played back via the QuickTime framework... different than expected, and tweaking things a bit causes the surround sound track to return. Apple does...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7303-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7303_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:14:32">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/12/when-it-comes-to-taxes-people-vote-differently-with-their-hands-feet/</link><title>When it comes to taxes, people vote differently with their hands, feet</title><description>... in a financial game that tested their willingness to cooperate. What they found was that people responded...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>