<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7304">carmen electra video</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:15:32" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7304-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7304_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:15:34">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/01/government-formally-drops-charges-against-aaron-swartz/</link><title>Government formally drops charges against Aaron Swartz</title><description>...In the wake of the tragic suicide of Aaron Swartz, the United States Attorney decided to formally drop the pending charges against the 26-year-old information hacktivist."In support of this dismissal, the government states that Mr. Swartz died on January 11, 2013," wrote Carmen Ortiz...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7304-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7304_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:16:17">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/01/web-video-framework-company-publishes-state-of-html5-video-document/</link><title>Web video framework company publishes State of HTML5 Video document</title><description>.... The HTML5 video element is already widely supported in modern Web browsers, but the capabilities and codecs that are available differ between implementations. A new State of HTML5 Video document offers some clarity by painting a clear picture of the current status of standards-based video across...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7304-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7304_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:16:54">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/05/video-reboots-that-need-the-boot-part-2-simcity/</link><title>Video: Reboots that need the boot, part 2— SimCity</title><description>...A video examination of EA's advertising platform masquerading as a city simulator. This is the second in our series of reboots that need the boot. We looked first at Alien vs. Predator. The third installment releases Sunday on Ars Technica.There is a small handful of game series that I've...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7304-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7304_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:17:59">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/03/open-video-alliance-launches-wikipedia-video-campaign/</link><title>Open Video Alliance launches Wikipedia video campaign</title><description>...The Open Video Alliance (OVA), a group that seeks to promote adoption of standards-based open video technologies, has launched a new campaign encouraging users to upload videos to the Wikipedia... awareness of the value that open video technologies can bring to the Web.The OVA's members...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7304-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7304_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:19:22">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/03/flickr-turns-on-video-for-all-hd-for-pro-members/</link><title>Flickr turns on video for all, HD for Pro members</title><description>...Flickr broke out of its photographic confines nearly a year ago with the introduction of video. Videos can be up to 90 seconds in length and 150MB in size, but until now, only Pro account holders... of HD video and sharing for all, though there are still some catches in place. Free account holders...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7304-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7304_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:20:34">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/05/ipad-may-be-pushing-160-increase-in-h264-video-online/</link><title>160% increase in H.264 video online since January</title><description>...The increasing criticism of Flash as a vehicle for online video delivery(as well as Apple's dislike of Flash)appears to be driving the adoption of H.264 video. A recent study by video search site MeFeedia reveals a 160 percent increase in the proportion of video encoded in the iPad-friendly...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7304-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7304_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:22:02">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/12/google-curbstomps-online-video-competitors-as-market-surges/</link><title>Google curbstomps online video competitors as market surges</title><description>...Internet users now watch 45 percent more videos online than they did a year ago. The entire online video sector is seeing explosive growth, especially Hulu, which doubled its reach in just a single..., its Google-owned propertiesmostly YouTubethat are absolutely demolishing the competition in terms of videos...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7304-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7304_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:22:46">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/12/are-the-floodgates-opening-for-3g-video-broadcasting-on-iphone/</link><title>The floodgates open for 3G video broadcasting on iPhone</title><description>...Today, Ustream Live Broadcaster is now available from the App Store, and it enables live video... to transmitting video over ATT's 3G network, it also seems at odds with ATT Mobility CEO Ralph de la... on the network.Just last week we told you about Knocking Live Video, an app that allows an iPhone 3GS...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7304-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7304_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:23:23">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/12/video-tour-the-ins-and-outs-of-the-steamos-beta-release/</link><title>Video tour: The ins and outs of the SteamOS beta release</title><description>...This morning we figured out a method to capture video on SteamOS. Though it's not the most super-optimized solution for capturing gameplay footage (and the comments for that article have collected some excellent ideas on how to improve!), it was definitely good enough to capture a video walk...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7304-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7304_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:23:57">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/02/ars-announces-the-science-video-contest-winners/</link><title>Ars Science Video Contest: the winners</title><description>...Last year, we asked the Ars audience to put together a short video explaining a scientific concept... would get to enjoy a collection of great video content that might make them just a touch smarter.... Exploring the 4th Dimension Biology: The biosciences were a bit more varied. Megan Carney sent in two videos...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>