<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7307">causes of the cold war</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:46:34" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7307-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7307_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:46:35">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/08/cold-call-victim-forces-telemarketers-to-pay-him-by-using-premium-number/</link><title>Cold call victim forces telemarketers to pay him by using premium number</title><description>...Lee Beaumont. BBCA British man fed up with cold calls from telemarketers set up a premium phone... here.He now gives out his 0871 line to any business that might cold call him, while giving friends... to increase his revenue by keeping cold callers talkingasking for more details about their services.He...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7307-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7307_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:47:30">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/03/just-cause-2-beautiful-stupidity/</link><title>Just Cause 2 on the PC is beautiful stupidity</title><description>...The first twenty minutes or so of Just Cause 2 are laughably bad. The voice acting is cringe inducing, the story doesn't exactly seem inspired, and the action is stilted as you try to get a feel for the controls. It's one of the worst openings for a good game in recent memory. The good news is thatJust Cause 2 gets good. It gets really good.The game plays like every bad impulse Michael...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7307-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7307_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:48:31">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/06/paradise-and-explosions-just-cause-2-at-e3/</link><title>Paradise and explosions: Just Cause 2 at E3</title><description>...Just Cause was one of those games that people seemed to either love or hate when it was first... leaping from vehicle to vehicle, shooting out tires (which causes the cars to flip spectacularly... like Just Cause 2 will be a great action title, thanks in large part to its open-ended and fast...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7307-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7307_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:49:21">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2014/01/facebook-uses-10000-blu-ray-discs-to-create-petabytes-of-cold-storage/</link><title>Facebook uses 10,000 Blu-ray Discs to create petabytes of “cold storage”</title><description>...Facebook has built a prototype cold storage system that uses Blu-ray Discs instead of traditional drives.Further ReadingWho needs HP and Dell? Facebook now designs all its own serversFacebook's newest data center won't have any OEM servers."The Blu-ray system reduces costs by 50 percent and energy use by 80 percent compared with its current cold-storage system, which uses hard disk...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7307-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7307_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:50:58">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/04/is-the-us-headed-toward-a-cyber-cold-war-with-china/</link><title>Is the US headed toward a cyber Cold War with China?</title><description>... ushering in a new Cold War era?Given US officials rhetoric and actions in recent months, it might... is a serious threat.A number of events have likely precipitated Cold War fears. The disclosures... officials are trying to fend off threats of a new Cold War, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7307-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7307_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:51:53">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/12/can-17000-patents-help-android-win-a-legal-cold-war/</link><title>Can 17,000 patents help Android win a legal Cold War?</title><description>... lawyer David Mixon."You always hear these analogies about the Cold War and stockpiling all your... entering the mobile market to prepare for all-out war, and legal experts we've interviewed... it's all-out war and you come to the war with your stacks of patents, and G...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7307-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7307_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:52:58">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/09/unofficial-multiplayer-mod-for-just-cause-2-causes-hilarity-riot/</link><title>Unofficial multiplayer mod for Just Cause 2 causes hilarity, riot</title><description>... but awesomely functional multiplayer modification for Just Cause 2, the sandbox game which lets... one. However, the Just Cause 2 engine is accessible enough that a concerted reverse-engineering effort... games lend themselves to emergent gameplay, and in Just Cause 2 multiplayer, hilariously creative...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7307-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7307_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:54:27">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/06/operation-prospero-the-cold-wars-battle-of-balloons/</link><title>Inciting revolts before Twitter: balloon infobattles of the Cold War</title><description>... to journalistic professionalism would be accelerated by one of the great tragedies of the Cold War...Sixty years ago this August, one of the strangest information wars ever fought raged over the skies... revolutions, it's worth taking a critical look at the Cold War's Battle of Balloons...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7307-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7307_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:55:31">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/09/the-long-complicated-voyage-of-the-dream-chaser-may-yet-end-in-space/</link><title>50 years to orbit: Dream Chaser's crazy Cold War backstory</title><description>... over Broomfield. The Dream Chaser isa Cold War product, replete with secret military programs, spy... called the new vehicle "Dream Chaser", causing some confusion, but eventually he agreed...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7307-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7307_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:56:28">http://arstechnica.com/staff/2012/03/legendary-star-wars-concept-artist-ralph-mcquarrie-passes-away/</link><title>Legendary Star Wars concept artist Ralph McQuarrie passes away at 82</title><description>...Ralph McQuarrie, best known to fans as the conceptual artist who brought the world of Star Wars... Wars that he became truly known for. George Lucas once called him "the gentle giant of the Star Wars universe." It was through his brush this universe, beloved by geeks around the world, began...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>