<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7326">volcanoe eruption</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:39:04" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7326-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7326_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:39:05">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/09/if-iceland-volcano-erupts-would-tragic-history-repeat/</link><title>If an Icelandic volcano erupts, would tragic history repeat?</title><description>...Beginning in 1783, Iceland endured an eight-month-long volcanic eruption that left a seemingly... of their livestock.The effects of the eruption at Laki were not limited to Iceland. In the Netherlands, trees... away as Italy. The mouthful that was Eyjafjallajkull reminded us in 2010 that volcanoes can easily...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7326-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7326_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:39:46">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/08/fast-magma-refills-suggest-some-volcanoes-connect-straight-to-the-mantle/</link><title>Fast magma refills suggest some volcanoes connect straight to the mantle</title><description>... that eruptions in a wider range of volcanoes might be predicted by techniques such as earthquake monitoring... an eruption of the Irazu volcano in Costa Rica, which occurred between 1963 and 1965, to draw...Because of their locations geology, Icelandic volcanoes are known to be dire...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7326-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7326_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:41:22">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/01/watching-volcanoes-deflate-aids-ash-forecast/</link><title>Watching volcanoes deflate aids ash forecast</title><description>... eruptions) and give us a better idea of how the ash plume high above the volcano is going to behave... Natures bag of tricks.Erupting volcanoes can hurl up huge clouds of ash made of microscopic particles of volcanic glass, a situation that creates a serious risk for airplane engines. Eruptions...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7326-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7326_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:42:20">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/09/indonesias-samalas-volcano-may-have-kickstarted-the-little-ice-age/</link><title>Indonesia’s Samalas volcano may have kickstarted the Little Ice Age</title><description>...A volcano in Indonesia may be the location of a massive mystery eruption that has perplexed volcanologists for decades, according to a new study. The eruption occurred in 1257... in the past 7,000 years.But where did the eruption happen? Not being able to find the volcano...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7326-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7326_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:43:04">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/04/understanding-the-split-personality-of-icelands-volcanoes/</link><title>Understanding the split personality of Iceland's volcanoes</title><description>... that individual volcanoes on the island may have a complicated eruption history. The other factor... doesn't produce eruptions as powerful as subduction zone volcanoes such as Pinatubo, which can send...The initial images of the Eyjafjallajkull eruption showed the sort of drama...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7326-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7326_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:43:32">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/09/researchers-ponder-whats-next-in-volcanic-yellowstone/</link><title>Researchers ponder what's next in volcanic Yellowstone</title><description>..., with a high concentration of geysers, hot springs, mud volcanoes, and similar features. These... that has triggered titanic eruptions in the distant past. Now, two of these geologists have looked into what... cubic kilometers of material in the process. An even larger eruption, about twice the size, occurred...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7326-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7326_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:44:40">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/07/volcanic-earthquakes-produce-a-seismic-scream-just-before-eruption/</link><title>Volcanic earthquakes produce a “seismic scream” just before eruption</title><description>... warning about impending eruptions.A 2009 eruption of Alaska's Redoubt Volcano may not get us... an explosive eruption. Shortly before the eruption, small faults within the volcano were breaking... a few minutes of the eruption, the scream got cut off as t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7326-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7326_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:45:43">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/09/mars-olympus-mons-may-have-company-in-biggest-volcanoes-clubon-earth/</link><title>Mars’ Olympus Mons may have company in biggest volcanoes club—on Earth</title><description>...Olympus Mons, Mars massive shield volcano that rises over 20 kilometers into the air and covers.... Its difficult to imagine such a gargantuan volcano on the surface of the Earth. But maybe thats... of eruptions, so you can imagine how much less we know about the plateaus at the bottom...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7326-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7326_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:46:09">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/04/volcano-40-miles-east-of-mexico-city-rumbles-back-to-life/</link><title>Volcano 40 miles east of Mexico City rumbles back to life</title><description>...Popocatpetl, the nearly 18,000 foot volcano straddling the border of Puebla andMorelosstates in central Mexico, has started a series of small eruptions, which could presage something more violent... and is connected by a saddle to another volcano, Iztacchuatl. Since the arrival of the Spanish in the 16th...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7326-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7326_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:47:24">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/10/oxygen-kept-out-of-atmosphere-until-volcanoes-rose-above-the-ocean-surface/</link><title>Oxygen kept out of atmosphere until volcanoes rose above the ocean surface</title><description>... for a change in the lava that erupted from these volcanoes. In other words, the composition... because volcanoes were increasingly exposed to the atmosphere. The new work uses chemical models to show... the volcano. A volcano beneath the surface of the ocean will produce much more H...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>