<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7328">reduce acne redness</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:58:25" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7328-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7328_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:58:26">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/11/red-hat-launches-new-server-virtualization-solution/</link><title>Red Hat takes on VMware with server virtualization solution</title><description>...Red Hat expanded its virtualization product portfolio this week with the launch of its Enterprise..., Red Hat began transitioning its virtualization strategy towards KVM and away from Citrix's Xen... choice for Red Hat. The company has invested considerable resources to boost KVM's capabilities...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7328-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7328_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:58:57">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/09/red-hat-moves-forward-with-kvm-virtualization-in-rhel-54/</link><title>KVM is the feather in Red Hat Enterprise Linux 5.4</title><description>...Red Hat announced Wednesday the release of Red Hat Enterprise Linux 5.4, a new major point update... for KVM and marks an important milestone in Red Hat's gradual transition away from Xen.KVM... environment," Red Hat explains in a blog entry. "This includes hardware and application...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7328-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7328_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:59:59">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/03/red-hat-succeeding-despite-recession/</link><title>Red Hat: recession is good for our business</title><description>... to reduce IT costs. Uptake of open source software is climbing in this environment, which means... over the previous year. Subscriptions to Red Hat's commercial support service, which accounts for $541 million of that revenue, were up 20 percent. Red Hat CEO Jim Whitehurst, a former Delta Airlines COO...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7328-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7328_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:00:39">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/11/red-hat-enterprise-linux-6-improves-scalability-virtualization/</link><title>Red Hat Enterprise Linux 6 improves scalability, virtualization</title><description>... and reducing power costs.During the press briefing, several of Red Hat's partners discussed...Red Hat has released a new major version of its flagship server platform, Red Hat Enterprise Linux... changes in the RHEL virtualization stack. Red Hat has transitioned its customers a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7328-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7328_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:01:21">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2011/04/the-rationale-for-ceylon-red-hats-new-programming-language/</link><title>The rationale for Ceylon, Red Hat's new programming language</title><description>...Red Hat engineer Gavin King, the creator of Hibernate, is developing a new programming language for enterprise software development. His team at Red Hat has apparently been working on the grammar... that intrinsic support for creating such expressive declarative structures in code will reduce the Java...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7328-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7328_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:01:54">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2008/11/msn-to-help-launch-redwire-on-december-1/</link><title>MSN to help launch (RED)WIRE on December 1</title><description>...(RED)Wire is (RED)'s latest initiative: a digital music magazine that allows you to discover... receiving the medicine you're paying for. Subscribers will receive their new music via the (RED)WIRE... Day, MSN will celebrate the launch of (RED)WIRE on red.msn.com, with the help of artists...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7328-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7328_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:02:43">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/12/accidents-increase-at-chicago-red-light-camera-intersections/</link><title>Accidents increase at Chicago red light camera intersections</title><description>...The Chicago suburbs are buying into the red light camera movement, but the results are not very.... The Chicago Tribune put together a handy page that contains yearly accident data for every red light... where cameras were installed in 2006 and 2007. The problem with red light camerasaside from the fact...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7328-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7328_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:03:12">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/12/perfect-enforcement-on-the-ground-in-the-red-light-camera-wars/</link><title>Perfect enforcement: On the ground in the red light camera wars</title><description>... enforcement will significantly reduce the number of red light violations in the City of Modesto... is highly effective in reducing red light violations and right-angle injury crashes associated with red... of the studies, the results all indicate that red ligh...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7328-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7328_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:04:22">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/04/red-steel-2-coming-this-year-with-motionplus-support/</link><title>Red Steel 2 coming this year, with MotionPlus support</title><description>...UbiSoft has a history of leading the way on the Wii: Red Steel was one of the system's first.... This trend is going to be continued, as Red Steel 2using the MotionPlushas been announced.And now, marketing speak. "Red Steel 2 returns with an artistic style and flair created just for Wii. Set...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7328-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7328_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:05:10">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/04/with-californias-red-light-cameras-are-pictures-admissible-evidence/</link><title>With California’s red light cameras, are pictures admissible evidence?</title><description>...Carmen Goldsmith was driving her BMW through Inglewood, a Los Angeles suburb, when she ran a red light. She instantly became one of countless people nationwide ticketed by a red light camera.The.... She appealed and lost.Further ReadingPerfect enforcement: On the ground in the red light camera warsIn...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>