<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7348">map of the united states</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:45:11" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7348-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7348_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:45:12">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/06/the-crooks-who-created-modern-wiretapping-law/</link><title>The crooks who created modern wiretapping law</title><description>... because their arrests, based on warrantless telephone taps, reached the United States Supreme Court. In the two... perspective on the matter, with their opinion delivered by a former President of the United States.... Olmstead vs. United States, the right of p...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7348-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7348_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:46:13">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/03/old-maps-online-lets-you-find-your-way-around-17th-century-holy-roman-empire/</link><title>Old Maps Online lets you find your way around 17th century Holy Roman Empire</title><description>...The worlds single largest online collection of historical maps launched earlier this week at Old Maps Online. By the end of the year, the site aims to have 60,000 maps available for public access... Republics Moravian Library and the San Francisco Bay Areas David Rumsey Map Collection. The University...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7348-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7348_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:46:52">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2011/05/new-mobile-web-google-maps-highlights-sorry-state-of-native-ios-app/</link><title>New mobile Web Google Maps highlights sorry state of native iOS app</title><description>...Google released an update to the mobile Web version of Google Maps on Friday, adding many features... Maps up to par with the native app Android users have had for some time, though the Web app is less... and directions. With the new mobile Web version of Google Maps, users have access to many features...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7348-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7348_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:47:32">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/06/us-leads-world-in-government-remova-requests/</link><title>US leads world in government removal requests to Google</title><description>...The United States government leads the world in content removal requests to Google, as measured... particularly rich given that not only does the United States lead the pack in terms of government takedown... assistant secretary of state in the US Bureau of Democracy, told attendees ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7348-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7348_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:48:46">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/03/the-cost-difference-in-mailing-netflx-vs-gamefly-all-of-gameflys-profits/</link><title>GameFly to USPS: higher postage than Netflix costs us $730K per month</title><description>... with the United States Postal Service alleging that Netflix mailings were given priorityovernot...;s delivery unit." Belair estimates that 97 percent of DVD mailers belong to Netflix, while only 1...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7348-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7348_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:49:28">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/06/united-kingdom-game-ratings-to-be-provided-by-pegi/</link><title>United Kingdom game ratings to be provided by PEGI</title><description>...There has been a long battle between the British Board of Film Classification and the Pan-European Game Information System over who gets to rate games for the UK, and now we know which system has won out. From now on, PEGI will be providing game ratings for the entirety of the United Kingdom."The Government has made absolutely the right decision for child safety. By choosing PEGI as the sing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7348-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7348_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:50:26">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/06/over-20-million-voip-subscribers-in-the-united-states/</link><title>Over 20 million VoIP subscribers in the United States</title><description>...VoIP users take noteyou now command a noticeable share of wireline telephone service in the United States. The Federal Communications Commission reports 21 million subscriptions to Voice over Internet Protocol accounts provided by companies like Vonage, as well as the telcos and cable providers...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7348-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7348_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:51:45">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/02/first-geologic-map-of-ganymede-made-with-voyager-data/</link><title>First geologic map of Ganymede made with Voyager data</title><description>...Maps have always been an integral part of exploration. They take the in out of terra incognita. Some things are easier to map than others, of course. The geology of a world a few hundred million miles away is one of those other things. Nevertheless, the United States Geological Survey just released...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7348-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7348_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:52:36">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/05/rare-earth-mining-rises-again-in-united-states/</link><title>Rare-earth mining rises again in United States</title><description>...With waste water eliminated, a sludge of unwanted residues will be left behind and gradually piled in this 90-acre pit at the base of Clark Mountain.The fight over the minerals that run the electronic world entered a new phase in March when the United States, the European Union, and Japan...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7348-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7348_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:53:46">http://arstechnica.com/security/2010/11/wikileaks-us-sought-dna-passwords-of-world-leaders/</link><title>Wikileaks: US sought DNA, passwords of world leaders</title><description>...Another tsunami of United States government documents is up on Wikileaks. We're talking confidential cables between the US State Department and 274 embassies around the world. 15,652 of them... of intelligence-gathering bombshells. Reporting and collection A number of State Department memos ask...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>