<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7402">little johnny</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:03:14" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7402-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7402_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:03:15">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/02/eruptions-not-quiet-sun-may-have-triggered-little-ice-age/</link><title>Volcanoes, rather than a quiet Sun, may have triggered the Little Ice Age</title><description>... it take to knock the Earths climate off balance? In the case of the Little Ice Age, a recent..., the most familiar of them being the "Little Ice Age." The effects of the Little Ice Age were especially... deposits as markers. It would be a mistake to characterize the Little Ice Age as a simple, s...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7402-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7402_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:04:06">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/09/indonesias-samalas-volcano-may-have-kickstarted-the-little-ice-age/</link><title>Indonesia’s Samalas volcano may have kickstarted the Little Ice Age</title><description>..., and it could have been one of the events that started a 600-year cold period called the Little Ice Age.Volcanic eruptions... be.More important, though, could be Samalas volcanos role in triggering the Little Ice Age. In a 2012... may have triggered the onset of the Little Ice Age. Although the precise timing varies somewhat...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7402-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7402_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:05:10">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/02/little-red-sled-fun-racing-for-girls/</link><title>Little Red Sled: Fun racing for girls</title><description>...If you have a little girl or if you're a little girl at heart, you may want to consider springing for the new Little Red Sled racing game. It costs just two bucks and, frankly, it's darling..., and otherwise do all the things that Real Men do in their sports games. But Little Red Sled is sweeter...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7402-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7402_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:05:39">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/09/industrial-revolution-likely-brought-the-little-ice-age-to-an-end/</link><title>Industrial Revolution likely brought the Little Ice Age to an end</title><description>... that continues to this day. Their retreat marked the end of the Little Ice Age. But according...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7402-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7402_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:06:23">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/04/court-denies-grooveshark-dmca-protection-for-songs-like-johnny-b-goode/</link><title>Court denies Grooveshark DMCA protection for songs like “Johnny B. Goode”</title><description>..., Chuck Berry's Johnny B. Goode (written in 1958) without Grooveshark's knowledge.A 2010 filing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7402-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7402_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:07:30">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/08/why-johnny-cant-stream-how-video-copyright-went-insane/</link><title>Why Johnny can't stream: How video copyright went insane</title><description>.... When the movie studios sued in the United States, the court had little difficulty claiming... a Santa Clara data center with hundreds of DVD players. When a customer hit play on, say, Little... Little Fockers, the DVD and player would go back into the pool for others to use. This meant...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7402-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7402_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:08:06">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/04/despite-all-my-rage-i-am-still-just-johnny-cage-ars-review-mortal-kombat/</link><title>Despite all my rage I am still just Johnny Cage: Ars reviews Mortal Kombat</title><description>...;s body, shown with neat little cinemas that show the internal organs and musculature of your character...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7402-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7402_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:08:53">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/05/amazon-sets-up-system-to-trade-on-controversial-fan-fiction/</link><title>Amazon sets up system to trade on fan fiction</title><description>... or a parody. Even so, those arguments do little to settle the temper of authors who feel... from fanfic. The launch list of licensors includes those of Gossip Girl, Pretty Little Liars, and Vampire...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7402-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7402_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:09:25">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/09/iphone-5-a-little-bit-taller-a-little-bit-baller/</link><title>iPhone 5: a little bit taller, a little bit baller</title><description>... in our grubby little hands. It's thinner. It's lighter. And it'staller.Apple brought...; it takes a little getting used to, but with a bit of practice I was able to make an almost... like the iPhone 5 tends to add a little extra exposure when you tap on subjects in darker areas...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7402-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7402_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:10:33">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/06/meet-prisms-little-brother-socmint/</link><title>Meet PRISM’s little brother: Socmint</title><description>...For the past two years, a tight-lipped and little talked about unit within the Metropolitan Police has been conducting blanket surveillance of British citizens' public social media conversations.Following an unintentional leak and a detailed investigation, we are finally able to see...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>