<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7403">usc trojans</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:11:16" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7403-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7403_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:11:17">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/01/android-trojans-downloaded-by-millions-still-on-android-market/</link><title>Android Trojans downloaded by millions, still on Android Market</title><description>...Symantec last week identified 13 new malicious applications on the Android Market, saying the combined download figuresreportedly up to 5 millionmake it "the highest distribution of any malware identified so far this year." The applications use Android.Counterclank, which Symantec says is "a bot-like threat that can receive commands to carry out certain actions, as well as steal in...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7403-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7403_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:12:15">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/01/pirated-version-of-iwork-09-contains-a-nasty-trojan/</link><title>Pirated version of iWork '09 contains a nasty trojan</title><description>..., you may end up infected with a trojan. Security firm Intego identified the trojan in question late yesterday. Dubbed OSX.Trojan.iServices.A, the trojan is hidden as an extra packageiWorkServices.pkgin... to install the software, the trojan installs as a startup item in /System/Library/StartupItems/iWorkS...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7403-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7403_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:12:57">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/09/crackdown-on-zeus-trojan-crime-ring-in-progress-60-charged/</link><title>Crackdown on Zeus Trojan crime ring in progress, 60 charged</title><description>...Law enforcement agencies say that over 60 people have been charged with trying to siphon millions of dollars out of banks by using the Zeus Trojan program. Police made about 11 of the arrests in New... Trojan is a sneaky little sucker. It's designed to trick users into downloading the program via...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7403-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7403_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:13:49">http://arstechnica.com/security/2013/06/behold-the-worlds-most-sophisticated-android-trojan/</link><title>Behold, the world’s most sophisticated Android trojan</title><description>... of malicious Windows applications, making it the world's most sophisticated Android Trojan, a security... than to other Android trojans, in terms of its complexity and the number of unpublished vulnerabilities it exploits... comment for this post. The trojan is initially distributed through spammed text messages...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7403-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7403_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:14:45">http://arstechnica.com/security/2013/02/viruses-trojans-and-worms-oh-my-the-basics-on-malware/</link><title>Viruses, Trojans, and worms, oh my: The basics on malware</title><description>...Some say we're living in a "post-PC" world, but malware on PCs is still a major problem for home computer users and businesses.The examples are everywhere: In November, we reported that malware was used to steal information about one of Japan's newest rockets and upload it to computers controlled by hackers. Critical systems at two US power plants were recently found infected...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7403-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7403_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:15:27">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/09/penguin-panic-trojan-targets-windows-iphone-users/</link><title>"Penguin Panic" trojan targets Windows iPhone users</title><description>...iPhone-toting Windows users should keep an eye out for a trojan targeting their somewhat specific... file called Penguin.Panic.zip. When opened, the Troj/Agent-HNY trojan is released and will wreak havoc on Windows systems. The trojan was brought to light by security firm Sophos yesterday, although...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7403-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7403_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:16:12">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2011/09/mac-trojan-poses-as-pdf-to-open-botnet-backdoor/</link><title>Mac trojan poses as PDF to open botnet backdoor</title><description>...; machines into botnet drones. The latter appears to be the case with a new Mac trojan posing as a PDF file... as Trojan-Dropper:OSX/Revir.A, which installs a backdoor, Backdoor:OSX/Imuler.A, onto the user's Mac... end up spreading to a wider audience.As mentioned earlier, this trojan spreads by masking itself...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7403-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7403_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:16:57">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/01/mac-trojan-variant-now-riding-along-with-pirated-photoshop/</link><title>Mac trojan variant now riding along with pirated Photoshop</title><description>...It seems malware writers really know how to stick it to pirates. After Intego identified a trojan... transmits the password when requested by the malware writer. Intego also says that the trojan makes repeated connections to two IP addresses.The first version of the trojan downloaded code that was then...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7403-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7403_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:17:39">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/08/new-android-trojan-records-all-phone-calls/</link><title>New Android trojan records phone calls, shares with remote server</title><description>...A new Android trojan has cropped up that records phone calls and related information, according to a blog post by an employee of security company Total Defense. The trojan is triggered... and settings used by the trojan. According to the post, the trojan presents itself as an "Android...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7403-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7403_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:18:42">http://arstechnica.com/security/2008/12/new-trojan-targets-firefox-masquerades-as-greasemonkey/</link><title>New trojan targets Firefox, masquerades as Greasemonkey</title><description>... the eye of malware authors, as a trojan is now targeting Firefox specifically BitDefender has identified... to the Chrome component of Firefox). The trojan installs itself into Firefoxs add-on directory, registers... of WarCraft account information, and your library card number. Please note, this trojan...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>