<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7405">light therapy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:27:00" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7405-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7405_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:27:01">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/11/light-kills-tumors-that-are-first-targeted-with-a-photosensitive-agent/</link><title>Antibodies and light combine for a cancer-killing therapy</title><description>.... They are one of the most successful targeted cancer therapies that have been tried. But that success has been limited by toxicity issues.Now, monoclonal antibodies have been paired with photodynamic therapy, which harnesses a photosensitizing chemical agent to allow light of a chosen wavelength to kill cells. This approach...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7405-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7405_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:28:00">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/07/the-future-of-lighting/</link><title>The future of lighting: walls of light, LEDs, and glowing trees</title><description>...Light bulbs haven't been sexy tech since Thomas Edison's day, but innovation has come to an industry that has seen relatively little of it for a century. Today, the lighting industry...-decade, a gradual shift toward more energy-efficient light sources has gathered momentum as nation...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7405-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7405_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:28:59">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/07/two-successful-gene-therapy-trials-block-inherited-diseases-in-humans/</link><title>Two successful gene therapy trials block inherited diseases in humans</title><description>... using a promising new method of gene therapy.The idea behind gene therapy is to replace a faulty... idea, though, has been challenging to achieve in practice. The first commercial gene therapy product... therapy technique, both these new studies have either prevented the onset of a serious...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7405-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7405_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:29:41">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/12/a-review-of-slow-and-fast-light/</link><title>Playing tricks with the speed of light</title><description>...Most people learn in physics class that light goes one speed: faster than anything else... on the premise that "nothing in normal space can go faster than light, but if you can do funny things to space, you can go faster than light."Conveniently, a recent review in Science delves into how...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7405-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7405_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:30:40">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/04/solar-cells-must-emit-light-to-attain-perfection-research-suggests/</link><title>Solar cells must emit light to attain perfection</title><description>... means of boosting the efficiency of flatplate solar cells by making them emit light. "What..., photons from some external light source (the sun, preferably) entering a solar cell excite...," a material that absorbs light must also emit light, to an extent determined...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7405-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7405_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:31:36">http://arstechnica.com/science/2008/10/weaving-light-through-an-obstacle-course/</link><title>Weaving light through an obstacle course</title><description>...Many of the things we see as opaque are not all that opaque. Take a sugar cube for instance: an individual sugar crystal is quite transparent, but the tiny reflections from its surface act to scatter the light a little bit. Put lots of them together and suddenly no light makes it through the cube and the object appears white. Flesh is similarfor instance, certain colors, particularly the near inf...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7405-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7405_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:32:25">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/12/getting-a-clear-view-through-the-fog-with-scattered-laser-light/</link><title>Getting a view through the fog with scattered laser light</title><description>... provides near-perfect privacy while still allowing light into a room. Similarly, biological tissue... window. To obtain an image, the researchers shine light through the window from many different angles. The light, when it happens to hit a fluorescent part of the material, creates a glow...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7405-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7405_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:33:05">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/04/with-californias-red-light-cameras-are-pictures-admissible-evidence/</link><title>With California’s red light cameras, are pictures admissible evidence?</title><description>... light. She instantly became one of countless people nationwide ticketed by a red light camera.The.... She appealed and lost.Further ReadingPerfect enforcement: On the ground in the red light camera warsIn 2013, red light camera use declined in the US for the first time. She based her argument in part...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7405-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7405_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:33:37">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/06/metro-last-light-e3-embargo/</link><title>Metro: Last Light won't be dumbed down, will be improved</title><description>...Metro 2033 remains one of my favorite games from last year, and I'm not alone in my enthusiasm for the title: the game's cult following is dedicated and large. The sense of dread and despair that spreads throughout the game, along with the supernatural touches that give the world such a surreal feeling, made this an interesting entry into the world of first-person shooters. It's no...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7405-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7405_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:34:16">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/06/new-oled-lighting-panel-hopes-to-outshine-fluorescent-bulbs/</link><title>New OLED lighting panel hopes to outshine fluorescent bulbs</title><description>...With the arrival of its OLED lighting panel, the Lumiblade GL350, Philips Lighting is attempting to quietly usher in the era of practical OLED lighting. The diminutive squares, 3.3mm thick with edges.... As organic light-emitting diodes go, that's really rather punchy. It's this higher output...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>