<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7406">does my child have adhd</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:35:29" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7406-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7406_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:35:30">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/03/hyperactivity-helps-adhd-boys-with-memorization/</link><title>Hyperactivity helps ADHD boys with memorization</title><description>... to focus on tasks like learning letters and numbers. Children with ADHD (Attention-Deficit... professor Mark Rapport and his fellow researchers report in the Journal of Abnormal Child Psychology that it may actually help children with ADHD concentrate on the task at hand. There isnt a general...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7406-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7406_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:36:12">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/08/ars-does-soylent-day-2-my-god-what-have-i-gotten-myself-into/</link><title>Ars does Soylent, Day 2: My God, what have I gotten myself into</title><description>... in my bellythe kind that could either be the sign of some harmless gas or the harbinger of the poopocalypse. I stayed in, instead watching a couple of episodes of The Wire with my wife, who ate a fine healthy dinner while I sipped my Soylent with an ever-souring gut. A bit after 8pm, the gas...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7406-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7406_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:37:03">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/02/signup-for-skybox-site-launches-dubbed-microsoft-my-phone/</link><title>Signup for SkyBox site launches, dubbed Microsoft My Phone</title><description>... the service "Microsoft My Phone." Make of that name what you will. The site lists the following features: Back up phone information to a password-protected web site: Microsoft My Phone..., calendar appointments, photos, and other information that you stored on My Phone to a compatible new...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7406-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7406_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:37:59">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/05/doe-gets-earful-from-smart-grid-companies-over-stimulus/</link><title>DOE gets earful from smart grid companies over stimulus</title><description>... money to fund smart grid projects. In order to get things moving quickly, the DOE had a short timeframe... the deadline, and the DOE has already acted to implement some of their suggestions. We've gone through some of the feedback provided to the DOE and talked with Loraine Hariton, Director for Public...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7406-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7406_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:38:40">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/12/childs-play-update-12600-raised-so-far-lets-keep-going/</link><title>Child's Play update: $12,600 raised so far, let's keep going</title><description>...I hope you'll indulge a touch of my personal life in this post. My wife's last pregnancy did not go well, and we ultimately ended up spending over two months in the hospital when our son..., and Steam. Every night I stayed up and beat classic games, allowing me to escape my surroundings...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7406-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7406_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:39:40">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/06/child-of-eden-is-an-emotional-swirling-painting-of-a-game/</link><title>Child of Eden is an emotional, swirling painting of a game</title><description>.... While Child of Eden may not share that game's name, it's the sequel to Rez,created... at once, you can increase your score. Child of Eden adds another wrinkle to the game with a machine gun attack that does less damage than your lock-on shots, but allows constant firing and can destroy...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7406-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7406_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:40:13">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/11/childs-play-2010-walking-dead-limbo-powerful-magnets/</link><title>Child's Play 2010: Walking Dead! Limbo ! Powerful magnets!</title><description>... sick is no fun; being sick when you're a child and suffering from a serious illness can be downright scary. When hospitals can hand a child a DS or a PSP with a game or two so they can pass..., but Invincible remains one of my favorite comic series of the past few years. This is the best way...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7406-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7406_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:41:08">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/03/predicting-silly-mistakes-from-inattentiveness/</link><title>Predicting mistakes from inattentiveness</title><description>... that the brain does give clues before it wanders. In their experiment, Mazaheri and his colleagues asked... activity for attention can also help people with ADHD. It would be an improvement over current methods...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7406-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7406_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:41:41">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/05/my-phone-beta-goes-public/</link><title>My Phone beta goes public</title><description>...It looks like the service upgrade that LiveSide warned My Phone users of yesterday was more than just your typical service downtime. Microsoft today announced that its new My Phone service is now available as a public beta. In celebration, Microsoft has given My Phone a new icon (pictured...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7406-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7406_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:42:13">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/04/online-child-porn-victims-lose-at-supreme-court/</link><title>Online child porn victims lose at Supreme Court</title><description>...A deeply divided Supreme Court set limits Wednesday to how much monetary compensation child victims... million judgement awarded to a woman whose pictures of her being raped as a child were widely..., does not have to pay that large sum, which is the total amount of damages the victim's lawyers...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>