<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7407">kim kardashian pregnant</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:42:55" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7407-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7407_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:42:56">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/08/dotcom-lawyer-nz-police-stopped-pregnant-wife-from-calling-a-doctor/</link><title>Dotcom lawyer: NZ police stopped pregnant wife from calling a doctor</title><description>...A pregnant Mona Dotcom was prevented from quickly seeking medical attention after the police seized the family's cell phones and vehicles during the dramatic January raid on the mansion she shared with her husband, Kim Dotcom.At least that's how Dotcom defense lawyer Paul Davison told...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7407-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7407_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:43:47">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/02/megauploads-kim-dotcom-granted-bail-barred-from-internet/</link><title>Megaupload's Kim Dotcom granted bail, barred from Internet</title><description>...AUCKLAND, New ZealandFile-sharing magnate Kim Dotcom was granted bail Wednesday morning New Zealand time, after the judge hearing his application ruled that the Megaupload founder has no access... pregnant wife Mona and three children to live in the mansion, however.The lawyers acting for the US...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7407-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7407_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:44:45">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/03/kim-dotcom-loses-key-evidence-ruling-at-nz-supreme-court/</link><title>Kim Dotcom loses key evidence ruling at NZ Supreme Court</title><description>...Megaupload founder Kim Dotcom received a big setback today in his ongoing legal quest to remain free in New Zealand, rather than in a US prison.Dotcom and his lawyers have lost a bid to force the United States to show them the evidence they plan to use in making their argument that he should be extradited. The Supreme Court of New Zealand published a 123-page rulingtoday, detailing their decision...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7407-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7407_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:45:39">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/12/extradition-trial-for-kim-dotcom-not-until-august-2013/</link><title>Extradition trial for Kim Dotcom? Not until August 2013</title><description>... for Kim Dotcom. The hearing is now set to take place in August 2013, after being postponed once... High Court ruled that the FBI had to provide Kim Dotcoms lawyers with more of the evidence..., putting another roadblock up in the effort to convict Kim Dotcom for piracy....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7407-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7407_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:46:27">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/01/in-apparent-scam-kim-dotcom-impersonator-contacts-ars/</link><title>In apparent scam, Kim Dotcom impersonator contacts Ars</title><description>...I've gotten a series of e-mails from Kim Dotcom these past few days. That's not as unusual as you might expect: despite being the defendant in an international criminal copyright case and founder of the infamous new file-sharing site Mega, Dotcom takes plenty of time to reach out to us press people.But these latest e-mails weren't from the real Dotcom. As the larger-than-life busin...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7407-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7407_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:47:06">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/06/kim-dotcom-could-be-safe-from-extradition-by-us-authorities-until-2014/</link><title>Kim Dotcom could be safe from extradition to the US until 2014</title><description>...As a result of Kim Dotcoms ongoing legal battles in New Zealand, his extradition hearing has now been delayed yet again. A North Shore District Court spokesperson told the Australian Associated Press... Zealand ruled (PDF) that Kim Dotcom should gain access to the data seized by local police during...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7407-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7407_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:48:02">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/09/kim-dotcoms-megabox-music-service-or-malware/</link><title>Kim Dotcom's Megabox: Music service or malware?</title><description>...While Kim Dotcom awaits the outcome of the increasingly scandalous efforts by the US and New Zealand governments to extradite him to face charges of copyright infringement, the founder of Megaupload is preparing to launch a new business line soona cloud music service called Megabox.Dotcom told...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7407-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7407_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:48:32">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/07/kim-dotcom-offers-to-come-to-us-rather-than-be-extradited/</link><title>Kim Dotcom offers to come to US rather than be extradited</title><description>...Even though he has been busy accusing Vice President Joe Biden of orchestrating the raidon his home(a charge since denied), having pool parties,and producing ridiculous rap videos, Kim Dotcom now says hes ready to come to the United States, rather than be extradited, as a way of speeding...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7407-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7407_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:49:05">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/07/kim-dotcom-says-twitter-facebook-refuse-to-recognize-him/</link><title>Kim Dotcom says Twitter, Facebook refuse to recognize him (Updated)</title><description>...Kim Dotcom, the Megaupload mogul, in addition to having a rough time with American and New Zealand... not to believe that "Dotcom" is his real last name. We reported earlier this year that Kim Dotcom had his name legally changed from his birth name, Kim Schmitz, to Kim Dotcom, in 2005.The two...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7407-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7407_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:49:52">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/12/us-unveils-the-case-against-kim-dotcom-revealing-e-mails-and-financial-data/</link><title>The case against Kim Dotcom, finally revealed</title><description>...Nearly two years after Kim Dotcom's New Zealand mansion was raided by police, US authorities have made their case as to why the man behind Megaupload shouldn't simply go bankrupt like previous copyright violators before havehe should go to jail, they argue.In a 191-page "Summary of Evidence," (PDF) government lawyers marshal Skype chats, financial data, and dozens of e-mails t...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>