<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7408">tom cruise</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:50:36" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7408-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7408_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:50:37">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/10/tom-clancys-endwar-goes-portable-on-ds-psp/</link><title>Tom Clancy's EndWar goes portable on DS, PSP</title><description>...Ubisoft has announced that its upcoming console RTS Tom Clancys EndWar will also be getting the portable treatment, coming to both the Nintendo DS and PlayStation Portable. The game has players.... The PSP and DS version of Tom Clancys EndWar will be released on November 4....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7408-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7408_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:51:26">http://arstechnica.com/business/2014/04/github-co-founder-quits-after-investigator-finds-errors-of-judgment/</link><title>GitHub co-founder quits after investigator finds “errors of judgment”</title><description>... against Tom and his wife of sexual or gender-based harassment or retaliation, or of a sexist...;the investigator did find evidence of mistakes and errors of judgment. In light of these findings, Tom has submitted his resignation, which the company has accepted. Tom has been a huge part of this company...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7408-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7408_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:51:56">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/04/new-fcc-chairman-is-former-lobbyist-for-cable-and-wireless-industries/</link><title>New FCC chairman is “former lobbyist for cable and wireless industries”</title><description>...President Barack Obama will nominate venture capitalist Tom Wheeler to be the next chairman... since 2005. "Tom was President of the National Cable Television Association (NCTA) from 1979... Tom for years, I believe that he will be an independent, proactive Chairman who will not allow...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7408-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7408_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:52:31">http://arstechnica.com/business/2014/02/fcc-throws-out-plan-to-question-reporters-about-news-coverage/</link><title>FCC throws out plan to question reporters about news coverage</title><description>... as the reasoning behind the decisions.Yesterday, FCC Chairman Tom Wheeler told staff to remove the offending...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7408-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7408_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:53:16">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/02/fcc-thinks-it-can-overturn-state-laws-that-restrict-public-broadband/</link><title>FCC thinks it can overturn state laws that restrict public broadband</title><description>...When FCC Chairman Tom Wheeler announced his net neutrality plans today, he also said he wants to examine state laws that prohibit or restrict the ability of cities and towns to offer Internet service.As we've written, ISP lobby groups have won restrictions on municipal broadband in 20 states...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7408-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7408_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:54:00">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/10/ex-cable-and-wireless-lobbyist-confirmed-as-fcc-chairman/</link><title>Ex-cable and wireless lobbyist confirmed as FCC chairman</title><description>...Tom Wheeler will take over as chairman of the Federal Communications Commission after receiving unanimous approval by the Senate today.Wheeler, a venture capitalist and former headof the National Cable Television Association (NCTA) andCellular Telecommunications Internet Association (CTIA...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7408-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7408_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:54:44">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/01/ubisofts-h-a-w-x-kicks-off-new-cohesive-clancy-universe/</link><title>Ubisoft's H.A.W.X. kicks off cohesive Clancy universe, MMO?</title><description>...When Ubisoft acquired the full rights to the Tom Clancy name, the company made clear its plans that integrating the assorted Tom Clancy gamesRainbow Six, Ghost Recon, Splinter Cell, and so oninto.... For the moment, its an air combat game with some connection with other [Tom Clancy games...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7408-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7408_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:55:31">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/01/obama-on-net-neutrality-i-wouldnt-be-president-without-an-open-internet/</link><title>Obama on net neutrality: I wouldn’t be president without an open Internet</title><description>... of the president's response:The new commissioner of the FCC, Tom Wheeler, who I appointed, I know... making there, based on my conversations with Tom Wheeler before he was appointed I'm pretty...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7408-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7408_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:56:48">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/06/fccs-new-chairman-wants-to-end-ban-on-cell-phone-unlocking/</link><title>FCC’s new chairman wants to end ban on cell phone unlocking</title><description>...The newly appointed chairman of the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) said today that he wants to end the ban on consumers unlocking their cell phones in order to switch wireless carriers. Tom Wheeler, a former lobbyist for the cable and wireless industries, was nominated by President Obama...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7408-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7408_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 03:57:32">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/05/red-hat-hires-lead-jruby-developers-alongside-engine-yard-partnership/</link><title>Red Hat hires lead JRuby developers alongside Engine Yard partnership</title><description>...Charles Nutter and Tom Enebo, key developers behind the JRuby project, are joining Red Hat. The news was announced at JRubyConf 2012 this morning and later confirmed by Nutter on Twitter.JRuby is an open source implementation of the Ruby programming language that targets the Java virtual machine...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>