<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7411">lenin mausoleum open</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:16:36" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7411-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7411_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:16:38">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2008/10/this-week-in-open-source-distro-betas-new-mono-and-python/</link><title>This week in open source: distro betas, new Mono and Python</title><description>... approval process for Microsofts Office Open XML (OOXML) format. This week also brought the long-awaited release of Mono 2.0, the latest version of Novells open-source implementation of the Microsoft .NET... and developers to try out the new version of Mono. Another leap forward for open-source programming...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7411-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7411_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:17:10">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2008/12/this-week-in-open-source-g1-wordpress-qt/</link><title>This week in open source: G1, Wordpress, Qt</title><description>... Thunderbird to tango: The open source Thunderbird e-mail client will get a new Linux theme for version... the bootloader of the Google phone. Stay tuned for more open source software news next week and keep an eye on Open Ended, our journal for Linux and open source software....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7411-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7411_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:17:45">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/01/this-week-in-open-source-kde-ext4-and-android/</link><title>This week in open source: KDE, Ext4, and Android</title><description>... that it delivers significantly better performance. IE continues losing market share to open source... of last year, while open source alternatives such as Firefox and Chrome continue to climb up the charts. Fedora... for the net panel. Google opens Jaiku source code: Google will no longer be maintaining the Jaiku...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7411-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7411_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:18:24">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/01/this-week-in-open-source-gtk-evolution-android/</link><title>This week in open source: GTK+, Evolution, Android</title><description>... release GUI debugging tool for GTK+: Two developers from VMware have released an open source GUI... the Android Cupcake soft keyboard. Stay tuned next week for more news from Open Ended, Ars Technicas journal about Linux and open source software....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7411-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7411_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:19:15">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2010/09/drones-chumbys-and-big-business-too-the-open-hardware-summit/</link><title>Drones, Chumbys, and big business: the Open Hardware Summit</title><description>...Last week, the New York Hall of Science played host to the Open Hardware Summit, a gathering... to Texas Instruments. Open Hardware may not have had the success of its software cousin when it comes... the Open Hardware route. Over the course of the day, two basic rationales for going open became apparent...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7411-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7411_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:20:00">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/05/obama-orders-agencies-to-make-data-open-machine-readable-by-default/</link><title>Obama orders agencies to make data open, machine-readable by default</title><description>...President Barack Obama issued an executive order today that aims to make "open and machine.... It would also expand an order issued in 2012 to open up government systems with public interfaces... resources shall be open and machine readable," the president's order reads. "Government...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7411-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7411_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:21:03">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2008/12/this-week-in-open-source-kde-4-2-python-3-and-opensolaris/</link><title>This week in open source: KDE 4.2b1, Python 3, and OpenSolaris hit 'Net</title><description>... distribution built on open source Solaris technology. The new release isnt capable of replacing... of Moonlight 1.0, an open source implementation of Microsofts Silverlight framework... that enables G1 screen autorotation. Stay tuned for more open source software news next week and keep...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7411-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7411_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:21:53">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2008/11/this-week-in-open-source-fedora-10-ubuntu-9-04-alpha/</link><title>This week in open source: Fedora 10, Ubuntu 9.04 alpha</title><description>...: The open source Telepathy messaging framework has gained preliminary support for file transfers.... SCOs futile legal assault on Linux will continue. Stay tuned for more open source software news next week and keep an eye on Open Ended, our journal for Linux and open source software....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7411-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7411_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:22:36">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2008/10/this-week-in-open-source-openoffice-org-3-firefox-3-1-b1/</link><title>This week in open source: OpenOffice.org 3, Firefox 3.1 b1</title><description>... Open XML (OOXML) format, and adds long-awaited native support for Apple's Mac OS X platform... administration workflow. Linux enthusiasts have had high hopes for the open platform's success..., Ajax, and various HTML tags. Stay tuned next week for more of our open source coverage, including...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7411-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7411_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:23:26">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/01/vietnam-mandates-government-adoption-of-open-source/</link><title>Vietnam mandates government adoption of open source</title><description>...;s government to open source software by the end of 2010. The ambitious plan, which was reported Wednesday by VietnamNet calls for rapid adoption of open source software and extensive training to ensure... this transition to be completely by the end of 2010. In addition to the open source migration...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>