<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7412">when queen elisabeth</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:24:12" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7412-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7412_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:24:13">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/08/singstar-queen-about-what-youd-expect-epic-difficult/</link><title>SingStar Queen about what you'd expect: epic, difficult</title><description>.... My vote? Queen. No front man had better charisma, no band mastered as many styles, no song catalog... so effortlessly.I was more than a little excited when Sony sent over a copy of SingStar Queen for the PS3. The SingStar franchise and Queen were made for each other, and the track list combined a good...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7412-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7412_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:24:32">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/singstar-to-get-extensive-set-of-queen-tracks/</link><title>Singstar to go classic rock with Queen release</title><description>...-imitated but never-duplicated Queen. Singstar Queen, which will be released for both the PS3...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7412-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7412_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:25:57">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/12/dairy-queen-using-video-game-as-part-of-new-marketing-plan/</link><title>Dairy Queen using video game as part of new marketing plan</title><description>..., a game designed to help freshen up Dairy Queens brand reputation. The New York Times is reporting... Hathaway to revitalize the Dairy Queen brand. The target audience for DQ Tycoon? Casual gamers, of course. Jill Anderson, the senior marketing manager for Dairy Queen, claims that a lot of these stay...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7412-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7412_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:26:46">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/08/this-week-in-game-releases-august-3-9-2009/</link><title>This week in game releases: August 3-9, 2009</title><description>...Pick of the week: SingStar Queen (PS2, PS3)While Rock Band and Guitar Hero may get all the glory when it comes to the rhythm game genre, we here at Opposable Thumbs have a soft spot for Sony's SingStar karaoke series. There's just something great about getting a bunch of friends together, and then looking (and sounding) like idiots while playing the game. The series has taken a turn tow...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7412-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7412_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:27:19">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/01/why-tropical-forests-have-more-tree-species-than-us-and-canada-combined/</link><title>Why tropical forests have more tree species than US and Canada combined</title><description>... to the observed tropical diversity.This explanation is known as the Red Queen hypothesis, which gets its name from a statement the Red Queen made to Alice in Lewis Carrolls Through the Looking-Glass:Now, here, you see, it takes all the running you can do to keep in the same place.The Red Queen Hypothesis...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7412-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7412_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:28:27">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/11/queen-we-sank-the-armada-we-can-sink-some-p2p-pirates/</link><title>Queen: We sank the Armada, we can sink some P2P pirates!</title><description>...Yesterday at 11:30am, the Queen made her way to Parliament in a coach, entered the robing room... to see the Queen, seated on her throne, who then opened a new session of Parliament with her customary... with their Speaker, Her Majesty was pleased to speak as follows," begins the transcript, and the Queen...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7412-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7412_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:29:13">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/12/purging-the-queens-english-of-tweet-app-and-sexting/</link><title>Purging the Queen's English of "tweet," "app," and "sexting"</title><description>...Using an app to tweet about sexting? One university wants you to watch your language.Lake Superior State University, though no doubt a fine institution of higher learning, doesn't have big name recognition. But it does have one annual PR stunt created by the school's public relations director back in 1975: a "word banishment" list for the year that just ended.The list's f...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7412-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7412_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:30:00">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/01/ninjavideo-queen-gets-22-months-in-jail-owes-200000-to-hollywood/</link><title>NinjaVideo "queen" gets 22 months in jail, owes $200,000 to Hollywood</title><description>...NinjaVideo.net's "queen" is going to jailand paying the MPAA over $200,000. A federal judge today sentenced Hana Amal "Queen Phara" Beshara to 22 months in a West Virginia prison and enrolled her (at her request) in a drug rehab program there. Beshara was the public face...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7412-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7412_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:30:40">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/12/why-some-wasps-cant-recognize-faces/</link><title>Wasps with many queens will remember your face as they sting you</title><description>... skills. Since there is more than one queen in each nest, having a hierarchy becomes important; wasps.... fuscatus, but with one important difference: each nest has just one queen. The researchers hypothesized...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7412-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7412_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:31:24">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/09/ninjavideo-queen-cops-to-criminal-copyright-infringement/</link><title>NinjaVideo "queen" cops to copyright infringement, admits $200,000 in earnings</title><description>...Hana Beshara, the co-founder and public face of the NinjaVideo movie-sharing site, has agreed to plead guilty to conspiracy and criminal copyright infringement. Each count carries a sentence of up to five years in prison.According to the government, Beshara has admitted to personally earning more than $200,000 from operating the site, and she has agreed to forfeit assets seized by Immigration and...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>