<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7413">alkan piano</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:32:28" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7413-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7413_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:32:29">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/04/paywall-startup-piano-believes-it-can-fix-publishers-problems/</link><title>Paywall startup Piano believes it can fix publishers' problems</title><description>... all that, and has had some limited success so far in Europe. Piano Media announced on Tuesday... funding will allow the site to expand globally."Piano is a united system for payments," Tom Bella, Pianos chief executive told Deutsche Welle, Germanys international broadcaster, in June 2011...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7413-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7413_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:33:33">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/10/channeling-the-piano-man-a-preview-of-the-rock-band-3-keyboard/</link><title>Channeling the Piano Man: a preview of the Rock Band 3 keyboard</title><description>...Rhythm games have been run into the ground, with multiple releases in multiple franchises choking retail shelves with plastic guitars and marked-down prices. Rock Band 3 has a hard road ahead of it, with the Guitar Hero series having already released DJ Hero 2 to good reviews, and more hardware being sold to gamers in order to take advantage of the "Pro" experience. Rock Band 3 is comin...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7413-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7413_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:34:15">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/10/how-mits-media-lab-gave-birth-to-hyperviolins-and-guitar-hero/</link><title>How MIT's Media Lab gave birth to Guitar Hero and hyperviolins</title><description>... involved the piano, specifically the player piano, a machine that played a regular upright piano... was then sent over the network to a MIDI piano that resided in the basement. From there, he moved...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7413-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7413_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:34:53">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/08/sealing-leaky-southern-ocean-carbon-pump-boosts-ice-ages/</link><title>Sealing leaky Southern Ocean carbon pump boosts ice ages</title><description>..., they examined several proxies for dust transport to the Southern Ocean. First, they measured alkanes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7413-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7413_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:35:51">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/07/ars-technicast-episode-6-music-to-our-ears/</link><title>Ars Technicast, Episode 6–Music to our ears</title><description>...In this weeks episode, we get up close and personal with music. Ryan and Jacqui, who both studied music, trade stories about playing digital upright pianos and evaluate the quality of their sound. We also discuss iPad apps used for music making and performance. Not all of us compose or play music...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7413-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7413_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:37:20">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/09/garageband-finally-gets-some-attention-more-lessons-added/</link><title>GarageBand finally gets some attention, more lessons added</title><description>... musicians to learn piano and guitar fundamentals as well as popular songs from their favorite artists...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7413-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7413_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:38:03">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/10/building-the-robots-of-marsand-running-them-from-manhattan/</link><title>Building the robots of Mars—and running them from Manhattan</title><description>... refurbishing pianos ended up setting the agenda on another planet from an office in Midtown Manhattan.Many... time and every time thereafterand use as little power as possible in doing so.From pianos to spaceThis... up working on restoring pianos. And, in doing so, he fell in love with the mechanics of a well-made...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7413-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7413_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:38:49">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/10/apple-announces-ilife-11-facetime-for-mac/</link><title>Apple announces iLife '11, FaceTime for Mac</title><description>... on the guitar and piano. Instruments are not included (the piano keyboard window is a poor substitute for an actual piano), so your mileage may vary. But if you've had a guitar lying around for a while...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7413-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7413_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:39:32">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/02/friday-apple-links-dancing-with-the-woz-edition/</link><title>Friday Apple Links: Dancing with the Woz edition</title><description>... and piano-playing. "I had an ergonomic problem and I paired it with a motivation," Westerman told... the piano was so much more graceful and expressive than using a computer keyboard, and I thought how great it would be if I pulled some of that expression from the piano to the computer experience...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7413-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7413_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:40:06">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/02/happy-birthday-copyright-defense-those-words-and-text-are-ours/</link><title>“Happy Birthday” copyright defense: Those “words” and “text” are ours</title><description>... most, it covers a particular piano arrangement and a second verse to Happy Birthday which has no commercial...." (Emphasis added.) The certificate further states: ( is claimed on arrangement as easy piano...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>