<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7415">most anticipated games of 2013</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:48:34" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7415-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7415_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:48:35">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/07/first-look-onenote-2013/</link><title>First look: OneNote 2013</title><description>... friendliness.OneNote is one of only two applications in the Office 2013 suite getting this treatment (the other is the Lync client); all the other Office 2013 applications are straightforward desktop apps. We've... application once it becomes available.Of all the applications in Office 2013, the desktop OneNote...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7415-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7415_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:49:12">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/07/first-look-outlook-2013/</link><title>First look: Outlook 2013</title><description>...For many of us, Outlook is the most important part of the entire Office suite. It's where we manage the steady trickle of e-mail that drives and directs our work, it's where we plan our days, and it's where we keep all our business contacts. We may be more directly productive in Word or Excel, but it's Outlook that guides that productivity.In common with the other applications...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7415-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7415_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:50:01">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/02/most-anticipated-games-list/</link><title>20 for 2010: Ars's most anticipated games of the year</title><description>... precious gaming time. And this year looks to be even better. In fact, just narrowing down our list of most anticipated games to 20 was a task itself, and that doesn't even include some of the great...2009 was a great year for gaming, with spectacular blockbusters like Assassin's Creed 2...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7415-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7415_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:51:11">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/07/why-bother-the-sad-state-of-office-2013-touch-support/</link><title>Why bother? The sad state of Office 2013 touch support</title><description>... platform at last with the new Metro-style interface and new Metro-style applications.Office 2013...'s no longer the case with Office 2013. The suite contains a range of improvements to make finger... in the quick access toolbar in the top left of the window.Enlarge / Above, Outlook 2013's ribbon...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7415-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7415_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:51:50">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/07/first-look-excel-2013/</link><title>First look: Excel 2013</title><description>... come as no surprise, then, that most of the changes seen in the Excel 2013 preview (aside... easier to analyze.We've already looked at the major design changes to the Office 2013 suite... version of the product.Enlarge / Like the rest of the Office 2013 suite, Excel wants to keep all your...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7415-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7415_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:52:49">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/02/why-microsofts-new-office-2013-license-may-send-users-to-google-docs/</link><title>Why Microsoft’s new Office 2013 license may send users to Google Docs</title><description>...If you buy a perpetual retail license for Office 2013, it will be locked to the computer you first install it on, forever. Buy a new PC and you won't be allowed to install your existing copy... a year subscription lets you use Office 2013 on up to five PCs, and those licenses float; you...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7415-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7415_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:53:19">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/07/first-look-powerpoint-2013/</link><title>First look: PowerPoint 2013</title><description>.... As with Word and Excel, PowerPoint is a large application. The focus with PowerPoint 2013... with all the Office 2013 applications, PowerPoint 2013 has been given a fresh coat of paint. It has a new icon... ratios, which the application defaults to.Enlarge / PowerPoint 2013 with its new look and feel...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7415-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7415_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:54:10">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/07/behind-the-joystick-at-the-evo-2013-fighting-games-championship/</link><title>Behind the joystick at the Evo 2013 fighting games championship</title><description>...LAS VEGASThe night before I left for Evolution 2013, I mentioned to a few friends that I wasn't going to be around for the weekend because I was heading to a big Street Fighter tournament. I'm used to having to explain that a bit: yes, people still play Street Fighter and other fighting games. Yes, people travel from all across the world to compete. And,yes, this is basically the Olympi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7415-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7415_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:55:33">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/04/apples-wwdc-2013-tickets-sold-out-in-a-record-two-minutes/</link><title>Apple’s WWDC 2013 tickets sold out in a record two minutes (or less)</title><description>...Apple's 2013 Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC) appears to have sold out in (wait for it) about two minutes. What we originally thought was a joke appears to actually be true, according to numerous developers who went to buy a ticket Thursday. This marked a new record for Apple's increasingly popular conference.Apple made an unusual move this year when announcing the dates for WWDC....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7415-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7415_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:56:19">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/06/photo-gallery-a-day-at-wwdc-2013/</link><title>Photo gallery: a day at WWDC 2013</title><description>... the keynote, developers began swarming San Francisco while wearing their signature WWDC 2013 jackets... 2013 jackets. Jacqui Cheng Moscone West decorated and ready for WWDC to begin. Jacqui Cheng... from Apple's dev community wore their WWDC 2013 jackets. Jacqui Cheng This is Clint Ecker, our intrepid...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>