<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7416">release date bioshock infinite</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:57:07" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7416-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7416_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:57:08">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/03/four-years-in-the-making-bioshock-infinite-hits-october-16/</link><title>Four years in the making, BioShock Infinite will hit October 16</title><description>...Developer Irrational Games has revealed that BioShock Infinite will be available for the Xbox 360, PS3, and PC in North America on October 16, 2012, with an international release October 19.Irrational President and Creative Director Ken Levine said the upcoming title has been "our sole focus for the last four years," and will be the culmination of a "vision for a follow up that dwa...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7416-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7416_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:57:55">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/12/oh-lord-ken-levine-didnt-remove-religious-lyrics-from-bioshock-infinite-trailer/</link><title>Oh, Lord: Ken Levine didn't remove religious lyrics from Bioshock Infinite trailer</title><description>...A new trailer for Bioshock Infinite was shown during the 2011 Video Game Awards, featuring in-engine gameplay while a new cover of the religious classic "Will the Circle Be Unbroken" plays over the images. The song is sung by Courtnee Draper, the voice actress who plays Elizabeth, the lead in the game.A few people online have already picked up on the fact that this version of the popula...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7416-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7416_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:58:38">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/09/10-minute-bioshock-infinite-trailer-hallucinatory-beautiful/</link><title>10-minute Bioshock Infinite trailer hallucinatory, beautiful</title><description>...It's rare that we run a post that consists mostly of "hey, watch this video." That said... hey, watch this video: Infinite Many people argued that we didn't need a sequel to Bioshock, but Bioshock 2 was enjoyable and very much worth the return trip to Rapture. At the end...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7416-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7416_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:59:08">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/07/the-14-minute-bioshock-infinite-demo-your-friday-must-see-video/</link><title>Your Friday must-see video: 14 minute Bioshock Infinite demo</title><description>...At E3, the press saw a demo of Bioshock Infinite played by Ken Levine, and it was glorious. While... Best of Show.Now, the whole demo has been released for wider consumption, and I'm going to stop writing and just let you watch the incredible video. Enjoy!Tags: GameTrailers.com, GTTV - BioShock...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7416-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7416_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 04:59:55">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/07/bioshock-infinite-dlc-brings-it-back-to-rapture/</link><title>Bioshock Infinite DLC brings it back to Rapture</title><description>...The First trailer for Part 1 of Bioshock Infinite: Burial at Sea. Bioshock Infinite DLC is starting to arrive, and Irrational Games has announced plans for a release that will take both of the games central characters back to Rapture, the setting of the first two Bioshock games. Entitled "Burial at Sea," the DLC will allow players to play as both Booker and Elizabeth.Burial at Sea opens...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7416-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7416_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:00:42">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/07/ask-ars-is-bioshock-infinite-going-to-be-one-long-escort-mission/</link><title>Ask Ars: will Bioshock Infinite be one long escort mission?</title><description>... our helpful tips page.Q: I'm really excited about Bioshock Infinite, but every time I see... mission?Elizabeth is one of the main characters of Bioshock Infinite, and after spending most of her life... to Bioshock Infinite without worry....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7416-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7416_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:01:46">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/05/bioshock-infinite-writeup-embargoed-to-death-and-back/</link><title>Bioshock Infinite preview: my beautiful dark twisted fantasy</title><description>... her there.This is the world of Bioshock Infinite, a game that was demoed for the press at a pre-E3 event.... Some fucked up part of my life."Bioshock Infinite is coming to the PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC...;I once dated a girl who had an abusive ex-boyfriend, and I saw conv...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7416-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7416_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:02:55">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/09/bioshock-2s-official-release-date-announced/</link><title>Bioshock 2 's official release date announced</title><description>...Take-Two Games has officially announced a new release date for Bioshock 2: Sea of Dreams. The new..., the game's upcoming release date was announced: "The wait is over! On February 9th, 2010... months away." Bioshock 2 was originally slated to be...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7416-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7416_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:04:05">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/02/bioshock-developer-irrational-games-announces-its-winding-down/</link><title>Bioshock developer Irrational Games announces it’s “winding down”</title><description>...In a surprise announcement on the Irrational Games website today, Irrational cofounder and creative director Ken Levine announced that the development house behind BioShock Infinite would be "winding down" as Levine moves on to start "a smaller, more entrepreneurial endeavor at [Irrational owner] Take-Two.""Seventeen years is a long time to do any job, even the best one,&amp;...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7416-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7416_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:05:09">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/03/ubisoft-teases-may-27-release-date-for-watch-dogs/</link><title>Ubisoft teases May 27 release date for Watch Dogs [Updated]</title><description>... game Watch Dogs will hit on May 27, the company announced today.The release date appears at the end of a new, story-focused trailer that first appeared on Xbox.com; it was later released... November 19 release date. "In a context of growing successes for mega-blockbusters...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>