<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7417">dota 2 heroes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:05:46" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7417-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7417_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:05:47">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/10/dj-hero-2-improves-virtual-wheels-of-steel-is-a-must-buy/</link><title>DJ Hero 2 improves virtual wheels of steel, is a must-buy</title><description>...DJ Hero was an original and brave release in a market clogged with rhythm games, and the sequel is no different.This is a game that shouldn't be overlooked.DJ Hero 2 improves on the original in every way, and is both a hypnotic solo experience and an engaging party game.There is more to do, and doing it feels better than in the original game. This is the best kind of sequel; the kind that of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7417-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7417_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:07:00">http://arstechnica.com/staff/2013/09/at-the-age-of-32-i-finally-get-sports-thanks-to-dota-2/</link><title>At the age of 32, I finally get sports, thanks to Dota 2</title><description>...I was always at a disadvantage as a child, because I never liked football. In the UK, football (or "soccer" as it's known in some parts of the world) is not merely a past-time or a recreation; it's a way of life.Every lunch break was spent kicking around a ragged tennis ball. The clich of jumpers-as-goalposts was a mundane reality. Saturday afternoons were marked by the interm...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7417-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7417_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:07:46">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/11/got-38000-burning-a-hole-in-your-pocket-why-not-buy-a-dota-2-courier-with-it/</link><title>Got $38,000 burning a hole in your pocket? Why not buy a Dota 2 courier with it?</title><description>...One of the ways in which the excellent free-to-play online strategy game Dota 2 is monetized... up.Some couriers can simply be bought in the Dota 2 store. Others are given as rewards for buying.... PAADABut many couriers can't simply be bought. Dota 2 rand...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7417-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7417_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:08:27">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/06/activision-continues-to-churn-out/</link><title>Guitar Hero gets new guitar, DJ Hero 2 extra turntable, mic</title><description>..., and has revealed details for two new titles in the genre: DJ Hero 2 and Guitar Hero: Warriors of Rock. Both..., and, of course, tracks to play.DJ Hero 2 is the sequel to one of last year's surprise successes... a free track from DJ Hero 2a mash up of Lad...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7417-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7417_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:09:06">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/04/guitar-hero-1-and-2-song-lists-for-smash-hits-revealed/</link><title>Guitar Hero 1 and 2 song lists for Smash Hits, revealed</title><description>... that will make it into the game were revealed. Today? Guitar Hero 2. Let's take a look.Here...;Take It Off"The Exies - "Hey You"And now here are the songs from Guitar Hero 2...Here is how Activision is handling which tracks from Guitar Hero: Smash Hits to reveal:...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7417-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7417_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:09:50">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/07/review-dota-2-is-a-colossal-time-sink-that-you-should-play/</link><title>Review: Dota 2 is a colossal time-sink that you should play</title><description>... by.Until you pick up Dota 2. In Dota 2 you can play for a hundred hours and still be the most useless... actually gain you much additional skill), Dota 2 has become hugely popular. It's the biggest... of Immortality, an item that resurrects you five secon...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7417-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7417_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:10:28">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/10/blizzard-unveils-dota-and-new-panda-focused-wow-expansion/</link><title>Blizzard unveils Dota and new panda-focused WoW expansion</title><description>... that pits two teams of heroes against one another to destroy each others structures on opposite sides of the map. The second was a WoW expansion centering on... panda bears?The DotA game, appropriately named Blizzard Dota, works similar to the popular game League of Legends where players control heroes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7417-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7417_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:11:17">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/08/super-monday-night-combat/</link><title>F2P Super Monday Night Combat will bring third-person shooting to DotA formula</title><description>... of months later. The game combined a simplified take on the DotA formula with third-person shooting... like a single game launch. You can expect more heroes to be added on a continual basis, as well... out there, but a third-person strategy game with heavy DotA influence? That sounds exciting."We worked...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7417-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7417_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:12:23">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/10/guitar-hero-warriors-of-rock-is-more-of-the-same/</link><title>Guitar Hero: Warriors of Rock is more of the same</title><description>... it. That night we played the original two Guitar Hero titles on the PlayStation 2, with the original guitars... forgiving the games had become.That forgiveness extends to Guitar Hero: Warriors of Rock. I've... weird things have gotten in the quest mode. Guitar Hero: Warriors of Rock ps3*, wii, xbox R...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7417-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7417_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:13:03">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/09/tiny-heroes/</link><title>Tiny Heroes on iOS has unique take on tower defense</title><description>...RPG heroes have a sense of entitlement. Whenever they see some goldwhether it's carefully... that's somebody's money, and in Tiny Heroes it's your job to keep that treasure safe.Though Tiny Heroes looks like a fairly standard tower defense game, it cleverly borrows a few ideas...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>