<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7420">Badland game for iphone</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:30:57" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7420-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7420_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:30:58">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/10/ars-looks-at-the-joy-and-pain-of-developing-iphone-games/</link><title>Ars looks at the joy (and pain) of developing iPhone games</title><description>...Creating games has never been easier, but that doesnt mean its a cakewalk, especially when developing for a new platform like the iPhone. Today, we talk with a part-time iPhone game developer named Arshad Rahman, who is also a member of the Ars Technica forums. Rahman has released three games on the App store to date and is creating more with his two-person company Manta Research. Heres his tale....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7420-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7420_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:31:48">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/02/its-good-to-be-1-gameloft-talks-iphone-gaming/</link><title>It's good to be #1: GameLoft talks iPhone gaming</title><description>...GameLoft has developed games for virtually every platform out there, but the company is perhaps best known for its work in the mobile space. And with more than 200 million games sold across all platforms, and 300 different ones available total, the developer has set its sites on the iPhone. Recently, GameLoft revealed that Apple had become its number one customer, with 28 games available on the p...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7420-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7420_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:32:36">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/03/iphone-games-clean-up-at-independent-games-festival/</link><title>iPhone games clean up at Independent Games Festival</title><description>...The 2009 Independent Games Festival (IGF) is wrapping up. This, of course, means that it's time to hand out the awards. 2009 marks the second year that the IGF has included a mobile games event, but this year is the first year that IGF Mobile has included iPhone games. AppleInsider has coverage of the 2009 IGF Mobile winners, and judging by the fact that an iPhone game won in almost every ca...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7420-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7420_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:33:25">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/01/new-iphone-game-summit-set-for-march-09/</link><title>New iPhone Game Summit set for March '09</title><description>...3rd Power LLC has announced that it will be holding the first iPhone Games Summit aimed at educating developers, investors, and executives about the iPhone gaming space. The summit will take place on Thursday, March 19 from 11:00AM until 5:30PM Pacific Time at the Mission Bay Conference Center on the University of California, San Francisco campus. The schedule thus far isnt very informative; the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7420-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7420_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:34:04">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/02/tiny-wings-is-everything-perfect-about-iphone-games/</link><title>Tiny Wings is everything perfect about iPhone games</title><description>... their noses up at iPhone games in general. Let them. There was a legitimate case to be made for the possibility of Angry Birds winning game of the year from the Academy of Interactive Arts and Sciences, no matter how simple or limited the concept. Now,Tiny Wings is the latest gaming success...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7420-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7420_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:35:03">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/12/iphone-as-gaming-console-whee-wii-whee/</link><title>iPhone as gaming console: Whee! Wii! Whee!</title><description>... is that one of those tracks is entirely devoted to iPhone game development technologies. From audio, touch input... on developing for the iPhone as a gaming console. According to Engadget, that program emphasis was echoed... about the iPhone as a gaming device...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7420-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7420_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:35:40">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/11/apple-may-be-building-more-first-party-games-for-iphone/</link><title>Apple may be building more first-party games for iPhone</title><description>...Apple has big on a big gaming push lately, specifically when it comes to the iPhone and iPod touch... at Ensemble Studios. Earlier this year, Devine took a position high up within Apple's iPhone Game... not proud of the iPhone being a game machine," J...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7420-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7420_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:36:07">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/12/apple-reveals-most-downloaded-iphone-games-of-2008/</link><title>Apple reveals most downloaded iPhone games of 2008</title><description>...Apples iPhone has been an interesting device for gaming. The combination of multi-touch control and accelerometers has made for some compelling games since the device launchedboth for-pay ones and free onesfrom developers of all sizes. Games have been steadily gaining attention on the platform...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7420-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7420_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:36:40">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/10/virus-an-iphone-game-that-is-good-for-your-blood-cells/</link><title>Virus: an iPhone game that is good for your blood cells</title><description>...This is an interesting case. I interviewed the creator of this game for a news story about iPhone.... To be fair, though, Virus is really a prototypical iPhone game in that its a very simple, well-executed... the game after the interview. So I told Frank to give it a look and didnt t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7420-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7420_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:37:32">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/01/angry-birds-hd-gets-gaming-award-nod-top-for-pay-apps-are-games/</link><title>Angry Birds HD gets gaming award nod; top paid iPhone apps are games</title><description>...The best portable gaming device is arguably the one you carry the most often, and in that regard the iPhone excels. The hardware is powerful enough to run Unreal Engine 3, iOS developers are creating experiences that are becoming cultural forces, and sales of the hardware remain strong. The power of iPhone gaming is coming into focus, as Angry Birds HD has been nominated for Game of the Year in t...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>