<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7421">story magic flute</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:38:05" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7421-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7421_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:38:07">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/11/apple-magic-mouse-drivers-for-windows/</link><title>Apple Magic Mouse drivers arrive for Windows</title><description>...So you spent $70 on the Apple Magic Mouse and then you realized it would only work with your Mac... Boot Camp. Inside are the goods you need: Magic Mouse drivers for Windows even if you aren't using... reportedly work on Windows 7. Make sure to check out our review of the Magic Mouse. Also let us know how...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7421-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7421_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:39:02">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/07/imacs-with-i7-ssd-and-magic-trackpad-make-their-debut/</link><title>iMacs with i7, SSD, and Magic Trackpad make their debut</title><description>...As anticipated, Apple released an update to the iMac line Tuesday morning. It also unleashed the rumored Magic Trackpad, a wireless "intuitive multi-touch" trackpad that brings gestures to the desktop. The iMacs still sport the same cosmetic design as the previous model, but are packed with more power and can even come equipped with an SSD drive.All iMacs have been given Intel's la...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7421-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7421_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:39:30">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/01/no-edits-from-fragging-noobs-to-walking-down-the-aisle-a-halo-love-story/</link><title>From fragging noobs to walking down the aisle: a Halo love story</title><description>...Its the oldest story in the book: boy meets girl, boy and girl exchange phone numbers, boy and girl... to girl, girl accepts, boy and girl are now getting married. The twist to this magical tale of romance... of this story doesnt end there, as the couple has themed their January wedding around Bungies celebrated...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7421-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7421_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:40:09">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/02/android-take-two-htc-magic-to-launch-sans-keyboard/</link><title>Android, take two: HTC Magic to launch sans keyboard</title><description>... HTC Magic smartphone to its customers. The carrier has nabbed exclusive rights for the UK, Spain... the most of their timethe HTC Magic helps meet that need."The HTC Magic device is a tablet-style phone without the physical keyboard that marked the T-Mobile G1. Like the Movit GiiNii, the Magic runs A...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7421-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7421_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:41:22">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/10/magic-mouse-oh-my-godits-full-of-capacitive-sensors/</link><title>Magic Mouse: Oh my God—it's full of capacitive sensors!</title><description>... has vivisected Apple's new Magic Mouse to see just how the "magic" happens. The gang... discovered is that Apple really does not want you to take the Magic Mouse apart. The whole thing is held... a few grams to the overall light weight of the Magic Mouse. Part of what makes the circuit so small...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7421-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7421_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:42:16">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/07/magic-trackpad/</link><title>Magic Trackpad or tragic Mac pad? A review</title><description>... various online Scrabble knockoffs. I use a Magic Mouse and the multitouch trackpad that is built into my... desktop.When Apple introduced the Magic Trackpad, a standalone Bluetooth trackpad designed for use.... The Magic Trackpad is designed to mirror the functionality and feel of the trackpads built...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7421-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7421_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:43:04">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/07/magic-trackpad-joining-mouse-in-attempt-to-thwart-voldemort-1/</link><title>Apple's Magic Trackpad one step closer to becoming a reality</title><description>... computer line, but one thing seems definite: with the filing of these papers, the Magic Trackpad...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7421-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7421_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:43:47">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/12/judge-oks-20-million-privacy-deal-for-facebooks-sponsored-stories/</link><title>Judge OKs $20 million privacy deal for Facebook's “sponsored stories”</title><description>...There's been a slew of litigation in the online privacy space in the past few yearsdespite the fact there aren't many online privacy laws to sue over. But the lawsuits have come nonetheless, tackling privacy issues ranging from data breaches to "supercookies."One of the most prominent cases was the Facebook lawsuit over "Sponsored Stories," in which users' pictu...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7421-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7421_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:44:23">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/08/facebook-users-in-sponsored-stories-can-get-15-each-court-rules/</link><title>Facebook users in Sponsored Stories can get $15 each, court rules</title><description>...Late last year, we reported on a $20 million class-action lawsuit covering people who were unwittingly featured in Facebook Sponsored Stories advertisements. User photos were used to endorse products they had "liked" without their permission and often without their knowledge. Worse still...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7421-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7421_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 05:45:06">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/10/magic-mouse-update-available-but-mice-nowhere-to-be-found/</link><title>Magic Mouse update available, but mice nowhere to be found (Updated)</title><description>...If you're looking to use one of Apple's new multi-touch Magic Mouse with your current Mac, especially to experience the glory of multi-touch gestures on a desktop, we have some good news and some bad news.The good news is that the update for Snow Leopard, which requires 10.6.1, and Leopard, which requires 10.5.8, is available now from Apple's software update downloads site. Softwar...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>