<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7424">best italian food Rome</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:01:25" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7424-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7424_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:01:26">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/10/wasted-food-may-be-untapped-source-of-energy-savings/</link><title>Wasted food may be untapped source of energy savings</title><description>...Wasted food could play an important role in the future of energy conservation, according to a study published in Environmental Science and Technology. By combining several data sets related to food... of available food on averageand about 52 million US households' worth of energy along with it. While...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7424-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7424_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:02:27">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/05/organic-food-is-not-for-the-birds/</link><title>Birds turn their beaks up at organic food</title><description>...Is organic food everything its advocates claim to be? A new study published in theJournal of the Science of Food and Agriculture describes an experiment in which the subjects were free from human biases. The authors found that wild birds preferred 'normal' bird food to the organic...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7424-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7424_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:03:00">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/04/the-tax-man-cometh-regulators-eye-tech-companies-free-food-options/</link><title>The tax man cometh: Regulators eye tech companies’ free food options</title><description>... to offer free food for employeesGoogle'sand Facebook'sofferingsare perhaps the best known...;examining whether the free food is a fringe benefit on which employees should pay additional tax.One... of the untaxed, free food programs say that workers at other companies are at a disadvantage."...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7424-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7424_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:03:33">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/11/climate-change-is-already-affecting-food-supplies/</link><title>Climate change is already affecting food supplies</title><description>... change is already affecting food security around the world.The report, which a spokesperson... climate change is affecting the world's food supplies today and how it is likely to affect the supply in the future.The report concludes that the climate is already having an effect on food security...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7424-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7424_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:04:33">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/05/3d-printable-food-nasa-wants-a-taste/</link><title>3D-printable food? NASA wants a taste</title><description>... of 3D-printable food, according to a report from Quartz. Anjan Contractor, who runs Systems Materials Research... carbs, and protein into edible food on demand.Contractor asserts that by the time the population...), we will have to change our perceptions of what food is in order to sustain everyone. A modified RepRap 3D...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7424-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7424_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:05:14">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/03/how-to-feed-9-billion-people-the-future-of-food-and-farming/</link><title>How to feed 9 billion people: the future of food and farming</title><description>... Advisor, which covered the "Future of Food and Farming: Challenges and Choices for Global... of the International Food Policy Research Institute; and incoming AAAS President Nina Fedoroff... about food security remain unanswered, and this panel, along with a recent UK government report, seek...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7424-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7424_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:05:58">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/05/lab-on-a-chip-detects-actual-food-allergies/</link><title>Lab-on-a-chip detects actual food allergies</title><description>... that they have at least one food allergy. In reality, the same study found, less than one in twenty has a food allergy. This disparity is due, in large part, to the difficult nature of determining if one actually has a food allergy.Standard allergy tests involve placing a small amount of allergen under...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7424-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7424_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:07:07">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/05/survey-apple-offers-compelling-shopper-experience/</link><title>Apple tops Whole Foods, Nordstrom for best shopper experience</title><description>... as having the best shopper experience among 60 top retailers. Number two, Whole Foods, was tops among 22... ranks far and above other leading retailers that offer the best shopper experience.Apple has long...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7424-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7424_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:08:07">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/09/total-war-rome-ii-review-a-total-mess/</link><title>Total War: Rome II review: A total mess</title><description>... with Rome II's tactical combat: it's not particularly tactical. At its best, Total War combat... not any one of those things.Like Rome itself, the Total War series could have been an empire that lasted..., messy, and complicated, but to sum it up: Rome II takes everything that the Total War seri...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7424-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7424_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:08:39">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2014/03/future-food-soylent-delayed-again-now-arriving-in-mid-to-late-april/</link><title>Future food Soylent delayed again—now arriving in mid-to-late April</title><description>...Bad news for future food backers awaiting their shipments of Soylent: the meal supplement/substitute's arrival has been pushed back again, this time to mid-April. In a blog post this afternoon... Soylent recipes. It's the best method to keep your need for convenient nutrient substances...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>