<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7425">coloring picture cars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:09:34" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7425-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7425_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:09:37">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/02/coloring-our-perception-blue-for-creativity-red-for-safety/</link><title>Coloring our perception: blue for creativity, red for safety</title><description>...Colors can have a profound effect on our behavior and cognitive performance. This much... different colors have on the human mind. Now a paper in Science this week adds some new data... were administered via computers, and the subjects were presented with a red, blue, or neutral-colored...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7425-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7425_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:10:20">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/11/new-nook-hd-prompts-price-cuts-for-nook-tablet-and-nook-color/</link><title>New Nook HD prompts price cuts for Nook Tablet and Nook Color</title><description>... and $179 for 16GB, down from $179 and $199, and the two-year-old Nook Color will now be available for $139... of the Nook Color after the Nook Tablet's introduction.Both the Nook Tablet and Nook Color... falling to their previous prices from $199 and $249 and the Nook Color falling from $169 to $149....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7425-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7425_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:11:03">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/02/interview-what-driving-will-be-like-in-five-to-ten-years/</link><title>Drive-by-wireless: why the future of cars is P2P mesh, 4G cellular, and the cloud</title><description>... or multicore processors have anything to do with cars, but you'd be wrong. They have everything... Hushyar, a former senior VP at ATT and current CEO of Telemetria, makers of the DashTop in-car compute appliance. In this fascinating interview, we talk about the ultimate evolution of not just the car...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7425-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7425_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:11:51">http://arstechnica.com/security/2013/06/after-burglaries-mystery-car-unlocking-device-has-police-stumped/</link><title>After burglaries, mystery car unlocking device has police stumped</title><description>... silently down a deserted residential street in Long Beach, California. Each one goes up to a car in the area, takes out a small electronic device, and pulls on the passenger side car handle. The first man tries a car in the street. It doesn't open, and he walks on. The other two men try...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7425-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7425_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:12:22">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2014/03/bloodhound-ssc/</link><title>Bloodhound SSC: How do you build a car capable of 1,000mph?</title><description>...Human beings achieved many 'firsts' in the 20th century. We climbed the planet's highest mountains, dived its deepest undersea trench, flew over it faster than the speed of sound, and even escaped it altogether in order to visit the moon. Beyond visiting Mars, it may feel like there are no more milestones left to reach. Yet people are still trying to push the envelope, even if they...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7425-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7425_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:13:17">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/10/legendary-pictures-looking-to-pick-up-epic-games/</link><title>Legendary Pictures looking to pick up Epic Games</title><description>...The world of film is coming ever closer to that of video games, as Variety is reporting that Legendary Pictures is in talks to purchase Gears of War developer Epic Games. The rumors come just a few weeks after Legendary boss Thomas Tull left game publisher Brash Entertainment, which he helped...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7425-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7425_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:13:58">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/06/expanding-the-gamut-sharp-to-increase-color-range-of-lcds/</link><title>Expanding the gamut: Sharp to increase color range of LCDs</title><description>...Sharp has developed a new LCD panel that uses five primary colors instead of the standard three primaries of red, green, and blue. The full 1920x1080 pixel panel is said to cover 99 percent of the Pointer "real world" color space and should far exceed that of the standard RGB color space used in current LCD models, even those that claim to cover the AdobeRGB color space.See, color space...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7425-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7425_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:14:42">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/12/nook-color-update-adds-netflix-app/</link><title>Nook Color update adds Netflix app</title><description>...Barnes and Noble has given Nook Color users the gift of Netflix, as well as a few other big apps... Color a little closer in OS functionality to the Nook Tablet, including better dictionary integration, portrait and landscape modes for reading, and more font selections.The Nook Color launched just...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7425-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7425_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:15:24">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/04/carsabi-points-the-way-forward-for-buying-a-used-car-online/</link><title>Carsabi points the way forward for buying a used car online</title><description>... that we want to get a car to share between the two of us. So, I turned to where most of us turn these days... changed since 1996! That means comparing car options involves lots of browser tabs and lots of patience...; That translates to about 1.5TB of crawled data every 24 hours. The site aims to do for used car sales...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7425-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7425_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:16:28">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/03/video-ipad-is-the-brain-for-self-driving-car/</link><title>Video: iPad is the brain for self-driving car</title><description>...Self-driving cars are quickly changing from a staple of sci-fi movies to reality in recent years. But not all self-driving cars are implemented the same way. One such variation has been developed...;s auto-driving capabilities.Oxford's iPad car aims to be a middle-of-the-road solution between...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>