<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7426">game bmx boy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:17:11" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7426-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7426_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:17:12">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/12/soulja-boy-video-game-is-coming-next-year/</link><title>Soulja Boy video game is coming next year</title><description>... Theft Auto IV are constantly being played on his tour bus, a Soulja Boy video game will be coming...Games starring hip-hop stars arent a rare thing, with titles like 50 Cent: Bullet Proof (and its delayed sequel) and the Def Jam series. Now, another such game has been revealed, starring the self...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7426-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7426_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:17:57">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/04/ars-looks-back-at-25-years-of-puke-green-game-boy-memories/</link><title>Ars looks back at 25 years of puke-green Game Boy memories</title><description>..., when Nintendo released the original Game Boy in Japan.A generation of tech-heads tapping awayat... at the four-color grayscale, 160144 screen while on the go. The Game Boy had its competitors..., and exclusive rights to mega-hit Tetris meant the Game Boy outl...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7426-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7426_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:19:31">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/04/game-boy-20th-anniversary/</link><title>Happy 20th b-day, Game Boy: here are 6 reasons why you're #1</title><description>...Twenty years ago this week, Nintendo released the Game Boy, its first handheld video game console. Excited Japanese customers snatched up the innovative monochrome handheld by the thousands, which retailed for 12,500 yen (about $94 at 1989 rates) at launcha small price to pay for what seemed to be an NES in your pocket. Nintendo initially offered four games for the new Game Boy: Super Mario Land,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7426-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7426_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:20:28">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/industry-veteran-writes-kids-book-about-gaming-too-much/</link><title>Industry veteran writes kids' book about perils of gaming</title><description>... and previously of a producer for the Medal of Honor games, tells the story of Sofa Boy, a kid...-olds shouldn't be playing Grand Theft Auto games seems like sound advice. Sofa Boy will receive...Over the years, we've all engaged in a marathon gaming session or two, many...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7426-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7426_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:21:24">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/01/noby-noby-boy-delayed-in-japan-gets-worldwide-release/</link><title>Noby Noby Boy delayed in Japan, gets worldwide release</title><description>..., called Noby Noby Boy. Unfortunately for Japanese gamers, the bizzare PlayStation Network game... be releasing the game simultaneously worldwide on February 19. The game has players controlling... a bit strange and confusing, so were looking forward to getting our hands on the game...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7426-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7426_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:21:57">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/03/a-boy-and-his-blob-is-revealed-for-nintendo-wii/</link><title>A Boy and His Blob revealed for Nintendo Wii</title><description>...Many gamers have fond memories of the odd friendship between a boy and his blob in... well, A Boy and His Blob. The David Crane-designed Game Boy title had you, the boy, feeding different-flavored jelly beans to change your blob into different forms to solve puzzles. Nintendo Power has revealed that the game is getting a makeover for the Nintendo Wii, care of Majesco.You can take a look at two pa...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7426-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7426_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:22:42">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/10/heres-how-to-build-your-own-game-boy/</link><title>Here's how to build your own Game Boy</title><description>... Game Boy, from the circuitry right down to the software. Pieces can be put together individually... the experience can be a great break from life and even from gaming. Its hard to deny the satisfaction... side project for those bored winter days when you feel like taking a break from playing on a gaming...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7426-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7426_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:23:14">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/08/be-prepared-to-litigate-boy-scouts-pressures-hacker-scouts-to-drop-scouts/</link><title>Be prepared to litigate: Boy Scouts pressures Hacker Scouts to drop “Scouts”</title><description>... local chapters.But the Boy Scouts of America (BSA) is not happy with the new scouting group... to court, wrote Cook.Since 1919, the Boy Scouts of America has held a congressional charter..., through organization, and cooperation with other agencies, the ability of boys to do things...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7426-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7426_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:23:51">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/06/indie-game-the-movie/</link><title>Indie filmakers tackle indie games in Indie Game: The Movie</title><description>...It's sometimes easy to forget that games are made by people. Game developers... associate specific designers with specific games. The aptly titled feature documentary Indie Game: The Movie is looking to change that by telling the stories of some of the most acclaimed indie games...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7426-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7426_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:24:30">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/03/video-a-boy-and-his-blob-looks-even-better-in-motion/</link><title>Video: A Boy and His Blob looks even better in motion</title><description>...Yesterday the gaming world got a welcome surprise with the revelation that WayForward was developing a brand new A Boy and His Blob title exclusively for the Wii. While the announcement didn't...;s abilities, which include transforming into a ladder or a hole in the ground in order to help the boy...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>