<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7428">rainy afternoon kids craft</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:26:14" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7428-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7428_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:26:15">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/07/hey-kids-learn-to-be-cyber-smart-from-the-nsas-youth-page/</link><title>Hey kids! Learn to be “cyber smart” from the NSA’s youth page!</title><description>...The National Security Agency wants your kids to know that it's cool to be "cyber smart... at children and adolescents. The "Kids Page," intended for elementary age children, appears... metadata collection and FISA Court warranted PRISM probes.Among the NSA's tips for kids is this sage...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7428-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7428_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:27:02">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/03/review-kid-icarus-uprising-loses-control-of-an-otherwise-enjoyable-mythological-romp/</link><title>Review: Kid Icarus: Uprising loses control of an otherwise enjoyable mythological romp</title><description>... is the case with Kid Icarus: Uprising, an imaginative, lighthearted, fun-filled game that ultimately falls... with the control scheme for Kid Icarus Uprising is a matter of functional overload on your left hand. Your right... push themselves. As I played Kid Icarus: Uprising, I couldn't help but think how the game...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7428-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7428_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:27:55">http://arstechnica.com/business/2010/01/obvious-report-on-increased-media-use-among-kids-is-obvious/</link><title>Kids consume media as a full-time job—many getting overtime</title><description>...We already have a pretty good idea that most kids and teens probably spend too much time watching..., including comparisons with data collected in 1999 and 2004. Trends suggest kids are spending more time... percent reported having a portable CD player, way down from 62 percent in 2004. Also, kids listened...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7428-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7428_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:28:43">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2011/02/ftc-says-it-will-look-into-apples-marketing-of-in-app-purchases-to-kids/</link><title>FTC says it will look into Apple's marketing of in-app purchases to kids</title><description>... purchases to children. The decision comes after a wave of complaints about kids running up huge bills... add-ons to kids, saying that he was "disturbed" by the reports. "Companies shouldnt..., but "share" an iPhone with a kid. Apple hasn't formally commented about the situation yet...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7428-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7428_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:29:38">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/08/lawsuit-disney-others-spy-on-kids-with-zombie-cookies/</link><title>Lawsuit: Disney, others spy on kids with zombie cookies</title><description>...Disney, Ustream, SodaHead, Warner Bros., and a number of other websites are spying on kids' Internet use, according to a lawsuit filed recently by a group of parents and their children. The suit accuses ad widget company Clearspring Technologies of enabling these sites to track kids...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7428-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7428_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:30:17">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/01/apple-q1fy2012-liveblog/</link><title>Liveblog: Apple's FY2012 Q1 earnings call this afternoon</title><description>...Apple plans to announce the results of its first fiscal quarter of 2012 this afternoon: January 24, 2012 at 2pm PDT. The results will be followed by the typical conference call where Apple executives... alike.Ars will be doing a liveblog of the earnings call and the fiscal results this afternoon...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7428-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7428_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:31:12">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2010/09/samsung-craft-first-lte-handset-launches-on-metropcs/</link><title>Samsung Craft first LTE handset, launches on MetroPCS</title><description>... in the world. Dubbed the Samsung Craft, the LTE/CDMA handset will be available on MetroPCS..., the Craft runs a proprietary Samsung-developed OS that a spokesperson described to Ars as "running.... For now, though, the Samsung Craft is only available through MetroPCS in the Las Vegas metropolitan area...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7428-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7428_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:31:57">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/01/preschoolers-better-at-navigating-iphone-than-tying-their-shoes/</link><title>Preschoolers better at navigating iPhone than tying their shoes</title><description>...;s not just us. According to a new survey from security software maker AVG, kids can grasp new tech skills long before they even learn how to do normal kid things, such as swimming or tying..., France, Italy, Germany, Spain, Japan, Australia and New Zealand. Nineteen percent said their kids...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7428-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7428_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:32:32">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/10/new-technology-turns-car-ride-into-a-video-game/</link><title>New technology turns car ride into a video game</title><description>...As if family vehicles with built-in TVs and game consoles werent enough to entertain your kids on those long car rides to the next holiday dinner at a relatives house, it turns out that theres a new.... This looks like it could be a great way to keep the kids happy if theyre stuck in the car for a while, though...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7428-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7428_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:33:03">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/02/friday-afternoon-apple-links-first-week-of-february-edition/</link><title>Friday afternoon Apple links: First week of February edition</title><description>...Happy Friday! We don't have a ton of links for you at the end of this week, but there's still a small handful of light reading for you to pass the time on a Friday afternoon. Read on:Ever wanted a blingy iPod nano with Elton John's signature on the back? If you're...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>