<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7431">navalni trial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:48:38" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7431-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7431_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:48:39">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/04/crowdsourcing-a-clinical-trial-to-treat-als/</link><title>Crowdsourcing a clinical trial to treat ALS</title><description>... this tendency to share information to crowdsource a sort of clinical trial, obtaining data... research, and promising results have been seen in some animal models and small clinical trials.... Although these patients didn't provide a randomized clinical trial population, they did present...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7431-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7431_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:49:23">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/02/labels-want-13-million-from-pirate-bay-as-trial-starts/</link><title>Big Content wants $13 million from Pirate Bay as trial starts</title><description>... million kronor). For a trial taking place in Sweden and broadcast only in Swedish... the world. With Swedish media outlets making the audio stream of the trial available, bilingual webheads... for past "bad behavior"). They are intent on seeing the trial as mere spectacle...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7431-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7431_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:50:15">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/08/trials-hd-impresses-with-violence-physics-and-insanity/</link><title>Simple, violent, addictive: Trials HD on Xbox 360</title><description>...When a game is great, we refer to it as a "beer warmer." The genesis of this term? You sit down for an evening of gaming, open a beer, then find yourself so engrossed in the title that the next time you remember to take a sip, the beer's no longer cold. Microsoft has been releasing beer warmers with surprising regularity during this year's Summer of Arcade promotion, and the t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7431-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7431_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:51:24">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/08/trials-hd-is-great-sharing-tracks-not-so-much/</link><title>Trials HD is great. It's a shame sharing tracks is broken</title><description>...Trials HD ended up being one of the biggest surprises during this year's Summer of Arcade, bringing some addictive actionwith impressive graphicsto the Xbox Live Arcade. While I'm guessing many Xbox Live Arcade fans will jump over to Shadow Complex this Wednesday, Trials HD has the chance...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7431-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7431_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:51:56">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/02/ifpi-boss-youre-either-with-us-or-against-us/</link><title>IFPI boss at TPB trial: you're either with us or against us</title><description>...Since it began last week, the trial of the Pirate Bay in Sweden has truly been a "spectrial"and not just because of juvenile Pirate Bay antics such as last night's open letter to IFPI boss John Kennedy. The spectacle kicked back into high gear Wednesday as Kennedy traveled from London to Sweden to give testimony in the trial on behalf of the worldwide major-label music industry. On...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7431-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7431_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:52:44">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/02/charges-droppedmaking-available-now-focus-of-tpb-trial/</link><title>Charges dropped—"making available" now focus of Pirate Bay trial</title><description>... megaphones, the tweets from the courtroom. But on day two of the trial, the prosecution dropped a spectacle... lawsuits to make it to trial and a verdictand the judge eventually set the verdict aside over doubts... to power the servers and pay some bills. Content owners, who are watching the trial closely, said...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7431-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7431_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:53:37">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/02/tpb-trial-witness-file-sharing-not-bad-for-music-business/</link><title>TPB trial witness: file-sharing not bad for music business</title><description>...The Pirate Bay trial settled into something (sort of) approaching normality today as two professors took the stand. One explained more about how BitTorrent functions; the other got into a fight... from WallisThe Twitterati continue to translate the trial...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7431-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7431_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:54:27">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/08/trials-hd-dev-xbox-live-not-ready-for-user-generated-content/</link><title>Trials HD dev: Xbox Live not ready for user-generated content</title><description>...Trials HD is one of the better games released during this year's Summer of Arcade promotion on Xbox Live, but the game does have a major flaw: the user-created tracks can only be traded among friends, and only the creator can give the track to a friend. This effectively stops the spread...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7431-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7431_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:55:14">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/09/for-clinical-trials-design-and-results-dont-always-match/</link><title>Anti-"publication bias" efforts not panning out for science</title><description>... to keep failed trials quiet. In 2005, medical journals forged a policy meant to ensure that a description of any clinical trial would be registered in public databases before it took place. A new study...: not every clinical study is being registered, and many trials result in publications that differ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7431-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7431_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:55:57">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/05/brocade-and-a10-settle-patent-case-one-hour-before-a-jury-hears-it/</link><title>Brocade and A10 settle patent case one hour before a jury hears it</title><description>... opening statements in a damages trial, according to Mike Swift, a reporter for the MLex legal.... The case became even more noteworthy after trial when a judge ruled that Brocade would win an injunction... of its flagship networking equipment in view of the court's injunction. A10 was facing a separate jury trial...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>