<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7432">ticket to mars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:57:02" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7432-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7432_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:57:03">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/04/more-than-20000-people-apply-for-one-way-ticket-to-mars/</link><title>More than 20,000 people apply for one-way ticket to Mars</title><description>...Last week we mentioned Mars One, the combination space mission/reality TV show project that aims..., at least 20,000 people have paid $38 to formally apply for Mars One. Various sources around... living out the remainder of their days in a questionable camera-stuffed habitat on Mars. Around 600...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7432-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7432_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:58:33">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/05/review-ticket-to-ride-on-ipad-a-high-quality-port-of-board-game/</link><title>Review: Ticket to Ride on iPad a high-quality port of board game</title><description>... game: Ticket to Ride. The game has become a family stapleit's challenging but not unwinnable... of you not familiar with the game, here's a quick recap. Ticket to Ride is a railway track... everyone. The iPad version of Ticket to Ride impresses right from the beginning. The play is directly...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7432-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7432_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 06:59:15">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/04/apple-mixes-things-up-for-wwdc-2013-pre-announced-ticket-sales/</link><title>Apple mixes things up for WWDC 2013, with pre-announced ticket sales</title><description>... Conference. Following five years of increasingly speedy sell-outs, Apple has announced that ticket orders...;s debacle. In 2012, all 5,000 tickets to WWDC sold out in about two hours. This marks a problematic trend. In 2011, tickets sold out in 12 hours; in 2010 it was about 10 days, while in 2009 it was a month...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7432-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7432_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:00:08">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/02/one-way-mars-one-mission-detractors-now-include-some-muslim-clerics/</link><title>One-way Mars One mission detractors now include some Muslim clerics (Updated)</title><description>...Enlarge / How Bas Lansdorp and the rest of the Mars One team imagine the first human colony on Mars will look in 2023. We've written before about Mars One, the combination space mission/reality.... A trip like the proposed Mars One mission, from which there is no plan (or really even possibility...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7432-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7432_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:00:55">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/08/curiositys-first-year-on-mars/</link><title>Curiosity’s first year on Mars</title><description>... most exciting work involves robots. Despite what 200,000 people think, a manned mission to Mars isnt... tooverstep the mark on copyright enforcement). After touching down on Mars and taking in the view... (Aeolis Mons).Today, just ahead of Spirits first (terran) anniversary on Mars, NASA and JPL released...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7432-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7432_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:01:42">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/02/wildly-optimistic-mission-to-mars-plan-earns-skepticism/</link><title>Wildly optimistic mission to Mars plan earns skepticism</title><description>...A newly announced and privately organized mission to Mars, dubbed "Inspiration Mars: A Mission For America," intends to give one man-and-woman married couple a round-trip ticket around... optimism.Inspiration Mars is the brainchild of Dennis Tito, an entrepreneur who paid $20 million in 2001 to t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7432-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7432_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:02:49">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/04/nasas-1966-plan-for-a-mission-to-mars/</link><title>NASA's 1966 plan for a mission to Mars</title><description>...) turned its attention to the scientific tasks astronaut-scientists might perform on Mars. In that year, as part of an ongoing series of Mars mission studies that began in 1962 with the EMPIRE manned Mars/Venus flyby/orbiter study, the Huntsville, Alabama-based NASA center contracted with Avco/RAD...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7432-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7432_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:03:42">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/08/pics-because-it-really-is-happening-on-mars/</link><title>Pics, because it really is happening on Mars</title><description>... rover on Mars. Although Curiosity is on track to be sending back data for years, its arrival and first.... NASACurrently, Mars is the best monitored planet outside of our own, which means that there is hardware... was able to direct the HIRISE camera on the Mars Reconnaissance Orbiter towards the area where...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7432-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7432_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:04:38">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/08/new-probe-to-provide-insight-into-mars-interior/</link><title>New probe to provide InSight into Mars' interior</title><description>...Mars is set to play host to another robot. The InSight (Interior Exploration using Seismic..., but with a much broader mission.The Mars rovers (Sojourner, Spirit, Opportunity, and Curiosity... to the Martian interior. Mars occupies a special niche in the Solar System: it is relatively Earth-like...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7432-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7432_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:05:36">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/07/nasas-next-mars-rover-to-prep-for-sample-returns-human-exploration/</link><title>NASA’s next Mars rover to prep for sample returns, human exploration</title><description>...NASA affirmed its addiction to Big Red this week, announcing plans for the next Mars rover... paving the way for a future human expedition.To look for evidence that life once existed on Mars... will undoubtedly create a healthy discussion about where on Mars to drop the rover for its mission.The sample...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>