<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7435">trendy bar Berlin</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:14:59" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7435-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7435_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:15:00">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/07/ios-401-tweaks-bar-display-doesnt-fix-signal-drop/</link><title>iOS 4.0.1 tweaks bar display, doesn't fix signal drop</title><description>...As most iPhone users likely know, Apple released a software update on Thursday to address the bar... this month, iOS 4.0.1 changes how Apple calculates the number of bars shown to the user in an attempt to give a more realistic picture of the cell signal being picked up by the phone (read: fewer bars...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7435-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7435_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:16:09">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/09/bars-restaurants-and-clubs-what-we-rely-on-net-for-the-most/</link><title>Report: What do we need the 'Net for? Bars, restaurants, and clubs</title><description>... for which the online landscape is "the most relied upon source." Here they are:Bars, restaurants...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7435-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7435_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:16:58">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/07/after-shining-kim-dotcom-light-art-on-us-embassy-artist-now-under-investigation/</link><title>Artist investigated after shining Kim Dotcom “light art” on US Embassy</title><description>...A German artist may now potentially face criminal charges in Germany after he projected a huge image onto the walls of the United States Embassy in Berlin last Sunday.The image was of fellow German Kim Dotcom, the embattled founder of Megaupload, along with the phrase United Stasi of America...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7435-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7435_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:17:40">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/09/german-pirate-party-boards-berlin-state-parliament/</link><title>German Pirate Party boards Berlin state parliament</title><description>...The German arm of the International Pirate Party saw a momentous victory in this week's Berlin state elections, as the Internet activist group won 15 seats in regional parliament.The groupwhich was founded to promote privacy, free speech, data protection and file sharing onlinewon 8.9 percent...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7435-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7435_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:18:41">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/10/germany-accuses-us-of-spying-on-chancellor-angela-merkels-phone/</link><title>Germany accuses US of spying on Chancellor Angela Merkel’s phone</title><description>... author. (Appelbaum currently lives in Berlin.)The article adds that Spiegel research was shared... research, the magazine noted that Berlin seems to have found their suspicions plausible enough...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7435-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7435_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:19:21">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/07/apple-says-iphone-4-algorithm-is-to-blame-not-signal/</link><title>Apple says iPhone 4 algorithm is to blame, not antenna</title><description>... to a mistake in the formula that calculates the number of bars to display. Apple says that a software... ways will reduce its reception by 1 or more bars. This is true of iPhone 4, iPhone 3GS, as well as many Droid, Nokia and RIM phones. But some users have reported that iPhone 4 can drop 4 or 5 bars...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7435-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7435_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:20:05">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/05/cell-bars-reception/</link><title>Four bars? The disconnect between bars and cell signal</title><description>... in September 2008.Count to five "More bars in more places," reads the latest slogan... to billboards to TV commercials. At least here in the US, it's pounded into our heads early on that bars... of bars being displayed on your cell phone gives a general idea of whether you have a good chance...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7435-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7435_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:21:02">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/08/apple-retail-300-million-served-so-far-in-2012/</link><title>Apple retail: 300 million served (so far) in 2012</title><description>... year.And those of you who have ever had trouble booking a Genius Bar appointment may...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7435-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7435_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:21:54">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/02/microsoft-plays-tag-with-the-bar-code/</link><title>Microsoft plays Tag with the bar code</title><description>... software that you can load on your cell phone; the phone's camera is used for scanning the bar...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7435-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7435_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:22:57">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/06/thunderbird-31-arrives-with-new-filter-bar/</link><title>Thunderbird 3.1 arrives with new filter bar</title><description>...Mozilla Messaging has announced the release of Thunderbird 3.1, a minor update that brings performance improvements, bug fixes, and some new features.The most significant enhancement in 3.1 is the new Quick Filter bar, which makes it easy to filter and search the contents of the current folder. It has several icons that you can click to filter for messages that are unread, starred, sent by a cont...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>