<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7439">make crown</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:48:47" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7439-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7439_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:48:48">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/08/are-two-heads-better-than-one-sometimes/</link><title>Are two heads better than one? Sometimes...</title><description>...Generally, we assume that making decisions as a group is beneficial because groups can come together to make better choices than their members would alone. Is this true, or is group decision-making... trick and secretly introduced "noise" into one of the partner's visual fields, making...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7439-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7439_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:49:25">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/08/singstar-queen-about-what-youd-expect-epic-difficult/</link><title>SingStar Queen about what you'd expect: epic, difficult</title><description>... up the Beatles, some argue for the The Who, and certain misguided souls may even make a case for U2... a challenging experience even on the lower difficulty levels.That doesn't make this a bad game, just..., but after one fun night of making fun of how badly everyone sings, it's hard to imagine...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7439-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7439_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:50:19">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/05/benchmark-new-chrome-beta-takes-the-speed-crown/</link><title>New Chrome beta takes the speed crown</title><description>... performance that will make it a real winner.Chrome's V8 JavaScript engine benefits...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7439-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7439_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:51:12">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/06/revenge-of-the-fallen-is-messy-unfunny-and-way-too-long/</link><title>Revenge of the Fallen is messy, unfunny, and way too long</title><description>...To lend some context to this review, I was a big fan of the first Transformers film. Sure, it was loud and the camera shook too much, but it was a great summer film and a solid take on the idea that alien robots wanted nothing more than to turn into Earth vehicles and fight each other. Peter Cullen came back to voice Optimus Prime, and just when the human characters became intolerable, there was...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7439-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7439_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:51:56">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/04/house-set-to-revise-cispa-language-to-add-more-privacy-protection/</link><title>House set to revise CISPA language to add more privacy protection</title><description>... to even make an effort to take out sensitive and personal information before sharing cybersecurity...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7439-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7439_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:52:46">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/03/diy-how-to-make-a-laptop-hammock-for-a-dollar/</link><title>DIY: Make your own laptop hammock, for a dollar</title><description>... see at the top of this post. Now I'll show you how to make one, on an incredible budget..., you do no sewing at all and use a t-shirt. It's true: you can make a laptop hammock without.... There are endless refinements you can make to the design (for instance, cutting holes in the sides...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7439-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7439_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:53:30">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/09/amds-latest-takes-gpu-crown-intels-larrabee-takes-a-bow/</link><title>AMD's latest takes GPU crown, Intel's Larrabee takes a bow</title><description>...? AMD's debut DirectX 11 GPU now has the single-GPU performance crown by a comfortable margin...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7439-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7439_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:54:23">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2010/12/apple-ios-chipping-away-at-ds-psp-for-handheld-gaming-crown/</link><title>Apple iOS chipping away at DS, PSP for handheld gaming crown</title><description>...A new market research report shows that mobile phones"particularly the iPhone"make up a large and growing percentage of the handheld gaming market, while use of dedicated gaming devices like Nintendo's DS and Sony's PSP is slowly waning. With Apple's iPod touch outselling...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7439-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7439_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:55:31">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/07/popcap-teams-with-10-year-old-to-grant-wish-create-fun-game/</link><title>PopCap teams with 9-year-old to grant wish, create fun game</title><description>... and designed by a 9-year-old.As part of the Make-A-Wish Foundation, 9-year-old Owain Weinertwho... up with the 4th and Battery crew to fulfill a wish to make a video game. And the result was Allied Star Police...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7439-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7439_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 07:56:22">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/12/first-internet-created-feature-film-debuts-next-month/</link><title>First Internet-created feature film debuts next month</title><description>..., because its driven by a creative purpose. The company is making a name for itself in part for being... other founder, hopes to also make money from advertising by building an audience before the film is made...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>