<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7441">barcelona real madrid goal messi</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:05:16" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7441-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7441_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:05:17">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/06/obama-administration-aims-to-fix-broken-real-id-act/</link><title>Obama administration aims to fix broken Real ID Act</title><description>...The Obama administration is making a last-minute effort to fix the controversial Real ID Act before the program's deadline is reached in December. Changes to the measure, which will be introduced soon in Congress, could add additional privacy safeguards and remove some of the program's most costly requirements.The Real ID Act, which was passed as a rider on a 2005 military spending bill...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7441-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7441_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:05:53">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/07/gamers-want-anonymity-so-blizzard-scuttles-real-id-plans/</link><title>Gamers crave anonymity, so Blizzard scuttles Real ID plans</title><description>...Blizzard did not make many friends with its recent decision to force users to post with theirreal names in its official forums. The response was immediate and deafening, with pages and pages of users complaining bitterly about the new rule. One Blizzard employee posted his own name to prove the system's safety only to have his personal information, including address and phone number, posted...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7441-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7441_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:06:51">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/05/say-hello-to-the-real-real-time-web/</link><title>Say hello to the real real-time Web</title><description>... at it on your phone. That's the end goal, to have real-time information streamed to everyone... backend. It would be real-time, meaning that every player would see every shot and every movement... in its supposed execution to be perceived as real. Recent development runtimes, such as Node, have made...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7441-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7441_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:07:45">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/12/real-big-shootin-add-on-for-the-gunstringer-lets-you-live-gamings-greatest-fantasy/</link><title>Real Big Shootin' add-on for the Gunstringer lets you live gaming's greatest fantasy</title><description>...How much do you love shooting galleries? The 240 point ($3) Real Big Shootin' DLC pack... multiplayer and scoreboards to keep your interest up. Real Big Shootin' This isn't... with a friend. Good enough for me. The Real Big Shootin' DLC pack for the Gunstringer is available...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7441-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7441_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:08:44">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/04/friendfeed-lifestreaming-goes-real-time-for-better-and-worse/</link><title>FriendFeed lifestreaming goes real-time for better and worse</title><description>... social grail: real-time, automatic updates.Registered users can access this "live" new... apparent: new updates will appear essentially in real time as you idle on the page, refresh-button... of how many new updates are waiting while you catch your social breath. This new real-time update...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7441-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7441_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:09:35">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/08/facebook-launches-first-real-cash-gambling-app-only-available-in-uk/</link><title>Facebook launches first "real cash" gambling app, only available in UK</title><description>...On Tuesday, a British online gambling firm became the first real cash game available on Facebook... users who are over 18."Real money gaming is a popular and well-regulated activity in the UK... real cash online gambling on Facebook. However, online gambling sites operating from the United...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7441-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7441_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:10:06">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/05/blizzard-delays-diablo-iii-real-money-auctions-indefinitely/</link><title>Blizzard delays Diablo III real-money auctions indefinitely</title><description>...Those of you hoping to quit your jobs and make a living selling your Diablo III loot for real money will have to keep flipping burgers a little while longer as Blizzard has announced the game's much-discussed real-money auction house has moved "outside the previously estimated May timeframe."The real-money auction service was originally planned to launch a week after the game'...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7441-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7441_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:10:42">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/06/real-money-auctions-launch-in-diablo-iii/</link><title>Real-money auctions launch in Diablo III</title><description>... has finally launched Diablo III's real-money auction house in the Americas.While players can't yet spend real money on commodities like gold and gemsa feature Blizzard says it is preparing to launch... to spend real money on Diablo III items on Friday, June 15, Eurogamer reports, whileplayers using...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7441-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7441_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:11:17">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2008/10/amd-were-well-on-our-way-to-shanghai-45nm-cpus/</link><title>AMD: We're well on our way to Shanghai, 45nm CPUs</title><description>... been following AMD, is a 45nm die-shrink of the companys Barcelona architecture with a 6MB L3 cache (up from 2MB on Barcelona), improved performance and power characteristics, and an additional set of as-yet... to Barcelona products. There appears, however, to have been a miscommunication at some point; CNet...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7441-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7441_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:12:16">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/06/blizzard-ups-security-reqs-for-diablo-iii-real-money-auctions/</link><title>Blizzard forces two-factor authentication for Diablo III real-money auctions</title><description>...With Blizzard finally ramping up to launch its long-promised and oft-delayed real-money auction house forDiablo III this week, the company has announced that players using the new feature will need to have two-factor authentication enabled on their accounts for security purposes.According to the game's newly updated terms of service, players that want to add or remove money from their Battle...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>