<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7445">marathon training</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:33:47" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7445-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7445_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:33:48">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/union-pacific-using-game-like-technology-for-recruitingtraining/</link><title>Union Pacific using gaming technology for recruiting/training</title><description>... of training an equally large group of new employees. As a result, companies like Union Pacific are utilizing game-like simulations to attract new workers.The company revealed that this training program began in 2005, when two employees started trying to figure out a way to train new UP workforce members...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7445-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7445_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:34:34">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/06/brain-training-games-may-help-a-subset-of-users/</link><title>Brain training boosts working memory, but only in some people</title><description>...When last we tackled the topic of brain training software, the prognosis did not look good... training can boost general performancebut only a specific type of exercise, and only among a subset... in performance. By this measure, brain training had failed. But it hadn't, at least not entirely...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7445-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7445_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:35:26">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/office-of-naval-research-gets-36-mil-for-virtual-training/</link><title>Office of Naval Research gets $36 mil. for virtual training</title><description>...;critical, one-of-a-kind futuristic training program" that will create virtual reality-like... likely to encounter overseas.The program, known as the Future Immersive Training Environment Joint... with the training and tools they need, ONRs Chief of Naval Research, Rear Admiral Nevin P. Carr...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7445-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7445_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:36:13">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2008/11/will-you-wifi-in-a-bus-on-a-train-on-a-boat-yes-apparently/</link><title>Will you WiFi in a bus? On a train? On a boat? Yes, apparently</title><description>...Usage of Internet access in buses, trains, and ferries is way up, said Icomera, the leading worldwide provider of such service. Icomera, a Swedish firm that pioneered Net access in trains, said..., on train lines like SJ in Sweden and National Express in the UK, is up 272 percent in the last 12...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7445-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7445_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:36:51">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/12/snowden-leak-examines-gaming-as-a-terrorist-propaganda-and-training-tool/</link><title>Snowden leak examines gaming as a terrorist propaganda and training tool</title><description>...The latest document dump from former National Security Agency contractor Edward Snowden is getting a lot of deserved attention for revelations that international security agencies are taking steps to monitor communications inside online games. But those leaked documents also include an in-depth report on the potential for games to be used as recruitment, training, and propaganda tools by extremis...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7445-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7445_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:37:44">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/06/amtrak-to-take-free-onboard-wifi-nationwide/</link><title>Amtrak to take free onboard WiFi nationwide</title><description>...Amtrak's Acela Express trains run along the Washington-Boston-New York corridor and offer two... could soon come to every Amtrak train nationwide. Guess which one? Onboard WiFi has been a huge hit on the Acela trains. Amtrak announced last week that 39 percent of all Acela riders had logged onto...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7445-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7445_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:38:21">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/04/boston-cellular-networks-flooded-but-service-was-not-cut-off/</link><title>Boston cellular networks flooded, but service was not cut off</title><description>...In light of this afternoon's tragedy at the Boston Marathon, many across the world scrambled... up their networks in advance of the Marathon, but even with the extra capacity the networks became flooded... told ABC News that the carrier did "augment capacity on its cell sites along the marathon...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7445-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7445_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:38:50">http://arstechnica.com/business/2014/03/ride-londons-abandoned-underground-mail-rail/</link><title>Ride London’s abandoned underground “Mail Rail”</title><description>... to transport mail by road.Since then, the trains and the tunnels have remained in place, but the goal...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7445-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7445_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:39:23">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/03/from-parody-to-production-how-petermolydeux-inspired-a-wacky-weekend-game-design-marathon/</link><title>From parody to production: How @petermolydeux inspired a wacky weekend game design marathon</title><description>... in the "What Would Molydeux?" Game Jam, a 48-hour group game design and programming marathon based..., 48-hour marathon might not seem like the best way to create quality conversions...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7445-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7445_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:40:12">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/03/people-like-virtual-trainers-that-look-act-like-them/</link><title>People like virtual instructors that look, act like them</title><description>... looking stock image) that guides you through tech support or an automated training session. Although..., a new study on virtual training instructors extends that to show that people work best with virtual... on the outcomes of training, and ethnic similarity actually making things worse. Combined, however...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>