<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7448">running shoes boston</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:55:05" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7448-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7448_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:55:08">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/04/how-to-donate-online-to-charities-supporting-boston-bombing-victims-and-first-responders/</link><title>How to donate online to charities supporting Boston bombing victims and first responders</title><description>...Our thoughts and concerns are with the greater Boston area on Friday, as the city remains on lockdown while law enforcement is conducting a manhunt for the second Boston Marathon suspect. (Ars... to contribute to Boston relief efforts online can do so in a number of ways:The American Red Cross...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7448-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7448_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:55:35">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/03/boston-pays-170k-to-settle-cell-phone-recording-lawsuit/</link><title>Boston pays $170k to settle cell phone recording lawsuit</title><description>...The City of Boston has agreed to pay Simon Glik $170,000 in damages and legal fees to settle a civil rights lawsuit. Glik was arrested in 2007 on Boston Common for using his cell phone to record...; First Amendment right to record the actions of public officials on a public sidewalk. Boston finally...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7448-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7448_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:56:23">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/07/boston-a-copper-hole-in-the-fiber-donut-demands-fios/</link><title>Boston, "a copper hole in the fiber donut," demands FiOS</title><description>...Verizon is currently wiring up New York City with fiber optic cables, but Boston mayor Thomas... cities, leaving Boston a "copper hole in the fiber donut," said Boston's Chief Information Officer, William Oates, to the Boston Globe. The Globe has waded into the issue, too, penning...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7448-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7448_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:57:00">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/11/boston-police-set-to-track-its-own-patrol-cars-via-gps-to-improve-dispatching/</link><title>Boston policemen complain about new plan to watch their movements</title><description>...It looks like Bostons Finest is going to be watched by its own. As the result of new contract negotiations between the City of Boston and the Boston Police Department, police cruisers... includes some additional changes and still needs to be approved by the Boston City Council.According...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7448-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7448_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:57:46">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/01/trying-and-failing-to-out-run-my-friends-hands-on-with-runkeeper-3-for-iphone/</link><title>Trying (and failing) to out-run my friends: Hands-on with RunKeeper 3 for iPhone</title><description>... like having written. I essentially feel the same way about running. Iwouldn'tcall myself a runner as such, but I do find myself lacing up my running shoes three to four times per week. And when I do... for now.)So now you have no excuse. Go grab your running shoes!...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7448-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7448_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:58:17">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2008/12/hp-will-be-first-notebook-maker-to-use-sonata-battery-from-boston-power/</link><title>HP notebooks to use Sonata battery from Boston-Power</title><description>...Boston-Power has announced that HP will be the first customer to offer its Sonata batteries in their notebook computers. Boston-Power Sonata batteries are a significant improvement over current... to specific notebooks already on the market. Further Reading: Boston-Power...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7448-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7448_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:59:00">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/07/hearst-tv-station-files-suit-to-stop-aereos-boston-expansion/</link><title>Hearst TV station files suit to stop Aereo’s Boston expansion</title><description>... in Boston, filed for an injunction that aims to halt Aereos rollout in Beantown, where it launched in May... with Aereos plans to expand in Boston and other cities across the country.Aereo itself has already sued CBS... took that and brought it into the modern age.In April 2013, before the Boston launch, Aereo won...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7448-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7448_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:59:34">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/10/judge-denies-boston-tv-stations-attempt-to-shut-down-aereo/</link><title>Judge denies Boston TV station’s attempt to shut down Aereo</title><description>... affiliate WCVB-TV in Boston, had argued in its July 2013 filing that Aereos business model relies...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7448-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7448_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:00:29">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/04/boston-police-chief-facial-recognition-tech-didnt-help-find-bombing-suspects/</link><title>Boston police chief: facial recognition tech didn’t help find bombing suspects</title><description>...While the whole country is relieved that this past weeks Boston Marathon bombing ordeal and subsequent lockdown of the city is finally over, Boston Police Commissioner Edward Davis told... the science side, two Boston medical researchers called for a special autopsy test to look...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7448-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7448_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:01:26">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/05/city-of-boston-we-want-our-authority-over-cable-back/</link><title>City of Boston: We want our authority over basic cable back</title><description>... was, in part, that the RCN company was running an Open Video System (OVS) for Boston. But according...Boston is on the warpath when it comes to basic cable rates. Its mayor Thomas M. Menino is filing... as competitive enough to keep prices down on its own. The FCC approved the deregulation of the Boston a...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>