<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7449">Asics GT 2000</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:02:15" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7449-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7449_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:02:18">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/02/kaz-a-filmmaker-documents-gran-turismos-impact-on-the-world/</link><title>Kaz : A filmmaker documents Gran Turismo’s impact on the world</title><description>... can buy a Nissan GT-R as easily in Los Angeles as a Corvette in Rome or Frankfurt.Sony commissioned... a good look at GT Academy and the Vision GT project, both of which are collaborations between Sony... from playing video games?GT Academy is a much more rigorous approach than mine, involving 1.4 million...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7449-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7449_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:02:52">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2008/09/ati-launches-sub-60-4550-4350-wraps-up-hd-4000-transition/</link><title>ATI launches sub-$60 4550, 4350; wraps up HD 4000 transition</title><description>... to see a low-profile 512MB GeForce 9600 GT at $129. Its not the cheapest 9600 GT on the market.... Turn up the resolution or detail levels even slightly, and Anand finds that NVIDIAs 9500 GT becomes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7449-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7449_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:03:28">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/02/microsoft-to-business-users-its-time-to-forget-2000-and-xp/</link><title>Microsoft to business users: it's time to forget 2000 and XP</title><description>... more than ever it can cause problems, because in less than a year Windows 2000, Windows XP, Windows... its business customers to ditch Windows 2000 and Windows XP. The long version is narrated to us... Windows 2000 computers to Windows Vista as soon as possible (extended support for Windows 2000 ends...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7449-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7449_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:04:19">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/07/support-for-windows-2000-and-windows-xp-service-pack-2-comes-to-an-end/</link><title>Support for Windows 2000 and Windows XP SP2 comes to an end</title><description>...Today is the last day that Windows 2000 and Windows XP Service Pack 2 will receive support... 3.Customers on Windows 2000 will not even have this option. The operating system is now out of its extended... options. Fewer than half a percent of Internet-connected machines appear to use Windows 2000...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7449-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7449_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:05:06">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/02/slim-ps-vita-hits-north-america-this-spring-with-borderlands-2/</link><title>Slim PS Vita hits North America this spring with Borderlands 2</title><description>...] as well.This Wi-Fi-only "PS Vita 2000" (a moniker that comes from its official model number... with six DLC packs and an 8GB PS Vita memory card. Though the Vita 2000 is available in numerous colors...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7449-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7449_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:05:45">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/12/support-for-windows-xp-sp2-windows-2000-ends-july-13-2010/</link><title>Support for Windows 2000, Windows XP SP2 ends next July</title><description>...Microsoft has issued a reminder this week that it will stop providing support for Windows 2000..., Windows 2000 Server will move out of Extended Support while Windows Server 2003 and Windows Server 2003... with just Self-Help Online Support. For Windows 2000, this means that Service Pack 4 is the end...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7449-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7449_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:06:21">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/09/support-for-older-windows-server-versions-grinding-to-a-halt/</link><title>Support for older Windows Server versions grinding to a halt</title><description>...Microsoft has released details on upcoming support lifecycle changes for Windows 2000 Server... on your calendar for the following changes: Extended Support for Windows 2000 Server will end and thus will no longer be publicly supported by Microsoft. Windows 2000 Server will continue to have Self-Help...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7449-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7449_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:06:58">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/01/slimmer-lighter-playstation-vita-redesign-coming-to-the-uk/</link><title>Slimmer, lighter PlayStation Vita redesign coming to the UK</title><description>...The Vita PCH-2000's Japanese unveiling. Early this morning, Sony announced that the redesigned PCH-2000 version of its PlayStation Vita portable would be coming to the United Kingdom on February 7 for 180 ($297), after launching in Japan last October.The new version of the system, which eliminates the 3G option available on the original Vita, is about 20 percent thinner and 15 percent lighte...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7449-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7449_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:07:27">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/03/wheres-my-knight-rider-2000-a-myford-touch-owners-lament/</link><title>Where's my Knight Rider 2000? A MyFord Touch owner's lament</title><description>...According to the Centers for Disease Control, about 1.3 million people die every year as the result of car crashesand driver distraction being a rapidly growing factor in those crashes. In a study released last week, the CDC found that nearly a third of drivers in the US text while driving. More than two-thirds admit to talking on their cell phones while driving.What the study didn't reveal ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7449-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7449_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:08:16">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/06/how-a-total-n00b-mined-700-in-bitcoins/</link><title>How a total n00b mined $700 in bitcoins</title><description>... ASIC-based Bitcoin minersmachines that are built around customized chips that do nothing except... felt confident that its application-specific integrated circuit (ASIC) designs would deliver... cooler air up from the front through the fins of the large heat sink mounted on the ASIC chip...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>