<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7450">thailand individual travel</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:09:04" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7450-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7450_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:09:07">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/07/thailand-bans-using-bitcoin-in-any-way-local-startup-reports/</link><title>Thailand bans using Bitcoin in any way, local startup reports</title><description>...A Bitcoin startup based in Thailand now says that it has suspended all operationsbecause the Bank of Thailand has effectively banned bitcoins in the southeast Asian country. As Bitcoin Co. Ltd... in Thailand:- Buying bitcoins- Selling bitcoins- Buying any goods or services in exchange for bitcoins...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7450-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7450_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:09:46">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/11/iphone-3g-coming-to-thailand-taiwan-which-may-signal-china-release/</link><title>iPhone 3G coming to Thailand, Taiwan, which may signal China release</title><description>... the iPhone 3G. Specifically, carriers in Thailand and Taiwan said that they have signed deals with Apple... one barrier to launch has been removed. Moving on to Thailand, Reuters is reporting that carrier True.... Launch details for Thailand also have yet to be finalized, but True Moves announcement...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7450-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7450_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:10:21">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/06/ars-technicast-episode-3-summer-travel-and-gadgets/</link><title>Ars Technicast Episode 3: summer travel and gadgets</title><description>...This week we are dedicating our show to summer travel and gadgets. What kind of gadgets do you bring along when you travel for work, and what kind do you bring when you're on vacation? Host... can leave us an iTunes store review.Direct Download URL: Ars Technicast Episode 3 summer travel...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7450-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7450_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:10:45">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/01/detecting-time-travelers-on-the-internet-is-remarkably-difficult/</link><title>Detecting time travelers on the Internet is remarkably difficult</title><description>... human has sorted out time travel. In one of the more unusual article introductions I've ever read... a convention for time travelers. No one claiming to come from the future showed up. S. Hawking did a similar experiment in July of 2012, holding a personal party for time travelers, but sending...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7450-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7450_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:11:33">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/11/why-i-use-tripit-to-organize-my-travel-plans/</link><title>Why I use Tripit to organize my travel plans</title><description>...Let's face it: sometimes planning travel can be a pain in the butt...;So, what time do I leave again, and where am I staying?" I'm no power traveler..., I'm getting frazzled just writing about it. Sure, some travel sites are making it easier...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7450-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7450_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:12:10">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/11/time-travel-doesnt-imbue-quantum-computers-with-superpowers/</link><title>Time-travel doesn't imbue quantum computers with superpowers</title><description>... of traveling through time?A paper that was published in the October 21st edition of Physical Review Letters... on a closed timelike circuit (CTC)a timeline that travels to the past before looping back onto... of the properties of the individual components. In fact, quantum mechanics is mathematically founded on the idea...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7450-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7450_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:12:45">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/05/ios-travel-apps-how-ars-books-executes-and-gets-around/</link><title>iOS travel apps: How Ars books, executes, and gets around</title><description>... only use when I travel, but they are quickly becoming essential to managing a smooth trip.When you search for travel apps in the App Store, however, the sheer magnitude of the selection... functions by allowing you to make in-app purchases for different cities and acts as a travel guide...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7450-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7450_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:13:38">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/04/much-slower-travel-couldnt-contain-influenza-even-in-1889/</link><title>Much slower travel couldn't contain influenza even in 1889</title><description>... the ocean despite the limited travel of that era. The way the word "pandemic" seems to be thrown... also realized that, despite much slower travel in the 19th century, the flu was able to spread... models that show that restricting air travel and similar tactics do little to stop flu spread...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7450-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7450_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:14:23">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/02/have-iphone-will-travel-without-a-data-plan/</link><title>Have iPhone, will travel—without a data plan</title><description>...With an iPhone as a travel companion, navigating strange places can be a breeze. Just open..., that is. But sometimes there's just no coverage. And when traveling abroad, cellular data... are traveling abroad and you have an unlocked GSM-compatible iPhone, you can often get a temporary SIM...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7450-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7450_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:14:53">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/06/traveling-abroad-this-summer-check-with-your-mobile-phone-service-now/</link><title>Traveling abroad with a cell phone? Do these things first</title><description>...;Wireless World Travel Week" and has launched a World Travel page which will offer lots of tips... has a list of links to the travel guide pages of the big four carriers: ATT, Verizon, Sprint, and T...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>