<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7451">buy animal farm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:15:36" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7451-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7451_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:15:38">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/05/fda-sued-over-growth-promoting-antibiotic-use-on-the-farm/</link><title>FDA sued over growth-promoting antibiotic use on the farm</title><description>... (NRDC), Center for Science in the Public Interest (CSPI), Food Animal Concerns Trust (FACT), Union... of seven classes of antibiotics that are critical in human medicine, on the grounds that farm micro... in treating human infections.The suit asks that the FDA respond to the petitions, examine the farm use...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7451-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7451_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:16:33">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/03/mysterious-hog-farm-explosions-stump-scientists/</link><title>Mysterious hog farm explosions stump scientists</title><description>...A strange new growth has emerged from the manure pits of midwestern hog farms. The results are literally explosive.Since 2009, six farms have blown up after methane trapped in an unidentified, pit... emitted by bacteria living in manure, which on industrial farms gathers in pits beneath barns...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7451-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7451_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:17:10">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/10/wind-farms-mix-air-and-temperatures/</link><title>Most efficient wind farm layout is also the least disruptive</title><description>..., research published in PNAS indicates that wind farms can also impact the local air temperature in a significant manner, and this must be taken into account to avoid unintended consequences. Wind farms.... In this paper, the authors used data from wind farms in San Gorgonio, California to show that near-surface...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7451-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7451_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:17:46">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/04/losing-labs-to-hurricane-sandy-and-animal-rights-protestors/</link><title>Losing labs to Hurricane Sandy and animal rights protestors</title><description>...For better or worse, the biological research community has become heavily reliant upon an animal... root cause. An animal rights group apparently managed to get a hold of a security card that granted them access to the University of Milan's animal facility. After chaining themselves to doors...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7451-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7451_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:18:30">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/02/massive-offshore-wind-farms-unexpected-benefit-hurricane-protection/</link><title>Massive offshore wind farms’ unexpected benefit: Hurricane protection</title><description>... of hurricanes vs. wind farms. In Sandy's case, the wind did very little direct damage; rather, the storm... by these wind farms cheaper than if it were generated using fossil fuels. And despite the high cost...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7451-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7451_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:19:06">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/03/what-scientists-really-think-about-animal-research/</link><title>What scientists really think about animal research</title><description>...Animal research has always been a polarizing topic; while it greatly advances science and medicine, it also causes the deaths of thousands of animals each year. PETA, the Animal Liberation Front, and other animal rights groups are outspoken about their side of the issue, but we hear less...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7451-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7451_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:19:44">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/04/wow-players-could-one-day-buy-fair-trade-gold-from-chinese-farms/</link><title>WoW players could one day buy "Fair Trade" gold from Chinese farms</title><description>...A new report from infoDev.org takes a fascinating, in-depth look at the so-called "virtual economy," which consists mostly of gold farming, power leveling, and other small tasks like reading CAPTCHA values. The angle that the report takes is that the market for virtual goods and services represents a growth opportunity for developing countries, and that NGOs should consider getting invo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7451-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7451_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:20:23">http://arstechnica.com/business/2014/04/open-source-comes-to-farms-with-restriction-free-seeds/</link><title>Open source comes to farms with restriction-free seeds</title><description>... organic farmers who want to keep Monsanto's products out of their farms and commercial farmers...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7451-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7451_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:21:01">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/02/leafy-rustle-you-hear-is-the-wind-farm-of-the-future/</link><title>The leafy rustle you hear could be the wind farm of the future</title><description>... from tearing itself to pieces. Without a similar level of control, your leafy wind farm might...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7451-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7451_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:21:53">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/12/strange-gelatinous-creature-gives-hints-of-the-first-animals-on-earth/</link><title>Strange gelatinous creature gives hints of the first animals on Earth</title><description>...A few years ago, the origins of all animals seemed very simple. Sponges lacked a nervous system, which placed them at the very root of the animal family tree. They did, however, have specialized... to be closely related to animals. Some choanoflagellate species get together in colonies, making it seem...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>