<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7452">arizona game and fish homepage</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:22:24" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7452-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7452_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:22:25">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2009/01/homepage-django-content/</link><title>Homepage Django Content</title><description>... Don't call it DRM: Microsoft explains new gaming piracy tech March 24, 10:20 p.m. UTC - by Ben Kuchera... additions to the Games for Windows platform, along with more protection for publishers. They want you... you to buy the games. Read more | Comment Reform groups blast telco-backed broadband mapper March 24...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7452-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7452_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:23:04">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/11/review-flick-fishing-for-iphone/</link><title>Review: Flick Fishing for iPhone</title><description>... was once only a single game (Flick Bowling) officially a series. Flick Fishing, a fishing simulator... in the game ranging from carp to blue marlin. Which fish you catch depends entirely on the venue you choose... have ever been fishing (if the answer is no, t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7452-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7452_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:23:56">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/06/reminder-mac-homepage-is-going-away-july-7/</link><title>Reminder: .Mac HomePage is going away July 7</title><description>... HomePage is going away for good on July 7. The phasing out of the online webpage creation tool... HomePage goes offline, users will no longer be able to create or edit existing pages.... It seems to suggest that content created with the HomePage application couldn't be edited...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7452-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7452_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:24:37">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/01/arizona-set-to-make-online-impersonation-a-felony/</link><title>Arizona set to make online impersonation a felony</title><description>...Arizona could soon become the latest state in the union to pass state legislation that would make online impersonation, or e-personation, a crime.According to the Arizona Republic, State Rep. Michelle Ugenti, (R-Scottsdale) willintroduce a bill that would make it a felony to use another persons...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7452-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7452_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:25:15">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/01/the-global-consequences-of-fish-poop/</link><title>The global consequences of fish poop</title><description>...We usually think of the oceans inorganic carbon cycle being dominated by tiny critters such as foraminifera, but a recent study suggests fish poop may also be an important contributor. You see, fish constantly drink calcium- and magnesium-rich sea water; to successfully use the water, they must first get rid of some of those ions. They do this by increasing the pH in their gut to around 8.4 to 9....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7452-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7452_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:25:46">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/07/a-catch-22-commercial-fishing-and-the-evolution-of-fish/</link><title>A catch-22: commercial fishing and the evolution of fish</title><description>...Few things illustrate the concept of sustainability as clearly as overfishing. When fish... shrinks along with it.But fish may actually be evolving in response to the pressure of fishing, reaching reproductive maturity more quickly. That adaptation comes at a cost, however. Fish that spawn...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7452-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7452_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:26:17">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/02/fish-nostrils-on-acid/</link><title>Fish lose their way with nostrils on acid</title><description>... by performing electron microscopy of fish nostrils. The researchers raised hundreds of baby clownfish... that is expected to have no benefit (and perhaps some drawbacks) for the fish. The unfavorable... avoiding the genetically risky proposition of incest. Once in the flume, the fish were allowed to pick...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7452-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7452_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:26:52">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/08/good-bye-shark-week-large-sharks-in-decline-due-to-fishing/</link><title>Good-bye Shark Week? Large sharks in decline due to fishing</title><description>..., but that didnt prepare them for commercial-scale fishing. Sharks, skates, and rays are fantastically abundant... one step down from apex predators.Fishing operations appear to be at fault. Targeted commercial fishing, by-catch, and even subsistence fishing are rearranging the chips in many marine ecosystems, knocking...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7452-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7452_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:27:18">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/07/carbon-dioxide-makes-fish-swim-right-into-enemies-clutches/</link><title>High CO2 concentrations can turn fish into daredevils</title><description>...High carbon dioxide concentrations in the ocean may turn fish into reckless daredevils, according to a study published in PNAS this week. When scientists exposed two different species of fish larvae to elevated carbon dioxide levels, the fish began to ignore the smell of predators, multiplying...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7452-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7452_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:28:03">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/06/elephantnose-fish-evolved-complex-eyes-to-see-in-muddy-water/</link><title>Elephantnose fish evolved complex eyes to see in muddy water</title><description>... in cats, for example, help them see best in the dark.And then there are elephantnose fish, whose.... In these fish, cone cells cluster into cups along the retina, which reduces the spatial resolution... have figured out how those cups help the fish (Gnathonemus petersii) see in murky African waters.Heres how...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>