<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7453">pc 2 games reviews</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:28:40" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7453-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7453_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:28:41">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/09/trackmania-2-re-introduces-play-to-racing-games/</link><title>Trackmania 2 Canyon on PC re-introduces play to racing games</title><description>... outcome. Trackmania 2 Canyon carves out a unique space in the world of racing games in order to provide... the limitations of international play. Trackmania 2 Canyon It doesn't hurt that the game looks... into "why the hell not?" territory.The game will be released fo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7453-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7453_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:29:31">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/11/modern-warfare-2-reviews-behind-the-scenes-of-early-access-1/</link><title>A Modern Warfare 2 primer on early access and game reviews</title><description>... version of the game, with reviewers given no option to try the PC version. Does this affect how reviewers...How important is it for readers of game reviews to understand the conditions under which a review was written? Would it change th...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7453-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7453_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:30:21">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/07/no-early-starcraft-2-reviews-well-be-playing-with-you/</link><title>No early StarCraft 2 reviews; we'll be playing with you</title><description>...Are you scouring the Internet for StarCraft 2 reviews? Don't bother. Blizzard has confirmed to Ars Technica that no outlets have been given early access to the game for final reviews; we'll... in PC gaming of the past few years... Blizzard doesn'...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7453-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7453_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:30:55">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/09/trackmania-2-canyon-on-pc-is-addictive-beautiful-and-oddly-local/</link><title>Trackmania 2 Canyon on PC is addictive, beautiful, and oddly local</title><description>.... Trackmania 2 Canyon The single player game is fun, but the real joy comes from joining a multiplayer... with your purchase. The game is available now on the PC for $25. If I had to dig deep to come...You control the cars in Trackmania 2 Canyon with the arrow keys on your keyboard. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7453-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7453_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:31:28">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/07/the-pillars-of-pc-gaming-why-starcraft-lan-play-matters/</link><title>The pillars of PC gaming: why StarCraft 2 LAN play matters</title><description>... Battle.net to be the ideal destination for multiplayer gaming with StarCraft 2 and future Blizzard...When the first stories began to spread about StarCraft 2 not supporting LAN play, the Internet began to fight back. Sure, it fought with mostly useless online petitions and griping on various gaming...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7453-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7453_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:32:01">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/04/starcraft-2-collectors-edition-will-be-100-worth-it/</link><title>StarCraft 2 Collectors Edition will be $100, worth it</title><description>...Blizzard has announced details of the $99.99 Collector's Edition of StarCraft 2, and it looks like it's time to start saving your money. This edition comes with the game, of course... from the game An exclusive 2GB USB flash drive replica of Jim Raynor's dog tag, which comes preloaded...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7453-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7453_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:32:42">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/08/a-decade-to-separate-us-ars-reviews-starcraft-2/</link><title>A decade to separate us: Ars reviews StarCraft 2</title><description>... of all time, and one of the world's most-played PC games, period. Blizzard certainly isn't afraid... all of Blizzard's properties.We've been playing StarCraft 2 since Monday, and the game is good... from scratch using the StarCraft 2 engine. The Lost Viking arcad...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7453-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7453_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:33:26">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/08/torchlight-2-trailer-gives-us-exactly-what-we-want/</link><title>Torchlight 2 trailer gives us exactly what we want</title><description>... this Torchlight 2 trailer. Why? It knows what we want, and we are given that thing. Behold... 3 is released, and then subtract two years from that date. These games are not competing... is served.Plus, if this game is released at $20, you'll be able to buy a copy for you and two...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7453-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7453_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:34:01">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/04/starcraft-2/</link><title>No more shackles: single-player StarCraft 2 goes full-bore</title><description>... of single-player games, you'll see things in StarCraft 2 the first game never hinted atthe care... of StarCraft 2 is unique. A competition-level multiplayer experience. A single-player game featuring... with the game. Every time we get to look at new cont...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7453-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7453_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:34:38">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/08/starcraft-2-replaces-demo-with-starter-edition/</link><title>StarCraft 2 replaces demo with "Starter Edition"</title><description>...Blizzard has replaced its traditional StarCraft 2 demo with a new bundle of content it's calling the StarCraft 2 "Starter Edition." Anyone with a Battle.net account can download... in Custom Games and Single-Player vs. AI.Access to the following custom maps (map selection may rotate...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>