<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7454">inuyasha pics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:35:00" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7454-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7454_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:35:01">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/08/pics-because-it-really-is-happening-on-mars/</link><title>Pics, because it really is happening on Mars</title><description>...This feels a bit like releasing a greatest hits album after one chart-topping single, but we're going to show you some of our favorite images from the landing and activation of the Curiosity rover on Mars. Although Curiosity is on track to be sending back data for years, its arrival and first few days on the Red Planet have been nothing short of spectacular, with a complicated landing plan g...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7454-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7454_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:35:38">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/08/pics-and-you-assume-it-did-happen/</link><title>Pics and you assume it did happen</title><description>...True or false: the macadamia nut is closely related to the peach. Most of us don't have the sort of background information that will let us answer that with confidence. Still, we have a gut feeling about the answer"Nuts and fruit? Probably not." These sort of gut reactions to things can be key to helping us navigate through a world where we often don't have complete informatio...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7454-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7454_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:36:24">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/04/plastics-out-metals-in-aluminum-lumia-catwalk-pics-leak/</link><title>Plastic’s out, metal’s in: Aluminum Lumia “Catwalk” pics leak</title><description>...Pictures of a phone that's purported to be Nokia's next flagship Windows Phone handset have hit the Web (via WPCentral). If it's real, it looks like the Finnish company is making some big stylistic changes to the Lumia line.Enlarge / What appears to be a micro-HDMI connector at the top of the Catwalk. The device, codenamed "Catwalk," discards the brightly colored polycarb...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7454-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7454_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:37:02">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/04/school-it-allegedly-took-thousands-of-pics-in-webcam-case/</link><title>School IT allegedly took "thousands" of pics in webcam case</title><description>...Remember the lawsuit filed by the family of 15-year-old Blake Robbins against the school district that spied on him at home via webcam? The latest news comes from a motion filed by the Robbins family claiming that the school took more than 400 photos of Blake in his roomsome while sleeping and others while he was "partially undressed."According to the motion filed Thursday, the Robbins ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7454-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7454_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:37:36">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/12/teens-blase-about-sexting-but-only-4-cop-to-sending-pics/</link><title>Teens blasé about sexting, but only 4% cop to sending pics</title><description>...For those of us who remember being teenagers (especially at the dawn of the Internet age), the fact that young people are making use of their cell phones to send sexually suggestive content is not only unsurprising, it's downright expected. Still, the phenomenon (tragically referred to as "sexting") is constantly being examined in the context of cyberbullying, privacy, and child po...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7454-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7454_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:38:09">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/01/pics-of-acer-aspire-one-with-10-inch-screen-surface/</link><title>Pics of Acer Aspire One with 10-inch screen surface</title><description>...Acer has had its 8-inch Aspire One netbook on the market for a while now. New photos have surfaced of the next netbook in the Aspire line, which sports a 10-inch screen. No official specifications are known yet, but some of the reported specifications have surfaced. What we do know is that the netbook will have a 10-inch screen sporting the 1024 x 600 screen resolution of the other 10-inch netboo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7454-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7454_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:38:47">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/07/the-oatmeal-mails-pics-of-cash-kodiak-bear-seduction-to-lawyer/</link><title>The Oatmeal mails pics of cash, Kodiak bear seduction to lawyer</title><description>...The FunnyJunk/Oatmeal/Carreon circuswhich raised issues of online defamation, copyright compliance, "cyber-vandalism," and the ethics of online fundraising, and which drew in groups as disparate as the American Cancer Society, the Electronic Frontier Foundation, and Public Citizenfinally looks set to pack up the big top and ride the rails out of town.The duffel taken to the bank to carr...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7454-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7454_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:39:24">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2012/05/hands-on-app-lets-you-bump-smartphone-pics-to-your-computer/</link><title>Hands-on: app lets you "Bump" smartphone pics to your computer</title><description>...Snapping a quick picture on your iPhone is easy, but getting the image on your desktop can sometimes be a chore. Bump, an early iPhone app that made it easy to swap contact info by "bumping" two iPhones together, now lets you bump your iPhone on your computer to send a selection of images straight to your computer's hard drive, or even to Bump's photo-sharing cloud service.I&amp;a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7454-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7454_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:40:24">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/01/india-obscene-pics-of-gods-require-massive-human-censorship-of-google-facebook/</link><title>India: obscene pics of gods require massive human censorship of Google, Facebook</title><description>...It's hardly the sort of Internet policy statement one hopes to hear from judges in major democracies. "Like China, we can block all such websites [who don't comply]," Justice Suresh Cait told Facebook and Google lawyers in India yesterday. "But let us not go to that situation." No, let's not. But it's what the government wants if Internet companies won&amp;apos...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7454-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7454_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:40:58">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2011/01/pics-of-the-new-antenna-wifi-sharing-prefs-on-verizon-iphone/</link><title>Pics of the new antenna, WiFi sharing prefs on Verizon iPhone</title><description>...The Verizon iPhone has finally arrived, offering users a CDMA alternative to the ATT version introduced in the summer of 2010. But aside from the fact that they use different cell networks here in the US, the Verizon version of the iPhone 4 has a few cosmetic differences. The most significant is the fact that the controversy-filled antenna no longer has a visible gap on the top, not to mention a ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>