<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7456">gps reviews</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:47:45" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7456-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7456_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:47:46">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/12/faster-gps-that-wont-kill-your-battery-needs-the-cloud-and-a-crowd/</link><title>Faster GPS that won't kill your battery via the cloud, and a crowd</title><description>...;s network of satellites. Part of that effort has included using a network of GPS-fixed reference stations to build an ever-improving model of satellite orbit data, which can be used to help GPS... of "near-real-time" GPS applications that promise to both squeeze additional accuracy...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7456-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7456_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:48:15">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/11/minnesota-its-ok-to-use-a-gps-tracker-on-your-spouse-if-you-co-own-the-car/</link><title>Minnesota: It's OK to use a GPS tracker on your spouse if you co-own the car</title><description>... involved GPS tracking, and although the court did not raise the issue and there was no statute...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7456-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7456_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:48:52">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/01/assisted-gps/</link><title>Inside assisted GPS: helping GPS help you</title><description>...Location, location, location The Global Positioning Satellite (GPS) system can help you find... expectations of GPS are that it works accurately, instantly, and reliably on all our devices. Thats asking a bit much from what is fundamentally 1990s-era technology. Fortunately, theres help. Assisted GPS...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7456-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7456_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:49:23">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2010/11/gps-enabled-smartphones-putting-squeeze-on-gps-makers/</link><title>GPS-enabled smartphones putting squeeze on GPS makers</title><description>..."Would you like to upgrade your car with a GPS?" "No thanks, I have my phone." That was the exchange I had while renting a car recently (right after I declined an upgrade to a Hummer). It made me wonder whether sales of dedicated navigation devices were suffering thanks to smartphones with GPS capabilities. According to a new report from industry research firm Berg Insight, th...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7456-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7456_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:50:02">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/11/predicting-the-movements-of-a-giant-gps-tagged-iceberg/</link><title>Predicting the movements of a giant GPS-tagged iceberg</title><description>.... Data from two GPS devices attached to the iceberg by the British Antarctic Survey will be used...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7456-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7456_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:50:46">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/02/uk-research-measures-growing-gps-jamming-threat/</link><title>GPS jammers and spoofers threaten infrastructure, say researchers</title><description>..., experts discussed the threat posed by a growing number of GPS jamming and spoofing devices..., because even low-power GPS jammers pose a significant threat to cell phone systems, parts... GPS signals for time-keeping, GPS jamming can throw them off and cause outages. "We're...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7456-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7456_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:51:17">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/04/lightsquared-broadband-a-threat-to-gps/</link><title>LightSquared broadband: a threat to GPS?</title><description>...The Pentagon and Department of Transportation have a written the Federal Communications Commission a letter insisting that they're more than a bit worried about a new satellite-based wholesale broadband service: LightSquared wireless."The new LightSquared business plan and the new FCC rules significantly expand the terrestrial transmission," the letter warns, "increasing the p...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7456-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7456_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:51:50">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/06/bipartisan-bill-would-end-governments-warrantless-gps-tracking/</link><title>Bipartisan bill would end government's warrantless GPS tracking</title><description>...Under a new bill dubbed the "GPS Act," law enforcement officials would no longer be able to obtain geolocation data from cellphones and GPS tracking devices without a warrant."I take... announcing the bill. "The law enforcement community is going too far" by using GPS trackers...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7456-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7456_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:52:28">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/02/real-jailbroken-gps-for-the-iphone-looks-promising/</link><title>Turn-by-turn GPS for (jailbroken) iPhones looks promising</title><description>..., but wasn't thrilled with the GPS capabilities and was wondering if she should just buy a dedicated unit... project, a solution that is quickly becoming a product that rivals standalone GPS units.The... the iPhone's built-in GPS or a module that you can purchase from the company.XWaves is getting ready...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7456-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7456_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:53:01">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/05/project-delays-not-putting-gps-at-risk-says-air-force/</link><title>Project delays not putting GPS at risk, says Air Force</title><description>... report, with seven different systems analyzed, only two of which are GPS programs, and its conclusions... the program avoid the inevitable cuts. The GPS systems haven't been immune to these sorts of issues, but they also face problems of their own. Right now, the second generation GPS satellites...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>