<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7457">the music man lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:53:28" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7457-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7457_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:53:29">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/10/lyrics-site-liveuniverse-slammed-with-6-6-million-copyright-judgment/</link><title>Lyrics site LiveUniverse slammed with $6.6 million copyright judgment</title><description>...Several years after music publishers began pursuing websites that published lyrics on the Web... from music publishers. That's $12,500 per song for the 528 songs whose lyrics he was accused... LiveUniverse makes it crystal clear: hosting an unauthorized lyrics site can get you i...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7457-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7457_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:54:20">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/01/isle-of-man-gets-unlimited-music-downloads-with-blanket-fee/</link><title>Isle of Man gets unlimited music downloads with blanket fee</title><description>..., an Isle of Man official announced a shocker: the island will soon feature a compulsory music license... like the Isle of Mans proposal. But we have yet to see a national music levy on ISP access...The Isle of Man is an odd place. Ruled by a woman called the Lord of Mann (Queen Eliz...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7457-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7457_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:54:45">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/02/inside-the-isle-of-mans-1month-unlimited-music-plan/</link><title>Inside the Isle of Man's</title><description>... in music or not. The grand planThe Isle of Man is a crown protectorate, a position that keeps it separate...Last month, the Isle of Man announced that it was going to try its governmental hand at addressing rampant music piracy. At today's Digital Music Forum East, Ron Berry, t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7457-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7457_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:55:18">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/10/chelsea-manning-speaks-from-prison-for-the-first-time-rejects-pacifist-label/</link><title>Chelsea Manning speaks from prison for the first time, rejects “pacifist” label</title><description>...In her first public statement since being sentenced to 35 years in prison, Chelsea Manning (formerly known as Bradley Manning) says that she rejects being called a pacifist.Manning recently received... it, Manning wrote on Tuesday. In fact, I first found out about the award when I began receiving mail...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7457-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7457_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:55:58">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/03/ms-splosion-man/</link><title>Ms. Splosion Man features a sexy, sociopathic, exploding... hero?</title><description>... joy in this business.Luckily,Ms. 'Splosion Man, Twisted Pixel's first sequel... leaveThe story, such as it is, concerns a now-captured 'Splosion Man and the creation of a female equivalent of the exploding, insane hero of the past game. Ms. 'Splosion Man has a bow...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7457-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7457_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:56:38">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/12/army-releases-2010-chat-log-between-manning-and-assange/</link><title>Army releases 2010 chat log between Manning and Assange</title><description>... chat logs from 2010 between former intelligence analyst Chelsea Manning (formerly known as Bradley Manning) and Wikileaks founder Julian Assange. After handing over a massive trove of diplomatic cables and other videos to Wikileaks, Manning was convicted in July 2013 of espionage, theft...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7457-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7457_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:57:14">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/11/bradley-manning-finally-fesses-up-over-wikileaks/</link><title>Bradley Manning finally fesses up over WikiLeaks...</title><description>...Bradley Manning, the US Army Private First Class accused of leaking classified documents... Meade, Maryland.To be clear, Manning has not pled guilty or not guilty in the case, where.... But this marks the first time Manning has offered to accept formal responsibility for leaking government...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7457-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7457_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:57:52">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/02/manning-shocked-by-the-bloodlust-went-with-wikileaks/</link><title>Manning, shocked by “the bloodlust,” went with WikiLeaks</title><description>...Over the course of two hours in a military courtroom today, Bradley Manning explained whyand... were not part of a plea bargain; Manning still faces trial in June on the most serious charges, such as "aiding the enemy."The Guardian's Ed Pilkington sets the scene:Manning was flanked...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7457-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7457_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:58:36">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/05/pac-man-is-30-celebrate-along-with-google/</link><title>Pac-Man is 30! Celebrate along with... Google?</title><description>...-Man above the search bar. The logo is the center of the maze and the game recreates the sights.... Authenticity was important. "Google doodler Ryan Germick and I made sure to include PAC-MANs... and developer wrote. If you put in another virtual coin, Ms. Pac-Man joins the fun for co-op play. Use the arrow...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7457-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7457_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 09:59:28">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/07/bradley-manning-not-guilty-of-aiding-the-enemy-convicted-on-19-other-counts/</link><title>Bradley Manning not guilty of “aiding the enemy,” convicted on most other counts</title><description>...After a military trial that lasted nearly two months, a military judge has found Private Bradley Manning guiltyof most of the countsthat he faced, butnot guilty of charges of aiding the enemy," the most serious of the remaining 12 charges he faced. However, the young soldier was convicted of espionage, theft and computer fraud charges.As The Guardian reported from the courtroom: "The ju...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>