<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7461">navalni trial latest news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:19:13" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7461-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7461_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:19:14">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/04/crowdsourcing-a-clinical-trial-to-treat-als/</link><title>Crowdsourcing a clinical trial to treat ALS</title><description>... this tendency to share information to crowdsource a sort of clinical trial, obtaining data... research, and promising results have been seen in some animal models and small clinical trials.... Although these patients didn't provide a randomized clinical trial population, they did present...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7461-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7461_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:20:06">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/02/labels-want-13-million-from-pirate-bay-as-trial-starts/</link><title>Big Content wants $13 million from Pirate Bay as trial starts</title><description>... million kronor). For a trial taking place in Sweden and broadcast only in Swedish... the world. With Swedish media outlets making the audio stream of the trial available, bilingual webheads... for past "bad behavior"). They are intent on seeing the trial as mere spectacle...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7461-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7461_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:20:35">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/04/is-permission-needed-to-retween-hot-news/</link><title>Is permission needed to retweet hot news?</title><description>...When an aggregator like Google News publishes newspaper headlines, is the company treading on thin... conference on the future of news and told the assembled audience (read the transcript PDF): What we're talking about is news-aggregation sites where they take headline and lead...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7461-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7461_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:21:16">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/05/news-corp-flabbergasted-anyone-could-oppose-three-strikes/</link><title>News Corp. flabbergasted anyone could oppose "three strikes"</title><description>...Rupert Murdoch's son James runs News Corp.'s sprawling operations in Europe and Asia, and he's had it with the search engines, consumer electronics companies, and users who want access to his company's content without paying a "fair contribution." In a speech this week...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7461-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7461_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:21:56">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/08/trials-hd-impresses-with-violence-physics-and-insanity/</link><title>Simple, violent, addictive: Trials HD on Xbox 360</title><description>...When a game is great, we refer to it as a "beer warmer." The genesis of this term? You sit down for an evening of gaming, open a beer, then find yourself so engrossed in the title that the next time you remember to take a sip, the beer's no longer cold. Microsoft has been releasing beer warmers with surprising regularity during this year's Summer of Arcade promotion, and the t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7461-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7461_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:22:35">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/09/the-week-in-review-stupid-users-lhc-woes-windows-reverse-engineering-and-more/</link><title>News week in review: stupid users, LHC woes, Windows reverse engineering, and more</title><description>... it will be offline well into the first part of 2009. Other news of note from the week gone by: It lives... to physical formats. The latest is slotMusic, 1GB microSD cards with 320kbps MP3sYoud think Blu-ray... infringement verdict against Jammie ThomaseBay keeps finding new ways to irritate its users. The latest...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7461-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7461_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:23:16">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/08/trials-hd-is-great-sharing-tracks-not-so-much/</link><title>Trials HD is great. It's a shame sharing tracks is broken</title><description>...Trials HD ended up being one of the biggest surprises during this year's Summer of Arcade, bringing some addictive actionwith impressive graphicsto the Xbox Live Arcade. While I'm guessing many Xbox Live Arcade fans will jump over to Shadow Complex this Wednesday, Trials HD has the chance...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7461-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7461_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:23:49">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/11/the-week-in-tech-news-depressing-internet-sex-revenge-seeking-admins-and-nehalem/</link><title>The week in tech news: depressing Internet sex, revenge-seeking admins, and Nehalem</title><description>.... Other news of note from the week gone by: That didnt take long: the T-Mobile G1, the first Android... least-favorite e-voting machine vendor was in the news last week. Diebold is being sued for improperly using GPL-licensed code in its voting machinesWith Halloween came news of a frightening Linux...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7461-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7461_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:24:37">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/10/news-week-in-review-night-vision-scammers-on-the-run-and-skype-blunders/</link><title>News week in review: night vision, scammers on the run, and Skype blunders</title><description>..., and some improvements for plug-in developers. Other news of note from the week gone by: The Nintendo DS...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7461-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7461_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:25:10">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/02/ifpi-boss-youre-either-with-us-or-against-us/</link><title>IFPI boss at TPB trial: you're either with us or against us</title><description>...Since it began last week, the trial of the Pirate Bay in Sweden has truly been a "spectrial"and not just because of juvenile Pirate Bay antics such as last night's open letter to IFPI boss John Kennedy. The spectacle kicked back into high gear Wednesday as Kennedy traveled from London to Sweden to give testimony in the trial on behalf of the worldwide major-label music industry. On...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>