<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7463">hollywood actress</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:31:34" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7463-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7463_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:31:35">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/06/study-p2p-customers-are-hollywoods-best-friend/</link><title>Study: P2P customers are Hollywood's best friends—really!</title><description>..., and that's clearly something that we don't think that Hollywood is very aware of."When I...;more reasonable" about conditions. Hollywood, though, hasn't been quick enough to learn the lessons...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7463-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7463_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:32:00">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/03/dotcom-says-hollywood-studios-once-courted-megaupload/</link><title>Dotcom says Hollywood studios once courted Megaupload</title><description>... had Megaupload accounts. And he reveals that between 2008 and 2010, multiple Hollywood studios... from several major Hollywood studios. E-mails supplied to TorrentFreak show employees at Disney, Warner.... But the breadth of Megaupload's user base, and the fact that multiple Hollywood studios apparently...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7463-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7463_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:32:36">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/07/kim-dotcom-predicts-victory-in-war-with-hollywood/</link><title>Kim Dotcom predicts victory in war with Hollywood</title><description>... from penning a defiant open letter to Hollywood."The very powerful and the very stupid have one thing in common," Dotcom said in the letter published by the Hollywood Reporter. "Instead... of dollars in video sales." He suggested that Hollywood should have adapted to locker sites like...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7463-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7463_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:33:11">http://arstechnica.com/business/2011/05/youtube-boosts-movie-rentals-with-over-3000-hollywood-titles/</link><title>YouTube boosts movie rentals with over 3,000 Hollywood titles</title><description>...YouTube's low-key movie rental service got a shot in the arm from major Hollywood studios on Monday. YouTube announced that it is adding thousands of feature films from Lions Gate, Sony Pictures, Warner Bros, and Universal to its stable of streaming movie content. US users will be able to rent...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7463-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7463_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:33:55">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/08/anonymous-donors-bring-hollywood-production-values-to-anti-mpaa-video/</link><title>Anonymous donors bring Hollywood production values to anti-MPAA video</title><description>...A video accusing the American government of selling out to Hollywood has made a splash after being...-Hollywood sentiment is nothing new, especially on The Pirate Bay, but what sets this video apart is its top-notchone might even say Hollywood-caliberproduction values.On Wednesday, Ars talked...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7463-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7463_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:34:26">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/06/tigon-hollywood-and-games-speak-different-languages/</link><title>Tigon: Hollywood and games speak different languages</title><description>..., the reason for the communication barrier is because neither Hollywood nor game developers take each... in Hollywood struggle to understand the creative decisions that we makethey don't get why something... in Hollywood and seeing some of their process, is just how little Ior anybody else around gamesknow...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7463-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7463_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:35:04">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/06/microsoft-prowls-hollywood-for-more-exclusive-xbox-one-video-content/</link><title>Microsoft prowls Hollywood for more exclusive Xbox One video content</title><description>...Microsoft CEO Steve Ballmer and Microsoft Entertainment Studios president Nancy Tellem have been trying to drum up exclusive entertainment content for the upcoming Xbox One, according toa report from Deadline. Ballmer is supposedly touting how the Xbox One will be able to take its viewing experience above and beyond that of a cable channel, possibly in hopes of securing companion programming for ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7463-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7463_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:35:30">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/09/actress-in-anti-islam-film-sues-youtube-on-copyright-grounds/</link><title>Actress in anti-Islam film sues YouTube on copyright grounds</title><description>...A California actress who appeared in the infamous Innocence of Muslims flick on YouTube is again asking a federal court to remove the anti-Islam footage that has spawned deadly protests and sparked... not remove the film when the actress agent sent five takedown notices naming 17 URLs on Sept. 24 and 25...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7463-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7463_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:35:59">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/08/us-movie-tickets-get-biggest-price-hike-in-history/</link><title>US movie tickets get biggest price hike in history</title><description>...," says Hollywood-focused publication The Wrap, "with average admission costs spiraling upward...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7463-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7463_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:36:37">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/10/when-a-virtual-actress-nude-images-leak-who-should-take-the-legal-blame/</link><title>When a gaming actress’ nude images leak, who should take the legal blame?</title><description>...When nude images of Jodie Holmes, actress Ellen Page's character from Beyond: Two Souls, began appearing on the Internet a few weeks ago (courtesy of a repositioned shower-scene camera running... that included direct nude images of the actress. This might be a thin technicality considering...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>