<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7466">interconnects skin effect</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:49:16" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7466-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7466_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:49:18">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/playstation-gets-its-own-skin-condition/</link><title>Playstation gets its own skin condition</title><description>...While critics of video games like to claim that playing too many video games is bad for your health, doctors have affirmed that playing games for extended periods of time can create rather painful sores on a person's hands. As a result, doctors have labeled this condition "PlayStation palmar hidradenitis," something that Sony is sure to be thrilled about.According to the BBC, the B...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7466-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7466_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:49:49">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2014/03/nvidia-and-ibm-create-gpu-interconnect-for-faster-supercomputing/</link><title>Nvidia and IBM create GPU interconnect for faster supercomputing</title><description>...Nvidia and IBM have developed an interconnect that will be integrated into future graphics..., compared to 16GB per second today.NVLink, the interconnect, will be part of the newly announced..., and machine learning will benefit from the new architecture. Nvidia also said the NVLink interconnect...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7466-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7466_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:50:13">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/07/gnomon-photo-tour-how-artists-get-into-video-games/</link><title>Gnomon School of Visual Effects: training the next generation of effects artists</title><description>... in the special effects industry would be in the best position to train others working... of Visual Effects so special.Gnomon has stayed in the same facility since it began, and art... from some of the biggest names in all the areas of special effects design and art. Reading the rsums of the people either...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7466-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7466_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:51:08">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/02/no-fix-for-mass-effect-2-text-issue-could-have-been-avoided/</link><title>No fix for Mass Effect 2 text; issue could have been avoided</title><description>...? We had readers contacting us to talk about their problems reading the text in Mass Effect 2...;We understand that on some standard definition TVs the smallest text in Mass Effect 2... this issue does affect a small portion of SDTV owners, we are unable to resolve it for Mass Effect 2...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7466-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7466_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:51:36">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/01/mass-effect-2-to-get-one-more-dlc-release-turns-off-news-network/</link><title>Mass Effect 2 to get one more DLC release, turns off news network</title><description>...Mass Effect 2's Cerberus Network, a service that provided story background for off-screen... one more DLC package coming to players before the release of Mass Effect 3\. The Cerberus Daily News... Effect 3, which is due out sometime this coming holiday season for the Xbox 360, PS3, and PC...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7466-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7466_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:52:01">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/upcoming-mass-effect-dlc-and-sequel-info-revealed/</link><title>Upcoming Mass Effect DLC and sequel info revealed</title><description>...Fans of Bioware's excellent sci-fi epic RPG Mass Effect now have even more reason to look..., trailers, and a documentary titled "The Future of Mass Effect." The documentary actually focuses on a couple of different topics, including upcoming downloadable content for Mass Effect...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7466-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7466_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:52:33">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/01/bioware-to-reveal-mass-effect-2-details-at-gdc/</link><title>Bioware to reveal Mass Effect 2 details at GDC</title><description>..., and Mass Effect, will be discussing the content for its upcoming Mass Effect 2 at the Game Developers... their development cycle: Lessons learned from Mass Effect lead to a detailed description of the new... about the second entry into the Mass Effect trilogy have been nonexistent to this point. It also ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7466-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7466_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:52:55">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/05/ea-and-bioware-detail-iphone-mass-effect-title-officially/</link><title>EA and Bioware detail iPhone Mass Effect title, officially</title><description>...Bioware doesn't seem too happy that news of the iPhone Mass Effect title was released before the company was ready, but in a recent post on the game's official forum the details were made official, and all the rumors were put to rest. So what's the real story behind the game?First off, the game is real, it's coming to the iPhone and the iPod touch, and someone broke a non-disc...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7466-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7466_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:53:53">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/12/mass-effect-3-coming-for-360-ps3-pc-in-holiday-2011/</link><title>Mass Effect 3 coming for 360, PS3, PC in "Holiday 2011"</title><description>...We're as excited as anyone about the idea of Mass Effect 3, but the series was always planned... taking placein the game play between the first and second Mass Effect titles, the new game is bound... who are just now getting a taste of Mass Effect 2....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7466-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7466_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 10:54:18">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/12/adobe-releases-after-effects-9-0-1-update-with-several-fixes/</link><title>Adobe releases After Effects 9.0.1 update with several fixes</title><description>...If youve had any issues with the CS4 release of Adobes After Effects software, there may now..., After Effects 9.0.1, which contains a goodly list of bug fixes just in time for the holidays. The 9.0.1 update... that are included in the After Effects update. Specific squashed bugs include two rendering issues, an Open...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>