<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7468">car change radiator fluid</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:00:15" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7468-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7468_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:00:16">http://arstechnica.com/science/2008/12/forming-a-planet-via-fluid-instabilities/</link><title>Forming a planet via fluid instabilities</title><description>..., it is known that, when two fluids with different densities (such as gas and gas-dust mixtures) flow next... at whether complex fluid effects are enough to keep the dust sufficiently mixed so as to prevent these gravitational instabilities. In the paper, Prof. Barranco developed and carred out a series of three...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7468-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7468_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:00:47">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/07/can-non-newtonian-fluid-behavior-explain-stuck-ketchup-bottles/</link><title>Can non-Newtonian fluid behavior explain stuck ketchup bottles?</title><description>... the answer.The context was the article I wrote last week about non-Newtonian fluids, where... slowly.Many non-Newtonian fluids exist that are staples of YouTube videos and science magic shows... my knowledge of fluid dynamics is pretty sketchy. However, condiments are of vital importance...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7468-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7468_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:01:27">http://arstechnica.com/science/2008/12/supercritical-fluids-and-more-freaking-cnts-no-touch-plz/</link><title>Supercritical fluid processing of carbon nanotube composites</title><description>...Supercritical fluids are quickly becoming an alternative to costly and dangerous organic solvents... and pressure, a supercritical fluid loses surface tension and can act as an impressive solvent. Readers... was only a matter of time before carbon nanotubes (CNTs) and supercritical fluids were put together...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7468-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7468_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:02:02">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/09/no-new-cars-or-power-plants-still-locked-into-13-of-climate-change/</link><title>No new cars or power plants? Still locked into 1.3° of climate change</title><description>... of climate change and ocean acidification. But most of those focus on future infrastructure and equipment... coal-fired power plants and the like. For land use changes, it relies on values in the IPCC report... key impacts of climate change, we conclude that sources of the most threatening emissions have yet...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7468-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7468_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:02:46">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/08/dennis-kucinich-wants-radiation-levels-clearly-labeled-on-your-cell-phone/</link><title>Dennis Kucinich wants radiation levels clearly labeled on your cell phone</title><description>... all of that (and some of the dubious science on cell phone radiation and electrosensitivity), Rep. Dennis Kucinich (D-OH... to update the outdated Specific Absorption Rate (SAR).Cell phone radiation is due to come up in the news... required by the Kucinich bill would mandate disclosure of RF radiation emissions levels, legal li...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7468-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7468_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:03:21">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/03/know-your-nukes-understanding-radiation-risks-in-japan/</link><title>Know your nukes: understanding radiation risks in Japan</title><description>... or more, so you need a substantial amount of the material for the radiation to really register.If you..., it can set off a rapid series of further decays that produce a lot of additional radiation. When it comes..., but decay fast enough that they can deliver high doses of radiation in a short span of time. This is why...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7468-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7468_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:03:50">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/05/council-of-europe-to-consider-ban-on-wifi-and-mobiles-in-classrooms/</link><title>Europe issues alert over "more or less potentially harmful" cell phone radiation</title><description>...The global movement for governments to err on the side of electro-magnetic caution got a huge boost this month. The Council of Europe has issued a new draft resolution and report on device radiation safety that urges its 47 member nations to adopt a "precautionary principle" when it comes to cell phone safety. Such a principle would apparently include banning all mobile phones, DECT pho...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7468-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7468_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:04:40">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/08/making-thz-radiation-stick-to-the-straight-and-narrow/</link><title>Inside the weird world of terahertz radiation</title><description>... to longer wavelengths; terahertz radiation(basically, heat), in particular, which has wavelengths... for this is that the sources for THz radiation are, well, unfriendly. They are either really bulky, or so small that they emit their radiation everywhere, making it impossible to collect efficiently. Fortunately, a recent...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7468-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7468_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:05:13">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/05/san-francisco-backtracks-on-cell-phone-radiation-bill/</link><title>San Francisco backtracks on cell phone radiation bill</title><description>...The City of San Francisco's controversial cell phone radiation disclosure bill has been put... about the accuracy of the radiation labels," the article notes, "which some say could actually lead shoppers to buy phones that emit more radiation than others."Easily accessible...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7468-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7468_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:05:46">http://arstechnica.com/security/2013/06/after-burglaries-mystery-car-unlocking-device-has-police-stumped/</link><title>After burglaries, mystery car unlocking device has police stumped</title><description>... that changes in a planned sequence to prevent would-be thieves from standing near the car... silently down a deserted residential street in Long Beach, California. Each one goes up to a car in the area, takes out a small electronic device, and pulls on the passenger side car handle. The first...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>