<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7469">ibm thinkpad t43 change fan</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:06:17" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7469-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7469_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:06:18">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/04/thinkpad-quality-tablet-style-lenovos-thinkpad-tablet-2-reviewed/</link><title>ThinkPad quality, tablet-style: Lenovo’s ThinkPad Tablet 2 reviewed</title><description>... applications.The insides of Lenovo's ThinkPad Tablet 2 are largely identical to those of the Acer Iconia.... What Lenovo's Clover Trail tablet brings to the table is the ThinkPad name, which many PC buyers still swear by. Lenovo's entry packs most of the ThinkPad line's virtues into a tablet...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7469-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7469_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:07:25">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/09/lenovo-announces-haswell-thinkpads-and-a-really-really-wide-monitor/</link><title>Lenovo announces Haswell ThinkPads and a really, really wide monitor</title><description>... when the holiday season rolls around. Lenovo is kicking things off for us with a number of ThinkPad announcementsthe new laptops are getting Haswell, but they still retain that classic ThinkPad look, right... of October. Lenovo The ThinkPad T440s is the slightly higher-end version of the laptop. Lenovo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7469-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7469_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:08:11">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/10/canonical-and-ibm-team-up-for-ubuntu-based-win-7-alternative/</link><title>Canonical and IBM team up on Ubuntu-based Win 7 alternative</title><description>...Canonical and IBM have teamed up to offer companies an alternative to Windows 7 and Microsoft's productivity software. IBM says that customers can save up to 50 percent by adopting its Client... with high hardware upgrade costs.The IBM Smart Work solution for Linux was originally launched last month...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7469-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7469_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:08:44">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/01/lenovos-thinkpad-x1-the-notebook-with-two-brains/</link><title>Lenovo's ThinkPad X1: the notebook with two brains</title><description>...Throwing another idea at the wall to see if it sticks, Lenovo introduced the ThinkPad X1 Hybrid at the CES Unveiled press pre-CES event here in Las Vegas on January 8. The follow-on to Lenovo's ultra-thin ThinkPad X1, the Hybrid is designed to maximize battery life by switching personalitiesfrom full-featured Windows mode to a power-sipping "Instant Media Mode" running on a separat...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7469-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7469_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:09:16">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/08/a-worthy-ultrabook-appears-the-thinkpad-x1-carbon-reviewed/</link><title>A worthy Ultrabook appears: the ThinkPad X1 Carbon reviewed</title><description>... specs to heart. Lenovo's ThinkPad X1 Carbon reflects what we feel is the true spirit... the silicone's tendency to pick up dust and detritus (it brushes away fairly easily). The ThinkPad..., you're out of luck. Two-finger zoom is present in theory, and the cursor changes perfectly...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7469-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7469_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:10:21">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/03/report-ibm-eyes-sun/</link><title>What IBM might gain by buying Sun Microsystems</title><description>...;s open-source portfolio would probably entail some licensing changes, though. IBM wasn't happy... the company around recently and that IBM is an interested party. The report indicates that if the talks... floated by IBM is $10 to $11 per share for Sun, which would put the total size of the deal at $8...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7469-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7469_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:10:58">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/09/pro-note-takers-take-note-hands-on-with-the-lenovo-thinkpad-tablet/</link><title>Pro note-takers, take note: hands on with the Lenovo ThinkPad tablet</title><description>...The ThinkPad tablet is Lenovos second recent entry into the tablet space, a professional cousin... ThinkPad tablet favors flexibility over portability, but its performance is middling at best when compared to other Android devices.The ThinkPad doesnt escape the thick-and-heavy profile that plagues...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7469-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7469_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:11:47">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2014/04/50-years-ago-ibm-created-mainframe-that-helped-bring-men-to-the-moon/</link><title>50 years ago, IBM created mainframe that helped send men to the Moon</title><description>... changes isn't possible, IBM tries to give users at least a year's warning before they'd...50 years ago today,IBM unveiled the System/360 mainframe, a groundbreaking computer that allowed new levels of compatibility between systems and helped NASA send astronauts to the Moon.While IBM...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7469-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7469_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:12:30">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/02/litigation-between-sco-and-ibm-to-resume/</link><title>Litigation between SCO and IBM to resume</title><description>...Litigation between IBM and disgraced UNIX vendor SCO is set to be reactivated, Groklaw reports... on the Linux operating system. The company claimed that IBM misappropriated code from UNIX and integrated... that SCO faced, however, was the fact that they don't even own the UNIX copyrights.The IBM...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7469-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7469_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:13:15">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/07/ibm-embraces-firefox-adopts-it-internally/</link><title>IBM embraces Firefox, adopts it internally</title><description>...A recent change to IBM's internal IT policy has made Firefox the company's default Web... environments. IBM plans to roll it out to employees on new computers and will encourage its staff...), which was developed by Firefox modification consultant Michael Kaply while he was employed by IBM...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>