<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7470">is sugar poison</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:13:39" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7470-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7470_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:13:40">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/03/sugar-labs-announces-new-version-of-sugar-learning-platform/</link><title>Sweet new version of Sugar Learning Platform on its way</title><description>...The Sugar Learning Platform was originally designed to serve as the interactive software... self-directed learning. Sugar Labs, the organization behind the project, announced this week... director Walter Bender, aims to bring Sugar to a broader audience and make it more accessible to students...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7470-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7470_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:14:29">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/04/sugar-labs-releases-beta-of-live-usb-learning-environment/</link><title>First taste: Sugar on a Stick learning platform</title><description>...Sugar Labs has launched the first beta release of Sugar on a Stick, a new version of the open source Sugar Learning Platform that is designed to boot on conventional desktop computers and run directly from USB flash memory devices.The Sugar software environment was originally created...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7470-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7470_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:15:32">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/06/sugar-on-a-stick-brings-sweet-taste-of-linux-to-classrooms/</link><title>Sugar on a Stick brings sweet taste of Linux to classrooms</title><description>...Sugar Labs, a nonprofit organization that builds open source educational software, has announced the official release of Sugar on a Stick, a Linux-based platform that includes a suite of child... about OLPC's long-term viability and commitment to the open source philosophy. Sugar Labs has taken...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7470-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7470_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:16:00">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/12/sugar-software-environment-gets-sweeter-with-version-2/</link><title>Sugar software environment gets sweeter with version 2</title><description>...Sugar Labs announced this week a major update of Sugar on a Stick, a Linux-based computing... strategy, Bender created Sugar Labs to ensure that OLPC's Sugar learning environment will continue to advance. His team's vision is to bring Sugar to a broader audience by making i...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7470-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7470_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:16:20">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2008/12/sugar-labs-gets-sweet-with-the-gnome-foundation/</link><title>Sugar Labs gets sweet with the GNOME Foundation</title><description>... Benderthe project's former president of softwareearlier this year. He launched Sugar Labs, a non-profit organization dedicated to improving and encouraging adoption of the Sugar environment... philosophies. The GNOME foundation announced today that Sugar Labs has become its latest member...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7470-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7470_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:16:54">http://arstechnica.com/security/2008/11/ddos-attacks-dns-cache-poisoning-keeping-isps-up-at-night/</link><title>DDoS attacks, DNS cache poisoning keeping ISPs up at night</title><description>... poisoning or other infrastructure weaknesses, but these fears arent being communicated to law enforcement... the most, the majority of ISPs chose bots and botnets (26 percent) with DNS cache poisoning jumping into second...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7470-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7470_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:17:31">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/05/evolution-helps-cockroaches-lose-their-sweet-tooth-increase-survival/</link><title>Evolution helps cockroaches lose their sweet tooth, increase survival</title><description>... of pie? For people, the downside of the deliciousness of sugar is simply feeling really full or gaining weight, but for cockroaches, their sweet tooth can be deadly.The poisoned baits people set to kill roaches in their homes lure the unsuspecting insects in with sugar. But it turns...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7470-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7470_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:18:01">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/01/getting-the-lead-out-to-prevent-poisoning/</link><title>Removing lead to prevent poisoning</title><description>...Lead poisoning is a serious problem for children, wildlife, and people who work in industries like battery manufacturing. Lead poisoning can permanently damage the central nervous system, kidneys, and various other organs. Children are particularly susceptible to elevated levels of lead...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7470-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7470_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:18:43">http://arstechnica.com/science/2008/11/environmental-purification-with-dna-and-a-sugar-ring/</link><title>Water purification with DNA and a sugar ring</title><description>... that a composite material of DNA and -cylcodextrin, a seven-membered sugar ring, would be able to accumulate both...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7470-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7470_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:19:19">http://arstechnica.com/security/2008/09/gov-is-latest-gtld-to-hop-aboard-the-dnssec-bandwagon/</link><title>Uncle Sam to fight cache poisoning with switch to DNSSEC</title><description>... to protect users from DNS cache poisoning. Poisoned DNS servers have been fooled into returning false information in response to a DNS lookup request. A client querying a poisoned DNS server... it straight at a different, malware-contaminated site. Part of what makes DNS cache poisoning such a nasty...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>