<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7472">python re tutorial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:26:15" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7472-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7472_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:26:16">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/04/tutorial-use-twitters-new-real-time-stream-api-in-python/</link><title>Tutorial: consuming Twitter's real-time stream API in Python</title><description>... informed feedback.This tutorial will show you how to consume and process data from Twitter's new streaming API. The code examples, which are written in the Python programming language... streaming in Python is to use PyCurl, the Python bindings for the well-known Curl network library...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7472-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7472_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:26:57">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/12/getting-a-grip-on-python-six-ways-to-learn-online/</link><title>Getting a grip on Python: six ways to learn online</title><description>... useful for your learning path. These represent just a fraction of the available online Python tutorial resources. Online Python tutorials Official Python Tutorial Its hard to go wrong when Python.org... to understand the big Python pictu...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7472-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7472_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:28:01">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/07/how-to-build-a-desktop-wysiwyg-editor-with-webkit-and-html-5/</link><title>How to build a desktop WYSIWYG editor with WebKit and HTML 5</title><description>... it with a simple native user interface.For this example we will use the Python programming language and the GTK... in some environments using the programming language with which you are building your program. The Python bindings... and dialogs. The whole thing is roughly 200 lines of code.#!/usr/bin/env python## Example Text Ed...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7472-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7472_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:28:43">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/07/howto-building-textbox-url-shortener-with-pygtk/</link><title>How to build a textbox URL shortener with PyGTK+</title><description>.... In this tutorial, I'll show you how to intercept and manipulate text as it is being pasted into a GTK... position. The insert-text callback provides the position as a parameter, but unfortunately the Python...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7472-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7472_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:29:06">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/03/python-wins-trademark-dispute-rival-stops-calling-itself-python/</link><title>Python wins trademark dispute, rival stops calling itself "Python"</title><description>...The Python Software Foundation recently went public with a battle against a company in Europe... by one of the world's most popular programming languages.Just a little over a month later, the Python Software... services under the name Python. PO Box Hosting was also seeking a figure trademark over a logo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7472-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7472_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:29:44">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/02/python-v-python-software-foundation-fights-for-trademark-in-eu/</link><title>Python v. Python: Software foundation fights for trademark in EU</title><description>...The Python programming language has been around for more than two decades, but today it is fighting for its name in Europe. The Python Software Foundation's chairman yesterday said the Python... the name Python is trying to get ownership of the mark.In a blog post, Foundation Chairman Van...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7472-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7472_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:30:28">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/08/openbossa-announces-new-lgpl-python-bindings-for-qt/</link><title>New LGPL Python bindings for Qt slither into the light</title><description>...OpenBossa and Nokia have launched a new project called PySide to build high-quality Python bindings... Python bindings for Qt. Riverbank distributed PyQt under a dual licensing model. The code is available... model that Trolltech previously used for Qt.Although I'm an enthusiastic fan of both the Python...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7472-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7472_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:31:08">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/09/python-3-3-arrives-with-new-yield-expression/</link><title>Python 3.3 arrives with new yield expression</title><description>...Today the release of Python 3.3.0 was made official, with a couple new syntax features, a handful... delegation to subgenerators or arbitrary subiterators. Python 3.3 also permits u'unicode' syntax which isnt in itself new, but restores Python 2's Unicode literal syntax, to make more code...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7472-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7472_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:31:48">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2010/04/python-support-in-gnome-gets-a-boost-from-hackfest/</link><title>Python support in GNOME gets a boost from hackfest</title><description>...Some GNOME developers have gathered in Boston for for a Python GNOME hackfest that is hosted... a strategy for delivering Python 3.0 compatibility for the GNOME platform and advancing the Python... itself is built with C, it can also be used with other programming languagesincluding Python, Ruby...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7472-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7472_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:32:24">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/03/python-adopts-the-mercurial-version-control-system/</link><title>Python adopts the Mercurial version control system</title><description>... strategy.Guido van Rossum, creator and lead developer of the Python programming language, announced... the migration before the Summer.Mercurial, which is built primarily in Python, was originally... some in the Python community. The decision was largely between Bazaar and Mercurial. In the end, van Rossum chose...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>