<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7473">noise canceling head phones</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:33:04" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7473-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7473_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:33:05">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/01/exploiting-the-noise-in-gps-data/</link><title>Exploiting the noise in GPS data</title><description>... of people finding unexpected signals in their noise. Such is the case with the present study, a study I... getting to a GPS instrument. Both the atmosphere and the land create problems called multi-path noise. This noise is suppressed as much as possible by the instruments, but it is never completely...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7473-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7473_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:33:41">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/04/canadians-may-soon-get-relief-from-harsh-cellphone-early-termination-fees/</link><title>Canadians may soon get relief from harsh cellphone early termination fees</title><description>..., and provide a reduction in cancellation fees for those planning to leave a contract early.A member..., cap cancellation fees, prevent automatic renewal and make cellphone contracts considerably... in order to purchase a comparably subsidized phone. If a user wishes to leave their contract early...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7473-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7473_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:34:13">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/01/hands-on-sonys-head-mounted-3d-display/</link><title>Hands-on: Sony's head-mounted 3D display</title><description>...Many consumers find it difficult to wrap their head around the idea of buying a new television just to get 3D functionality. Sony's answer is a 3D television that wraps around your head. The company's new head-mounted 3D display is designed to give users a theater-like 3D viewing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7473-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7473_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:35:02">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/04/facebooks-chat-heads-headed-to-ios-later-today/</link><title>Facebook’s chat heads headed to iOS later today (Updated)</title><description>... chat heads would be arriving on the Facebook iOS app later today, in addition to stickers (a popular... of the app.What exactly are chat heads? They're not as scary as they sound if you're already used... receiving, you will instead see a bubble with the head of the person who's trying to get...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7473-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7473_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:35:50">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/04/hack-replaces-normal-ios-notifications-with-facebook-chat-heads/</link><title>Hack replaces normal iOS notifications with Facebook “Chat Heads”</title><description>... iPhones lets Chat Head notifications appear across the operating system, as they do for Android phones with the new Facebook Home installed.Chat Heads are part of the Facebook Home environment...A developer has created a hack that allows the new Chat Heads feature in the iOS Facebook app...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7473-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7473_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:36:39">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/11/oculus-delays-dev-kits-for-rift-head-mounted-display-by-three-months/</link><title>Oculus delays dev kits for Rift head-mounted display by three months</title><description>...When Oculus Technology launched the Kickstarter for its 3D head-mounted display, the Oculus Rift, those who pledged $300 or more were told they could expect to try out a development kit in December... integrated with Unreal Engine 3. Hey, we've already waited at least 18 years for a head-mounted...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7473-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7473_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:37:29">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/01/valves-experimental-steamvr-brings-games-to-head-mounted-displays/</link><title>Valve’s SteamVR is Steam—for your head-mounted display</title><description>...Roughly a year and a half after moving from the computer monitor to the TV with Big Picture mode, Valve has transitioned its Steam interface to head-mounted displays this week, launching SteamVR on the beta version of its popular game distribution client.As noted in the newly launched SteamVR section of the Steam Community website, users with a head-mounted display like the Oculus Rift Developers...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7473-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7473_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:38:06">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/10/efor-all-officially-dead-as-e3-morphs/</link><title>E for All officially dead as E3 morphs</title><description>... for All is definitely canceled. Unfortunately, E for All will not be occurring in 2009, as our focus now...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7473-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7473_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:38:43">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/11/on-the-move-vrcade-combines-free-motion-with-head-mounted-virtual-reality/</link><title>On the move: VRCade combines free motion with head-mounted virtual reality</title><description>... standing in a virtual room that recalls the Doom series: a dark, neon-coated space base. I move my head... of Wii launch game Elebits, modified to let you tie one Wiimote to your head for aiming purposes... with VRCade in mind doesn't need animations coded for things like head bob, reloads, and the like...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7473-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7473_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:39:29">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/06/no-windows-phone-8-upgrade-for-current-phones/</link><title>No Windows Phone 8 upgrade for current phones</title><description>...As long suspected, users of the current Windows Phone 7.5 platform won't be able to upgrade to the next major version of Microsoft's smartphone operating system, Windows Phone 8.Instead, they'll receive an update called Windows Phone 7.8. The only feature that Microsoft has confirmed...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>