<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7474">php convert special symbols to html</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:40:00" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7474-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7474_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:40:01">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/10/zend-targets-mobile-and-cloud-with-new-php-tools/</link><title>Zend targets mobile and cloud with new PHP tools</title><description>... three new products that aim to extend the reach of the PHP scripting language beyond the web, bring... for rapid mobile app development and cloud back-ends to make PHP an even bigger contender... building applications that integrate cloud-based services using PHP and the Zend Framework, rapidly...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7474-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7474_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:40:29">http://arstechnica.com/business/2011/10/zend-builds-a-pick-your-partner-php-cloud-platform/</link><title>Zend builds a pick-your-partner PHP cloud platform</title><description>... developed in the PHP web server-side scripting language on Tuesday at the ZendCon conference in Santa... the popular kid as of late, PHP is still the leading web technology in terms of the raw number of deployments, with over 20 million domains using the Apache PHP module alone. A number of PHP-based plat...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7474-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7474_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:41:05">http://arstechnica.com/business/2011/01/html-to-lose-the-version-number/</link><title>HTML to lose the version number</title><description>...In a blog entry Thursday, HTML specification editor Ian Hickson announced that the HTML..., sort of like a rolling release model.The need for clear HTML versioning has diminished and is arguably superfluous. Browser vendors tend to implement new HTML features at their own pace regardless...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7474-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7474_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:41:38">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/12/web-served-part-3-bolting-on-php-with-php-fpm/</link><title>Web served, part 3: Bolting on PHP with PHP-FPM</title><description>... scripting language called PHP. That's what we're going to install, because it's relatively easy to get PHP up and running and because having PHP available gives you a tremendous amount... is the ease with which PHP can be enabled. Nginx, unlike Apache, has no ready-made modules to install...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7474-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7474_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:42:08">http://arstechnica.com/business/2011/12/facebook-looks-to-fix-php-performance-with-hiphop-virtual-machine/</link><title>Facebook looks to fix PHP performance with HipHop virtual machine</title><description>..., or "HipHop," an interpreter that allows PHP script to be converted first into an abstract...++ code. While converting PHP to a lower-level language wasn't a new conceptRoadsend, for example, converts PHP to C code and compiles itconverting to C...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7474-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7474_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:42:30">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/02/unethical-html-video-copy-protection-proposal-criticized-by-standards-stakeholders/</link><title>"Unethical" HTML video copy protection proposal draws criticism from W3C reps</title><description>...A new Web standard proposal authored by Google, Microsoft, and Netflix seeks to bring copy protection mechanisms to the Web. The Encrypted Media Extensions draft defines a framework for enabling the playback of protected media content in the Web browser. The proposal is controversial and has raised concern among some parties that are participating in the standards process.In a discussion on the W...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7474-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7474_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:43:25">http://arstechnica.com/security/2014/03/php-bug-allowing-site-hijacking-still-menaces-internet-22-months-on/</link><title>PHP bug allowing site hijacking still menaces Internet 22 months on</title><description>...A vulnerability that allows attackers to take control of websites running older versions of the PHP... Ars reported 22 months ago, the code-execution exploits worked against PHP sites only when they ran... are still using it, understanding that a major part of the install base of PHP does not update on a regular...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7474-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7474_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:44:03">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2008/12/converter-coupon-funds-will-run-out-in-january/</link><title>Converter coupon funds will run out in January</title><description>.... The Digital converter coupon program has been around for much of the year to provide those needing a converter with $40 of the purchase price and according to Reuters; those funds are estimated to run out in early January. That means that any consumers who need a converter and have yet to apply...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7474-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7474_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:44:44">http://arstechnica.com/security/2013/10/hackers-compromise-official-php-website-infect-visitors-with-malware/</link><title>Hackers compromise official PHP website, infect visitors with malware (updated)</title><description>...Maintainers of the open-source PHP programming language have locked down the php.net website... Networks blog post here. The attacks started Tuesday and lasted through Thursday morning, PHP... of servers, PHP officials wrote in an earlier statement. There's no evidence that any of the code...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7474-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7474_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:45:20">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/08/apple-webkit-engineer-named-co-chair-of-html-working-group/</link><title>Apple WebKit engineer named co-chair of HTML Working Group</title><description>... Stachowiak, manager of the WebKit WebApps Team at Apple, as one of the new co-chairs of the HTML... Berners-Lee in an e-mail to the W3C HTML mailing list. "I am pleased that all three co-Chairs...."Further Reading:Read up on the history of HTML from 1999 to 2007.Some more information...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>