<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7475">software consultant work at home</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:45:41" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7475-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7475_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:45:42">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/04/study-surfing-the-internet-at-work-boosts-productivity/</link><title>Study: surfing the Internet at work boosts productivity</title><description>...Workers are more productive when they are able to occasionally do non-work stuff online..., enables the mind to rest itself, leading to a higher total net concentration for a days work... softwareclaimed that Web surfing at work was costing businesses almost $200 billion per year (hmm...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7475-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7475_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:46:14">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/12/researchers-store-working-memory-in-brain-slices/</link><title>Researchers store working memory in brain slices</title><description>... tasks. And, even though we have a decent idea of how individual neurons work, scientists are still... of short-term, working memories in the neurons of a rat brain and, in the process, managed to read and write individual bits into a brain slice. Working memory provides the short-term recall capacity...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7475-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7475_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:46:45">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/09/report-workers-spend-25-of-work-time-goofing-around-online/</link><title>Report: workers spend 25% of work time goofing around online</title><description>... that Excel spreadsheet, then youre likely one of the workers that spend about 25 percent of their work time... consultant firm Voco says that CEOs and CIOs of companies are often completely unaware of what employees are doing online during work hours, allowing them (especially the tech-savvy ones) to get away...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7475-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7475_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:47:22">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/12/sonys-home-juggles-free-speech-with-hate-speech/</link><title>Sony's Home juggles free speech, hate speech</title><description>...Sonys Home has had a rocky start. Server issues, lack of compelling content, and a somewhat hostile... its discrimination, Michael Marsh, a gamer who wanted to set up a gay/straight alliance in Home, told..., which contains the word Hell. This points to a larger problem that Home will be forced to deal...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7475-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7475_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:48:17">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2014/01/the-battle-for-the-home-why-nest-is-really-googles-new-smart-home-division/</link><title>The battle for the home: Why Nest is really Google’s new smart home division</title><description>...Guess who's now the leader in the connected-home space? Google's 3.2 billion dollar... of the connected home. With the dust settled and news of the acquisition sinking in, it's time to take a look at what Google might have in store for the company.Google's Smart Home DivisionOne...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7475-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7475_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:48:42">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/12/hands-on-with-sodium-one-not-quite-the-evolution-home-needs/</link><title>Hands-on with Sodium One: not quite the evolution Home needs</title><description>...After over a year of existence, PlayStation Home is still struggling to find its place. Despite a wealth of game-themed spaces and even an alternate reality game, there isn't much to do while in Home, something that's been a problem for the service from the very beginning. Enter Sodium One. The curiously named Home space is being billed by Sony as the "next evolutionary step"...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7475-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7475_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:49:12">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/01/biologists-wipe-out-a-mouses-spatial-working-memory/</link><title>Biologists wipe out a mouse's spatial working memory</title><description>...Working memory is the place we hold temporary information that we're using to handle ongoing... recall that you make a left at the third traffic lightbut working memory plays an essential role in many processes, and a person's working memory capacity seems to correlate with their performance...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7475-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7475_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:49:33">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/01/slap-happy-sam-playstation-home/</link><title>Slap Happy Sam makes PlayStation Home fun, Conspiracy falters</title><description>...Ever since the release of Home, Sony has experimented with various ways to entice users to enter... of mini-games. Now Sony is attempting something different: releasing Home games crafted by actual..., but not any more interesting. This is an action-style game set in Home, and as such it doesn't play...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7475-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7475_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:50:08">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2008/11/november-update-for-windows-home-server-full-of-improvements/</link><title>November update for Windows Home Server full of improvements (Updated)</title><description>...Following the release of Power Pack 1, the Windows Home Server team has been hard at work looking at a revamped UI, considering splitting the OS in two, and putting together the next update. Today a minor software update of Windows Home Server (WHS) has been released via Windows Update. According to KB Article 957825, this is primarily a bug fix release: This update improves the interaction betwe...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7475-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7475_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:50:38">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2008/10/orphan-works-copyright-reform-fails-in-wake-of-bailout-bid/</link><title>"Orphan Works" copyright reform fails in wake of bailout bid</title><description>...The Orphan Works Act of 2008 was passed by the Senate last week, but the House failed to take.... The bill would have loosened restrictions on using copyright-protected works that have been abandoned... of specificity. The House version of the bill states that individuals are entitled to make use of a work...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>