<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7477">china bird flu</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:57:12" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7477-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7477_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:57:13">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/04/new-strain-of-bird-flu-hops-to-humans-in-china/</link><title>New strain of bird flu hops to humans in China</title><description>... deaths, word has arrived that China may be facing a new threat from an influenza virus typically limited to birds. Currently, there have been nine confirmed infections that resulted in three deaths... (for more on the H/N nomenclature, see our influenza primer). It's typically confined to birds...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7477-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7477_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:57:47">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/01/transgenic-chickens-glow-green-block-spread-of-bird-flu/</link><title>Transgenic chickens glow green, block spread of bird flu</title><description>..., it looks like a promising approach to limiting the bird flu. Science, 2011. DOI... designed to block a broad range of avian flu viruses. Oddly, the antiviral transgene doesn't seem to help the birds that carry it, but somehow limits the spread of the virus. The researchers adopted...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7477-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7477_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:58:16">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/04/h7n9-bird-flu-still-spreading-in-china-worrying-who/</link><title>H7N9 bird flu still spreading in China, worrying WHO</title><description>...Three weeks ago, there were only nine confirmed cases of the new H7N9 bird flu, three... about the risk posed by the virus. Since then, testing in China has greatly expanded, and the World... of China, whichwas found in a Taiwanese businessman who had recently visited the Chinese city...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7477-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7477_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:58:39">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/05/research-finally-published-showing-how-bird-flu-virus-can-spread-among-mammals/</link><title>Bird flu paper published despite worries of weaponization</title><description>...For years, public health officials have been watching the H5N1 bird flu virus warily. When it hops from birds to people, it has a disturbing tendency to kill them. So far, however, it has been unable to spread from person to person, which has kept the world safe from a lethal pandemic. That posed a rather significant question: could the bird flu ever evolve the ability to spread among mammals, an...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7477-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7477_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:59:22">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/04/mutant-h5n1-bird-flu-virus-papers-to-be-published-in-full/</link><title>Mutant H5N1 bird flu virus papers to be published in full</title><description>...Scientists have explained the decision to publish the full versions of two papers on the H5N1 bird flu virus just months after they had opted to release only edited versions.At a Royal Society... that the WHO had assembled to combat avian flu." In particular, WHO was worried that countries...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7477-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7477_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 11:59:48">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/02/archaeologists-find-evidence-of-birds-dinosaur-ancestors/</link><title>Paleontologists find evidence of birds' dinosaur ancestors</title><description>... evidence that they share a common ancestry. Two new studies of fossils from China show that bird-like dinosaurs predate the earliest official birds, and shed light on the origin of feathers. Scientists...Many different kinds of animals coexisted during the Jurassic period, from primitive birds to two...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7477-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7477_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:00:36">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/01/researchers-hit-pause-on-controversial-killer-flu-research/</link><title>Researchers hit pause on controversial killer flu research</title><description>..., requiring prolonged contact with infected birds or people. That it could become more contagious... terrorists could use the research to develop weaponized flu strains. Another, perhaps more frightening...-security laboratories in the United States, and its thought that one now-global flu strain may actually...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7477-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7477_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:01:14">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/05/flu-cases-subside-as-people-contemplate-flu-parties/</link><title>Flu cases subside as people contemplate "flu parties"</title><description>... its earlier warnings that the virus behind the recent flu outbreak had the potential to cause a pandemic... public health measuresworked to moderate the impact of the virus. Confirmed and suspected flu cases... will turn some other flu strain entirely into our next pandemic. Flu parties? You've got...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7477-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7477_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:01:52">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/03/study-early-birds-had-four-wings/</link><title>Study: early birds had four wings</title><description>...The ancestors of modern birds probably had four wings rather than two, according to a study of fossils found in a Chinese museum.The four-winged early birds had been identified from fossilised remains a number of years ago, but it was unclear whether the creatures were precursors to modern birds...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7477-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7477_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:02:18">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/05/flu-update-initial-outbreak-widespread-but-slowing/</link><title>Flu update: how do scientists know it's "swine flu," anyhow?</title><description>...The world is getting a clearer picture of the extent and shape of the recent flu outbreak... Control seem to think that the spread observed so far is not atypical for a flu virus. Lethality outside... described virus is the complexity of the process. Because of the large genetic diversity of the flu...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>