<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7478">protect kids online</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:02:43" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7478-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7478_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:02:44">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/01/report-biggest-online-threat-to-kids-is-other-kids/</link><title>Report: biggest online threat to kids is other kids</title><description>..., one in which it promised to do more to protect its younger users from various dangers thought to be lurking online. Although the agreement included a variety of specific steps to be taken by the social... the issue of the online safety of children more generally. That task force has now completed its work...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7478-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7478_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:03:13">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/12/government-toughens-up-online-privacy-rules-for-kids-websites/</link><title>Government toughens up online privacy rules for kids' websites</title><description>... used to regulate it, change over time. The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (or COPPA... more clarity to enforcing privacy protection for kids in the changing tech world, especially when dealing...There is currently no federal online privacy law, which makes it essentia...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7478-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7478_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:03:29">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/12/ftc-drags-out-old-tired-ideas-for-protecting-kids-online/</link><title>FTC drags out old, tired ideas for protecting kids online</title><description>...;s on top of the fact that the biggest threat to kids online is... other kids. According to a 2009 report... targeted by adults online is very low compared to kids targeting other kids. In this case, trying... online. When parents are awa...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7478-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7478_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:03:58">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/07/hey-kids-learn-to-be-cyber-smart-from-the-nsas-youth-page/</link><title>Hey kids! Learn to be “cyber smart” from the NSA’s youth page!</title><description>... information on protecting kids' identities online, including how to behave on social networks...The National Security Agency wants your kids to know that it's cool to be "cyber smart... at children and adolescents. The "Kids Page," intended for elementary age children, appears...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7478-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7478_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:04:39">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2008/10/two-new-laws-try-to-keep-kids-safe-from-online-creeps/</link><title>Two new laws try to keep kids safe from online creeps</title><description>... of legislation recently signed by President Bushthe Protect Our Children Act and the Keeping the Internet Devoid of Sexual Predators Actthat actually aim to frustrate Internet Uncle Ernies. Online... sex between minors could encroach upon protected speechthink Romeo and Juliet. But, in a ruling...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7478-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7478_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:05:21">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/03/review-kid-icarus-uprising-loses-control-of-an-otherwise-enjoyable-mythological-romp/</link><title>Review: Kid Icarus: Uprising loses control of an otherwise enjoyable mythological romp</title><description>... is the case with Kid Icarus: Uprising, an imaginative, lighthearted, fun-filled game that ultimately falls... with the control scheme for Kid Icarus Uprising is a matter of functional overload on your left hand. Your right.... This story is mainly told via a nearly constant banter between Pit and his protective goddess Palutena...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7478-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7478_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:06:25">http://arstechnica.com/business/2010/01/obvious-report-on-increased-media-use-among-kids-is-obvious/</link><title>Kids consume media as a full-time job—many getting overtime</title><description>... to about two hours. Unsurprisingly, kids spend most of their time online at social networking sites.... The report notes that kids spend less time reading magazines or newspapers, though online reading...We already have a pretty good idea that most kids and teens probably spend too ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7478-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7478_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:06:55">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2011/02/ftc-says-it-will-look-into-apples-marketing-of-in-app-purchases-to-kids/</link><title>FTC says it will look into Apple's marketing of in-app purchases to kids</title><description>... purchases to children. The decision comes after a wave of complaints about kids running up huge bills... add-ons to kids, saying that he was "disturbed" by the reports. "Companies shouldnt be able to use Smurfs and snowflakes and zoos as online ATMs pulling money from the pockets...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7478-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7478_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:07:34">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/08/protect-ip-act-would-cost-taxpayers-47-million-private-sector-much-more/</link><title>PROTECT IP Act would cost taxpayers $47 million, private sector much more</title><description>...The Congressional Budget Office has released a new estimate of the cost of the PROTECT IP Act... administration, the CBO estimates that the enforcement activities of PROTECT IP will cost taxpayers... of large-scale Internet censorship infrastructure mandated by the PROTECT IP Act, so it's hard...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7478-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7478_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:08:25">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/12/california-sues-delta-for-failing-to-put-privacy-policy-on-mobile-app/</link><title>California sues Delta for failing to put privacy policy on mobile app</title><description>... it is not in compliance with the Online Privacy Protection Act. That legislation, enacted by the California... has decided to make an example of the airline.The Online Privacy Protection Act applies...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>