<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7479">dunbar number social networks</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:09:02" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7479-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7479_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:09:03">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/04/social-networks-may-self-segregate-naturally/</link><title>Spotting social networks before they disintegrate</title><description>... social networks, as defined by common interests or shared experiences, exist within subsets... social network. One focuses on our ability to identify communities within the larger population graph... decided to find out how they might affect a social network. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7479-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7479_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:09:36">http://arstechnica.com/business/2011/06/googles-eric-schmidt-says-he-screwed-up-on-social-networking/</link><title>Google's Eric Schmidt says he "screwed up" on social networking</title><description>... of the competitive threat posed by upstart social networking websites like Facebook and LinkedIn... he didnt focus more on social networking, Schmidt had a simple answer:I was busy, he said.Earlier... with AllThingsDs Kara Swisher, Schmidt described Googles social stumble as his big...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7479-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7479_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:10:04">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/02/hands-on-virb-20-social-network-gets-smarter-integrated/</link><title>Hands on: Virb 2.0 social network gets smarter, integrated</title><description>...In 2007, Virb wrapped the social aspects of Facebook with the rich, media-centric platform of MySpace in a gorgeous package that looks better than both. Now the company has launched a major redesign with a more refined approach to helping users showcase their online activity and content, as well as stay on top of what their friends and favorite artists are up to. Virb may be "yet another soc...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7479-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7479_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:10:36">http://arstechnica.com/business/2010/08/nielsen-social-networking-and-gaming-up-email-uncertain/</link><title>Most Internet time now spent with social networks, games</title><description>...Just in case you needed further confirmation that blogs, social networks, and games are overtaking everything else on the 'Net, Nielsenhas released its latest statistics. They show that Americans now spend almost a quarter of their PC/laptop days and nights on social networking sites and blogs. That's a 43 percent jump from a year ago.Social networking now has a 22.7 percent share of th...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7479-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7479_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:11:05">http://arstechnica.com/business/2010/09/google-planning-to-ape-facebook-for-google-me-social-network/</link><title>Google planning to ape Facebook for "Google Me" social network</title><description>...Google plans to incorporate more social networking features across its services this fall according to comments made by CEO Eric Schmidt during the Google Zeitgeist conference on Tuesday. The initiative is internally referred to as "Google Me" inside the company, though according to Schmidt it won't be a separate service.Google has had mixed success with social networking in its pa...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7479-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7479_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:11:38">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/06/tagging/</link><title>Tag networks on social sites may predict next Internet fad</title><description>... networks of concepts, but also describe network-level connections among users and concepts... started deploying complex network theory, which involves the mathematical dissection... complex network theory from regular network theory is the ability to account for unusual or subtle...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7479-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7479_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:12:08">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/12/the-long-tail-may-be-vanishing-on-the-social-networks/</link><title>The long tail may be vanishing on the social networks</title><description>... will create a rich get richer situation, in which a limited number of sites wind up attracting the vast... a draft of a new study indicates the same may not hold true on social sharing sites like Digg...: the social news site Digg and the video site YouTube. Both have public APIs for accessing data...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7479-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7479_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:12:49">http://arstechnica.com/business/2010/12/old-fogies-catching-up-on-social-networking-online-video/</link><title>Old fogies catching up on social networking, online video</title><description>..."Kids" these days may still lead the pack when it comes to new online activities, but older users are catching up quickly. A new report from the Pew Internet American Life Project says that people 34 and older are more and more likely to watch online video, use online classifieds, and even use social networking siteswith the over-74 crowd making the biggest gains."Millennials"...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7479-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7479_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:13:39">http://arstechnica.com/security/2010/02/browser-history-hijack-social-networks-lost-anonymity/</link><title>Browser history hijack + social networks = lost anonymity</title><description>...Simply joining a few groups at social networking sites may reveal enough information for hackers to personally identify you, according to some recent computer science research. In a paper that will be presented at a security conference later this year, an international team of academics describes how they were able to build membership sets using information that social networking sites make avail...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7479-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7479_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:14:12">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/03/a-friendly-exchange-about-the-future-of-online-liability/</link><title>Dialogue: the future of online obscenity and social networks</title><description>...When the Communications Decency Act (CDA) was enshrined into law with the passage of the historic Telecommunications Act of 1996, it contained a number of controversial provisions that covered "obscene or indecent" online content. But at the behest of ISPs and others concerned about the potentially stifling effects of possible obscenity suits on the still-young network, the CDA also inc...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>