<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7480">phd comics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:15:08" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7480-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7480_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:15:08">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/04/the-phd-problem-what-do-you-do-with-too-many-doctorates/</link><title>The PhD problem: are we giving out too many degrees?</title><description>..., many of those PhD holders cant find a job; in Japan, academic jobs are few and far between... had hoped: only half of Japans crop of 2010 PhD recipients had jobs lined up by the time they finished.China drives a large amount of the worldwide trend, with its PhD output increasing 40 percent across...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7480-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7480_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:16:01">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/09/yes-the-phd-comics-movie-is-coming/</link><title>PHD Comics Movie is coming, providing an inside view of science</title><description>...Earlier this year, graduate students suddenly found themselves deprived of a major source of procrastination when updates of the Piled Higher and Deeper (PHD) Comics suddenly reduced to trickles. The hiatus led to a widespread speculation that Jorge Cham, the creator of the comics, fell victim to (*gasp*) procrastinitis after advocating for the habit over many years through his worldwide speech t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7480-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7480_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:16:44">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/12/exclusive-preview-retelling-supermans-origin-story-in-action-comics-no-5/</link><title>Exclusive preview: retelling Superman's origin story in Action Comics No. 5</title><description>...I have been reading comics for a couple of decades, starting with The Death of Superman. Since then.... But Action Comics No. 5, previewed exclusively on Wired.com and hitting stores Jan. 4... Comics relaunch debut. DC Comics move to reboot its entire line of books earlier this year met...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7480-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7480_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:18:07">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/06/comic-jumper-mixing-humor-with-hardcore-design/</link><title>Comic Jumper : mixing humor with hardcore design</title><description>... Pixel's Comic Jumper: The Adventures of Captain Smiley, a (generally) 2D hybrid brawler/action... of its tongue-in-cheek approach: the titular Captain Smiley's comic book hasn't been doing well... had, has been forced to jump into other comic worlds in an effort to raise enough cash to save his own ailing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7480-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7480_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:18:56">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/10/ny-comic-con-a-day-in-photos/</link><title>NY Comic Con: A day in photos</title><description>...NY Comic Con is happening in New York City this weekend, and we trekked to Javits Center to meet... now, Batman's face could be the new Dark Pancake. Cesar Torres At Comic Con, these cosplayers... friend to the end the very end. Unlocking that NY Comic Con Foursqaure badge is way more important...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7480-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7480_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:19:28">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/new-game-based-comics-announced-at-nycc-09/</link><title>New game-based comics announced at NYCC 09</title><description>...The relationship between comics and video games became a little closer this weekend, as a number... at New York Comic Con 2009. Both Marvel and DC Comics are working on bringing some major franchises back to comic book pages. Unsurprisingly, Marvel Comics is reaffirming its love affa...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7480-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7480_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:20:03">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/10/video-ny-comic-con-attendees-share-their-lovable-weirdness/</link><title>Video: NY Comic Con attendees share their lovable weirdness</title><description>...We spent a day at NY Comic Con taking pictures and showing you all the fun of the event (check it out in our photo gallery). Between movie and TV star appearances, comic artist signings, and stuff... City. But the heart of the fun is really all about the attendees. The fans make Comic Con what...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7480-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7480_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:20:57">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/11/dc-comics-digital-titles-are-finally-sold-in-your-tablet-bookstore/</link><title>DC Comics' digital titles are finally sold in your tablet bookstore</title><description>...On Wednesday, DC Comics announced digital versions of its monthly titles would be available in iPad... of digital comics since fall 2011, users had to find those titles through third-party appslike... to add to your comics to that," Kanalz said. "You're going to have to commit to what...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7480-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7480_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:21:39">http://arstechnica.com/business/2010/05/invincible-walking-dead-writer-trades-ars-comics-for-mario/</link><title>Invincible, Walking Dead writer trades us comics for Mario</title><description>...It's a hard job to launch a single successful comic book series, but right now Robert Kirkman writes two of the bestnot to mention most popularseries in comics at the moment: Walking Dead... favorite writer in comics? Probably not. But why let that stop you?He agreed on the condition that I...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7480-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7480_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:22:14">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/05/tomorrow-is-free-comic-book-day-plan-accordingly/</link><title>Tomorrow is Free Comic Book Day, so plan accordingly</title><description>...The first Saturday in May is a glorious day for comic book fans, or anyone who likes to get things for free. You find a participating comic store in your area, you walk in, and you get to grab a few comic books for free. That's it. No strings attached, other than the fact my family tends...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>