<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7481">worms nexus 7</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:22:48" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7481-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7481_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:22:49">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/08/something-is-up-with-the-2013-nexus-7s-gps/</link><title>Something is up with the 2013 Nexus 7’s GPS</title><description>...It's not uncommon for new hardware to have issues early in its run, and it looks like the 2013 Nexus 7 will be no exception. PhoneArena has spotted reports from users complaining that the GPS in the new tablet becomes non-functional after a period of sustained use, and only rebooting...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7481-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7481_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:23:21">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/07/nexus-7-tablets-begin-shipping-from-google-play/</link><title>Nexus 7 tablets begin shipping from Google Play</title><description>...If you pre-ordered one of the new Nexus 7 tablets from Google Play since they were announced... support line is saying that Nexus 7 pre-orders have begun shipping, as reported by Android Police... number.The $199 Nexus 7 is competing in the same price class as ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7481-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7481_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:24:12">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/07/nexus-7-arrives-on-virtual-shelves-a-few-days-early/</link><title>Nexus 7 arrives on virtual shelves a few days early</title><description>...Google announced the successor to its Nexus 7, also called the Nexus 7, on Wednesday..., South Korea, France, and Australia will be able to buy the new Nexus 7 in the coming weeks.The... that the original Nexus 7 of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7481-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7481_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:24:40">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/07/the-2013-nexus-7-performance-preview-a-huge-speed-upgrade-in-every-way/</link><title>The 2013 Nexus 7 performance preview: a huge speed upgrade in every way</title><description>... all cutting-edge, but the new Nexus 7 seems like it will bring a sizable performance bump for just... 7 and where it fits in compared to the smaller Nexus 4 and the larger Nexus 10.First, a refresher on the internals: the new Nexus 7 is ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7481-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7481_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:25:31">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/07/pictures-of-the-next-nexus-7-appear-ahead-of-july-24-google-event/</link><title>Pictures of the next Nexus 7 appear ahead of July 24 Google event</title><description>...An entire year has passed since the launch of the original Nexus 7. Weexpecteda successor to be announced before this year's Google I/O, and potential specifications have been floating around for longer than that. Imagine our disappointment then, when Google I/O's opening day keynote eschewed new hardware (and the Android version bump that customarily comes with new hardware) in favor o...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7481-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7481_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:26:12">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/05/ars-readers-speak-up-seven-things-you-want-to-see-in-a-new-nexus-7/</link><title>Ars readers speak up: seven things you want to see in a new Nexus 7</title><description>...Google I/O officially kicks off on Wednesday, and the current scuttlebutt is that Google will be announcing a follow-up to the Nexus 7 tablet at its day-one keynote. We still like the original Nexus 7, but last week we put together a list of improvements we wanted to see in the new version. We also asked you what you would liked to see in a new Nexus 7, and you came through with some solid sugges...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7481-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7481_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:26:53">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/06/review-the-hisense-sero-7-pro-is-a-nexus-7-clone-for-50-less/</link><title>Review: The Hisense Sero 7 Pro is a Nexus 7 clone for $50 less</title><description>...A few weeks ago we reviewed Hisenses Sero 7 Lite, a new budget Android tablet that isnt very good until you consider that it costs $99. The tablet that Hisense really wants you to see, though, is the $149 Sero 7 Pro. This tablet runs a quad-core Nvidia Tegra 3 SoC. It comes with a 1280800 7-inch screen, 1GB of RAM, and Android 4.2. If these specs sound familiar to you, its probably because theyre...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7481-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7481_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:27:42">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/05/seven-things-we-want-to-see-in-an-updated-nexus-7-at-google-io/</link><title>Seven things we want to see in an updated Nexus 7 at Google I/O</title><description>...When we reviewed Google and Asus Nexus 7 tablet last summer, we called it a fantastic $200 tablet. That assessment still holds true today, but in the year since it was introduced, the 7-to-8-inch tablet space has gotten much more crowded. New Kindle Fires, the iPad mini, and Samsungs Galaxy Note 8.0 are just a few of the high-profile devices that have risen to challenge the Nexus 7 in the last 12...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7481-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7481_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:28:25">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/07/the-2013-nexus-7-review-meet-the-new-standard-for-android-tablets/</link><title>Cheaper than most, better than all: the 2013 Nexus 7 reviewed</title><description>...Just over a year ago, Google released its first Nexus tablet. The 2012 Nexus 7 wasn't perfect... of the world, no one tablet really did well enough to merit the attention of developers or users. The Nexus 7... from Amazon and a new, smaller iPad from Apple. Since it launched, pr...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7481-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7481_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:29:23">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/04/new-nexus-7-reportedly-gets-qualcomm-chip-better-screen-and-lower-price/</link><title>New Nexus 7 reportedly gets Qualcomm chip, better screen, and lower price</title><description>...Google and Asus' Nexus 7 tablet won us over quickly upon its release last year with its size... after the original Nexus 7, and that Asus will still be the manufacturer of choice. The new tablet... Nexus 7 could have a 1080p screen, and while this is possi...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>