<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7482">popular twitter stars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:30:05" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7482-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7482_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:30:06">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/08/twitter-not-so-popular-with-the-young-people/</link><title>Twitter not so popular with the young people</title><description>...Twitter has a reputation as that "new Internet trend" that's all the rage among kids... Twitter, market research powerhouse Nielsen decided to take a look at its own data... as one might expect.According to Nielsen's data, Twitter reached 10.7 percent of all active Internet...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7482-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7482_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:30:49">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2011/03/twitter-tells-third-party-devs-to-stop-making-twitter-client-apps/</link><title>Twitter tells third-party devs to stop making Twitter client apps</title><description>...In a statement issued today by Twitter on its official developer mailing list, the company informed third-party developers that they should no longer attempt to build conventional Twitter client applications. In a move to increase the "consistency" of the user experience, Twitter wants...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7482-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7482_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:31:39">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/03/twitter-weird-a-half-dozen-oddball-twitter-experiences/</link><title>Twitter weird: a half dozen oddball Twitter experiences</title><description>...Here at Ars, we all use Twitter, and not just because it's a kind of virtual pub... can catch up with at any time.So Twitter is a lot of things, and often, it's just plain weird... to build on the service and create new ways to use it. Some of these Twitter add-ons are fabulous...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7482-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7482_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:32:18">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/game-industry-to-writers-embargos-include-twitter/</link><title>Game industry to writers: embargos include Twitter</title><description>...You can learn much about the game industryboth the industry side and the job of reporting on itfrom following the right people on Twitter. The rules for what game writers can and can't say aren't exactly clear, although at a recent press event the embargo was made explicit for those attending: you're not allowed to Twitter about what you've just seen.While it's not exactl...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7482-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7482_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:32:54">http://arstechnica.com/business/2010/04/twitter-launching-annotation-feature-streaming-api/</link><title>Twitter launching annotation feature, streaming API</title><description>...Twitter, the popular micro-messaging service, is preparing to launch several new features for end users and third-party application developers. Twitter is moving into new territory with a richer real-time streaming API and an annotation system that will make it possible for developers to piggy-back additional data on top of tweets.These new features were announced at Chirp, an official Twitter de...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7482-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7482_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:33:20">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/03/freedom-shmeedum-turkeys-government-moves-to-wipe-out-twitter/</link><title>Freedom-schmeedum: Turkey’s government moves to “wipe out” Twitter</title><description>...After declaring on Thursday that he would wipe out Twitter, Turkish Prime Minister Recep Tayyip... to YouTube and promoted widely by Twitter users.Unlike some recent Internet crackdowns, however, the Turkish Twitter blockade is easily avoided. Twitter has posted instructions for Turkish users on how...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7482-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7482_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:33:48">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/12/twitter-immediately-reverses-course-on-changes-to-block-behavior/</link><title>Twitter immediately reverses course on changes to “block” behavior</title><description>...Twitter prompted an outcry and backlash from some of its more vocal users this evening... that the changes were reversed just a few hours later following a rare late-night meeting of Twitter executives. This meeting followed several hours of complaints from Twitter users and from various...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7482-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7482_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:34:27">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/10/for-shame-trolls-defeat-scientific-american-popular-science/</link><title>For shame: Trolls defeat Scientific American , Popular Science</title><description>... about Popular Science and Scientific American, two of the oldest and most revered publications for the popularization and support of the scientific enterprise. Both publications will easily survive...: SciAmoriginally claimed via Twitter that the post was not appropriate because it was not about discovering...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7482-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7482_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:34:57">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/mature-games-dominate-most-popular-xbox-360-downloads/</link><title>"Most popular" Xbox 360 add-on content: a closer look</title><description>...One of the best features of the updated Xbox 360 user interface is the ability to browse games by popularity. Though not always a reliable indicator of "awesomeness," popularity may..., when coupledwith other popularity lists in the Marketplace, add-on popularity is aninsightful look into what...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7482-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7482_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:35:35">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/01/koo-af-yinz-regional-us-slang-thrives-on-twitter/</link><title>Koo af, yinz: regional US slang thrives on Twitter</title><description>... accents and standardized "proper" English usage; will services like Twitter, where people... University finds that, so far, regional variation is alive and well on Twitter. All yinz... of friends.Yinz, a contraction of the second-person plural "you ones," lives on Twitter...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>