<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7483">facebook paying?</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:36:27" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7483-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7483_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:36:28">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/08/meet-matt-kruse-the-man-making-facebook-better/</link><title>Meet Matt Kruse, the man making Facebook better</title><description>... am.Kruse spends those hours making Facebook better. He doesnt get paid for it, and hes not an employee... one of the most popular solutions for anyone who doesnt like Facebooks interface. Kruse says he doesnt have an exact... that boasts 1.4 million subscribers.Social Fixer uses Javacript to modify Facebooks interface...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7483-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7483_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:36:57">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/06/facebooks-app-center-aims-to-make-discovering-third-party-apps-easier/</link><title>Facebook's App Center aims to make discovering third-party apps easier</title><description>...Facebook has built a new application discovery tool to help its users find third-party mobile and Web applications that integrate with the popular social network. The Facebook App Center, which launched this evening with approximately 600 application listings, is accessible through Facebooks...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7483-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7483_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:37:53">http://arstechnica.com/security/2010/07/leaked-data-of-100m-facebook-users-came-from-public-info/</link><title>"Leaked" data of 100M Facebook users came from public info</title><description>...Much has been made of a recent Facebook "leak" which allegedly disclosed information on over 100 million Facebook users. What some reports have failed to highlight, however... that the user has allowed Facebook to make public. This includes names, profile images, and small sampling...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7483-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7483_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:38:29">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2014/02/objections-to-class-action-deal-over-facebook-sponsored-stories-flare/</link><title>Objections to class-action deal over Facebook “Sponsored Stories” flare</title><description>...A recent Facebook settlement over "Sponsored Stories," a system for placing users' photos in ads, would have paid several hundred thousand users $15 each. But now serious objections are being raised to the settlement; Public Citizen and other advocacy groups have filed an appeal asking for the settlement to be revoked, because it allows Facebook to use the images of minors without...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7483-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7483_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:39:12">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/12/facebook-connect-goes-live-to-one-and-all/</link><title>Facebook Connect goes live to one and all</title><description>...The web is now free to get even more social today with Facebooks announcement that Facebook Connect..., Facebook Connect allows users to harness their Facebook credentials and data on participating external websites, then bring those experiences back to the Facebook community, all ba...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7483-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7483_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:39:57">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/03/facebook-timeline-rolls-out-to-all-brand-pages/</link><title>Facebook timeline rolls out to all brand pages</title><description>...Facebook pushed its Timeline profile to all brand pages on Friday, a major aesthetic revamp... is a running list of your interactions with Facebook. Status updates, photos and app posts... one of Facebooks hackathon sessions and was originally dubbed Memories. Until today, activating Timeline...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7483-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7483_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:40:34">http://arstechnica.com/business/2014/01/facebooks-paper-is-facebook-without-the-facebook/</link><title>Facebook’s Paper is Facebook without the Facebook</title><description>...Facebook announced Thursday a new app that will revamp the presentation of content on the site... for some time, but its release as a new standalone app comes as a surprise. Facebook has a mixed.... The default section in the app is the users Facebook news feed, but users can pull new sections...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7483-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7483_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:40:58">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2008/10/live-search-arrives-for-facebook/</link><title>Live Search arrives for Facebook</title><description>...The announcement of the collaboration came back in July, and now Facebook has finished integrating... deal for Microsoft; Facebook is the biggest social network in the world and is quickly catching.... Microsoft then began selling ads for Facebook outside of the US and became the sites exclusive ad...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7483-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7483_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:41:36">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/08/stream-resistance-is-futile-facebook-assimilates-friendfeed/</link><title>Stream resistance is futile: Facebook assimilates FriendFeed</title><description>...Social networking giant Facebook announced on Monday that it has reached an agreement to acquire competitor FriendFeed. Facebook will reportedly assimilate FriendFeed's biological..., Facebook has conducted several redesigns that place a strong emphasis on stream-based social...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7483-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7483_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:42:07">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/05/facebook-launches-support-for-openid-logins/</link><title>Facebook lowers barrier for new users with OpenID logins</title><description>...Social networking giant Facebook has implemented support for OpenID logins. The move reflects...; party and that users will consequently be able to register for Facebook using their authentication credentials from compatible third-party services. This makes Facebook the single largest Web service...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>