<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7486">board games teenagers</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:55:28" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7486-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7486_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:55:30">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/04/one-of-a-kind-custom-tron-light-cycle-board-game-impresses/</link><title>One-of-a-kind Tron light cycle board game? Yessir</title><description>...The iconic light cycles from the Tron films aren't necessarily the first thing you'd think of when creating a new board game, but that doesn't mean it can't work. Brett King created a custom game to play with his kids and posted the results on YouTube, and we can't help but be impressed. Custom Tron board game The board itself is made from laser-etched, smoked acrylic, wi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7486-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7486_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:56:06">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/01/video-games-breathe-new-life-into-pinball/</link><title>Video games breathe new life into pinball, board games</title><description>...Video games have been slowly killing physical games like pinball and board games, but now they're starting to bring them back. Thanks to new distribution channels and control methods, these old-school games are making a comeback and reaching a brand new audience, one that is partially made up of players who have never experienced a real-world pinball machine or board game. Ars spoke with sev...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7486-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7486_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:56:27">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/12/library-holds-video-game-event-for-teens/</link><title>Library holds video game event for teens</title><description>...Libraries seem to have realized that embracing video games is a great way to reignite teenagers... in National Gaming Daywhich featured a mix of board and video gamesand a library in North Carolina... this Monday. The Loutit District Librarys first video game competition was attended...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7486-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7486_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:57:02">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/05/small-world-shows-ipad-capability-for-board-games/</link><title>Small World shows iPad capability for board games</title><description>... controls allow for many gameplay options, including board games. We were sent a review code for Small... well.Small World is a French board game that sees different races spreading across a fantasy land...; the physical copy of the board game has been written ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7486-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7486_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:57:38">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/02/forgotten-lore-ars-reviews-our-newest-board-game-obsession-crows/</link><title>Forgotten lore: Ars reviews newest board game obsession, Crows</title><description>...Crows is a brand new tile-based board game from Tyler Sigman, the man who brought the excellent PlayStation Network game Hoard to life. Sigman is never going to get rich designing games like these, but I'll be damned if he's not making our lives just a little bit more fun. That's definitely worth a tip of the hat.The concept behind Crows is simple, and the game is easy to learn. Yo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7486-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7486_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:58:22">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/05/catan-junior-brings-serious-board-game-strategy-to-tots/</link><title>Catan Junior brings serious board game strategy to tots</title><description>...Catan JuniorBoardgameRecommended age: 6 - 10 yearsPrice: $26.99Buy it from AmazonEuropean-style board games have been quickly surging in American popularity and availability for about three or four years now. I remember being tickled to find Carcassonne at a Barnes and Noble for the first time, though it was strange to see the board games placed in a completely different section of the store from...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7486-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7486_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:59:19">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/02/villagers-chambers-danger-the-designer-of-latest-dd-board-game-speaks/</link><title>Villagers, chambers, traps: DandD board game designer explains changes</title><description>...Castle Ravenloft was a fun way to spend an hour or so playing an entire Dungeons and Dragons adventure, but the board game was definitely heavy on the combat, and it often felt a little dry unless you began to adjust the rules. The latest game in the series, Wrath of Ashardalon, adds a number of new mechanics and concepts to the 4th Edition board game, and the changes are for the better.We had th...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7486-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7486_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 12:59:59">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/09/castle-ravenloft-the-fourth-edition-horror-dd-board-game-of-doom/</link><title>Castle Ravenloft: the 4th Edition DandD horror board game of DOOM!</title><description>...When I went to buy Castle Ravenloft at the local hobbyshop, they told me they didn't take American Express. "Oh, c'mon man, this is for work!" I told him, going back to my wallet for my personal debit card. "I have to bring this game to the Internet!" "Like in Tron?" he asked. Sometimes my job provides moments of great fun, and that was certainly one of the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7486-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7486_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:00:36">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/07/conquest-of-nerath-takes-dd-board-gaming-to-an-epic-scale/</link><title>Conquest of Nerath takes DandD board gaming to an epic scale</title><description>...We've been enjoying the past few Dungeons and Dragons board games, as they provide an easy way...-out game board, dice, 110 cards, and 252 plastic playing pieces representing champions and the armies... game in the series isConquest of Nerath, which steps away from the line of c...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7486-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7486_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:01:16">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/01/tmnt-returns-with-new-wii-game-from-smash-bros-creators/</link><title>TMNT returns with new Wii game from Smash Bros. creators</title><description>...There are few mainstream franchises that have been treated as well in the video game world as Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles. The original beat-'em-up games based on the hit TV and film series... In Time. And while the recently released games in the series haven't fared well, Ubisoft is hopeful...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>