<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7487">april fools day ideas</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:01:47" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7487-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7487_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:01:48">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/04/ea-apologizes-for-april-fools-day-tweet-bashing-the-wii-u/</link><title>EA apologizes for April Fools’ Day tweet bashing the Wii U</title><description>... seems to have forgotten that rule when it used April Fools' Day as an excuse to tweet a few jokes... apologies to partners @NintendoAmerica fan @FrostbiteEngines poor attempt at April Fools not condoned by EA... the day reportedly joked that the engine would power Half-Life 3 a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7487-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7487_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:02:28">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/04/april-fools-day-comes-to-copyright-law/</link><title>April Fools' Day comes to... copyright law?</title><description>... intimate theaters." Yes, it's a joke. Copyright law might seem an unlikely subject for an April Fools' Day joke, but Public Knowledge has found a way. The prank's comedic value...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7487-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7487_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:03:01">http://arstechnica.com/security/2009/03/confickerc-primed-for-april-fools-activation/</link><title>Conficker.C primed for April Fool's activation</title><description>...We've been tracking the Conficker worm since it launched itself into the wild last November; despite the best efforts of security officials worldwide, the worm still hasn't been completely crushed. The original flavor and its nastier follow-up (Conficker.A and Conficker.B) have been locked down, but the worm's creators have a third version (Conficker.C, naturally) prepared to hit t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7487-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7487_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:03:27">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/03/google-gets-the-jump-on-april-fools-with-new-pokemon-master-job-listing/</link><title>Google gets the jump on April Fools with new “Pokémon Master” job listing</title><description>... to be Google's April Fools Day stunt for this year, the latest in a list of elaborate pranks that includes a toilet-based ISP and a dating site. Unlike those pranks, though, this year's April Fools...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7487-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7487_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:04:06">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/02/reports-microsoft-planning-to-unveil-xbox-successor-at-april-event/</link><title>Reports: Microsoft planning to unveil Xbox successor at April event</title><description>..., developer-centric details before a fuller April event.One thing seems clear: every day people spend... is planning a "one-off media event" to show off its new system in early April, based on information..., saying it has "also received word of the April event," and National Alliance S...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7487-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7487_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:04:46">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/04/hands-on-with-biowares-garrus-vakarian-body-pillow-very-very-hands-on/</link><title>Hands-on with Bioware’s Garrus Vakarian body pillow—very, very hands-on</title><description>...Specs at a glance: Garrus Vakarian Body PillowDimensions6'4", dreamy, lotsa scars, heavily armedNo, the PILLOW's dimensionsOh. Uh, about 6' tall and rectangularyou know, pillow-shaped.MaterialSome kind of cotton blend? Who even knows.Texture accuracyDisappointingly pillow-like and not at all TurianesqueSnuggleability8.66 out of 10Calibrations performedAll of themWill Garrus re...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7487-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7487_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:05:11">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/03/fasting-from-technology-saturday-is-no-tech-day/</link><title>Fasting from technology: Saturday is No Tech Day</title><description>...Saturday, March 27th, is "No Tech Day." Sponsored by UK charity Practical Action, No Tech Day is a time to set aside the luxury gadgets for 24 hours "to raise awareness of how much... without your computer and mobile phone for a day is supposed to ease stress but also give "a taste...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7487-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7487_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:05:51">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/06/fathers-day-gift-guide-gaming/</link><title>Ars Father's Day Gift Guide: Gamer Dad Edition</title><description>...Back in the 8-bit console era, when many of us Ars staffers were young whipper-snappers whose idea... an Xbox Live account is the new golf club membership.The Ars Father's Day Gift Guide: Gamer Dad... hardware they want for Father's Day, and if you're not a gamer yourself then it's tough...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7487-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7487_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:06:38">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2009/06/fathers-day-gift-guide-hacker/</link><title>Ars Father's Day Gift Guide: Hacker Dad Edition</title><description>... for an optimal father's day trip. Product: TuxDroid Manufacturer: Kysoh Price: $149 (Buy)The TuxDroid... year, meaning that it can save you from agonizing over gift ideas next year. Product: 101 piece...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7487-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7487_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:07:12">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/06/fathers-day-gift-guide-dead-tree/</link><title>Ars Father's Day Gift Guide: Dead-tree-loving Dad Edition</title><description>...;s Day this time around? Look no further than this list of a few of our own favorite (paper-based... scientific ideas we've developed, but he describes how they developed, and keeps you awake while doing... be fooled by the seemingly pedestrian nature of this book; after all, beans are the magical fruit. Ratio...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>