<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7488">DIY shops london open sunday</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:07:30" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7488-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7488_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:07:31">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/09/sound-taxi-tours-london-translating-city-noise-into-live-music/</link><title>Sound Taxi tours London translating city noise into live music</title><description>... discussing their Savile Row suits (though one mouth did momentarily drop open), Old Bond Street shop... of London on the 20th and 21st of September 2012. The hubbub of the citytinkering bikes, hissing buses and booming sirenshave been transformed into melodic tracks by a suped-up London cab that translates...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7488-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7488_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:08:08">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/03/warioware-diy-making-games-an-inch-wide-a-mile-deep/</link><title>WarioWare D.I.Y. : making games an inch wide, a mile deep</title><description>... with Wario Ware D.I.Y., the latest game in the now venerable series of microgames. Each release.... The games can be played on the Wii with the optional WarioWare D.I.Y. Showcase for that system... title, this could be as close as many of us get. WarioWare D.I.Y. comes to the Nintendo DS...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7488-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7488_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:08:39">http://arstechnica.com/business/2013/02/london-real-estate-anticipates-us-tech-expansion-into-europe/</link><title>London real estate anticipates US tech expansion into Europe</title><description>... American grocery chain opened its first European store in London in 2007, with its second store opening...LONDON, ENGLANDIn recent decades, the Kings Cross neighborhood in central London was known... days, the former railyard sitejust steps from one of Londons...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7488-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7488_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:09:20">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/01/trailblazing-diy-pinball-game-snags-pioneer-award-for-bill-budge/</link><title>Trailblazing DIY pinball game snags Pioneer Award for Bill Budge</title><description>... game designs was the inspiration for a host of hit DIY games to come, from SimCity...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7488-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7488_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:09:46">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/03/demographics-cat-map-plots-locations-names-and-colors-of-london-felines/</link><title>DeMOGraphics: Cat Map plots locations, names, and colors of London felines</title><description>...TheZoological Society of London(ZSL) has launched an initiative to collect data about the cats of London into a map. It's called, perhaps unsurprisingly, Cat Map.Cat Map invites mog owners... awareness about the conservation of tigers and the launch of London Zoo's Tiger Territory...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7488-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7488_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:10:35">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/09/first-nyclondon-cable-in-a-decade-promises-sub-60ms-latency/</link><title>First NYC/London cable in a decade promises sub-60ms latency</title><description>...-latency connection between New York and London. Hibernia Atlantic today announced plans to build its new "Project Express," which claims to bring sub-60ms latency to the crucial New York/London... Express will offer the lowest latency from New York to London and provide demanding customers the speed...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7488-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7488_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:11:19">http://arstechnica.com/staff/2012/07/beyond-first-second-or-third-london-2012-by-the-numbers-so-far/</link><title>Beyond first, second, or third: London 2012 by the numbers (so far)</title><description>... are a few quick numbers to frame the first weekend and prep you for the rest of London 2012:4xThat's how much stronger the network capacity in London is compared to Beijing when it hosted the '08 games. Apparently, the event could use a bit more.Fans attending the Olympics on Sunday...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7488-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7488_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:12:07">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/02/diy-book-scanning-is-easier-than-you-think/</link><title>How we built a DIY book scanner with speeds of 150 pages per minute</title><description>...Bookshelves today are simply not as appealing as they used to be, and there's no shortage of people looking to digitize their own book collections. Fortunately, we now have easy and relatively inexpensive ways to digitize those books. You don't have to slave away at your copier or scanner, eitherwere talking about building a book scanner of your very own.We're not talking about the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7488-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7488_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:12:48">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/12/amazon-mobile-for-the-iphone-shopsand-remembers/</link><title>Amazon Mobile for the iPhone shops?and remembers</title><description>... is fastmaybe even faster than the desktop version of amazon.com. If you have a lot of online holiday shopping...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7488-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7488_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:13:18">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/07/londons-police-is-spending-11-per-minute-to-stake-out-julian-assange/</link><title>London’s police spend over $16,000 per day to stake out Julian Assange</title><description>...According to a new letter from the Metropolitan Police, London is spending an average of 10,982..., but the WikiLeaks founder did not respond to our queries.The letter was sent by the Met to London assembly member... of that represented increased overtime payments.The Met seems to dismiss Jones' concerns that London...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>