<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7489">make skull mask</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:14:04" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7489-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7489_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:14:05">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/06/skulls-of-the-shogun-backs-off-windows-8-exclusivity-on-pcs/</link><title>Skulls of the Shogun backs off Windows 8 exclusivity on PCs</title><description>...Until now, if you wanted to play 17-bit Studios' excellent turn-based strategy title Skulls of the Shogun on PC, you had to play onWindows 8. This put it in a rather exclusive set of only a few dozen games that were part of the confusing "Xbox on Windows 8" brandingand also closed...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7489-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7489_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:14:42">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/06/microsofts-age-of-empires-coming-to-non-windows-phones/</link><title>Microsoft’s Age of Empires coming to non-Windows phones</title><description>... would make that platform choice, considering that Windows Phone has less than 2 percent... make that decision with one of its biggest exclusive properties.Microsoft said the Age of Empires... announced plans to release a version of Skulls of the Shogun that is free of previous Windows 8...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7489-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7489_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:15:26">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/08/are-two-heads-better-than-one-sometimes/</link><title>Are two heads better than one? Sometimes...</title><description>...Generally, we assume that making decisions as a group is beneficial because groups can come together to make better choices than their members would alone. Is this true, or is group decision-making... trick and secretly introduced "noise" into one of the partner's visual fields, making...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7489-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7489_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:15:53">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/08/singstar-queen-about-what-youd-expect-epic-difficult/</link><title>SingStar Queen about what you'd expect: epic, difficult</title><description>... up the Beatles, some argue for the The Who, and certain misguided souls may even make a case for U2... a challenging experience even on the lower difficulty levels.That doesn't make this a bad game, just..., but after one fun night of making fun of how badly everyone sings, it's hard to imagine...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7489-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7489_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:16:20">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/01/kingdom-of-the-skulls-review-shogun-control/</link><title>Skulls of the Shogun : Turn-based strategy finds fresh blood in... cannibalism?</title><description>...Ahead, across the river, lies my foe's most precious possession: a stone shrine. The enemy's healer monk, summoned from that very shrine, has grown far too powerful during battle. At this point, my only hope for victory is to run my fastest horseback rider across a field of dead bodies to break that shrine down and claim the monk as my own.But not yet. I've ordered the horseman to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7489-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7489_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:16:59">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/12/p2p-first-seeders-pirates-or-masked-philanthropists/</link><title>P2P first seeders: pirates or "masked philanthropists"?</title><description>...Do some P2P file sharers see themselves as the Robin Hoods of the digital agetaking from the greedy content companies and giving to the global have-nots? Amidst all the angst over illegal Internet file sharing and what to do about it, there's a related debate raging over two questionswhy do people share files and what do they think about the ethics of the practice?Obviously lots of BitTorren...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7489-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7489_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:17:33">http://arstechnica.com/security/2014/02/meet-mask-possibly-the-most-sophisticated-malware-campaign-ever-seen/</link><title>Meet Mask, possibly the most sophisticated malware campaign ever seen</title><description>... firms, activists, energy companies, and companies in other industries. The sophistication of Mask makes it likely that the campaign is the work of attackers sponsored by a well-resourced nation-state... of sophisticated, we put Careto above Duqu, Gauss, RedOctober, or Icefog, making...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7489-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7489_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:18:12">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2009/01/audio-bone-uses-your-skull-for-music/</link><title>Audio Bone uses your skull for music</title><description>... down to under $100, this would make a great buy for anyone who wants music while still being able...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7489-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7489_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:18:39">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/02/cleaning-up-dirty-coal-could-lead-to-temperature-spike-in-a-few-decades/</link><title>Climate commitment: greenhouse warming masked by past pollution</title><description>... of the previous studies. Particulate pollutants are known to mask the greenhouse effect and can keep the global... activities. The implication of the particulate pollutants short residence time is that the masking...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7489-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7489_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:19:11">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/06/revenge-of-the-fallen-is-messy-unfunny-and-way-too-long/</link><title>Revenge of the Fallen is messy, unfunny, and way too long</title><description>...To lend some context to this review, I was a big fan of the first Transformers film. Sure, it was loud and the camera shook too much, but it was a great summer film and a solid take on the idea that alien robots wanted nothing more than to turn into Earth vehicles and fight each other. Peter Cullen came back to voice Optimus Prime, and just when the human characters became intolerable, there was...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>