<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7490">convert wav mp3</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:19:38" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7490-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7490_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:19:39">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2008/12/converter-coupon-funds-will-run-out-in-january/</link><title>Converter coupon funds will run out in January</title><description>.... The Digital converter coupon program has been around for much of the year to provide those needing a converter with $40 of the purchase price and according to Reuters; those funds are estimated to run out in early January. That means that any consumers who need a converter and have yet to apply...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7490-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7490_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:20:09">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/02/vmware-vcenter-converter-version-40-released/</link><title>VMware vCenter Converter version 4.0 released</title><description>... in order to make things as easy as possible. For instance, VMware's vCenter Converter enables... even more when combined with something like Converter. As the name suggests, VMware Converter creates VMware virtual machines from a wide range of sources, including physical machines. Converter 4.0 now...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7490-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7490_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:20:50">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/02/retailers-may-run-out-of-dtv-converter-boxes-soon/</link><title>Retailers may run out of DTV converter boxes soon</title><description>...-to-digital converter boxes around, roughly, this month."The worst case scenario... this latest cliffhanger? Most converter box manufacturers, bless their souls, actually believed...; Petricone concludes, "we believe that new converter boxes will arrive on store shelves in mid...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7490-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7490_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:21:29">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/09/psp-go-cable-converter-substitutes-form-for-function/</link><title>PSP Go cable converter substitutes form for function</title><description>... you purchase the Converter Cable Adapter.The awkward looking add-on makes the PSP Go compatible... receiver for the PSP Go, which will launch the same day as the cable converter, for 4980 yen (or, around US...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7490-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7490_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:21:58">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/04/review-convert-pbf-vs-convertbot-for-iphone/</link><title>Review: Convert (PBF) vs. ConvertBot for iPhone</title><description>...To say unit converters are the new tip calculators of the App Store wouldn't be that far... of them allso we decided to pit two of the newer entries against one another: Convert fromPolar Bear... the illusion that you are interacting with a robot. Convert, while attractive, does suffer from quite...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7490-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7490_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:22:49">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/12/review-dells-acrobatic-xps-12-is-the-windows-8-convertible-to-beat/</link><title>Review: Dell’s acrobatic XPS 12 is the Windows 8 convertible to beat</title><description>...For better or worse, Windows 8 has prompted some of the most adventuresome PC designs we've seen in years. Many of these are trying to capitalize on both of the new operating systems facesthe new touch-oriented Start screen and its apps on one, and the classic desktop environment on the other.Most of these computers are either good laptops but questionable tablets (the Lenovo IdeaPad Yoga 13...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7490-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7490_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:23:31">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/06/samsung-unveils-new-win8android-ativ-q-convertible-tablet-with-3200x1800-screen/</link><title>Samsung unveils new Win8+Android Ativ Q convertible tablet with 3200×1800 screen</title><description>...In addition to unveiling its new EVIL (Electronic Viewfinder with Interchangeable Lens) camera, the Galaxy NX, Samsung used its press event in London this afternoon to show two new Windows 8 Ativ mobile devices: the 13.3-inch convertible Ativ Q and the smaller 10.1-inch Ativ Tab 3.Enlarge The Ativ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7490-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7490_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:24:11">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/09/in-the-best-pcs-of-this-years-ifa-the-resolution-wars-are-in-full-swing/</link><title>In the best PCs of this year’s IFA, the resolution wars are in full swing</title><description>...-end convertible or Ultrabook, these are the cream of the crop (and the ones that show the general... convertible laptop designs on the market. LenovoLenovo is one of the only PC makers whose share... all the way back to convert the laptop into tablet mode, but it's also rigid enough to be used...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7490-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7490_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:24:40">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/10/poll-technica-will-you-buy-new-touch-hardware-for-windows-8/</link><title>Poll Technica: Will you buy new touch hardware for Windows 8?</title><description>... for a "standalone tablet," one without a keyboard dock. Finally, a "convertible...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7490-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7490_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:25:17">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/09/myspace-music-extends-right-hand-of-fellowship-to-big-four-middle-finger-to-indies/</link><title>MySpace Music extends right hand of fellowship to Big Four, middle finger to indies</title><description>... out to music, but it has also partnered with Amazon to incorporate an MP3 store for purchasing tracks. Each song can be purchased as a DRM-free MP3 download, and Amazons optional PC and Mac-compatible...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>