<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7492">oldest jokes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:31:39" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7492-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7492_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:31:40">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2014/04/ea-apologizes-for-april-fools-day-tweet-bashing-the-wii-u/</link><title>EA apologizes for April Fools’ Day tweet bashing the Wii U</title><description>...One of the first rules of good humor is that you should always punch up, not down. Someone at EA seems to have forgotten that rule when it used April Fools' Day as an excuse to tweet a few jokes at the expense of the struggling Wii U.Yesterday, the official Twitter account for EA's Frostbite Enginewhich powers everything from Battlefield and Need for Speed to Plants vs. Zombies: Garden...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7492-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7492_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:32:05">http://arstechnica.com/science/2010/10/the-oldest-thing-weve-ever-seen/</link><title>The oldest thing we've ever seen</title><description>... and oldest galaxies known to exist. Buried within a similar image was a speck known as UDFy-38135539... of the galaxy's immense agewas indeed correctUDFy-38135539 is officially the oldest object ever seen.Not only is UDFy-38135539 the oldest object known, it comes from a critical time...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7492-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7492_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:32:22">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/02/the-oldest-piece-of-the-earth-examined-atom-by-atom/</link><title>The oldest piece of the Earth, examined atom-by-atom</title><description>... look at the very oldest minerals we've found on Earth. The results lay to rest worries... which they formed.But the oldest zircons aren't found in an igneous rock. As the mineral most resistant.... That means the age of the oldest mineral grain is confirmed, and this zircon can keep its crown.If you know...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7492-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7492_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:33:18">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/07/did-you-hear-the-joke-about-the-comedian-and-copyright-law/</link><title>Did you hear the joke about the comedian and copyright law?</title><description>.... But comedians don't. So why hasn't the joke well gone dry?That's the question asked... always better IP rights.For comedians, ripping off a joke is a major sin, but such cases almost... some different details are free to do so.This hasn't led to a dearth of jokes. Instead...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7492-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7492_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:34:11">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/04/dihydrogen-monoxide-joke-gets-djs-suspended/</link><title>“Dihydrogen monoxide” joke gets DJs suspended</title><description>...There's an old joke that plays on the public's scientific illiteracy. It goes like... until you spell out the formula, which is H2O. Or plain water. The joke has been around for long... about other hazardous chemicals.That doesn't mean, however, that everybody's in on the joke...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7492-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7492_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:34:54">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/07/uk-high-court-overturns-conviction-for-twitter-joke/</link><title>UK High Court overturns conviction for Twitter joke</title><description>...Paul Chambers, the man who was found guilty of sending a menacing tweet in 2010, has won his High Court appeal against conviction, and has been acquitted of the crime.Back In January 2010, Chambers joked that he would blow up Robin Hood Airport in South Yorkshire airport if it was not reopened...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7492-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7492_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:35:28">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/06/pixeljunk-lifelike-demo-an-elaborate-joke-on-the-gaming-press/</link><title>Pixeljunk Lifelike demo: an elaborate joke on the gaming press?</title><description>.... It was that moment where I became convinced that Sony was pulling an elaborate joke on the press, trying...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7492-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7492_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:38:14">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/03/hubble-telescope-dates-oldest-star-at-14-5-billion-years-old/</link><title>Hubble telescope dates oldest star at 14.5 billion years old</title><description>...The Hubble space telescope has enabled astronomers to identify the oldest known star whose age we can reliably estimate.With a birthdate around 14.5 billion years ago and a margin for error of 0.8... has been given the slightly more memory-friendly name "the Methuselah star", a reference to the oldest...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7492-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7492_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:39:38">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/01/your-ipad-is-an-arcade-cabinet-the-journey-from-joke-to-product/</link><title>Your iPad is an arcade cabinet: the journey from joke to product</title><description>..., so they know there is the potential there." The last product to go from joke to reality was a sleeping bag...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7492-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7492_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:41:09">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/05/rock-of-ages-40000-year-old-musical-instruments-the-worlds-oldest/</link><title>Rock of ages: 40,000 year-old musical instruments the world's oldest</title><description>...Oxford University in the UK has announced that researchers from that school and Germany's University of Tbingen have determined the age on the world's oldest musical instruments: a collection of flutes, made of mammoth ivory and bird bones. Other bones found at the same level...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>