<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7493">islam discussions social media</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:43:19" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7493-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7493_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:43:20">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/05/new-york-city-imposes-new-social-media-rules-for-teachers/</link><title>New York City imposes new social media rules for teachers</title><description>... for the use of social media, underscoring the importance for teachers and staff to keep a clear distinction... practices."Social media practices across educational institutions have been a mixed bag... social media policies." They added that "Sc...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7493-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7493_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:45:38">http://arstechnica.com/business/2010/03/five-insights-into-the-behaviors-of-social-media-users/</link><title>Five insights into the behaviors of social media users</title><description>...We do a decent amount of social media coverage here at Ars, but not everything that happens with Facebook, Twitter, and the like is worth its own story. Sometimes, though, we happen across things that make us say "huh, that's interesting." It turns out there are a lot of things we thought we knew about social media users, but not all of them are true. Here are a few tidbits we gath...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7493-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7493_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:48:12">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/03/us-militarys-social-media-policy-gets-a-makeover/</link><title>US military surrenders to social media, changes policy</title><description>...Members of the US Military will now have limited access to certain social media sites thanks to a new policy (PDF) from the Department of Defense. The DoD finally released its updated policy late last week, which will also apply to parts of the military that have banned social media use from their own networks. Commanders will still have the ability to cut down on the use of Twitter or Facebook i...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7493-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7493_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:50:07">http://arstechnica.com/ars-podcast/2013/04/ars-technicast-ep-25-would-you-like-some-social-media-with-your-news/</link><title>Ars Technicast Ep. 25: Would you like some social media with your news?</title><description>...These days, when a big story breaks, one of the first places that people go to for information is social media, as was the case in the recent attacks in Boston. The hack of the Associated Press' Twitter accountand the drop in the financial markets afterward also reflects how much the public at large has come to rely on social media for news delivery.In turn, public reaction on social media h...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7493-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7493_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:51:30">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2008/10/clips-1-1-brings-social-media-previews-abbreviations/</link><title>Clips 1.1 brings social media previews, abbreviations</title><description>...We went hands-on with Conceited Softwares Clips 1.0, a high-powered clipboard utility from the makers of Linkinus, and found it to be pretty impressive but a little buggy (as 1.0 so often are these days). Fortunately, a new 1.1 update brings some unique new social media integration, TextExpander-like abbreviations for snippets you want to reuse on a regular basis, as well as a good handful of oth...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7493-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7493_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:52:31">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/12/new-social-media-tools-same-old-lesson-moderation/</link><title>New social media tools, same old lesson: moderation</title><description>...We can tweet our rants in 140 SMS-friendly characters on Twitter, make some friends while posting our resume to LinkedIn, and stay on top of every last byte of activity those friends publicize on Friendfeed and Facebook. As with all uncharted territories, these and other social media (a.k.a., web 2.0) services have attracted enthusiastic users, service evangelists, and dismissive critics. Some sa...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7493-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7493_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:55:05">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/11/15-year-old-offender-cant-lose-right-to-use-social-media-court-rules/</link><title>15-year-old offender can't lose right to use social media, court rules</title><description>...A teenager who was put on probation for molesting a 2-year-old, and restraining a 13-year-old, still can't have his rights to use social media taken away, a California Appeals court ruled.The... to modify the terms of probation, especially regarding use of social media and the blanket computer...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7493-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7493_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:57:16">http://arstechnica.com/business/2009/10/sports-leagues-largely-striking-out-with-social-media/</link><title>Tweeting from the field: Sports meet social media</title><description>...Social media, for all its downfalls, has proven to be a powerful tool for organizations to interact directly with customers and fans. This is especially true for athletes, musicians, and other celebritiespeople love communicating directly with their favorite icons via Twitter and Facebook. The celebrities seem to enjoy it, too. Just look at the camaraderie that THE_REAL_SHAQ (Shaquille O'Nea...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7493-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7493_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:58:14">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/04/chinas-deletes-accounts-on-twitter-like-service-as-part-of-social-media-crackdown/</link><title>China deletes accounts on Twitter-like service as part of social media crackdown</title><description>...Just two days after President Obama and the United States government hit Syria and Iran with new sanctions "to hold accountable those who assist in or enable such [human rights] abuses through the use of information and communications technology," China has now stepped up its online crackdown in the wake of a political scandal.China has been embroiled in a massive political scandal invo...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7493-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7493_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:00:28">http://arstechnica.com/business/2011/01/republicans-have-caught-up-to-democrats-in-social-media-use/</link><title>Dose of hot Tea catches Republicans up to Democrats in social media use</title><description>...Social media is becoming an increasingly important part of US elections, but the group... social media in 2010, and Republican supporters of the Tea Party helped to lead the way with their heavy online engagement.Democrats dominated social media during the 2008...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>