<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7494">cartoons festival</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:02:31" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7494-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7494_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:02:32">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/04/weekend-arts-cartoon-college/</link><title>Weekend Ar(t)s: Cartoon College may be the Indie Game of comics</title><description>... at the only logical institution of higher learning: The Center for Cartoon Studies.No joke, that path... now.A better comparison: Cartoon College feels reminiscent of Indie Game: The Movie. Both productions... Game had Jonathan Blow as a headliner and followed the developments of Fez and Super Meat Boy. Cartoon...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7494-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7494_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:04:41">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/05/science-festival-alliance-helps-connect-scientists-and-the-public/</link><title>Science Festival Alliance helps connect scientists and the public</title><description>...Since our coverage of the San Diego science festival in 2009, science festivals have built momentum... its first festival this month, and San Francisco will join it later in the year. A network run by the Science Festival Alliance is helping cities plan and organize events to connect scientists with the pu...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7494-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7494_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:05:54">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/01/ne-fusionfall-review/</link><title>Review: Cartoon Network Universe: FusionFall</title><description>...Cartoon Networks new MMO, FusionFall, faces the daunting task of providing a quality gameplay... combat/leveling, as well as a story that will most likely appeal to the vast majority of Cartoon Cartoons fans, though, the game is actually surprisingly fun. As embarrassing as it is to admit, Ive...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7494-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7494_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:08:20">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/07/3-million-for-a-national-science-festival-network/</link><title>NSF gives $3 Million for a National Science Festival Network</title><description>...The National Science Foundation (NSF) recently awarded UC San Diego and its partners, the MIT Museum, the Franklin Institute (Philadelphia) and UC San Francisco, $3 million to fund science outreach programs. These include establishing a National Science Festival Network, hosting science enrichment activities, and funding the 2010 San Diego Science Festival.Back in April, we reported the success o...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7494-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7494_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:10:32">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/10/infamous-festival-of-blood/</link><title>When an electric superhero goes vampire: Infamous: Festival of Blood for PS3</title><description>...: Festival of Blood applies this same concept to games. It's a somewhat goofy, somewhat dark $10... a decent-size chunk of the city, which has been overtaken by a strange Halloween-meets-Mardi Gras festival that makes it easy for a guy with blood all over his face and shirt to blend in. Infamous: Festival...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7494-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7494_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:12:18">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/06/world-science-festival-year-two-parallel-universes-and-more/</link><title>World Science Festival year two: parallel universes and more</title><description>...Last year, New York City hosted the first World Science Festival, a series of programs... philosophy and ethics. The festival was intended to be an annual event and, true to its promises..., and other festivals in other countries do. They say that this year's theme...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7494-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7494_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:12:57">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2009/01/apple-cancels-insomnia-film-festival-lets-students-sleep-in/</link><title>Apple cancels Insomnia Film Festival, lets students sleep in</title><description>...For the last few years, Apple has run an "Insomnia" film festival where students... this year's festival.As pointed out byTUAW, Apple postponed the 2008 Insomnia Film Festival...;unable to reschedule the festival as hoped." A visit to the Apple's Insomnia page confirms...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7494-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7494_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:14:16">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/11/ars-and-the-world-science-festival-want-our-readers-to-explore-the-fabric-of-the-universe/</link><title>World Science Festival wants Ars readers to explore the Fabric of the Universe</title><description>...Brian Greene is a theoretical physicist and co-founder of the World Science Festival. In his spare... would like you to take part. The World Science Festival has set aside two prizes for Ars readers....) The World Science Festival staff will collect all the questions submitted by Ars readers and pick...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7494-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7494_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:15:32">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/04/gallery-apple-pop-up-museum-and-vintage-computer-festival-southwest/</link><title>Gallery: Apple Pop-Up museum and Vintage Computer Festival Southeast</title><description>...Were you in Atlanta last weekend to visit the Apple Pop-Up Museum as part of the Vintage Computer Festival Southeast (VCFSE)? Some Ars readers were there, and we now have some photos from them... before its opening to the public. "The festival was a huge success, and my group is intending...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7494-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7494_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:17:14">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/12/festive-littlebigplanet-content-coming-this-week/</link><title>Festive LittleBigPlanet content coming this week</title><description>... pack aptly titled The Festive Pack. The pack includes the following: Two new Costumes: Christmas Tree... texture). Two new Objects: A Festive Sleigh and holiday themed light. Six new Decorations: A Festive...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>