<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7496">why IEEE member</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:40:00" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7496-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7496_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:40:02">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2008/12/standards-group-ieee-fights-trolls-with-new-patent-pools/</link><title>Standards group IEEE fights trolls with new patent pools</title><description>... of Electrical and Electronics Engineers, better known as the IEEE. The nonprofit organization helps set.... To help prevent this from occurring, the IEEE is teaming up with a licensing company owned by Dolby Labs... its standards. The deal, announced this morning, partners the IEEE with Via Licensing, a wholly...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7496-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7496_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:43:19">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/05/house-members-hear-why-itu-cant-be-trusted-with-internet-regulation/</link><title>House members hear why ITU can't be trusted with Internet regulation</title><description>...On Thursday morning, Vint Cerf, the most famous member of the fathers of the Internet club (whose secret greeting is the TCP 3-Way handshake)testified before the House of Representatives Energy... title: WCIT-12), where all 193 member nations are set to convene.Many larger nations, including China...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7496-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7496_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:44:50">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/09/goodbye-drm-hello-stealable-digital-personal-property/</link><title>Goodbye, DRM; hello "stealable" Digital Personal Property</title><description>...Consumers hate DRMall that "phoning home," the outside control over one's behavior, the fact that you can't resell encrypted digital media, the worries about activation servers dying. But what if digital rights management could be turned into "consumer rights management" and people could actually own and fully control the digital content they purchase? That's th...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7496-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7496_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:45:27">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/06/ieee-working-group-considers-kinder-gentler-drm/</link><title>IEEE working group considers kinder, gentler DRM</title><description>... though sharing a physical item like a CD remains trivial. A new IEEE working group has an ambitious... else is deprived of their use) when copying is the basic activity of digital devices. But the IEEE... behind the idea, which we profiled a year ago when the IEEE first consented to study the idea. A few...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7496-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7496_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:48:10">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2011/07/new-wireless-specs-for-white-space-up-to-22mbps-over-12000-square-miles/</link><title>New white space standard: up to 22Mbps over 12,000 square miles</title><description>...The new IEEE 802.22 standard has been published and will finally allow manufacturers to start producing standardized devices that will use the white space vacated by analog TVs over two years ago..., so a single device may provide an incredibly large coverage area. According to the new IEEE standard...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7496-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7496_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:51:13">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2010/09/netgear-offers-500mbps-powerline-networking-via-next-gen-standard/</link><title>Netgear offers 500Mbps powerline networking via next-gen standard</title><description>...Even as the IEEE P1901 working group was set to meet this week to recommend its draftstandard... landlord.While the IEEE P1901 standard promises speeds up to 1Gbps, no powerline adapters come close to the top... to Netgear. The P1901 WG expects its standard to be submitted the IEEE for adoption as an official...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7496-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7496_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:54:18">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/10/researchers-see-through-walls-with-wireless-mesh-gear/</link><title>Researchers see through walls with wireless mesh</title><description>... that smart devices and remote controls that use the short-range IEEE 802.15.4 protocol will find a place... otherwise see into. IEEE 802.15.4 is a short-range wireless standard that allows simple, low bandwidth... the work is the assumption that transmissions between any two IEEE 802.15.4 devices travel within...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7496-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7496_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:56:32">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/12/federal-agency-wants-black-boxes-in-every-car-by-september-2014/</link><title>Federal agency wants black boxes in every new car by September 2014</title><description>... at the Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers (IEEE) that has been pushing for an EDR..., Inc. in Southern Pines, NC, and one of the co-authors of that public draft IEEE standard (known... in November 2012.In anticipation of the IEEE standard becoming more widespread, Kowalick has already released...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7496-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7496_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:00:27">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/11/nand-flash-gets-baked-lives-longer/</link><title>NAND flash gets baked, lives longer</title><description>...An article has been published in the December 2012 edition of IEEE Spectrum that highlights an interesting and potentially useful discovery by ROM manufacturer Macronix. Researchers...;s used. The IEEE article notes that the 800C hot spot is "restricted to the area near the [floating...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7496-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7496_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:02:52">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/02/the-bigger-the-group-the-more-unique-the-members/</link><title>For animals, the bigger the group, the more distinct its members</title><description>... be more obvious to predators, and members have to compete for food, mates, and territories. In species where recognizing specific individuals is important, its also much harder for members to identify each other when living among lots of group members. Fortunately, there's a solution to this last problem...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>