<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7497">shostakovich life</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:03:48" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7497-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7497_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:03:49">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/09/unravelling-the-origins-of-life-with-mathematical-chemistry/</link><title>Unraveling the origins of life with mathematical chemistry</title><description>...How life began is one of the most compelling questions humanity ever asked. Atoms and molecules... at the start of life, when some unknown molecule somehow became self replicating, for example, hold the key to understanding how life began and how likely it is to have sprouted throughout the Universe.Martin...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7497-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7497_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:04:41">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/09/phosphorous-minerals-stoke-speculation-of-life-beginning-on-mars/</link><title>Phosphorous minerals stoke speculation of life beginning on Mars</title><description>... on the heels of this fundamental gap in our knowledge are two further questions onThe ObserverlistHow did life... of Florida suggested, in his talk at the conference, that life first kicked off with the organization of sugars into ribose, and then ribonucleic acid (RNA), one of the fundamental molecules key to life...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7497-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7497_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:05:39">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/01/did-a-life-start-with-a-replicating-molecule-or-a-metabolism/</link><title>Did life start with a replicating molecule or a metabolism?</title><description>...Early biologists may have been at a loss when they wondered how life on Earth could ever... chemistries that could have produced cells and therefore life; the challenge lies in figuring... and their organization into Life As We Know It: understanding how those biological compounds, once synthesized, became...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7497-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7497_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:06:23">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/02/good-news-astronomers-have-found-life-on-earth-using-polarized-light/</link><title>Astronomers find hints of life on Earth by looking at the Moon</title><description>... of discovering life on other worlds is much closer to reality than it has ever been before. However, in many... the presence of life on other planets would be to confirm the existence of life on Earth, using... instruments, nobody has made a successful observation of life on Earth using data that's a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7497-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7497_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:07:06">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/10/valve-registers-european-trademark-for-half-life-3/</link><title>Valve registers European trademark for Half-Life 3 [Updated]</title><description>...;sOffice for Harmonization in the Internal Market,tells Ars that the Half-Life 3trademark application... went public last night and guess what project was listed there. Yup! Half-Life 3 (also Left 4 Dead 3.... Half-Life 3\. It exists. Well, it exists as a trademark application. In Europe.Still! It's really...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7497-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7497_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:08:01">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/11/half-life-is-ten-years-old-replay-the-classic-on-steam-for-1/</link><title>Half-Life is ten years old! Replay the classic on Steam for $1</title><description>...Looking back, its hard to remember what life was like before Half-Life. The game changed the way... you played Half-Life? Can you believe its been ten years? Valves Marc Laidlaw told GameSpy.... That didnt take into account the fact that Half-Life was going to be a success. We were prepared...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7497-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7497_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:08:39">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/12/reuters-jumps-second-life-ship/</link><title>Reuters jumps Second Life ship</title><description>... Life. While the game might be a rather expansive territory to cover, one can only cover so many wife... Life site and discovered that the latest story posted was actually posted at the end of September. A subsequent phone call revealed that Reuters Second Life bureau had actually been shut down. Were still...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7497-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7497_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:09:20">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/09/life-with-playstation-is-like-your-ex-pretty-but-shallow/</link><title>Life With PlayStation is like your ex: pretty, but shallow</title><description>...Sony has announced that the Life With PlayStation application is now available for the PlayStation... from the comfort of their console. Like the Wii forecast channel, Life With PlayStation features.... In addition to weather information, Life With PlayStation also provides up to date news from Google News...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7497-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7497_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:10:17">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/08/half-life-3-is-not-in-the-works-says-valve-voice-actor/</link><title>Half-Life 3 is not in the works, says Valve voice actor</title><description>...Half-Life 3 is not in the works, according to some dissenting statements posted by John Patrick... an actor and translate those movements to a 3D rendering. Half-Life 2 used a mechanic where NPCs would turn... on other upcoming titles as reasons Half Life 3 remains on the shelf.Shortly after posting the comments, Lowrie...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7497-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7497_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:11:01">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/09/3-5-billion-year-old-organic-deposts-show-signs-of-life/</link><title>3.5 billion year old organic deposits show signs of life</title><description>...How long did it take for life to get started on Earth? The planet formed roughly 4.5 billion years ago, although it was uninhabitable for a while afterward. By 2.7 billion years ago... out the gap between the obvious presence of life and the origin of multicellular animals, suggesting...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>