<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7498">syria chemical weapons</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:11:56" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7498-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7498_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:11:58">http://arstechnica.com/science/2008/12/clothing-that-destroys-warfare-chemicals/</link><title>Clothing that destroys chemical weapons</title><description>...The deployment of chemical weapons in an urban population center isnt simply a hypothetical threat... and corrosive chemicals usually comes in the form of bulky suits. Outside of suits... the skin to become a health risk themselves. Chemical protection suits. Chemically modified clot...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7498-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7498_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:12:35">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2012/05/game-overhow-sanctions-and-violence-doomed-syrias-gaming-industry/</link><title>Game over—how sanctions and violence doomed Syria's gaming industry</title><description>...;The entertainment industry was the first to be affected by the revolution," said Kasmiya, who left Syria... in retrospect, the presence of any sort of game development presence in Syria still seems a bit odd... to be desired, especially compared with some of its neighbors."Jordan, Syria, and Lebanon...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7498-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7498_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:13:53">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/12/paint-it-black-how-syria-methodically-erased-itself-from-the-net/</link><title>Updated: Paint it black—How Syria methodically erased itself from the 'Net</title><description>... equipment to "dozens" of local councils in areas of Syria no longer under government control in order to bypass Syria's government-controlled networks.But the Internet blackout in Syria... the sudden drop-off in network traffic from Syria on Thursday as the country essentially erased...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7498-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7498_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:14:42">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/11/syria-deletes-itself-from-internet-as-fighting-intensifies/</link><title>Syria deletes itself from Internet as fighting intensifies</title><description>...Fighting near Damascus has already cut off Syria's capital from the rest of the world byshutting down its airport. At the same time, the government has further severed the country by shutting down its connection to the Internet and shutting down cellular phone service in some regions of the country.At 12:26 Damascus time today, Internet monitoring company Renesys reportedall IP addresses in ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7498-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7498_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:15:19">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/05/syria-drops-offline-again/</link><title>Update: Syria drops offline for a day</title><description>... Networks.At about 2:45 Eastern time (18:45 UTC) on May 7 , Internet traffic in and out of Syria came... or a full cable cut (of Syria's three outbound connections)."The last time Syria disappeared... outside of Syria over Indian telecom provider Tata's networks. Domain name resolution...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7498-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7498_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:16:30">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/08/us-sanctions-give-china-an-opportunity-to-supply-bandwidth-to-syrian-isps/</link><title>Syria sidesteps sanctions by turning to China for Internet bandwidth</title><description>.... With growing international diplomatic pressure and sanctions against Syria, the Syria..., for its role in"tracking and targeting citizens for violence." Syriatel owns SAWA, Syrias.... Other countries have been following suit, making it harder for Syria to buy bandwidth. But China...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7498-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7498_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:17:30">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2014/03/navy-will-deploy-first-ship-with-laser-weapon-this-summer/</link><title>Navy will deploy first ship with laser weapon this summer</title><description>... weapon to the fleet. When it puts to sea this summer, the afloat forward staging base ship USS Ponce will be equipped with the Navys Laser Weapon System (LaWS).LaWS is a system based on a design developed... prototype of the Laser Weapon System (LaWS) at sea in a test in 2013. While the Navy will still depend...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7498-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7498_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:18:11">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/04/wanted-review/</link><title>Game Review: Wanted: Weapons of Fate</title><description>... Wanted: Weapons of Fate, a game that continues the story of 2008's Wanted movie with mixed...;s family has been battling the group for over two decades. Title Wanted: Weapons of Fate Developer Grin Games Publisher Warner Bros Interactive Price $59.99 Platform Xbox 360, PS3, PC Weapons of Fate...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7498-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7498_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:18:56">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2013/08/soon-your-phone-may-be-able-to-help-feds-monitor-nuclear-weapons/</link><title>Soon, your phone may be able to help feds monitor nuclear weapons</title><description>... that they are there. There are items associated with warheads, chemical weapons that can cue you in. Weapons need a support structure... sure that weapons of mass destruction dont fall into the hands of terrorists. And they want to use..., whether dealing with chemical warfare, nucl...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7498-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7498_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:19:37">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/07/wikileaks-italian-firm-sold-syria-secure-radios-as-crackdown-raged/</link><title>Wikileaks: Italian firm sold Syria secure radios as crackdown raged</title><description>...As the US and Europe leveled increasingly severe sanctions on Syria, Western tech companies... political noose of trade sanctions to bring a joint project in Syria to completion. That project?A secure... continued throughout the violent suppression of dissidents in Syria through February of this year...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>