<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7499">gold price</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:20:31" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7499-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7499_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:20:32">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/09/im-not-leaving-without-a-gold-one-tales-from-the-iphone-5s-line/</link><title>“I‘m not leaving without a gold one!” Tales from the iPhone 5S line</title><description>... with the kind of people who want gold iPhones.How the iPhone 5S Gold came to be. Apple didn't provide Ars...; the available quantity of white and gold iPhone 5Ss was continually brought up.The person in line behind me... quite nice!she asked how many gold iPhones were left."Oh, we only got five,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7499-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7499_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:21:16">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/08/microsoft-details-home-gold-sharing-program-for-xbox-one/</link><title>Microsoft details “Home Gold” sharing program for Xbox One</title><description>... Xbox Live Gold accounts for a reduced price of $100/year, but itabruptly stopped offering...Microsoft has confirmed that multiple users will be able to take advantage of Xbox Live Gold features on a single Xbox One console as long as any one user is a Gold subscriber.In a post today on Xbox...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7499-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7499_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:22:24">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/03/30-percent-of-online-gamers-reportedly-buy-gold/</link><title>30 percent of online gamers reportedly buy gold</title><description>...Anyone who's played an MMO can testify to the fact that grinding for gold and loot is a hassle that most would rather avoid. As a result, most of us have at least thought about buying some gold... number.In a feature about gold-trading in MMOs, Eurogamer recently spoke to an anonymous figure...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7499-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7499_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:23:16">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/ubisoft-and-golds-gym-creating-game-together/</link><title>Ubisoft and Gold's Gym creating game together</title><description>...Nintendo's winning formula that is Wii Fit has proven to be such a huge success that everyone is trying to get a piece of the pie that is fitness video gaming, often with less-than-amazing titles. Ubisoft has revealed that it's hoping to get in on the action by teaming up with fitness chain Gold's Gym. Gold's Gym: Cardio Workout will unsurprisingly use the Wii Fit balance boar...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7499-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7499_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:23:56">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/08/game-dvr-functions-on-xbox-one-require-an-xbox-live-gold-account/</link><title>Game DVR functions on Xbox One require an Xbox Live Gold account [updated]</title><description>... subscription. The price for an Xbox Live Gold subscription rose from $50 to $60 annually back... Gold subscription.The news comes via an Xbox Live Gold features list published on Xbox.com... calling, NFL on Xbox, and the "OneGuide" customized view of live TV content as Gold...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7499-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7499_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:25:34">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/recent-channel-checks-indicate-ps3-price-cut-says-analyst/</link><title>Channel checks point to PS3 price cut, says analyst</title><description>...To price cut, or not to price cut? That is the question for Sony, and if Janco analyst Mike Hickey can be trusted, a PS3 price cut announcement is just around the corner. "Recent channel checks indicate increased speculation for a PS3 price cut announcement from Sony in the next couple of days...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7499-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7499_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:26:27">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/08/bethesda-pushing-against-xbox-live-gold-fee-for-elder-scrolls-online/</link><title>Bethesda “pushing” against Xbox Live Gold fee for Elder Scrolls Online</title><description>... to get Microsoft to agree to waive the additional requirement of an Xbox Live Gold subscription... Live Gold account to play any and all online games on the system, even otherwise free-to-play titles... who are only paying The Elder Scrolls Online and don't want to pay for an Xbox Live Gold subscription...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7499-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7499_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:27:11">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2013/05/blizzard-fixes-diablo-iii-gold-duplication-bug-but-the-damage-may-be-done/</link><title>Blizzard fixes Diablo III gold duplication bug, but the damage may be done</title><description>... an exploit that let savvy users create in-game gold out of thin air, wreaking havoc on the in-game..., players on the 1.0.8 patch would get twice as much gold returned to them, creating an easy source..., since the in-game auction houses let duplicated gold be traded for other players' items...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7499-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7499_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:28:20">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/03/sony-drops-price-on-the-wrong-playstation/</link><title>Sony drops price on the wrong PlayStation</title><description>...While the buzz at GDC was about a possible price break on the PlayStation 3, today all the rumors about a Sony price drop have been confirmed... for the PlayStation 2. Starting April 1, new PS2 hardware will cost $99.99, coming in below the magical $100 price point. Compared to $400 for the PS3...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7499-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7499_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:28:51">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/02/as-budgets-tighten-the-price-on-games-begins-to-come-down/</link><title>Recession, choosy gamers lead to price drops on games</title><description>..., more games priced lower than the $59.99 standard MSRP of "seventh generation" games...;s clear that consumers are becoming increasingly focused on the price of their entertainment... to code for, meaning the savings in development can allow publishers to release games for a lower price...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>