<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7502">baby todler snowsuit</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:38:35" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7502-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7502_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:38:36">http://arstechnica.com/staff/2009/03/baby-technica-help-me-find-a-baby-gate/</link><title>Baby Technica: help me find a baby gate!</title><description>...Shame on me for abusing my "blog" here, but isn't that what staff blogs are for? Look, I know one of you out there has a solution to my problem, so I'm willing to get all gooey and talk some baby business here.My 7 month old daughter is on the verge of crawling, so I need a baby...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7502-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7502_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:39:48">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/09/software-patents-theres-no-baby-in-this-bathwater/</link><title>Software patents: there's no "baby" in this "bathwater"</title><description>... one. Supporters of software patents insist that barring software patents would be throwing the baby out with the bathwater. But it's not clear there was a baby in there to begin with. Empirical...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7502-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7502_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:40:24">http://arstechnica.com/science/2009/08/what-population-decline/</link><title>More advanced countries have more babies</title><description>... countries produce fewer babies. Enter Mikko Myrskyl. A statistician at the University of Pennsylvania...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7502-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7502_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:41:07">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/09/baby-sharks-birthed-in-artificial-uterus/</link><title>Baby sharks birthed in artificial uterus</title><description>...Baby sharks birthed in artificial uterus An artificial uterus, designed to give live birth to sharks, rests in the lab of the Port Stephens Fisheries Institute, in the New South Wales... and die by accident, said Otway. And the death of even one is a huge loss, since babies are so hard...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7502-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7502_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:41:42">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/02/baby-exoplanets-photographed-during-formation/</link><title>Baby exoplanets photographed during formation</title><description>... of at least one planet.We think were seeing the baby photos of a planetary system that is just forming...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7502-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7502_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:42:12">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/06/happy-birthday-baby-the-65th-anniversary-of-computer-software/</link><title>Happy Birthday, Baby—The 65th anniversary of computer software</title><description>...,Tom Kilburn, and Geoff Tootil, Baby wasn't the first programmable computer. But the technology proven in Baby, with its 1,024 bits of cathode-tube based RAM, would become the basis of the first... and cables. Parrot of Doom "Baby," the Manchester Small-Scale Experimental Machine (SSEM...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7502-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7502_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:43:11">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/05/blame-baby-monitors-not-congestion-for-your-wifi-woes/</link><title>Blame baby monitors, not congestion, for your WiFi woes</title><description>...Many users chalk up WiFi connection problems to congestion, especially when living in apartment buildings or urban areas; there's just too much data being pushed through those 11 meager channels! But a thorough new report (PDF) commissioned by UK regulators sent researchers into the streets to pinpoint WiFi's connection problems, and the culprit turns out to be... baby monitors.Well, no...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7502-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7502_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:44:02">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/11/governments-register-objections-to-wtf-islam-and-baby-tlds/</link><title>Governments register objections to .wtf, .islam and .baby TLDs</title><description>...An international panel representing a selection of governments from around the world has registered more than 240 objections to proposed generic top level domains, including .wtf, .baby...;Oreal's application), .baby (from Johnson Johnson Services Inc), and .antivirus (Symantec Corporation...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7502-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7502_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:44:37">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/10/its-official-to-protect-babys-brain-turn-off-the-tv/</link><title>It's official: to protect baby's brain, turn off the TV</title><description>... a new, science-heavy policy statement on babies watching television, videos or any other passive media..., it distracts babies from play, an activity that is known to have deep developmental benefits. And for parents..., such as the controversial Baby Einstein videos.The way these kids programs came out was, These are really...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7502-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7502_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:45:54">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/11/babies-eyes-may-hold-early-clues-about-autism/</link><title>Babies’ eyes may hold early clues about autism</title><description>... was strapped into their car seat or a baby carrier and placed in front of a monitor. Here, they watched videos...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>