<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7504">leiden schools</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:48:33" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7504-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7504_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:48:34">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/11/texas-school-districts-rfid-tracking-of-students-goes-to-court/</link><title>Texas school district's RFID tracking of students goes to court</title><description>...A Texas high school sophomore has filed suitagainst San Antonio's Northside Independent School... badge in school. The girl and her parents are claiming the policy is a violation of her First Amendment... issuing RFID badges to students at two schools in September as part of an effort to track students...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7504-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7504_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:49:17">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/04/facebook-debuts-groups-for-schools-includes-25mb-filesharing-function/</link><title>Facebook debuts "Groups for Schools," includes 25MB filesharing function</title><description>... corresponding .edu addresses will be able to gain access.As part of Groups for Schools, Facebook... to Groups for Schools (my alma mater, Syracuse University, still waiting. You can check herefor yours). The school exclusivity harkens back to the early days of Facebook, as does the file sharing. Mark...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7504-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7504_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:50:00">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/03/violent-nintendo-power-removed-from-middle-school-library/</link><title>"Violent" Nintendo Power removed from middle school library</title><description>...A minor controversy erupted in Clevelend, Ohio recently, where a teachers union and school board... from a middle school library. The issue in question features a character from Grand Theft Auto..., which states that all staff must put in a formal request to the school board before a publication...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7504-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7504_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:50:35">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2009/04/create-a-school-resurrected-in-ncaa-10-dubbed-teambuilder/</link><title>Create-a-school resurrected in NCAA 10, dubbed TeamBuilder</title><description>... that I just discovered over on Uni Watch. Create-a-school is returningnew and improvedto EA's NCAA... your own school, uniforms (helmets, jerseys, pants, socks, and shoes), rosters, and even recruiting pitches. Unlike the old create-a-school feature, TeamBuilder will be accessible via a Web browser...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7504-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7504_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:51:25">http://arstechnica.com/apple/2013/07/apples-back-to-school-promo-is-back-gives-you-more-to-spend-on-apple/</link><title>Apple’s back-to-school promo is back, gives you more to spend on Apple</title><description>...Apple's annual back-to-school promotion is back for another year, and the terms are much the same as they were last year: students, teachers, and staff of K-12 or higher education institutions who qualify for educational pricing on Apple's products can get App Store gift cards...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7504-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7504_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:52:02">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/08/the-ars-pc-laptop-buying-guide-back-to-school-edition/</link><title>PC laptop buying guide—back to school edition</title><description>.... To give you some guidance in this back-to-school season, we've set up three basic laptop...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7504-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7504_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:52:42">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/05/schools-cant-stop-wondering-what-students-are-up-to-on-facebook/</link><title>Schools can't stop wondering what students do on Facebook</title><description>... almost ubiquitous teen hangouts.For instance: can school administration use social networking to keeps tabs on what students do during the school day? What about things they do after leaving school... school students, despite the fact that no one knew who she was. On April 5, the school's former...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7504-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7504_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:53:36">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/04/school-it-allegedly-took-thousands-of-pics-in-webcam-case/</link><title>School IT allegedly took "thousands" of pics in webcam case</title><description>...Remember the lawsuit filed by the family of 15-year-old Blake Robbins against the school district... claiming that the school took more than 400 photos of Blake in his roomsome while sleeping... on all school-issued computers, the family has discovered more than 400 photos of Blake alone...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7504-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7504_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:54:36">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2010/10/school-settles-laptop-spying-case-to-protect-taxpayers/</link><title>School settles laptop spying case to "protect taxpayers"</title><description>...The school district accused of spying on students at home via laptop webcam has agreed to settle two student lawsuits for a total of $610,000. The Lower Merion School District board of directors... of the story.The webcam issue first came to light in February when high school student Blake J...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7504-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7504_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:55:09">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/01/court-no-right-to-shout-douchebag-in-a-crowded-blog/</link><title>Court: No right to shout "douchebag" in a crowded blog</title><description>..., which upheld the right of public school administrators to discipline a student for speech... High Schoolthis past summer. Following a dust-up with school administrators about the possible..., been canceled, though school officials say Doninger was wrong about this.) When the school retaliated...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>