<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7505">ethnic myanmar</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:55:44" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7505-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7505_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:55:46">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/09/umpires-show-ethnic-bias-in-ballstrike-callsunless-theyre-feeling-watched/</link><title>Umpires show ethnic bias in ball/strike calls—unless they're feeling watched</title><description>... ethnic group, So, an umpire that's white might be expected to favor a white pitcher, giving him... together the ethnic origins of all the major league players and umpires involved. And then... ethnic group as the pitcher, they were more likely to call a pitch a strike, at least at a ball park...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7505-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7505_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:56:32">http://arstechnica.com/uncategorized/2008/09/manipulating-racial-identity-to-get-out-the-vote/</link><title>Manipulating racial identity to get out the vote</title><description>...As the election draws near, we are being bombarded with messages that are designed to either reinforce or blur our sense of social identity, drawing us to make alliances based on who we think we are and who we think were not. Both Democrats and Republicans use what are called affirmational speeches and ads that reinforce our sense of identity and suggest that their candidates are ordinary people ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7505-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7505_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:57:14">http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/03/drug-resistant-malaria-takes-new-ground-raising-fears-of-global-spread/</link><title>Drug resistant malaria takes new ground, raising fears of global spread</title><description>... Organization. The new area in Thailand joins previous hot spots in Cambodia, Vietnam, and Myanmar... Thailand, near the border with Myanmar. It's unclear if Mae Sot represents a spread of drug... spots in Cambodia, one in Vietnam, and several confirmed and suspected regions in Myanmar. Chinese...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7505-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7505_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:58:10">http://arstechnica.com/science/2014/03/a-field-report-from-malarias-cradle-of-drug-resistance/</link><title>A field report from malaria’s cradle of drug resistance</title><description>... of Myanmars 130 or so ethnic groupswho were fleeing persecution from the majority Bamar government. Nosten...The meandering MoeiRiver marks the natural boundary between Thailand and Myanmar. Its muddy waters... boat. In the dry season, he could wade across. As he steps onto the western riverbank in Myanmar...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7505-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7505_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:59:22">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/03/people-like-virtual-trainers-that-look-act-like-them/</link><title>People like virtual instructors that look, act like them</title><description>... personality shares our gender and ethnic background, just as we are when we work with living humans. Now... of gender and ethnic similarity than past work had suggested, with gender similarity having no effect on the outcomes of training, and ethnic similarity actually making things worse. Combined, however...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7505-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7505_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:00:06">http://arstechnica.com/science/2013/11/dating-still-segregated-but-people-cross-racial-lines-once-contacted/</link><title>Dating still segregated, but people cross racial lines once contacted</title><description>... all of the ethnic groups he examined, there's a strong tendency for people to send messages to other users who belong to the same ethnic group. But people who are willing to go against that trend... messages, and they generally send them to people of their own ethnicity. "Men and women...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7505-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7505_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:00:43">http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/06/using-tor-and-squid-to-loosen-iranian-repression-by-proxy/</link><title>Using Tor and Squid to loosen Iranian repression by proxy</title><description>... on all services (a route apparently taken by Myanmar during recent protests there). Private households...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7505-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7505_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:01:53">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/09/week-in-science-zombie-caterpillar-edition/</link><title>Week in science: zombie caterpillar edition</title><description>..., or rarely productive.Umpires show ethnic bias in ball/strike callsunless they're feeling watched... with their own ethnicity. But, as an umpire monitoring system was rolled out, that bias began...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7505-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7505_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:02:51">http://arstechnica.com/business/2012/04/flyrights-app-aims-to-streamline-tsa-complaint-process/</link><title>FlyRights app aims to streamline TSA complaint process</title><description>... towards Sikhs and other religious and ethnic minorities at airports around the United States.In the wake... not profile passengers on the basis of race, ethnicity or religion. We continually engage...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7505-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7505_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:03:32">http://arstechnica.com/science/2011/09/week-in-science-know-it-all-physicists-and-interbreeding-hominins/</link><title>Week in science: know-it-all physicists and interbreeding hominins</title><description>... ethnic bias in ball/strike callsunless they're feeling watched: Major League Baseball's umpires exhibited a subtle but significant bias towards favoring pitchers with their own ethnicity...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>