<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7506">I touch myself singer dead</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:04:18" name="Ars Technica" id="FW14-e167"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e167-7506-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7506_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:04:19">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/08/ars-does-soylent-day-2-my-god-what-have-i-gotten-myself-into/</link><title>Ars does Soylent, Day 2: My God, what have I gotten myself into</title><description>... and blender slowly, bargaining with myself. Just a small cup this morning, I think, my gorge rising as I... return to work, I want to do something to burn through the Soylent funk I feel myself falling...Day 1 recap: Like trench warfare in FranceI ended the pr...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7506-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7506_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:05:16">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/01/dead-space-on-the-ipad-expands-story-uses-touch-controls-well/</link><title>Dead Space on the iPad expands story, uses touch controls well</title><description>...EA's Dead Space for iOS devices is a prequel to Dead Space 2, and it helps explain what... much of the look and the feel of the game EA was able to cram into these devices. I played the game... and a surprise in Dead Space 2 for registering your copyall you have to do is log into your EA account...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7506-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7506_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:05:49">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2010/06/left-4-dead-1-campaign-i-hate-mountains-high-quality/</link><title>Left 4 Dead 1 campaign "I Hate Mountains" high quality</title><description>...There is a small but dedicated group of players who still think that Left 4 Dead 1 is a superior... the team behind the sublime add-on campaign "I Hate Mountains" drew much inspiration... and the game's flow is impressive. (I will note that there is a little more exploration...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7506-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7506_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:06:36">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/09/should-i-continue-teaching-myself-how-to-code-or-should-i-go-pro/</link><title>Should I continue teaching myself how to code or should I go pro?</title><description>... and organization of my code are different.It's a mixture of several things I do. I tend to blend several programming paradigms together like Functional and OO. I lean to the Functional side more than OO, but I see the use of OO when something would make more sense as an abstract entitylike a game...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7506-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7506_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:07:45">http://arstechnica.com/business/2010/12/season-1-of-walking-dead-is-over-but-where-did-it-get-us/</link><title>Season one of Walking Dead is over; where did it get us?</title><description>... lights and computerswas a nice touch, but did we need the digital countdown? I kept wondering... version ofWalking Dead where you realize that not only is no one safe, the rules about where and when violence can occur are being changed. Walking Dead creator Robert Kirkman is gifted at creating what...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7506-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7506_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:09:10">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2008/10/is-dead-space-scary-yes/</link><title>Is Dead Space scary? Yes.</title><description>...Weve been looking forward to Dead Space for quite a long time now, and I had the entirely terrible task of spending most of last night and today playing the game. While I wont talk much about specifics until we run our feature review, I will say one thing: the game is scary. Last night I took the game over to a friends house and we killed the lights, put the volume at a comfortable level and then...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7506-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7506_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:09:53">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2012/06/liveblog-google-2012-io-opening-keynote/</link><title>Live from the opening keynote at Google I/O 2012</title><description>...View LiveblogGoogle I/O is the search giants annual event for software developers. The popular conference offers third-party developers who build on top of Googles platforms and services an opportunity to engage directly with the companys engineers.During the Google I/O 2012 morning keynote...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7506-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7506_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:10:29">http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2011/06/dead-island-delivers-dark-fun-action-in-single-and-multiplayer/</link><title>Dead Island delivers dark, fun action in single- and multiplayer</title><description>... is a major selling point. I keep thinking that I'm bored with co-op zombie games, but Dead Island...Dead Island takes place on a beautiful tropical island, and you are tasked with taking control...-open world to explore, but while it may be constantly compared to other games like Dead Rising...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7506-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7506_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:11:36">http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2013/05/google-io-in-pictures-keynotes-sessions-and-little-green-robots/</link><title>Google I/O in pictures: keynotes, sessions, and little green robots</title><description>...So far this year's Google I/O has been very developer-centricperhaps not surprising given that I/O is, at the end of the day, adeveloper's conference. Especially compared to last year's skydiving, Glass-revealing, Nexus-introducing keynote, yesterday's three-and-a-half-hour keynote presentation focused overwhelmingly on back-end technologies rather than concrete products aimed...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e167-7506-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e167/7506_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:12:42">http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/05/a-second-look-at-google-io-androids-robots-and-the-show-floor/</link><title>A second look at Google I/O: Androids, robots, and the show floor</title><description>...We spent the week at I/O sitting in sessions, walking around the show floor, and congregating..., available by the bushel. Florence Ion A Google Play for Education panel takes place in one of the Google I/O... Ion Nope, sorry, those are just Android's. Florence Ion Recon Instruments was exhibiting at I...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>