<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7024">reinforcement learning</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:23:16" name="WebMD" id="FW14-e076"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e076-7024-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7024_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:23:17">http://www.webmd.com/brain/autism/autism-treatment-overview</link><title>Autism - Treatment Overview</title><description>WebMD provides in-depth autism treatment information including behavioral therapy, speech therapy,...learning aspects of a child's life will be most successful. The American Academy of Pediatrics...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7024-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7024_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:26:49">http://www.webmd.com/mental-health/mental-health-pica</link><title>Mental Health and Pica</title><description>Pica is the persistent eating of substances with no nutrition, such as dirt or paint. Learn more...through the use of positive reinforcement. There are many potential complications of pica, such as:...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7024-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7024_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:28:55">http://www.webmd.com/cancer/tc/ncicdr0000618162-training-in-communication-skills</link><title>Communication in Cancer Care (PDQ®): Supportive care - Health Professional Information [NCI] - Training in Communication Skills</title><description>Training Providers Some believe that effective communication between doctor and patient is a core clinical skill that should be...when working with patients. Employing longitudinal reinforcement.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7024-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7024_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:30:04">http://blogs.webmd.com/healthy-children/2006/01/teaching-your-children-do-as-i-do-not-as-i-say.html</link><title>Teaching your children: Do as I do, not as I say « Healthy Children</title><description>...behave in the world? Sure there is the usual positive and negative reinforcement you always hear about when they are young. And there are fancy...of the most important ways children learn is...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7024-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7024_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:34:54">http://blogs.webmd.com/anxiety-and-stress-management/2006/01/curing-ptsd.html</link><title>Curing PTSD « Anxiety and Stress Management</title><description>...done by Drs. McGaugh and Cahill at the Center for Neurobiology of Learning and Memory at UC Irvine. One med that has proven especially interesting...decay. Blunting the symptoms quickly may do an...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7024-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7024_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:35:25">http://www.webmd.com/add-adhd/childhood-adhd/adhd-inattentive-type</link><title>ADHD: Inattentive Type</title><description>WebMD explains the inattentive type of ADHD in children, including symptoms of this condition and...that can mimic inattentive ADHD, including: hearing or vision problems learning disability anxiety...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7024-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7024_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:36:30">http://www.webmd.com/brain/autism/autism-topic-overview</link><title>Autism - Topic Overview</title><description>WebMD provides information to your family about dealing with autism and answers common autism...his or her language skills. Symptoms of autism include: A delay in learning to talk, or not talking...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7024-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7024_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:38:31">http://www.webmd.com/parenting/guide/potty-training-preschoolers</link><title>Potty Training and Your Preschooler</title><description>What if your preschooler hasn't mastered potty training yet or isn't interested in trying? WebMD has...average age at which a child will start to show interest in learning to potty train is around...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7024-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7024_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:39:58">http://www.webmd.com/add-adhd/tc/attention-deficit-hyperactivity-disorder-adhd-treatment-overview</link><title>Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD) - Treatment Overview</title><description>Learn about ADHD treatment and how to successfully manage ADHD with medications, therapy, group or...of ADHD and an understanding of your child's strengths and weaknesses. Learning about ADHD will...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7024-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7024_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:43:29">http://www.webmd.com/brain/autism/parenting-child-with-autism-special-challenges</link><title>Tips for Parenting a Child With Autism</title><description>If you are parenting a child with autism, learn more from WebMD about treatment options and special...parents and improving communication, social, behavioral, adaptive, and learning aspects of a...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>