<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7046">tuning fork</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:25:01" name="WebMD" id="FW14-e076"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e076-7046-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7046_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:25:03">http://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/hearing-tests</link><title>Hearing Tests</title><description>A hearing (audiometric) test is part of an ear examination that evaluates a person's ability to hear...bone behind your ear. Again, you will signal each time you hear a tone. Tuning fork tests A...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7046-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7046_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:27:28">http://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/diabetic-neuropathy-medical-history-and-physical-exam-topic-overview</link><title>Diabetic Neuropathy: Medical History and Physical Exam - Topic Overview</title><description>When you have diabetic neuropathy, your doctor will get your medical history and may ask you about the following:SymptomsWhat...evaluate your sensation of temperature, a cold metal tuning fork may be...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7046-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7046_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:29:54">http://www.webmd.com/pain-management/ruptured-eardrum-symptoms-and-treatments</link><title>Ruptured Eardrum: Symptoms and Treatments</title><description>WebMD explains the causes, symptoms, diagnosis, and treatment of a ruptured ear drum...how much effect the ruptured eardrum has had on your hearing; he or she may use a tuning fork to test it. The...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7046-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7046_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:30:30">http://www.webmd.com/cancer/tc/late-effects-of-treatment-for-childhood-cancer-treatment-patient-information-nci-pdq-senses</link><title>Late Effects of Treatment for Childhood Cancer (PDQ®): Treatment - Patient Information [NCI] - Senses</title><description>Ears Childhood cancer survivors may have late effects that affect hearing. Certain factors increase the risk that hearing loss...if he or she can hear the high-pitched hum of a tuning fork when it is...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7046-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7046_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:35:01">http://www.webmd.com/diabetes/tc/type-1-diabetes-living-with-complications-exams-and-tests</link><title>Type 1 Diabetes: Living With Complications - Exams and Tests</title><description>Because you have a complication from type 1 diabetes, you need to have regular exams and tests to...assesses your sense of light touch or pressure. A cold metal tuning fork held to your leg evaluates...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7046-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7046_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:38:34">http://www.webmd.com/multiple-sclerosis/neurological-examination-for-multiple-sclerosis</link><title>Neurological Examination for Multiple Sclerosis</title><description>Before conducting a neurological examination for multiple sclerosis (MS), the doctor will collect information about your symptoms...a light touch, temperature, and vibration (a tuning fork). Sense the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7046-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7046_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:39:05">http://www.webmd.com/balance/features/8-reasons-slow-down</link><title>8 Reasons To Slooow Down</title><description>Winding down the pace of your life just a tad can make you happier and healthier. Here's how!...you're full before taking those final few bites and drop your fork, you may cut out as many as 100...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7046-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7046_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:39:32">http://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/hearing-loss-overview</link><title>Hearing Loss - Overview</title><description>What is hearing loss?Hearing loss is a sudden or gradual decrease in how well you can hear. Depending on the cause, it can range...to do the tests. These tests may include: A tuning fork test, which...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>