<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7068">Speech and Language Processing: An Introduction to Natural Language Processing, Computational Linguistics, and Speech Recognition</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:42:17" name="WebMD" id="FW14-e076"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e076-7068-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7068_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:42:18">http://www.webmd.com/alzheimers/tc/alzheimers-disease-prevention</link><title>Preventing Alzheimer's</title><description>Alzehiemer's Disease has no known cure, and the secrets to preventing it are not yet known. But research supported by the National...as thinking, decision-making, and language skills). This...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7068-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7068_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:43:53">http://www.webmd.com/men/news/20001205/dyslexia-cure</link><title>New Clues Point to Possible Dyslexia Cure</title><description>In this day and age, dyslexia is a common term, but what's really known about it, and do doctors really know how to treat it?...with reading, spelling, understanding language they hear, or expressing.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7068-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7068_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:46:39">http://www.webmd.com/brain/autism/news/20140114/sight-sound-out-of-sync-in-kids-with-autism-study-finds</link><title>Sight, Sound Out of Sync in Kids With Autism: Study</title><description>Researcher compares the processing delay to a poorly dubbed movie...have trouble matching sounds, especially speech, to their sources. "They're...kinds of consequences for the language abilities of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7068-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7068_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:47:52">http://www.webmd.com/children/guide/detecting-learning-disabilities</link><title>Detecting Learning Disabilities</title><description>WebMD explains the warning signs and diagnosis of learning disabilities, including information on testing and the types of...problems associated with dyspraxia include: Speech difficulties...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7068-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7068_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:50:02">http://www.webmd.com/brain/autism/tc/aspergers-syndrome-symptoms</link><title>Asperger's Syndrome - Symptoms</title><description>Although there are many possible symptoms of Aspergers syndrome, the main symptom is severe trouble...able to read others' body language, start or maintain a conversation...to recognize subtle...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7068-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7068_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:50:39">http://www.webmd.com/brain/autism/news/20130918/young-adults-with-autism-less-likely-to-have-jobs-live-independently</link><title>Young Adults With Autism Less Likely to Have Jobs</title><description>Surveys looked at life after high school for 20-somethings with various disorders...80 percent of those with speech and language difficulties reported having at least...with autism earned $8.10 an...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7068-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7068_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:53:52">http://www.webmd.com/children/news/20131205/slower-brain-connections-may-be-at-root-of-dyslexia</link><title>Slower Brain Connections May Be at Root of Dyslexia</title><description>Researchers find new insight into reading disorder...brain's storage space for speech sounds and the brain regions that process language. The results were surprising, said...in people with dyslexia,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7068-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7068_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:54:53">http://www.webmd.com/brain/brain-damage-symptoms-causes-treatments</link><title>Brain Damage: Symptoms, Causes, Treatments</title><description>...examines common causes of brain damage as well as the types, symptoms, and treatments for brain...Brain damage is an injury that causes the destruction...of brain damage include: Difficulty...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7068-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7068_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:58:35">http://www.webmd.com/parenting/helping-children-with-dyslexia</link><title>Helping Children with Dyslexia</title><description>Dyslexia is a common learning disability that is unrelated to a person's intelligence. Find out what to do if you suspect your...reading and comprehension of written language. Since reading is a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7068-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7068_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:02:16">http://blogs.webmd.com/food-and-nutrition/2012/04/you-say-cacao-i-say-cocoa-we-both-say-chocolate.html</link><title>You Say Cacao, I Say Cocoa, We both Say CHOCOLATE! « Real Life Nutrition</title><description>...originate from Latin-based romance languages but is in essence used...than 250 studies show that natural cocoa and dark chocolate have...your diet each day as an ingredient mixed in beverages or..</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>