<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7083">I'm on the road again</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:37:44" name="WebMD" id="FW14-e076"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e076-7083-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7083_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:37:46">http://blogs.webmd.com/healthy-skin/2010/07/eight-skin-care-tips-on-the-road.html</link><title>Eight Skin Care Tips on the Road « Healthy Skin</title><description>...NY where I am preparing with my skin team for an appearance on the Today Show to discuss the different types of psoriasis . With all...different environments — from very hot to humid — I’ve been...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7083-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7083_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:38:19">http://blogs.webmd.com/pet-tales/2011/08/on-the-road-again-safety-restraints-for-car-traveling-pets.html</link><title>On the Road Again: Safety Restraints for Car-Traveling Pets « Tales from the Pet Clinic</title><description>...destinations this summer. Sixty-one percent of pet owners take their pets on vacation . If you do the math, that equals nearly 19 million car...as a driving distraction. Proper restraint keeps your...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7083-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7083_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:42:39">http://www.webmd.com/women/features/viola-davis-health-love-resilience</link><title>Viola Davis on Health, Love, and Resilience</title><description>The actress reflects on her latest role (in "Won't Back Down"), the importance of self care, and the joys of becoming a mom later...time to be creative or to focus on myself. But I'm also more...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7083-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7083_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:46:06">http://www.webmd.com/diet/features/9-ways-to-take-your-diet-on-vacation</link><title>9 Ways to Take Your Diet on Vacation</title><description>Expert tips for choosing healthy restaurant foods and enjoying your vacation without blowing your...take a trip, does your diet go on vacation, too? Many people use vacations as...enjoy it later...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7083-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7083_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:47:30">http://blogs.webmd.com/tanzania-travel/2006/05/wednesdaythursday-montezumas-revenge-strikes-again.html</link><title>Wednesday/Thursday: Montezuma’s Revenge Strikes Again « Tanzania Travels</title><description>I noticed on Wednesday night during my return from Arusha to Dar Es Salaam that...at least Tanzania, is no place to have this problem on the road. The ‘toilets’ especially outside of Dar Es Salaam...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7083-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7083_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:48:15">http://blogs.webmd.com/tasty-easy-healthy/2010/11/getting-back-on-track-after-turkey-day.html</link><title>Getting Back On Track After Turkey Day… « Tasty. Easy. Healthy.</title><description>...Thanksgiving we end up eating out (or on the road, or in an airport) because we are...day marathon of food on Thursday. Friday, again, there are the leftovers, which usually include...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7083-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7083_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:48:55">http://www.webmd.com/women/features/kyra-sedgwick-work-family-empty-nests</link><title>Kyra Sedgwick on Work, Family, and Empty Nests</title><description>The actress opens up about her long marriage, life as a working mom, and her new movie, 'The...Kyra Sedgwick has to jump on another phone. It's her husband calling...band with brother Michael; they...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7083-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7083_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:51:08">http://www.webmd.com/health-insurance/mn/20131017/minn-reports-3700-enrollments-underway-but-a-rocky-road-for-consumers</link><title>In Minn., 3,700 Obamacare Applications Under Way</title><description>Minn. Reports 3,700 Enrollments Underway, But A Rocky Road For Consumers...first public glimpse into how many Minnesotans have not only created accounts on the new health insurance site, but also...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7083-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7083_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:56:13">http://www.webmd.com/fitness-exercise/how-to-stay-active</link><title>Fitness: Making It a Habit</title><description>It’s one thing to start an exercise or activity program. It’s quite another to turn it into a habit so that you're staying active...you can use to get yourself back on track and stay there. If you...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7083-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7083_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:58:38">http://www.webmd.com/parenting/baby/bottle-feeding-9/bottle-to-cup</link><title>Weaning Baby From Bottle to Cup</title><description>Ready to wean your baby from a bottle to a cup? Here’s how to make the transition easier on everyone...it? To help you wean your baby, we asked pediatricians and parents on WebMD’s parenting message...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>