<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7128">where to donate clothes in nyc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:40:22" name="WebMD" id="FW14-e076"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e076-7128-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7128_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:40:23">http://www.webmd.com/beauty/style/are-you-in-a-style-rut</link><title>Are You in a Style Rut?</title><description>WebMD talks to style experts about how to revive your style and why a style rut is sometimes about more than just your clothes...in your life, you are merely going through the motions? There are...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7128-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7128_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:44:13">http://blogs.webmd.com/all-ears/2008/02/the-generosity-of-people.html</link><title>The Generosity of People « Family Webicine</title><description>...processing, a venture that helps to support the orphanage. They said that clothes are needed, so this became our mission for this year. We are...big, plastic garbage cans in our lobby and asked our...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7128-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7128_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:44:40">http://blogs.webmd.com/pet-tales/2011/12/new-years-resolutions-for-pets-and-pet-lovers.html</link><title>New Year’s Resolutions for Pets and Pet Lovers « Tales from the Pet Clinic</title><description>...in an eco-friendly pet bed Empty plastic water bottles and old clothes contribute to landfill accumulation at a rapid pace. We all know we should have reusable water bottles and should donate our...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7128-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7128_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:45:38">http://www.webmd.com/beauty/hair-styling/9-ways-your-hair-is-aging-you</link><title>9 Ways Your Hair Is Aging You</title><description>Try these 9 tips for turning your damaged, old hairstyle into a fresh, new look...time for a new look," says Nick Arrojo, owner of Arrojo Studio, NYC. "You're not wearing the same clothes — why have...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7128-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7128_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:47:26">http://blogs.webmd.com/pet-tales/2011/07/national-pet-fire-safety-day.html</link><title>National Pet Fire Safety Day « Tales from the Pet Clinic</title><description>...buildings and rescued by New York’s bravest, our friends at the NYC Fire Department. As a pet lover, you can take action to prevent...shaped to fit a pet’s nose. If you are feeling philanthropic,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7128-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7128_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:50:27">http://blogs.webmd.com/health-ehome/2010/08/budget-friendly-back-to-school-wardrobe-guide.html</link><title>Budget-Friendly Back-to-School Wardrobe Guide « Healthy Begins Here</title><description>...hitting thrift stores and the internet to find things like backpacks and clothes. The absolute best way to cut costs and protect the planet is...For every swap on thredUP throughout the month of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7128-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7128_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:54:56">http://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/features/clutter-control</link><title>Clutter Control: Is Too Much 'Stuff' Draining You?</title><description>Get your clutter under control, and your attitude and health just may improve, too...When something comes in, something must go out. If you buy new clothes, part with some old ones. Ewer did that to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7128-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7128_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:56:59">http://www.webmd.com/women/features/live-well-on-less</link><title>Live Well On Less</title><description>Just because the economy looks bleak doesn't mean you have to deprive yourself and your family...swaps with my friends and relatives where we exchange unused or unwanted clothes," says Kathy Ryan,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7128-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7128_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:00:21">http://www.webmd.com/mental-health/news/20050907/americans-feel-katrinas-emotional-toll</link><title>Americans Feel Katrina's Emotional Toll</title><description>Horrible images and stories following the devastation of Hurricane Katrina have left many Americans...Kaslow. "If you don't have money, you can volunteer, you can donate clothes. Many people are...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7128-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7128_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:04:12">http://www.webmd.com/news/20050831/what-you-can-do-to-help-katrinas-survivors</link><title>What You Can Do to Help Katrina's Survivors</title><description>Hurricane Katrina and the floods and destruction that followed have sparked concern far and wide...is how you can help. You may have canned goods, toiletries, and clothes to spare, but don't overlook...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>