<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7146">why do leaves fall</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:11:27" name="WebMD" id="FW14-e076"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e076-7146-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7146_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:11:28">http://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/hip-injuries-age-11-and-younger-prevention</link><title>Hip Injuries,Age 11 and Younger - Prevention</title><description>The following tips may prevent the chance of hip injuries. Always be gentle with your child. Do not grab your child by his or her...of hip injuries. Always be gentle with your child. Do not grab your...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7146-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7146_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:14:36">http://blogs.webmd.com/anxiety-and-stress-management/2006/02/do-we-need-more-diet-books.html</link><title>Do We Need More Diet Books? « Anxiety and Stress Management</title><description>...anddid its job beautifully and didn’t leave you feeling either hungry or wanting to...then everything else in life would just fall into place. Wrong. Diets are distractions and making people...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7146-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7146_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:16:08">http://blogs.webmd.com/health-ehome/2009/09/7-fall-time-tips-for-a-fabulous-organic-lawn.html</link><title>7 Fall Time Tips for a Fabulous Organic Lawn « Healthy Begins Here</title><description>...fabulous non-toxic and organic lawn this Fall season (of course, different regions and different...open to dehydration and disease. Rake your leaves. Excessive leaf cover can kill the grass...the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7146-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7146_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:19:22">http://www.webmd.com/multiple-sclerosis/video/ms-things-you-can-do</link><title>MS Things You Can Do</title><description>Healthy lifestyle choices can help you manage your MS.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7146-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7146_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:23:25">http://blogs.webmd.com/pet-tales/2012/10/dog-strollers-a-do-or-a-dont.html</link><title>Dog Strollers: A Do or a Don’t? « Tales from the Pet Clinic</title><description>...One of my most favorite things to do here in New York City is to...A Sunday afternoon walk to see the leaves changing color sounds just right for a fall afternoon, but halfway through the walk,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7146-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7146_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:23:59">http://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/preventing-falls-in-the-hospital-topic-overview</link><title>Preventing Falls in the Hospital - Topic Overview</title><description>During a hospital stay, you may have a higher-than-normal risk of falling. You might get medicines that make you dizzy and more...make you dizzy and more likely to fall. You may get weak and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7146-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7146_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:27:04">http://blogs.webmd.com/sleep-disorders/2011/08/do-your-kids-text-while-theyre-asleep.html</link><title>Do Your Kids Text While They’re Asleep? « Sleep Well</title><description>...puberty make it harder for teens to fall asleep and stay asleep. Their lifestyles—increasing...at odds with this biological tendency, which leaves teens at risk for sleep deprivation. Lack...media...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7146-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7146_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:29:33">http://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/getting-help-around-the-house-topic-overview</link><title>Getting Help Around the House - Topic Overview</title><description>If pain is starting to get you down,let people know when you need a helping hand. Get family members or friends to help out with...it to "pay" a friend to do some housecleaning or yard work for you...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7146-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7146_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:30:56">http://www.webmd.com/allergies/mold-allergy</link><title>Mold Allergy</title><description>Do your allergy symptoms last all year? You may be fighting a mold allergy. Here's how to treat it...have a mold allergy, he'll probably do allergy testing to confirm it. When Mold Allergies Happen...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7146-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7146_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:32:26">http://www.webmd.com/stroke/tc/stroke-rehabilitation-overview</link><title>Stroke Rehabilitation - Overview</title><description>...of health professionals works with you to regain skills you lost as the result of a stroke. Rehab can help you to: Do as well and...a stroke. Rehab can help you to: Do as well as you can and be..</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>