<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7180">blink reflex</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:39:42" name="WebMD" id="FW14-e076"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e076-7180-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7180_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:39:43">http://www.webmd.com/baby/pregnancy-your-babys-growth-development-months-7-to-9</link><title>Your Baby's Growth and Development In the Third Trimester of Pregnancy</title><description>Find out from WebMD how your baby continues developing in the third trimester of pregnancy...to grow and mature. His or her lungs are nearly fully developed. Your baby's reflexes are coordinated so he...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7180-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7180_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:43:37">http://blogs.webmd.com/eye-on-vision/2006/04/rapid-recovery-predicted-for-teri-hatcher.html</link><title>Rapid Recovery Predicted for Teri Hatcher « Eye On Vision</title><description>...in her clear cornea . She has been successfully treated and will soon be able to resume work. The eye has remarkable protective properties. The blink reflex is faster than a deploying airbag...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7180-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7180_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:47:01">http://www.webmd.com/eye-health/tc/eye-injuries-caused-by-ultraviolet-uv-light-topic-overview</link><title>Eye Injuries Caused by Ultraviolet (UV) Light - Topic Overview</title><description>Eye injuries from ultraviolet (UV) light can be serious. Injuries include exposure to: High-intensity light from welding equipment...usually don't involve the eyeball because the blink reflex protects...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7180-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7180_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:49:15">http://www.webmd.com/eye-health/tc/eye-problems-noninjury-prevention</link><title>Eye Problems,Noninjury - Prevention</title><description>Take good care of your eyes to prevent eye problems. Injuries from ultraviolet (UV) light can be...video games, or frequent computer use can decrease your child's natural blink reflex, which can cause...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7180-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7180_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:49:45">http://blogs.webmd.com/eye-on-vision/2008/11/permanently-pain-free-feel-good-to-you.html</link><title>Permanently Pain-Free…Feel Good to You? « Eye On Vision</title><description>...the epithelial cells and are immediately exposed following any trauma to those outer protective cells. These same nerves activate the instantaneous blink reflex whenever anything approaches our...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7180-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7180_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:52:22">http://blogs.webmd.com/eye-on-vision/2006/07/botox-for-therapeutic-lid-paralysis.html</link><title>BOTOX for Therapeutic Lid Paralysis « Eye On Vision</title><description>...the muscles that close the eyelids (orbicularis oculi). Most cases are temporary. When Bell’s Palsy occurs the eyeball is threatened because the blink reflex is lost along with voluntary lid closure.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7180-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7180_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:53:06">http://www.webmd.com/baby/guide/your-pregnancy-week-by-week-weeks-35-40</link><title>Your Pregnancy Week by Week: Weeks 35-40</title><description>Your Pregnancy Week by Week: Weeks 35-40...stomach can cause nausea. Your baby continues to grow and mature. The lungs are nearly fully developed. Your baby's reflexes are coordinated so he or she can...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7180-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7180_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:54:22">http://www.webmd.com/eye-health/understanding-astigmatism-treatment</link><title>Understanding Astigmatism -- Diagnosis &amp; Treatment</title><description>Get the basics on the diagnosis and treatment of astigmatism from WebMD...used to measure your prescription. Sometimes, the doctor looks at the light reflex from your eye through a handheld device...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>