<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7216">salmonella</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:06:52" name="WebMD" id="FW14-e076"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e076-7216-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7216_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:06:53">http://www.webmd.com/food-recipes/food-poisoning/news/20120820/deaths-in-salmonella-outbreak-traced-to-cantaloupe</link><title>Deaths in Salmonella Outbreak Traced to Cantaloupe</title><description>Kentucky health officials say two people have died in a 20-state salmonella outbreak that has sickened 141 people. The outbreak...from Kentucky have died in an ongoing 20-state salmonella outbreak...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7216-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7216_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:07:45">http://www.webmd.com/fda/fda-acts-to-reduce-the-risk-of-salmonella-infection</link><title>FDA Acts to Reduce the Risk of Salmonella Infection</title><description>Find out how the FDA is trying to reduce the risk of salmonella infection by enforcing a ban on...turtles designed to protect the public from the disease-causing bacteria Salmonella. Turtles often...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7216-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7216_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:09:48">http://www.webmd.com/food-recipes/food-poisoning/news/20131008/salmonella-outbreak-chicken</link><title>Salmonella Outbreak Traced to Chicken</title><description>Salmonella Outbreak Traced to Chicken From California Plants...chicken packaged at three Foster Farms facilities in California has been identified as the cause of a salmonella outbreak that has sickened...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7216-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7216_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:11:32">http://www.webmd.com/fda/pet-turtles-cute-but-contaminated-with-salmonella</link><title>Pet Turtles: Cute But Contaminated With Salmonella</title><description>FDA warns about the risk of illness from pet turtles...look cute and harmless, but small turtles can make people very ill. Turtles commonly carry bacteria called Salmonella on their outer skin and shell...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7216-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7216_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:14:55">http://www.webmd.com/food-recipes/food-poisoning/ss/slideshow-salmonella</link><title>Slideshow: Salmonella Infection Causes, Symptoms, Treatment, and Prevention</title><description>See what salmonella bacteria look like and learn more about the causes, symptoms, and treatments of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7216-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7216_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:17:28">http://www.webmd.com/food-recipes/food-poisoning/salmonella-directory</link><title>Salmonella</title><description>Salmonella bacteria can be transmitted by contaminated foods or by animals. Follow the links below to find WebMD's comprehensive...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7216-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7216_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:20:20">http://www.webmd.com/food-recipes/food-poisoning/news/20130809/salmonella-outbreak-sickens-307-in-37-states</link><title>Salmonella Outbreak Sickens 307 in 37 States</title><description>CDC says infections are linked to baby poultry from multiple hatcheries...More than 300 people in 37 states have been sickened to date in a major multistate outbreak of salmonella infection linked to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7216-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7216_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:21:13">http://blogs.webmd.com/pet-tales/2012/05/salmonella-in-pets-and-humans.html</link><title>Salmonella in Pets and Humans « Tales from the Pet Clinic</title><description>...dog food. Since the initial recall, several other brands of food manufactured in a South Carolina plant have been voluntarily recalled for possible Salmonella contamination. Voluntary recalls of pet...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7216-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7216_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:24:03">http://blogs.webmd.com/breaking-news/2012/04/sushi-suspected-as-salmonella-sickens-93-in-19-states.html</link><title>Sushi Suspected as Salmonella Sickens 93 in 19 States « WebMD Newsroom</title><description>by Daniel J. DeNoon Sushi is suspected but not confirmed as the source of a salmonella food-poisoning outbreak that so far has sickened 93 people in 19 states and the District of Columbia. Ten people...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7216-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7216_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:26:01">http://blogs.webmd.com/child-health-411/2010/08/eggs-salmonella-and-food-poisoning-oh-my.html</link><title>Eggs, Salmonella, and Food Poisoning, Oh My! « Child Health 411</title><description>...iStockphoto Eggs have been making the news lately with three major nationwide recalls due to potential contamination with the bacteria, salmonella . The recalls involve eggs from Wright County and...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>