<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7452">arizona game and fish homepage</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:12:56" name="WebMD" id="FW14-e076"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e076-7452-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7452_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:12:57">http://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/coping-with-memory-loss</link><title>Coping with Memory Loss</title><description>A look at various causes of memory loss and treatment approaches...in saturated fat and cholesterol and eating fish with beneficial omega-3 fatty acids, such...reading, writing, learning a new skill,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7452-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7452_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:13:54">http://www.webmd.com/diet/features/healthy-living-in-the-real-world</link><title>Healthy Living in the Real World</title><description>Quick and easy guidelines for healthy living in the real world...Proteins Foods rich in omega-3 fats (fish, wild game) Lean meats Plant-based proteins (tofu, beans...professor of medicine at the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7452-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7452_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:15:08">http://www.webmd.com/men/features/diet-plans-men</link><title>The Manly Art of Healthy Eating</title><description>Just for men: Foods that can make a difference in the way you feel...most men score dangerously low in the game of healthy eating, experts say. The foods...found in foods such as cold-water fish,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7452-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7452_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:15:42">http://blogs.webmd.com/food-and-nutrition/2011/10/football-food.html</link><title>Football Food – Don’t Let Game Day Throw Off Your Game « Real Life Nutrition</title><description>...Brett Favre’s text message history (zing!). So let’s healthy-up game day, starting with tailgating in the stadium parking lot. Grills rock, so...advantage. Think outside the typical hot dog and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7452-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7452_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:16:59">http://blogs.webmd.com/food-and-nutrition/2012/07/the-hunger-game.html</link><title>The Hunger Game « Real Life Nutrition</title><description>...70% of the protein in the American diet comes from animal and fish sources. Studies show a high-protein meal can increase satiety for people...released after their digestion. Soy: Lean animal...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7452-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7452_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:18:36">http://www.webmd.com/diet/features/take-me-out-to-the-ballgame</link><title>Take Me Out to the Ball Game!</title><description>Rooting for the home team doesn't have to mean running afoul of your diet...Take me out to the ball game ... and it's one, two, three strikes, your eating healthy plan is...Most popular food items: The...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7452-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7452_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:20:16">http://www.webmd.com/diet/features/mind-games</link><title>Mind Games</title><description>...sticking to a weight loss program day after day can be tough. Weight loss is really a mind game. When you think about it you can...day can be tough. Weight loss is really a mind game. When you...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7452-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7452_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:21:31">http://blogs.webmd.com/breaking-news/2011/01/tragedy-in-arizona-a-personal-call-to-action.html</link><title>Tragedy in Arizona: A Personal Call to Action « WebMD Newsroom</title><description>...shopping on Saturday mornings. But this day, she had a kids’ soccer game just a short distance away. We have often gone out of our...SWAT for eight years and serves on the board of the Southern...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7452-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7452_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:22:55">http://www.webmd.com/fda/start-store-7-ways-prevent-foodborne-illness</link><title>Start at the Store: 7 Ways to Prevent Foodborne Illness</title><description>Food safety for consumers should begin at the supermarket or grocery store. Here are useful hints to...or thawed and refrozen. In such cases, choose another package. Meat, poultry, fish and eggs...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e076-7452-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e076/7452_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:24:11">http://www.webmd.com/baby/guide/top-7-pregnancy-myths</link><title>Pregnancy Myths, Dos, and Don'ts</title><description>WebMD gives the facts about what you should and shouldn't do while pregnant...In March 2004, the FDA and EPA issued joint guidelines regarding eating fish during pregnancy. They advise women who are...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>