<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7002">exhaled NO IBS papers</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:33:57" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7002-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7002_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:34:06">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:313107</link><title>Clinical Utility of Exhaled Nitric Oxide</title><description>Petsky, Helen (2013). Clinical Utility of Exhaled Nitric Oxide PhD Thesis, School of Medicine, The University of Queensland.

 0.58

26

5</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7002-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7002_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:34:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:161749</link><title>Stratiform and Strata-Bound Zn-Pb-Ag Deposits in Proterozoic Sedimentary Basins, Northern Australia</title><description>Large, Ross R., Bull, Stuart W., McGoldrick, Peter J., Walters, Steve, Derrick, Geoff M. and Carr, Graham R. (2005). Stratiform and Strata-Bound Zn-Pb-Ag Deposits in Proterozoic Sedimentary Basins, Northern Australia. In Jeffrey W. Hedenquist, John F. H. Thompson, Richard J. Goldfarb and Jeremy P. Richards (Ed.), Economic geology : One hundredth anniversary volume : 1905-2005 (pp. 931-963) Littleton, CO, United States: Society of Economic Geologists.

 0.29

214</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7002-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7002_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:34:53">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:155618</link><title>Paediatric Chronic Cough: Defining illness burden and causes</title><description>Dr Julie Marchant (2008). Paediatric Chronic Cough: Defining illness burden and causes PhD Thesis, School of Medicine, The University of Queensland.

 0.25

318

14</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7002-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7002_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:35:25">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:218965</link><title>Chronic suppurative lung disease and bronchiectasis in children and adults in Australia and New Zealand</title><description>Chang, AB, Bell, SC, Byrnes, CA, Grimwood, K, Holmes, PW, King, PT, Kolbe, J, Landau, LI, Maguire, GP, McDonald, MI, Reid, DW, Thien, FC and Torzillo, PJ (2010) Chronic suppurative lung disease and bronchiectasis in children and adults in Australia and New Zealand. Medical Journal of Australia, 193 6: 356-365.

 0.24

112

11

27

Cited 32 times in Scopus32</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7002-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7002_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:35:51">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:12815</link><title>Two times three little pigs: Dysfluency, cognitive complexity and autism</title><description>Stirling, Lesley, Barrington, Graham and Douglas, Susan (2007). Two times three little pigs: Dysfluency, cognitive complexity and autism. In: Ilana Mushin and Mary Laughren Annual Meeting of the Australian Linguistic Society, Brisbane, Australia, (). 7-9 July 2006.

 0.23

920

969</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7002-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7002_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:36:18">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:294280</link><title>Burning prophecies: the scholastic tradition of comet interpretation as found in the works of the Venerable Bede</title><description>Hudepohl, Jessica (2012). Burning prophecies: the scholastic tradition of comet interpretation as found in the works of the Venerable Bede. In: Marcus K. Harmes, Lindsay Henderson, Barbara Harmes and Amy Antonio, The British World: Religion, Memory, Society, Culture: Proceedings of the Conference. The British World: Religion, Memory, Society, Culture, Toowoomba, Qld, Australia, (1-13). 2 - 5 July 2012.

 0.21

64

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7002-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7002_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:36:43">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:267427</link><title>A geochemical and stable isotope study of the Panguna porphyry copper deposit, Bougainville</title><description>Ford, Jeffrey Harold. (1977). A geochemical and stable isotope study of the Panguna porphyry copper deposit, Bougainville PhD Thesis, School of Physical Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.19

162

11</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7002-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7002_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:37:10">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:272123</link><title>The Coping with Caring Program: a self-directed, evidence-based correspondence intervention for carers of older people with dementia</title><description>Zoe L. Barnett (). The Coping with Caring Program: a self-directed, evidence-based correspondence intervention for carers of older people with dementia Professional Doctorate, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.19

94

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7002-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7002_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:37:38">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:253415</link><title>The hormonal influences on asthma in women</title><description>Rice-McDonald, Glenn Gordon (2004). The hormonal influences on asthma in women PhD Thesis, School of Medicine, The University of Queensland.

 0.19

246

5</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7002-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7002_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:38:06">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:277278</link><title>Energy expenditure, physical activity and body composition of children with cerebral palsy</title><description>Kristie L. Bell (2005). Energy expenditure, physical activity and body composition of children with cerebral palsy PhD Thesis, School of Medicine, The University of Queensland.

 0.18

115

4</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>