<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7003">Male circumcision</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:38:27" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7003-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7003_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:38:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:142182</link><title>Circumcision of healthy boys: criminal assault?</title><description>Boyle, G. J., Svoboda, J., Price, C. and Turner, J. N. (2000) Circumcision of healthy boys: criminal assault?. Journal of Law and Medicine, 7 February: 301-310.

 1.06

68</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7003-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7003_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:38:57">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:282911</link><title>Circumcision in Australia: further evidence on its effects on sexual health and wellbeing</title><description>Ferris, Jason A., Richters, Juliet, Pitts, Marian K., Shelley, Julia M., Simpson, Judy M., Ryall, Richard and Smith, Anthony M. A. (2010) Circumcision in Australia: further evidence on its effects on sexual health and wellbeing. Australian and New Zealand Journal of Public Health, 34 2: 160-164.

 1.04

40

8

Cited 8 times in Scopus8

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7003-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7003_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:39:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:289150</link><title>Why women object to male circumcision to prevent HIV in a moderate-prevalence setting</title><description>Kelly, Angela, Kupul, Martha, Aeno, Herick, Shih, Patti, Naketrumb, Richard, Neo, James, Fitzgerald, Lisa, Kaldor, John M., Siba, Peter M. and Vallely, Andrew (2013) Why women object to male circumcision to prevent HIV in a moderate-prevalence setting. Qualitative Health Research, 23 2: 180-193.

 1.01

29

5

Cited 5 times in Scopus5

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7003-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7003_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:39:49">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:272436</link><title>"Now we are in a different time; various bad diseases have come." Understanding men's acceptability of male circumcision for HIV prevention in a moderate prevalence setting</title><description>Kelly, Angela, Kupul,Martha, Fitzgerald, Lisa, Aeno, Herick, Neo, James, Naketrumb, Richard, Siba, Peter, Kaldor, John M., Vallely, Andrew and Male Circumcision Acceptability and Impact Study (2012) "Now we are in a different time; various bad diseases have come." Understanding men's acceptability of male circumcision for HIV prevention in a moderate prevalence setting. Bmc Public Health, 12 1: 67-1-67-13.

 0.97

40

7

Cited 8 times in Scopus8

5</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7003-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7003_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:40:16">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:2389</link><title>Exorcising Excision: Medico-Legal Issues Arising from Male and Female Genital Surgery in Australia</title><description>Christine Mason (2001) Exorcising Excision: Medico-Legal Issues Arising from Male and Female Genital Surgery in Australia. Journal of Law and Medicine, 9 1: 58-67.

 0.83

138

813</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7003-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7003_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:40:43">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:285225</link><title>Vasectomy as a proxy: extrapolating health system lessons to male circumcision as an HIV prevention strategy in Papua New Guinea</title><description>Tynan, Anna, Vallely, Andrew, Kelly, Angela, Law, Greg, Millan, John, Siba, Peter, Kaldor, John and Hill, Peter S. (2012) Vasectomy as a proxy: extrapolating health system lessons to male circumcision as an HIV prevention strategy in Papua New Guinea. BMC Health Services Research, 12 1: 299.1-299.12.

 0.82

43

2

Cited 3 times in Scopus3

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7003-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7003_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:41:13">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:328425</link><title>Health workers, health facilities and penile cutting in Papua New Guinea: implications for male circumcision as an HIV prevention strategy</title><description>Tynan, A., Vallely, A., Kelly, A., Kupul, M., Law, G., Millan, J., Siba, P., Kaldor, J. and Hill, P. S. (2011) Health workers, health facilities and penile cutting in Papua New Guinea: implications for male circumcision as an HIV prevention strategy. Papua New Guinea Medical Journal, 54 3-4: 109-122.

 0.81

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7003-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7003_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:41:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:309365</link><title>Listening to diverse community voices: the tensions of responding to community expectations in developing a male circumcision program for HIV prevention in Papua New Guinea</title><description>Tynan, Anna, Hill, Peter S., Kelly, Angela, Kupul, Martha, Aeno, Herick, Naketrumb, Richard, Siba, Peter, Kaldor, John and Vallely, Andrew (2013) Listening to diverse community voices: the tensions of responding to community expectations in developing a male circumcision program for HIV prevention in Papua New Guinea. BMC Public Health, 13 749: 749.1-749.18.

 0.77

22

0

Cited 0 times in Scopus0

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7003-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7003_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:41:53">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:298609</link><title>Sociocultural and individual determinants for motivation of sexual and reproductive health workers in Papua New Guinea and their implications for male circumcision as an HIV prevention strategy</title><description>Tynan, Anna, Vallely, Andrew, Kelly, Angela, Kupul, Martha, Neo, James, Naketrumb, Richard, Aeno, Herick, Law, Greg, Milan, John, Siba, Peter, Kaldor, John and Hill, Peter S. (2013) Sociocultural and individual determinants for motivation of sexual and reproductive health workers in Papua New Guinea and their implications for male circumcision as an HIV prevention strategy. Human Resources for Health, 11 7: .

 0.72

20

1

Cited 2 times in Scopus2

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7003-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7003_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:42:15">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:247329</link><title>A typology of penile cutting in Papua New Guinea: results of a modified Delphi study among sexual health specialists</title><description>Hill, Peter S., Tynan, Anna, Law,Greg, Millan, John, Browne, Kelwyn, Sauk, Joyce, Kupul, Martha, Kelly, Angela, Siba, Peter, Kaldor, John and Vallely, Andrew (2012) A typology of penile cutting in Papua New Guinea: results of a modified Delphi study among sexual health specialists. AIDS Care, 24 1: 77-86.

 0.69

55

5

Cited 4 times in Scopus4

1</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>