<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7020">synovial joint</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:26:59" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7020-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7020_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:27:02">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:145296</link><title>The synovial response to exogenous phospholipid (synovial surfactant) injected into the equine radiocarpal joint compared with that to prilocaine, hyaluronan and propylene glycol</title><description>Ethell, M. T., Hodgson, D. R. and Hills, B. A. (1999) The synovial response to exogenous phospholipid (synovial surfactant) injected into the equine radiocarpal joint compared with that to prilocaine, hyaluronan and propylene glycol. New Zealand Veterinary Journal, 47 4: 128-132.

 1.26

120

3

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7020-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7020_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:31:42">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:161244</link><title>Synovial osteochondromatosis</title><description>Langguth, D. M., Klestov, A. and Denaro, C. (2002) Synovial osteochondromatosis. Internal Medicine Journal, 32 8: 419-420.

 1.16

110

1

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7020-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7020_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:33:25">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:235914</link><title>Lysosomal enzymes in inflammatory synovial effusions</title><description>Hadler, N. M., Spitznagel, J. K. and Quinet, R. J. (1979) Lysosomal enzymes in inflammatory synovial effusions. Journal of Immunology, 123 2: 572-577.

 1.16

16

49</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7020-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7020_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:35:56">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:228410</link><title>Effect of palosein (superoxide dismutase) and catalase upon oxygen derived free radical induced degradation of equine synovial fluid</title><description>Auer, D. E., Ng, J. C. and Seawright, A. A. (1990) Effect of palosein (superoxide dismutase) and catalase upon oxygen derived free radical induced degradation of equine synovial fluid. Equine Veterinary Journal, 22 1: 13-17.

 1.08

31

13

Cited 9 times in Scopus9</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7020-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7020_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:39:04">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:8824</link><title>Binding of Haptoglobin, Inter-trypsin Inhibitor, and Proteinase Inhibitor to Synovial Fluid Hyaluronate and the Influence of These Proteins on its Degradation by Oxygen Derived Free Radicals</title><description>Hutadilok, N., Ghosh, P. and Brooks, P. M. (1988) Binding of Haptoglobin, Inter-trypsin Inhibitor, and Proteinase Inhibitor to Synovial Fluid Hyaluronate and the Influence of These Proteins on its Degradation by Oxygen Derived Free Radicals. Annals of the Rheumatic Diseases, 47 5: 377-385.

 1.02

198

152

57

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7020-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7020_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:41:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:59118</link><title>Association of clinical, radiological and synovial immunopathological responses to anti-rheumatic treatment in rheumatoid arthritis</title><description>Pettit, AR, Weedon, H, Ahern, M, Zehntner, S, Frazer, IH, Slavotinek, J, Au, V, Smith, MD and Thomas, R (2001) Association of clinical, radiological and synovial immunopathological responses to anti-rheumatic treatment in rheumatoid arthritis. Rheumatology, 40 11: 1243-1255.

 1.00

48

15

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7020-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7020_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:45:32">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:233397</link><title>Histamine levels in human synovial fluid</title><description>Frewin, D. B., Cleland, L. G., Jonsson, J. R. and Robertson, P. W. (1986) Histamine levels in human synovial fluid. Journal of Rheumatology, 13 1: 13-14.

 0.97

31

51

Cited 39 times in Scopus39</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7020-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7020_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:47:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:77838</link><title>Penetration of a topically applied nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drug into local tissues and synovial fluid of dogs</title><description>Mills, Paul C., Magnusson, Beatrice M. and Cross, Sheree E. (2005) Penetration of a topically applied nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drug into local tissues and synovial fluid of dogs. American Journal of Veterinary Research, 66 7: 1128-1132.

 0.96

86

235

4

Cited 4 times in Scopus4

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7020-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7020_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:49:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:69732</link><title>Detection of surfactant protein A (SP-A) and surfactant protein D (SP-D) in equine synovial fluid with immunoblotting</title><description>Kankavi, O and Roberts, MS (2004) Detection of surfactant protein A (SP-A) and surfactant protein D (SP-D) in equine synovial fluid with immunoblotting. Canadian Journal of Veterinary Research-revue Canadienne De Recherche Veterinaire, 68 2: 146-149.

 0.91

57

8

Cited 10 times in Scopus10</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7020-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7020_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:51:39">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:235913</link><title>Protease inhibitors in inflammatory synovial effusions</title><description>Hadler, N. M., Johnson, A. M., Spitznagel, J. K. and Quinet, R. J. (1981) Protease inhibitors in inflammatory synovial effusions. Annals of the Rheumatic Diseases, 40 1: 55-59.

 0.89

28

40

Cited 6 times in Scopus6

0</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>