<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7024">reinforcement learning</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:47:53" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7024-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7024_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:47:58">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:184619</link><title>Deutero-learning: Implications for managing public health change</title><description>Rowe, P. A. and Boyce, R. A. (2009) Deutero-learning: Implications for managing public health change. The Learning Organization, 16 4: 298-310.

 0.83

42

Cited 1 times in Scopus1

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7024-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7024_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:50:16">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:222551</link><title>Optimal local basis: A reinforcement learning approach for face recognition</title><description>Harandi, Mehrtash T., Ahmadabadi, Majid Nili and Araabi, Babak N. (2009) Optimal local basis: A reinforcement learning approach for face recognition. International Journal of Computer Vision (IJCV), 81 2: 191-204.

 0.82

56

11

Cited 17 times in Scopus17

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7024-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7024_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:53:04">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:259965</link><title>Reinforcement learning in first person shooter games</title><description>McPartland, Michelle and Gallagher, Marcus (2011) Reinforcement learning in first person shooter games. Ieee Transactions On Computational Intelligence and Ai in Games, 3 1: 43-56.

 0.81

32

3

Cited 12 times in Scopus12

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7024-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7024_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:53:46">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:176787</link><title>Creating a multi-purpose first person shooter bot with reinforcement learning</title><description>McPartland, M. and Gallagher, M. (2008). Creating a multi-purpose first person shooter bot with reinforcement learning. In: P. Hingston and L. Barone, Computational Intelligence and Games 2008. IEEE Symposium on Computational Intelligence and Games 2008 (CIG '08), Perth, Australia, (143-150). 15-18 December 2008.

 0.81

316

1

Cited 3 times in Scopus3

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7024-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7024_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:55:05">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:72410</link><title>System for foreign exchange trading using genetic algorithms and reinforcement learning</title><description>Hryshko, A. and Downs, T. (2004) System for foreign exchange trading using genetic algorithms and reinforcement learning. International Journal of Systems Science, 35 13-14: 763-775.

 0.79

164

2

Cited 3 times in Scopus3

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7024-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7024_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:59:31">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:176782</link><title>Learning to be a Bot: Reinforcement learning in shooter games</title><description>McPartland, M. and Gallagher, M. (2008). Learning to be a Bot: Reinforcement learning in shooter games. In: Darken, C. and Mateas, M., Proceedings, the Fourth Artificial Intelligence and interactive Digital Entertainment Conference. 4th Artifical Intelligence for Interactive Digital Entertainment Conference, Stanford, California, (78-83). 22-24 October, 2008.

 0.77

90

Cited 4 times in Scopus4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7024-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7024_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:03:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:100841</link><title>A system for electricity trading using genetic algorithm and reinforcement learning</title><description>Hryshko, A. and Downs, T. (2004). A system for electricity trading using genetic algorithm and reinforcement learning. In: G. Walker, Proceedings of the Australasian Universities Power Engineering Conference 2004. The Australasian Universities Power Engineering Conference 2004, Brisbane, (1-7). 26-29 September, 2004.

 0.75

174</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7024-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7024_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:05:14">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:128466</link><title>Distinguishing between learning and motivation in behavioral tests of the reinforcement sensitivity theory of personality</title><description>Smillie, LD, Dalgleish, LI and Jackson, CJ (2007) Distinguishing between learning and motivation in behavioral tests of the reinforcement sensitivity theory of personality. Personality And Social Psychology Bulletin, 33 4: 476-489.

 0.70

12

21

Cited 22 times in Scopus22

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7024-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7024_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:07:07">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:272813</link><title>Mean and variance responsive learning</title><description>Oyarzun, Carlos and Sarin, Rajiv (2012) Mean and variance responsive learning. Games and Economic Behavior, 75 2: 855-866.

 0.69

32

0

Cited 0 times in Scopus0

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7024-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7024_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:09:28">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:12911</link><title>Learning for fun: The unique contribution of educational leisure experiences</title><description>Packer, Jan (2007) Learning for fun: The unique contribution of educational leisure experiences. Curator: The Museum Journal, 49 3: 329-344.

 0.67

563

1808

2</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>