<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7031">Thomas test</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:26:15" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7031-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7031_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:26:20">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:247127</link><title>Acquiring multiple parameters from multiple tests: The real principle of multimodality imaging</title><description>Marwick, Thomas H. and Narula, Jagat (2011) Acquiring multiple parameters from multiple tests: The real principle of multimodality imaging. JACC: Cardiovascular Imaging, 4 6: 688-689.

 0.75

33

1

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7031-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7031_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:28:37">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:231711</link><title>A comparison of four serological tests for the detection of banana bunchy top virus in banana</title><description>Geering, A. D. W. and Thomas, J. E. (1996) A comparison of four serological tests for the detection of banana bunchy top virus in banana. Australian Journal of Agricultural Research, 47 3: 403-412.

 0.75

48

8

Cited 8 times in Scopus8

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7031-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7031_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:31:32">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:276991</link><title>Exercise testing in asymptomatic patients after revascularization: Are outcomes altered?</title><description>Harb, Serge C., Cook, Thomas, Jaber, Wael A. and Marwick, Thomas H. (2012) Exercise testing in asymptomatic patients after revascularization: Are outcomes altered?. Archives of Internal Medicine, 172 11: 854-861.

 0.75

26

10

Cited 13 times in Scopus13

10</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7031-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7031_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:32:40">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:247137</link><title>Environmental impact of cardiac imaging tests for the diagnosis of coronary artery disease</title><description>Marwick, Thomas H. and Buonocore, Jonathan (2011) Environmental impact of cardiac imaging tests for the diagnosis of coronary artery disease. Heart, 97 14: 1128-1131.

 0.73

37

3

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7031-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7031_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:35:08">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:324148</link><title>Pre-manipulative testing and the use of the velocimeter</title><description>Thomas L.C., Rivett D.A. and Bolton P.S. (2008) Pre-manipulative testing and the use of the velocimeter. Manual Therapy, 13 1: 29-36.

 0.72

5

Cited 4 times in Scopus4

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7031-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7031_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:36:35">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:309431</link><title>Recognition vocabulary knowledge as a predictor of academic performance in an English as a foreign language setting</title><description>Roche, Thomas and Harrington, Michael (2013) Recognition vocabulary knowledge as a predictor of academic performance in an English as a foreign language setting. Language Testing in Asia, 3 12: 1-13.

 0.71

43

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7031-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7031_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:40:47">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:104647</link><title>Large-scale column testing of hypersaline tailings</title><description>Williams, D J and Stolberg, D. J. (2006). Large-scale column testing of hypersaline tailings. In: H R Thomas, Fifth International Congress on Environmental Geotechnics. Fifth International Congress on Environmental Geotechnics, Wales, United Kingdom, (976-983). 26-30 June 2006.

 0.71

79</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7031-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7031_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:44:33">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:135835</link><title>Children’s understanding of the relation between delayed video representation and current reality: A test for self-awareness?</title><description>Suddendorf, Thomas (1999) Children’s understanding of the relation between delayed video representation and current reality: A test for self-awareness?. Journal of Experimental Child Psychology, 72 3: 157-176.

 0.69

80

41

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7031-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7031_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:47:21">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:95470</link><title>Application of stress echocardiography as a screening test for coronary disease in asymptomatic patients: Is it ever worthwhile?</title><description>Marwick, T. H., Case, C., Sawada, S., Vasey, C. and Thomas, J. E. (2001). Application of stress echocardiography as a screening test for coronary disease in asymptomatic patients: Is it ever worthwhile?. In: , European Heart Journal: Abstracts of the XXIII Congress of the European Society of Cardiology. XXIII Congress of the European Society of Cardiology, Stockholm, Sweden, (355-355). 1-5 September, 2001.

 0.69

63

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7031-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7031_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:49:29">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:77454</link><title>The integrity of the science base: A test case</title><description>Edwards, Griffith, West, Robert, Babor, Thomas F., Hall, Wayne and Marsden, John (2005) The integrity of the science base: A test case. Addiction, 100 5: 581-584.

 0.68

50

9

Cited 9 times in Scopus9

0</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>