<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7045">Natural Parks America</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:24:37" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7045-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7045_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:24:41">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:9531</link><title>Management objectives and economic value of national parks: Preservation, conservation and development</title><description>Suh, Jungho and Harrison, Steve (2005) Management objectives and economic value of national parks: Preservation, conservation and development. Discussion Paper No. 337, School of Economics, The University of Queensland.

 0.60

1275

695</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7045-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7045_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:28:28">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:225120</link><title>Laminitic pain: Parallels with pain states in humans and other species</title><description>Collins, SN, Pollitt, C, Wylie, CE and Matiasek, K (2010) Laminitic pain: Parallels with pain states in humans and other species. Veterinary Clinics of North America - Equine Practice, 26 3: 643-671.

 0.57

32

5

Cited 7 times in Scopus7

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7045-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7045_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:30:46">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:221484</link><title>Validating the use of expert opinion in management effectiveness assessments of protected areas in Australia</title><description>Carly Cook (2010). Validating the use of expert opinion in management effectiveness assessments of protected areas in Australia PhD Thesis, School of Integrative Systems, The University of Queensland.

 0.56

229

18</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7045-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7045_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:34:43">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:223614</link><title>Ascertaining the value of Noosa National Park: an application of the contingent valuation and travel cost methods</title><description>Blackwell, Boyd D. (1995). Ascertaining the value of Noosa National Park: an application of the contingent valuation and travel cost methods Honours Thesis, School of Economics, The University of Queensland.

 0.54

59</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7045-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7045_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:39:27">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:10061</link><title>Optimal Fire Management for Maintaining Community Diversity</title><description>Richards, Shane A., Possingham, Hugh P. and Tizard, James (1999) Optimal Fire Management for Maintaining Community Diversity. Ecological Applications, 9 3: 880-892.

 0.52

383

703

85

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7045-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7045_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:44:04">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:260151</link><title>The influence of mega events on city structure under contemporary urban governance: The example of Sydney's Olympic Games</title><description>Searle, Glen (2008). The influence of mega events on city structure under contemporary urban governance: The example of Sydney's Olympic Games. In Alana Hay and Richard Cashman (Ed.), Connecting cities: Mega event cities. A publication for the 9th World Congress of Metropolis (pp. 87-105) Sydney, NSW, Australia: Sydney Olympic Park Authority for Metropolis Congress 2008.

 0.52

93

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7045-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7045_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:48:00">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:241084</link><title>Analysis of protected area management effectiveness evaluation data and its application for increasing understanding of management</title><description>Josephine Kelman (2010). Analysis of protected area management effectiveness evaluation data and its application for increasing understanding of management PhD Thesis, School of Geography, Planning and Environmental Management, The University of Queensland.

 0.51

155

23</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7045-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7045_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:49:19">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:238026</link><title>Diverting places: Linking travel, pleasure and protection</title><description>Stolton, Sue, Dudley, Nigel and Kun, Zoltan (2010). Diverting places: Linking travel, pleasure and protection. In Sue Stolton and Nigel Dudley (Ed.), Arguments for protected areas: Multiple benefits for conservation and use (pp. 189-204) London, U.K. ; Washington, DC, U.S.A.: Earthscan.

 0.51

21

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7045-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7045_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:51:42">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:222660</link><title>The determination of socially optimal recreation outputs and entry prices for national parks in Southwestern Queensland</title><description>Beal, Diana J. (Diana Joy), 1945- (1996). The determination of socially optimal recreation outputs and entry prices for national parks in Southwestern Queensland PhD Thesis, School of Economics, The University of Queensland.

 0.51

106

7</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7045-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7045_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:55:18">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:298590</link><title>What are the benefits of interacting with nature?</title><description>Keniger, Lucy E., Gaston, Kevin J., Irvine, Katherine N. and Fuller, Richard A. (2013) What are the benefits of interacting with nature?. International Journal of Environmental Research and Public Health, 10 3: 913-935.

 0.50

24

5

3

Cited 2 times in Scopus2

22</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>