<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7064">Korea weather</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:50:04" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7064-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7064_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:50:08">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:219169</link><title>The emergence of Korea as an industrialised nation and its implications for Australia as a trade partner</title><description>Dixon, Samantha. (1996). The emergence of Korea as an industrialised nation and its implications for Australia as a trade partner Master's Thesis, School of Economics, The University of Queensland.

 0.73

79</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7064-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7064_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:51:28">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:222799</link><title>North Korea : making the transition from central planning to market</title><description>Park, Monica E. (2000). North Korea : making the transition from central planning to market Honours Thesis, School of Economics, The University of Queensland.

 0.62

46</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7064-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7064_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:54:08">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:255690</link><title>Full flow-path design optimisation of axisymmetric scramjets with premixed fuel / air</title><description>Ogawa, Hideaki and Boyce, Russell R. (2011). Full flow-path design optimisation of axisymmetric scramjets with premixed fuel / air. In: , 14th Australian Aeronautical Conference (AIAC14-AERO). AIAC14 Fourteenth Australian International Aerospace Congress, Melbourne, Australia, (). 28 February-3 March 2011.

 0.53

118

10</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7064-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7064_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:54:52">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106744</link><title>Principle of competition : a study of Japanese anti-Korean racism, 1875-1923</title><description>Ishiguro, Yoshiaki (2004). Principle of competition : a study of Japanese anti-Korean racism, 1875-1923 PhD Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion, and Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.48

247

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7064-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7064_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:57:29">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:230402</link><title>Socioecological changes and Dengue fever transmission in Queensland, Australia: A spatial Bayesian approach</title><description>Hu, Wenbiao, Clements, Archie, Williams, Gail and Tong, Shilu (2011). Socioecological changes and Dengue fever transmission in Queensland, Australia: A spatial Bayesian approach. In: , January Supplement 2011, 2010 Joint Conference of International Society of Exposure Science &amp; International Society for Environmental Epidemiology. 2010 Joint Conference of International Society of Exposure Science &amp; International Society for Environmental Epidemiology, Seoul, Republic of Korea, (S138-S138). 28 August-1 September 2010.

 0.47

71

0

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7064-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7064_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:58:23">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106436</link><title>Constructing tourism in South Korea : nation state and the tourist gaze</title><description>Lee, Young-Sook (2003). Constructing tourism in South Korea : nation state and the tourist gaze PhD Thesis, School of Social Science, The University of Queensland.

 0.44

277

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7064-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7064_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:02:14">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:319816</link><title>Japanese Imperial influences on Korean primary language textbooks written in Japanese from 1910 to 1945</title><description>Kim, Haisuk (2013). Japanese Imperial influences on Korean primary language textbooks written in Japanese from 1910 to 1945 Honours Thesis, School of Languages and Comp Cultural Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.43

7

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7064-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7064_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:05:39">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:224142</link><title>Japan under the DPJ - coping well or just muddling through?</title><description>Vaughan, Michael (2010). Japan under the DPJ - coping well or just muddling through?. , School of Political Science &amp; Internat'l Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.41

147

374</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7064-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7064_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:09:04">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:283912</link><title>Productivism, culture and the challenges of sustainable beef production in Australia</title><description>Richards, Carol, Lawrence, Geoffrey and Kim, Chul-Kyoo (2012) Productivism, culture and the challenges of sustainable beef production in Australia. Eco, 16 1: 101-128.

 0.40

135

46</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7064-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7064_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:12:32">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:319815</link><title>The Construction of cultural values in middle school English language textbooks in Korea: a critical discourse analaysis</title><description>Cho, Yeun Ji (2013). The Construction of cultural values in middle school English language textbooks in Korea: a critical discourse analaysis Honours Thesis, School of Languages and Comp Cultural Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.40

25

5</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>