<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7067">used kindle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:33:02" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7067-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7067_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:33:06">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:143636</link><title>Behavioral analysis of PTZ-kindled rats after acute and chronic ethanol treatments</title><description>Davidson, M, Chen, WB and Wilce, PA (1999) Behavioral analysis of PTZ-kindled rats after acute and chronic ethanol treatments. Pharmacology Biochemistry and Behavior, 64 1: 7-13.

 1.13

58

1

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7067-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7067_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:34:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:200547</link><title>Morphological and functional changes of blood–brain barrier in kindled rats with cortical dysplasia</title><description>Kaya, Mehmet, Gurses, Candan, Kalayci, Rivaze, Ekizoglu, Oguzhan, Ahishali, Bulent, Orhan, Nurcan, Oku, Basar, Arican, Nadir, Ustek, Duran, Bilgic, Bilge, Elmas, Imdat, Kucuk, Mutlu and Kemikler, Gonul (2008) Morphological and functional changes of blood–brain barrier in kindled rats with cortical dysplasia. Brain Research, 1208 : 181-191.

 0.84

83

13

Cited 13 times in Scopus13

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7067-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7067_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:36:28">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:194723</link><title>Protease-activated receptor-2 regulates trypsin expression in the brain and protects against seizures and epileptogenesis</title><description>Lohman, Rink-Jan, Cocks, Thomas M. and O'Brien, Terence J. (2008) Protease-activated receptor-2 regulates trypsin expression in the brain and protects against seizures and epileptogenesis. Neurobiology of Disease, 30 1: 84-93.

 0.60

39

18

Cited 19 times in Scopus19

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7067-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7067_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:38:19">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:122805</link><title>Glutamate metabotropic receptors as targets for drug therapy in epilepsy</title><description>Moldrich, RX, Chapman, AG, De Sarro, G and Meldrumb, BS (2003) Glutamate metabotropic receptors as targets for drug therapy in epilepsy. European Journal of Pharmacology, 476 1-2: 3-16.

 0.51

87

93

Cited 109 times in Scopus109

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7067-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7067_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:40:32">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:128720</link><title>A structural basis for the pH-dependent increase in fluorescence efficiency of chromoproteins</title><description>Battad, J. M., Wilmann, P. G., Olsen, S. C., Byres, E., Smith, S. C., Dove, S. G., Turcic, K. N., Devenish, R. J., Rossjohn, J. and Prescott, M. (2007) A structural basis for the pH-dependent increase in fluorescence efficiency of chromoproteins. Journal of Molecular Biology, 368 4: 998-1010.

 0.45

131

15

Cited 15 times in Scopus15

6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7067-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7067_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:44:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:293445</link><title>An anthropology of singularity? Pastoral perspectives for an embodied spirituality in the annus virtualis and beyond</title><description>Van den Berg, Jan Albert (2012). An anthropology of singularity? Pastoral perspectives for an embodied spirituality in the annus virtualis and beyond. In Asuncion Lopez-Varela (Ed.), Social sciences and cultural studies - issues of language, public opinion, education and welfare (pp. 429-440) Rijeka, Croatia: InTech.

 0.40

44

7

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7067-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7067_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:47:54">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:108398</link><title>Insights from a systems view: How modelling can inform reform</title><description>Jerry Vanclay (2007). Insights from a systems view: How modelling can inform reform. In: Steve Harrison, Annerine Bosch and John Herbohn, Improving the Triple Bottom Line Returns from Small-scale Forestry: Proceedings from an International Conference. Improving the Triple Line Bottom Line Returns from Small-scale Forestry, Ormoc, the Philippines, (367-374). 18 - 21 June 2007.

 0.31

401

490</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7067-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7067_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:50:07">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:211543</link><title>Building the Cairns Range Railway</title><description>Collinson, J. W. (1954) Building the Cairns Range Railway. Journal of the Royal Historical Society of Queensland, 5 3: 1069-1075.

 0.31

119

350</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7067-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7067_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:54:12">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:177605</link><title>Gene expression in the alcoholic brain</title><description>Rosemarie Kryger (2008). Gene expression in the alcoholic brain PhD Thesis, School of Chemistry and Molecular Biosciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.30

154

10</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7067-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7067_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:57:12">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:235286</link><title>Music of Betty Beath</title><description>Schindler, Margaret, Beath, Betty, Delpratt, Janet, Dunn, Susan, Pollett, Patricia, Spiers, Colin, Camerata of St John's, Joyce, Brendan, Queensland Symphony Orchestra and Mills, Richard (2009) Music of Betty Beath. Wollongong, NSW, Australia, Wirripang.

 0.30

71

3</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>