<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7068">Speech and Language Processing: An Introduction to Natural Language Processing, Computational Linguistics, and Speech Recognition</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:59:11" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7068-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7068_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:59:20">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:167629</link><title>Speech Pathology Service Provision for Children with Speech and/or Language Impairment in Tasmania</title><description>Belinda Jessup (2007). Speech Pathology Service Provision for Children with Speech and/or Language Impairment in Tasmania PhD Thesis, , The University of Queensland.

 0.95

226

13</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7068-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7068_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:00:41">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:283090</link><title>Assessment and treatment of speech and language disorders in traumatic brain injury</title><description>Murdoch, Bruce E., Lewis, Fiona M. and Knuepffer, Christina (2013). Assessment and treatment of speech and language disorders in traumatic brain injury. In Nathan D. Zasler, Douglas I. Katz and Ross D. Zafonte (Ed.), Brain injury medicine: principles and practice 2 ed. (pp. 1086-1110) New York, NY, United States: Demos Medical Publishing.

 0.85

109

71

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7068-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7068_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:02:37">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:159799</link><title>Relationship between the music audiation capacities and language comprehension capacities of children age 5 years</title><description>Mrs Leah Shephard (2008). Relationship between the music audiation capacities and language comprehension capacities of children age 5 years MPhil Thesis, School of Music, The University of Queensland.

 0.85

168

21</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7068-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7068_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:05:14">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:159128</link><title>Speech-Language Pathology Support to Adolescents in Queensland, Australia Who Are Experiencing Oral Language Difficulties</title><description>Ms Karen Hollands (2008). Speech-Language Pathology Support to Adolescents in Queensland, Australia Who Are Experiencing Oral Language Difficulties PhD Thesis, School of Education, The University of Queensland.

 0.79

376

50</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7068-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7068_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:09:11">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:185401</link><title>Measuring the ability to understand everyday speech in children with middle ear dysfunction Tegan Michelle Keogh A thesis submitted for the degree of Doctor of Philosophy at The University of Queensland in March 2009 School of</title><description>Tegan Keogh (2009). Measuring the ability to understand everyday speech in children with middle ear dysfunction Tegan Michelle Keogh A thesis submitted for the degree of Doctor of Philosophy at The University of Queensland in March 2009 School of PhD Thesis, School of Health &amp; Rehabilitation Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.76

154

11</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7068-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7068_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:11:20">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:310797</link><title>The phonological forms and perceived functions of janyarrp, the Gurindji 'baby talk' register</title><description>Jones, Caroline and Meakins, Felicity (2013) The phonological forms and perceived functions of janyarrp, the Gurindji 'baby talk' register. Lingua, 134 : 170-193.

 0.74

54

2

0

Cited 0 times in Scopus0

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7068-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7068_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:13:55">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:107072</link><title>The nature of nurture : measuring some environmental correlates of first language acquisition</title><description>Purcell, Anne (2004). The nature of nurture : measuring some environmental correlates of first language acquisition PhD Thesis, School of Social Science, The University of Queensland.

 0.73

300

7</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7068-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7068_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:16:32">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106051</link><title>On the origins of linguistic structure : computational models of the evolution of language</title><description>Tonkes, Bradley. (2002). On the origins of linguistic structure : computational models of the evolution of language PhD Thesis, School of Information Technology and Electrical Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.71

119

4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7068-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7068_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:19:56">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106634</link><title>Language, difference and diversity : bilingual perspectives in social work</title><description>Harrison, Gai (2003). Language, difference and diversity : bilingual perspectives in social work PhD Thesis, School of Social Work and Applied Human Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.70

297

19</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7068-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7068_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:21:46">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:152713</link><title>Lipreading skills in children with hearing impairment</title><description>Woodhouse, Lynn Mary (2007). Lipreading skills in children with hearing impairment PhD Thesis, School of Health and Rehabilitation Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.70

677

120</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>