<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7078">count in korean</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:31:36" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7078-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7078_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:31:42">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106744</link><title>Principle of competition : a study of Japanese anti-Korean racism, 1875-1923</title><description>Ishiguro, Yoshiaki (2004). Principle of competition : a study of Japanese anti-Korean racism, 1875-1923 PhD Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion, and Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.79

249

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7078-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7078_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:32:14">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:319816</link><title>Japanese Imperial influences on Korean primary language textbooks written in Japanese from 1910 to 1945</title><description>Kim, Haisuk (2013). Japanese Imperial influences on Korean primary language textbooks written in Japanese from 1910 to 1945 Honours Thesis, School of Languages and Comp Cultural Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.71

9

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7078-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7078_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:34:42">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158486</link><title>History and Hermeneutics: A Historical Development of OT Studies in Korean Presbyterianism, 1884-1960, with Specific Focus on the History of the Appropriation of Western OT Hermeneutic Method</title><description>Park, Won-Ju (2007). History and Hermeneutics: A Historical Development of OT Studies in Korean Presbyterianism, 1884-1960, with Specific Focus on the History of the Appropriation of Western OT Hermeneutic Method PhD Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion, and Classics, University of Queensland.

 0.64

252

6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7078-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7078_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:36:24">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:271871</link><title>The role of multicultural festivals in a society in transition: From being ethnically homogeneous to becoming multicultural</title><description>Insun Sunny Lee (2012). The role of multicultural festivals in a society in transition: From being ethnically homogeneous to becoming multicultural PhD Thesis, School of Tourism, The University of Queensland.

 0.61

538

24</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7078-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7078_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:37:04">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106254</link><title>A Linguistic study of culture-specific speech acts : politeness in English and Korean.</title><description>Yu, Kyong-Ae. (2002). A Linguistic study of culture-specific speech acts : politeness in English and Korean. PhD Thesis, School of Languages and Comparative Cultural Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.58

1703

12</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7078-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7078_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:38:01">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106436</link><title>Constructing tourism in South Korea : nation state and the tourist gaze</title><description>Lee, Young-Sook (2003). Constructing tourism in South Korea : nation state and the tourist gaze PhD Thesis, School of Social Science, The University of Queensland.

 0.54

279

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7078-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7078_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:38:35">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:319815</link><title>The Construction of cultural values in middle school English language textbooks in Korea: a critical discourse analaysis</title><description>Cho, Yeun Ji (2013). The Construction of cultural values in middle school English language textbooks in Korea: a critical discourse analaysis Honours Thesis, School of Languages and Comp Cultural Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.53

27

5</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7078-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7078_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:40:57">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:240488</link><title>Particularism and universalism in the book of Isaiah : Isaiah's implications for a pluralistic world from a Korean perspective</title><description>Jang, Se Hoon. (2002). Particularism and universalism in the book of Isaiah : Isaiah's implications for a pluralistic world from a Korean perspective PhD Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion, and Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.50

104

5</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7078-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7078_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:42:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:302760</link><title>The end of the affair? : the dynamics of the Korean developmental alliance</title><description>Hundt, David (2005). The end of the affair? : the dynamics of the Korean developmental alliance PhD Thesis, School of Political Science &amp; Internat'l Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.50

71

8</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7078-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7078_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:44:09">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:289029</link><title>Translating Korean fiction novel into English: a focus on the issue of metaphors</title><description>Neo, Manlin Maybelline (2012). Translating Korean fiction novel into English: a focus on the issue of metaphors Honours Thesis, School of Languages and Comparative Cultural Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.46

49

7</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>