<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7081">translation bloopers</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:34:23" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7081-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7081_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:34:28">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:239935</link><title>Political Chronicles - Queensland</title><description>(1997) Political Chronicles - Queensland. Australian journal of politics and history, 43 2: 233-239.

 0.27

28

44</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7081-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7081_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:36:59">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:278020</link><title>My favourite things: Spin-off products and television memories</title><description>Bonner, Frances (2012). My favourite things: Spin-off products and television memories. In Kate Darian-Smith and Sue Turnbull (Ed.), Remembering television. Histories, technologies, memories (pp. 173-191) Newcastle upon Tyne: Cambridge Scholars Publishing.

 0.18

52

3</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7081-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7081_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:38:24">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:185195</link><title>Site/counter-site: A semiotic study of the Gold Coast</title><description>Barcan, Ruth Margaret (1994). Site/counter-site: A semiotic study of the Gold Coast PhD Thesis, School of English, Media Studies and Art History, The University of Queensland.

 0.13

146

114</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7081-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7081_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:39:59">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158811</link><title>The 1996 Olympic Games: Emotive Narrative and National Identity</title><description>Mitchell, Andrea (2007). The 1996 Olympic Games: Emotive Narrative and National Identity PhD Thesis, School of English, Media Studies and Art History, University of Queensland.

 0.13

420

15</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7081-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7081_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:43:02">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106679</link><title>A telling story : five journalist-novelists and Australia's writing culture</title><description>Conley, David P. (2003). A telling story : five journalist-novelists and Australia's writing culture PhD Thesis, School of English, Media Studies and Art History, The University of Queensland.

 0.12

110

4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7081-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7081_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:44:59">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:260202</link><title>A Telling Story: Five Journalist-Novelists and Australia's Writing Culture</title><description>Conley, David (2003). A Telling Story: Five Journalist-Novelists and Australia's Writing Culture PhD Thesis, School of Journalism and Communication and School of English, Media Studies and Art History, The University of Queensland.

 0.12

260

1843</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7081-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7081_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:47:13">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:269242</link><title>Fault and fracture zone detection based on soil gas mapping and gamma ray survey at the extension site of an open pit coal mine</title><description>Ma, Ye, Bringemeier, Detlef, Scheuermann, Alexander, Molebatsi, Tiro and Li, Ling (2012). Fault and fracture zone detection based on soil gas mapping and gamma ray survey at the extension site of an open pit coal mine. In: , Proceedings of the 2012 Coal Operators' Conference. 2012 Coal Operators' Conference, Wollongong, NSW, Australia, (379-387). 16-17 February 2012.

 0.12

150

20

0</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>