<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7082">The raven</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:49:19" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7082-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7082_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:49:27">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:84612</link><title>An explanation of expanded paramedic healthcare roles of Queensland</title><description>Raven, S., Tippett, V., Ferguson, J. and Smith, S. (2006) An explanation of expanded paramedic healthcare roles of Queensland Brisbane: Qld Ambulance Service/University of Queensland

 0.98

116</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7082-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7082_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:51:59">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:133700</link><title>Expanded paramedic healthcare roles in rural and remote communities</title><description>Raven, S., Tippett, V., Murdoch, J., Stephens, J. and O'Brien, A. (2007). Expanded paramedic healthcare roles in rural and remote communities. In: , Proceedings of the 9th National Rural Health Conference. 9th National Rural Health Conference, Albury/Wondonga, (). 7-10 March, 2007.

 0.88

257</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7082-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7082_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:56:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:79812</link><title>Death of two pups from spider envenomation</title><description>O'Hagan, B. J., Raven, R. J. and McCormick, K. M. (2006) Death of two pups from spider envenomation. Australian Veterinary Journal, 84 8: 291-291.

 0.80

37

0

Cited 0 times in Scopus0

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7082-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7082_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:57:52">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:317716</link><title>Responding to evidence: Breastfeed baby if you can the sixth public health recommendation to reduce the risk of sudden and unexpected death in infancy</title><description>Frcna J.Y., Watson K., Ellis L. and Raven L. (2012) Responding to evidence: Breastfeed baby if you can the sixth public health recommendation to reduce the risk of sudden and unexpected death in infancy. Breastfeeding Review, 20 1: 7-15.

 0.80

7

Cited 1 times in Scopus1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7082-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7082_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:59:40">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:292782</link><title>The raven's seal</title><description>Baltakmens, Andrei The raven's seal. Oak Park, IL, United States: Top Five Books, 2012.

 0.80

19</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7082-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7082_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:00:08">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:236534</link><title>Sustainable support for health professionals delivering evidence-based safe sleeping messages to families: A multi-agency approach.</title><description>Young, J., Higgins, N. and Raven, L. (2010). Sustainable support for health professionals delivering evidence-based safe sleeping messages to families: A multi-agency approach.. In: , Abstracts of the Joint Conference of the International Stillbirth Alliance (ISA) and International Society for the Study and Prevention of Infant Death (ISPID). Joint Conference of the International Stillbirth Alliance (ISA) and International Society for the Study and Prevention of Infant Death (ISPID)., Sydney, Australia, (26-27). 8th-10th October 2010.

 0.77

51

14</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7082-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7082_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:01:54">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:221062</link><title>Do wheezy infants recovering from bronchiolitis respond to inhaled salbutamol</title><description>Sly, P.D., Lanteri, C.J. and Raven, J.M. (1991) Do wheezy infants recovering from bronchiolitis respond to inhaled salbutamol. Pediatric Pulmonology, 10 1: 36-39.

 0.77

26

46

Cited 43 times in Scopus43

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7082-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7082_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:02:38">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:220936</link><title>Effect of forced expiration on thoracic gas volume in wheezy infants</title><description>Lanteri, C.J., Raven, J.M. and Sly, P.D. (1990) Effect of forced expiration on thoracic gas volume in wheezy infants. Pediatric Pulmonology, 9 4: 220-223.

 0.77

52

1

Cited 2 times in Scopus2

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7082-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7082_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:06:14">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:257124</link><title>An Institutional Embeddedness of Welfare Opinions? The Link between Public Opinion and Social Policy in the Netherlands (1970-2004)</title><description>Raven, Judith, Achterberg, Peter, van der Veen, Romke and Yerkes, Mara (2011) An Institutional Embeddedness of Welfare Opinions? The Link between Public Opinion and Social Policy in the Netherlands (1970-2004). Journal of Social Policy, 40 2: 369-386.

 0.77

64

3

Cited 0 times in Scopus0

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7082-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7082_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:09:14">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:103451</link><title>Carvedilol causes greater persistent blockage of beta2- than beta1-adrenoceptors in human failing myocardium</title><description>Kaumann, A. J., Christ, T., Ravens, U. and Molenaar, P. (2005). Carvedilol causes greater persistent blockage of beta2- than beta1-adrenoceptors in human failing myocardium. In: , BPS Summer Meeting 2005. BPS Summer Meeting 2005, Cambridge, U.K., (157P-157P). July, 2005.

 0.72

38</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>