<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7084">Burn after reading review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:10:56" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7084-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7084_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:11:03">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:292851</link><title>‘A person’s a person, no matter how small’: the effects of trauma on preschool children after being burned</title><description>Licence, Miranda (2012). ‘A person’s a person, no matter how small’: the effects of trauma on preschool children after being burned Honours Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.67

38

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7084-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7084_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:14:36">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:276606</link><title>Challenges in management of infections on a burn injury unit.</title><description>Bhavik Patel (2011). Challenges in management of infections on a burn injury unit. MPhil Thesis, School of Medicine, The University of Queensland.

 0.65

172

11</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7084-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7084_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:18:12">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:187774</link><title>First aid treatment of burn injuries: Optimum treatment and mechanisms of action</title><description>Leila Cuttle (2009). First aid treatment of burn injuries: Optimum treatment and mechanisms of action PhD Thesis, School of Medicine, The University of Queensland.

 0.65

349

15</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7084-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7084_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:20:41">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:271040</link><title>“Phantom Skin Pain” Neuropathic Pain Following Burn Injury – An Examination of Incidence and Treatment</title><description>Paul Gray (2011). “Phantom Skin Pain” Neuropathic Pain Following Burn Injury – An Examination of Incidence and Treatment PhD Thesis, School of Medicine, The University of Queensland.

 0.59

349

17</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7084-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7084_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:23:09">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:256733</link><title>Dysphagia following thermal burn injury: Clinical risk factors, anatomical and physiological characteristics and road to resolution and recovery</title><description>Anna Rumbach (2011). Dysphagia following thermal burn injury: Clinical risk factors, anatomical and physiological characteristics and road to resolution and recovery PhD Thesis, School of Health and Rehabilitation Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.58

295

75</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7084-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7084_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:23:40">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:284697</link><title>Virtual reality to reduce acute pain in adolescents during burn wound care</title><description>Kipping, Belinda (2012). Virtual reality to reduce acute pain in adolescents during burn wound care MPhil Thesis, School of Health and Rehabilitation Sciences and School of Medicine, The University of Queensland.

 0.54

89

8</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7084-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7084_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:26:20">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:138972</link><title>Predicting functional outcome upon admission following burn injury in children aged 5 to 14 years.</title><description>Simons, Megan A. (2008). Predicting functional outcome upon admission following burn injury in children aged 5 to 14 years. PhD Thesis, School of Health &amp; Rehabilitation Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.52

312

135</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7084-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7084_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:27:01">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:205951</link><title>Some Burning Questions</title><description>John Fraser (2009). Some Burning Questions PhD Thesis, School of Medicine, The University of Queensland.

 0.50

336

11</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7084-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7084_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:30:13">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106382</link><title>Investigating the combustion mechanisms of bulk metals through microanalysis of post-test 3.2 mm diameter metallic rods burned in oxygen-enriched atmospheres</title><description>De Wit, John Robert (2003). Investigating the combustion mechanisms of bulk metals through microanalysis of post-test 3.2 mm diameter metallic rods burned in oxygen-enriched atmospheres PhD Thesis, School of Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.49

122

5</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7084-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7084_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:32:48">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:251852</link><title>Site-specific theatre and political engagement across space and time: The psychogeographic mapping of British Petroleum in Platform's And While London Burns</title><description>Tompkins, Joanne (2011) Site-specific theatre and political engagement across space and time: The psychogeographic mapping of British Petroleum in Platform's And While London Burns. Theatre Journal, 63 2: 225-243.

 0.49

112

2</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>