<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7099">lecture manova</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:31:31" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7099-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7099_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:31:35">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:292833</link><title>Uncertainty and focused attention: effects on attributions and uncertainty-reducing behaviours</title><description>Knobl, Nicole (2012). Uncertainty and focused attention: effects on attributions and uncertainty-reducing behaviours Honours Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.45

24

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7099-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7099_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:32:37">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:264789</link><title>What They Think, What They Expect, and What They Practise: A Multivariate Analysis of Students′ Perceptions about Teaching and Learning in Higher Education</title><description>Alauddin, Mohammad (2011). What They Think, What They Expect, and What They Practise: A Multivariate Analysis of Students′ Perceptions about Teaching and Learning in Higher Education PhD Thesis, Education, The University of Queensland.

 0.39

144

22</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7099-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7099_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:35:14">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:219696</link><title>Retailer equity and consumer innovativeness relationships : an empirical study of two retail extensions</title><description>Chong, Merissa. (2006). Retailer equity and consumer innovativeness relationships : an empirical study of two retail extensions Honours Thesis, School of Business, The University of Queensland.

 0.34

104

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7099-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7099_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:37:29">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:303094</link><title>Conclusion: understanding and enacting the strategic role of tourism</title><description>Fayos-Sola, Eduardo, Ruhanen, Lisa, de Bruyn, Christophe, Munoz Mazon, Ana, Fuentes, Laura and Alonso, Alba Fernandez (2012). Conclusion: understanding and enacting the strategic role of tourism. In Eduardo Fayos-Sola and Ulysses Foundation (Ed.), Knowledge management in tourism: Policy and governance applications (pp. 323-345) Bingley UK: Emeral Group Publishing Limited.

 0.32

64

3</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7099-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7099_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:39:27">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106849</link><title>Communication accommodation in the workplace : status, sex, goals and strategies</title><description>Willemyns, Michael. (2004). Communication accommodation in the workplace : status, sex, goals and strategies PhD Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.32

327

4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7099-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7099_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:42:54">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158651</link><title>Cinderella vs. Princess Fiona: Actual and perceived functioning in stepfamilies and biological families</title><description>Planitz, Judith (2007). Cinderella vs. Princess Fiona: Actual and perceived functioning in stepfamilies and biological families PhD Thesis, School of Psychology , University of Queensland.

 0.31

513

12</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7099-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7099_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:43:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:308180</link><title>Language learning strategies by learners of Chinesse as a Foreign Language (CFL): the effect of proficiency and gender</title><description>Lim, Yan Ting Melissa (2013). Language learning strategies by learners of Chinesse as a Foreign Language (CFL): the effect of proficiency and gender Honours Thesis, School of Languages and Comp Cultural Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.30

28

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7099-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7099_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:46:32">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106898</link><title>An evaluation of learning styles, learning issues and learning problems of Confucian heritage culture students studying hospitality and tourism management in Australia</title><description>Barron, Paul Edward. (2004). An evaluation of learning styles, learning issues and learning problems of Confucian heritage culture students studying hospitality and tourism management in Australia PhD Thesis, School of Tourism, The University of Queensland.

 0.28

716

3</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7099-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7099_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:47:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:307050</link><title>A pilot randomised control trial of a brief video to improve wellbeing in university students</title><description>Bagraith, Sukhveer (2012). A pilot randomised control trial of a brief video to improve wellbeing in university students Honours Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.28

63

11</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7099-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7099_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:50:01">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:220772</link><title>Walking in Their Footsteps: Influence of a Learning Experience on the Knowledge, Attitudes and Beliefs of First Year Occupational Therapy Students towards Aboriginal Australians</title><description>Rebekah White (2010). Walking in Their Footsteps: Influence of a Learning Experience on the Knowledge, Attitudes and Beliefs of First Year Occupational Therapy Students towards Aboriginal Australians PhD Thesis, School of Health and Rehabilitation Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.27

204

21</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>