<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7104">How to go from New York to Montreal</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:53:47" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7104-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7104_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:53:54">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:205174</link><title>Diplomacy of good sense : Sir William Glasgow in Canada</title><description>Harry, Ralph, 1917-2002 (1980) Diplomacy of good sense : Sir William Glasgow in Canada. Journal of the Royal Historical Society of Queensland, 11 1: 103-118.

 0.38

58

166</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7104-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7104_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:55:54">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:313744</link><title>Inside the UN Security Council: The influence of the social environment on decision making</title><description>Gifkins, Jessica (2013). Inside the UN Security Council: The influence of the social environment on decision making PhD Thesis, School of Political Science &amp; International Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.35

31

5</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7104-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7104_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:58:59">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:120219</link><title>Designing for learning through multimodal production: film narrative and spectatorship in Director’s Cut</title><description>Deacon, Andrew E., Morrison, Andrew and Stadler, Jane (2005) Designing for learning through multimodal production: film narrative and spectatorship in Director’s Cut. International Journal of Education and Development Using Information and Communication Technology, 1 1: 72-89.

 0.35

117</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7104-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7104_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:59:56">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:216899</link><title>Gendering the podium : the journeys of professional women conductors</title><description>Bartleet, Brydie-Leigh. (2004). Gendering the podium : the journeys of professional women conductors PhD Thesis, School of Music, The University of Queensland.

 0.35

165

7</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7104-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7104_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:02:51">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:237222</link><title>Male ex-inmates living crime-free: A phenomenological study.</title><description>J F (2010). Male ex-inmates living crime-free: A phenomenological study. PhD Thesis, School of Education, The University of Queensland.

 0.35

150

15</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7104-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7104_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:05:09">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:229132</link><title>Grasping the logic of practice: Theorizing through practical rationality</title><description>Sandberg, Jörgen and Tsoukas, Haridimos (2011) Grasping the logic of practice: Theorizing through practical rationality. Academy of Management Review, 36 2: 338-360.

 0.35

402

8

35

Cited 51 times in Scopus51

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7104-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7104_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:06:42">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:265351</link><title>Creative city strategies in Toronto and Vancouver: Towards a comparative analysis with Australian cities (Melbourne and Brisbane</title><description>Darchen, Sebastien (2011). Creative city strategies in Toronto and Vancouver: Towards a comparative analysis with Australian cities (Melbourne and Brisbane. In: , State of Australian Cities National Conference 2011. State of Australian Cities National Conference 2011, Melbourne, Australia, (1-10). 29 November - 2 December 2011.

 0.34

90

4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7104-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7104_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:09:24">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:282714</link><title>Overview: experiencing and managing emotions in the workplace</title><description>Ashkanasy, Neal M., Hartel, Charmine E. J. and Zerbe, Wilfred J. (2012). Overview: experiencing and managing emotions in the workplace. In Neal M. Ashkanasy, Charmine E. J. Hartel and Wilfred J. Zerbe (Ed.), Experiencing and Managing Emotions in the Workplace (pp. 1-10) Bingley, United Kingdom: Emerald Group Publishing.

 0.34

137

4

0

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7104-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7104_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:10:34">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:294936</link><title>Fostering a creativity mindset for teaching (and learning)</title><description>O'Brien, Mia (2012) Fostering a creativity mindset for teaching (and learning). LEARNing Landscapes, 6 1: 315-334.

 0.34

68

3</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7104-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7104_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:11:09">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:219276</link><title>The Use of Music in Youth Peacebuilding Projects</title><description>Lesley Pruitt (2010). The Use of Music in Youth Peacebuilding Projects PhD Thesis, School of Political Science and International Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.34

323

45</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>