<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7107">grimm episodes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:51:28" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7107-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7107_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:51:37">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:266698</link><title>"And then the devil will take me away:" Adaptation, narrative evolution, and The Brothers Grimm's suppression of taboo motifs in The Girl Without Hands</title><description>Ashley, Melissa (2009). "And then the devil will take me away:" Adaptation, narrative evolution, and The Brothers Grimm's suppression of taboo motifs in The Girl Without Hands. In: , Double Dialogues 2009: Hidden Stories. Abstracts. DD09. Hidden Stories: A Double Dialogues Conference, Southbank, VIC, Australia, (). 11-12 December 2009.

 0.82

70</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7107-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7107_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:55:53">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:236723</link><title>'And Then the Devil Will Take Me Away': Adaptation, evolution, and The Brothers Grimm's suppression of taboo motifs in 'The Girl without Hands'</title><description>Ashley, Melissa (2010) 'And Then the Devil Will Take Me Away': Adaptation, evolution, and The Brothers Grimm's suppression of taboo motifs in 'The Girl without Hands'. Double Dialogues, 1 12: .

 0.78

80</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7107-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7107_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:57:04">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:184596</link><title>Girl without hands: extract from the manuscript of a novel. The Maiden without hands: from folktale and fairy ale to contemporary novel</title><description>Melissa Ashley (2009). Girl without hands: extract from the manuscript of a novel. The Maiden without hands: from folktale and fairy ale to contemporary novel MPhil Thesis, English, Media Studies, and Art History, The University of Queensland.

 0.31

610

17</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7107-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7107_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:59:04">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:301323</link><title>Fairy tale transformations and gender: The Little Mermaid's metamorphoses in Japanese and English</title><description>Fraser, Lucy (2013). Fairy tale transformations and gender: The Little Mermaid's metamorphoses in Japanese and English PhD Thesis, School of Languages and Comparative Cultural Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.28

280

13</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7107-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7107_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:00:05">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:239742</link><title>Self harm in children: A comparison of child inpatients who self-harm and those who do not</title><description>Bonnie Palmer (2010). Self harm in children: A comparison of child inpatients who self-harm and those who do not Honours Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.24

148

18</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7107-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7107_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:03:14">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:164833</link><title>Prognostication in Low Back Pain:A Biopsychosocial Index</title><description>John Nicholas Penney (2008). Prognostication in Low Back Pain:A Biopsychosocial Index PhD Thesis, School of Medicine, The University of Queensland.

 0.24

273

19</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7107-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7107_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:06:53">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158675</link><title>The Nineteenth Century in the Recent Australian Imaginary</title><description>Duthie, Fiona (2007). The Nineteenth Century in the Recent Australian Imaginary PhD Thesis, School of English, Media Studies and Art History, University of Queensland.

 0.23

685

31</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7107-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7107_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:07:42">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:291294</link><title>The role of Brangaene in the medieval versions of Tristan</title><description>Wissler, P. (1976). The role of Brangaene in the medieval versions of Tristan M.A. Thesis, School of Languages and Comparative Cultural Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.23

27

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7107-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7107_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:11:14">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:223954</link><title>The professional Service Firm and Strategy in a Fragmented Industry (Architecture)</title><description>Gunther, Andrew (1995) The professional Service Firm and Strategy in a Fragmented Industry (Architecture). , Graduate School of Management, The University of Queensland.

 0.23

27

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7107-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7107_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:12:14">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:198495</link><title>Fantasy and Belief: fiction and media as conjunct locales for metaphysical questing and spiritual understanding</title><description>Danielle Kirby (2009). Fantasy and Belief: fiction and media as conjunct locales for metaphysical questing and spiritual understanding PhD Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion &amp; Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.22

394

10</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>