<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7109">best place to eat pho in new york</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:40:09" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7109-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7109_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:40:16">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:238927</link><title>Before selling, before telling: Understanding tourism entities and tourist behavior</title><description>Lee, Timothy J. L. and Stanciu, Cristina (2011). Before selling, before telling: Understanding tourism entities and tourist behavior. In Gabriela Stanciulescu and Timothy J. L. Lee (Ed.), Tourism Challenges for New Enlarged Europe (pp. 157-174) Bucharest, Romania: ASE Publishing House.

 0.32

76

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7109-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7109_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:44:50">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:219294</link><title>Accommodating the Discarnate: Spirit houses in contemporary urban Thailand</title><description>Michael Pearce (2010). Accommodating the Discarnate: Spirit houses in contemporary urban Thailand PhD Thesis, History, Philosophy, Religion and Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.31

541

18</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7109-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7109_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:48:27">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:269467</link><title>Who is in control : the diabetic or diabetes? lived experience of adults living with diabetes in Bangkok</title><description>Naemiratch, Bhensri (2005). Who is in control : the diabetic or diabetes? lived experience of adults living with diabetes in Bangkok PhD Thesis, School of Population Health, The University of Queensland.

 0.29

94

3</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7109-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7109_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:51:36">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158210</link><title>Anyone for rice? : Australian food culture, multiculturalism and Asian-Australian identities</title><description>Widarsito, Sinta Jean (2006). Anyone for rice? : Australian food culture, multiculturalism and Asian-Australian identities PhD Thesis, School of English, Media Studies and Art History, University of Queensland.

 0.27

1069

54</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7109-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7109_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:54:23">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:243639</link><title>Knowledge, belief and practice on dengue vector control : a comparison study between rural and urban communities in northeastern Thailand</title><description>Phuanukoonnon, Suparat. (2003). Knowledge, belief and practice on dengue vector control : a comparison study between rural and urban communities in northeastern Thailand PhD Thesis, School of Population Health, The University of Queensland.

 0.27

213

4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7109-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7109_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:57:52">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:198606</link><title>Technology and the body in aboriginal identity making</title><description>Hafner, Diane and Brian, Deborah (2010). Technology and the body in aboriginal identity making. In Bianca Maria Pirani and Ivan Varga (Ed.), Acting bodies and social networks: A bridge between technology and working memory (pp. 329-347) Lanham, Maryland, USA: University Press of America.

 0.26

112

6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7109-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7109_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 05:58:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:195243</link><title>Cultures of Authenticity: Popular Music, Food Television, and Travel Writing</title><description>Gunders, John (2009). Cultures of Authenticity: Popular Music, Food Television, and Travel Writing PhD Thesis, School of English, Media Studies and Art History, The University of Queensland.

 0.25

370

28</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7109-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7109_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:01:34">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:308309</link><title>Conservation of photographs</title><description>Eastman Kodak Company Conservation of photographs. Rochester, NY: Eastman Kodak Co., 1985.

 0.25

92

4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7109-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7109_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:02:54">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:207865</link><title>Are Words with Effector Specific Motor Related Meaning Represented Somatotopically on the Motor Cortex?</title><description>Natasha Postle (2009). Are Words with Effector Specific Motor Related Meaning Represented Somatotopically on the Motor Cortex? PhD Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.25

105

14</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7109-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7109_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:04:19">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:205332</link><title>Visual learning and perception in Drosophila</title><description>van Swinderen, B. (2010). Visual learning and perception in Drosophila. In Bing Zhang, Marc R. Freeman and Scott Waddell (Ed.), Drosophila neurobiology: A laboratory manual (pp. 411-427) New York , U.S.A: Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory Press.

 0.24

72

3</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>