<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7110">civil engineering jobs pennsylvania</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:08:26" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7110-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7110_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:08:33">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:105498</link><title>"Throwing off the shackles of party" : the rise and fall of the Know-Nothing Party in Pennsylvania, 1852-1858</title><description>Mark Dash (2001). "Throwing off the shackles of party" : the rise and fall of the Know-Nothing Party in Pennsylvania, 1852-1858 PhD Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion, and Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.53

143

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7110-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7110_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:09:05">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:221599</link><title>A Multilevel Analysis of the Occupational Stressor-Strain Process: Contextual Variables as Additional Moderators in the Job Demand-Control Model</title><description>Michelle Tucker (2010). A Multilevel Analysis of the Occupational Stressor-Strain Process: Contextual Variables as Additional Moderators in the Job Demand-Control Model PhD Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.41

237

20</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7110-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7110_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:10:34">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:226226</link><title>Self-managing teams in the public sector: an evaluation of effects on job design, job sanctification and performance</title><description>Sparshott, Dean (1996) Self-managing teams in the public sector: an evaluation of effects on job design, job sanctification and performance The University of Queensland:

 0.38

78

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7110-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7110_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:12:39">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:258230</link><title>Fostering creative problem solving and collaborative skills through impromptu design in engineering design courses</title><description>Reidsema, Carl (2005). Fostering creative problem solving and collaborative skills through impromptu design in engineering design courses. In: David Radcliffe and Josh Humphries, Proceedings of the 4th Global Colloquium on Engineering Education. 4th ASEE/AaeE Global Colloquim of Engineering Education (GCEE 2005), Sydney, Australia, (). 26-29 September 2005.

 0.38

61

87</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7110-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7110_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:16:39">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:274453</link><title>Unique Opportunities: forging unity and national identity through anniversary commemorations in post-war America</title><description>Galina Myers (2012). Unique Opportunities: forging unity and national identity through anniversary commemorations in post-war America PhD Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion &amp; Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.36

103

15</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7110-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7110_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:17:42">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:284155</link><title>An imported railway - the background to construction of Queensland's early railway</title><description>Buchanan, Robyn (2012). An imported railway - the background to construction of Queensland's early railway MPhil Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion &amp; Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.35

107

14</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7110-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7110_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:18:56">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:159310</link><title>Complex Systems Approach to Engineering Competence</title><description>Mr Joachim Walther (2008). Complex Systems Approach to Engineering Competence PhD Thesis, School of Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.34

291

59</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7110-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7110_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:22:21">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158122</link><title>Towards a philosophy of engineering: context, pluralism and paradox</title><description>Solomon, Fiona Louise (1997). Towards a philosophy of engineering: context, pluralism and paradox PhD Thesis, School of Engineering, University of Queensland.

 0.34

168

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7110-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7110_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:24:50">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:226442</link><title>Applications of Artificial intelligence in engineering</title><description>Afuni, Munir Omar (1985) Applications of Artificial intelligence in engineering The University of Queensland:

 0.33

94

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7110-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7110_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:28:36">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:287599</link><title>Managerial identity, career progression and job satisfaction among middle managers in the health care sector</title><description>Meissner, Ellen, Callan, Victor and Wilson, Jill (2012). Managerial identity, career progression and job satisfaction among middle managers in the health care sector. In: Werner Soontiens, 26th Annual Australian and New Zealand Academy of Management Conference: Managing for Volatility and Instability. ANZAM 2012 Conference, Perth, Australia, (1-18). 5-7 December 2012.

 0.32

111

6</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>