<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7124">yves saint laurent boots</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:31:26" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7124-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7124_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:31:29">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:230264</link><title>The Blue Poppy Sea: reflections on writing from the leaky boat of an ethnographic novel</title><description>Jennaway, Megan Gayle (2010). The Blue Poppy Sea: reflections on writing from the leaky boat of an ethnographic novel MPhil Thesis, School of English, Media Studies and Art History, The University of Queensland.

 0.16

73

9</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7124-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7124_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:33:04">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:287560</link><title>Scaling 3-36KW microturbines</title><description>Head, Adam Joseph and Visser, W. P. J. (2012). Scaling 3-36KW microturbines. In: , Proceedings of ASME Turbo Expo 2012: GT2012. ASME Turbo Expo 2012: Power for Land, Sea and Air, Copenhagen, Denmark, (609-618). 11-15 June 2012.

 0.15

171

22</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7124-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7124_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:36:11">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:107349</link><title>Patterns of Divergence: The Evolution of the Qipao and Cheongsam in Modern Chinese Society</title><description>Mashi, Edweana Elizabeth Shalini (2005). Patterns of Divergence: The Evolution of the Qipao and Cheongsam in Modern Chinese Society MPhil Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion, and Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.15

959

8</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7124-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7124_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:38:59">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:231175</link><title>Cryotherapy of the equine digit for the treatment of laminitis: Assessment of a novel method by measuring digital venous temperature</title><description>Reesink, Heidi L., Divers, Thomas J., Bookbinder, Lauren, van Eps, Andrew W., Soderholm, Vince, Wildenstein, Michael J. and Cheetham, Jonathan (2010). Cryotherapy of the equine digit for the treatment of laminitis: Assessment of a novel method by measuring digital venous temperature. In: , 2010 American College of Veterinary Surgeons Veterinary Symposium: Scientific presentation abstracts. 2010 American College of Veterinary Surgeons Veterinary Symposium, Seattle, WA, United States, (E49-E49). 21-23 October 2010.

 0.15

117

426

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7124-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7124_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:42:25">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:190020</link><title>Little theatre: Its development, since World War II, in Australia, with particular reference to Queensland</title><description>Radbourne, Jennifer J. (1979). Little theatre: Its development, since World War II, in Australia, with particular reference to Queensland M.A. Thesis, School of English, Media Studies and Art History, The University of Queensland.

 0.15

108

393</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7124-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7124_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:45:12">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158383</link><title>Anima/Animus: Depardieu and the Projection of Masculinities</title><description>Ward, Wendy H. (2007). Anima/Animus: Depardieu and the Projection of Masculinities PhD Thesis, School of Languages and Comparative Cultural Studies, University of Queensland.

 0.14

261

8</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7124-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7124_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:47:39">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106354</link><title>Confined within the margins : representations of masculinity, femininity, and gender roles in Australia's popular magazines of the 1960's</title><description>Ustinoff, Julie P. (2003). Confined within the margins : representations of masculinity, femininity, and gender roles in Australia's popular magazines of the 1960's PhD Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion and Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.12

598

16</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7124-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7124_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:48:45">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:244810</link><title>Analytical and classified catalogue of the Library of the Parliament of Queensland</title><description>Queensland. Parliament. Library. and O'Donovan, Denis. Analytical and classified catalogue of the Library of the Parliament of Queensland 2nd ed. ed. Brisbane: Govt. Printer, 1899.

 0.12

162

31</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7124-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7124_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:50:38">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:281824</link><title>Australian journal of communication</title><description>Australian journal of communication (1982) Volume 1 -21

 0.10

237

18</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>