<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7127">which cities surround long beach ca</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:26:51" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7127-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7127_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:26:59">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:190670</link><title>The economics of coastal foreshore and beach management: Use, safe bathing facilities, erosion and conservation</title><description>Blackwell, Boyd D. (2003). The economics of coastal foreshore and beach management: Use, safe bathing facilities, erosion and conservation PhD Thesis, School of Economics, The University of Queensland.

 0.55

501

213</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7127-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7127_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:29:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:205723</link><title>Rivers and resorts: how rivers and sheltered waters influenced the location of the Sunshine Coast's resort towns.</title><description>Osborne, Peter, 1962- (2009). Rivers and resorts: how rivers and sheltered waters influenced the location of the Sunshine Coast's resort towns.. In: , Journeys through Queensland history: Landscape, place and society: Proceedings of the Professional Historians Association (Queensland) conference, Brisbane 3-4 September 2009 : marking the sesquicentenary of Queensland 1859-2009. Professional Historians Association Queensland Conference, St Lucia, Queensland, Australia, (43-56). 3-4 September, 2009.

 0.46

47

139</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7127-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7127_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:32:52">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:288082</link><title>Approaches to risk assessment on Australian coasts: A model framework for assessing risk and adaptation to climate change on Australian coasts: final report</title><description>Woodroffe, Colin D., Cowell, Peter J., Callaghan, David P., Ranasinghe, Roshanka, Jongejan, Ruben, Wainwright, David J., Barry, Stephen J., Rogers, Kerry and Dougherty, Amy J. Approaches to risk assessment on Australian coasts: A model framework for assessing risk and adaptation to climate change on Australian coasts: final report. Woolongong, NSW, Australia: University of Wollongong and the National Climate Change Adaptation Research, 2012.

 0.46

104

12</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7127-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7127_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:35:11">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:155136</link><title>People patterns in paradise: an investigation of the socio-spatial structure of a postmodern city</title><description>Taylor, Alison Louise (2008). People patterns in paradise: an investigation of the socio-spatial structure of a postmodern city PhD Thesis, School of Geography, Planning and Architecture, The University of Queensland.

 0.44

384

93</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7127-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7127_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:36:32">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:298090</link><title>Modelling as an aid to understand the evolution of Australia’s central east coast in response to late Pleistocene-Holocene and future sea level change</title><description>Patterson, David Charles (2013). Modelling as an aid to understand the evolution of Australia’s central east coast in response to late Pleistocene-Holocene and future sea level change PhD Thesis, School of Civil Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.41

115

23</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7127-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7127_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:39:23">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:260117</link><title>Planning for sustainable coastal tourism development in Southeast Asia</title><description>Lei Tin Ong (2011). Planning for sustainable coastal tourism development in Southeast Asia PhD Thesis, School of Geography, Planning and Environmental Management, The University of Queensland.

 0.40

875

24</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7127-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7127_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:41:12">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:190684</link><title>Sallyanne Atkinson's Brisbane guide.</title><description>Atkinson, Sallyanne, 1942- Sallyanne Atkinson's Brisbane guide. Rev. ed. ed. St. Lucia, Qld. ; London ; New York: University of Queensland Press, 1985.

 0.39

66

234</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7127-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7127_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:43:57">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:200810</link><title>Discovering coastal Queensland : the complete guide to the Queensland coast, Great Barrier Reef, Stradbroke, Moreton, and Fraser Islands</title><description>Queensland. Dept. of Mapping and Surveying, Queensland. National Parks and Wildlife Service and Great Barrier Reef Marine Park Authority Discovering coastal Queensland : the complete guide to the Queensland coast, Great Barrier Reef, Stradbroke, Moreton, and Fraser Islands. St. Lucia, Qld.: University of Queensland Press, 1988.

 0.39

92

5</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7127-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7127_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:46:21">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:324915</link><title>Brisbane and its river / prepared for [the] 43rd ANZAAS congress, Brisbane, 1971.</title><description>ANZAAS. Congress (43rd : 1971 : Brisbane, Qld.) Brisbane and its river / prepared for [the] 43rd ANZAAS congress, Brisbane, 1971.. Brisbane: University of Queensland. Dept. of Geography., 1971.

 0.39

24

39</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7127-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7127_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 11:49:20">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:274979</link><title>Tourism and small coastal settlements: a cultural landscape approach for urban design</title><description>O'Hare, Daniel John. (1997). Tourism and small coastal settlements: a cultural landscape approach for urban design PhD Thesis, Joint Centre for Urban Design, Oxford Brookes University.

 0.39

253

429</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>