<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7129">avg home edition</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:11:44" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7129-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7129_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:11:49">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:292284</link><title>Get outside and smell the roses: the benefits of contact with nature during designated work-breaks</title><description>Fenwick, Caitlin (2012). Get outside and smell the roses: the benefits of contact with nature during designated work-breaks Honours Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.43

48

6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7129-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7129_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:12:21">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:239698</link><title>The Effect of Defendant Gender and Crime Orientation on Juror Decision-Making</title><description>Alice Miller (2010). The Effect of Defendant Gender and Crime Orientation on Juror Decision-Making Honours Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.43

213

17</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7129-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7129_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:15:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:243550</link><title>Turbulent velocity and suspended sediment concentration measurements in an urban environment of the Brisbane River Flood Plain at Gardens Point on 12-13 January 2011</title><description>Brown, Richard, Chanson, Hubert, McIntosh, Dave and Madhani, Jai (2011) Turbulent velocity and suspended sediment concentration measurements in an urban environment of the Brisbane River Flood Plain at Gardens Point on 12-13 January 2011. Hydraulic Model Report Series Hydraulic Model Report CH83/11, School of Civil Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.43

1032

468</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7129-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7129_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:16:00">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:301658</link><title>Haulage road pavement design for 300+ tonne trucks</title><description>James, Justin W C (2001). Haulage road pavement design for 300+ tonne trucks B.Sc Thesis, School of Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.32

56</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7129-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7129_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:18:38">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:220618</link><title>An optimised cellular automata model based on adaptive genetic algorithm for urban growth simulation</title><description>Liu, Yan and Feng, Yongjiu (2010). An optimised cellular automata model based on adaptive genetic algorithm for urban growth simulation. In: Eric Guilbert, Brian Lees and Yee Leung, ISPRS. Proceedings of the Joint International Conference on Theory, Data Handling and Modelling in GeoSpatial Information Science. Joint International Conference on Theory, Data Handling and Modelling in GeoSpatial Information Science, Hong Kong, (45-50). 26-28 May 2010.

 0.32

95

4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7129-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7129_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:19:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158601</link><title>THE ROLE OF FLUENCY IN MATHEMATICAL DEVELOPMENT: FACTORS ASSOCIATED WITH EARLY LEARNING DIFFICULTIES IN MATHEMATICS</title><description>Finnane, Maureen Kathryn (2007). THE ROLE OF FLUENCY IN MATHEMATICAL DEVELOPMENT: FACTORS ASSOCIATED WITH EARLY LEARNING DIFFICULTIES IN MATHEMATICS PhD Thesis, School of Education , University of Queensland.

 0.32

1477

13</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7129-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7129_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:21:55">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:288150</link><title>Alternate nightly haemodialysis in the home setting</title><description>van Eps, Carolyn Louise (2012). Alternate nightly haemodialysis in the home setting PhD Thesis, School of Medicine, The University of Queensland.

 0.30

56

12</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7129-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7129_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:23:25">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:217546</link><title>Tests of weak form efficiency in the Australian and American futures market</title><description>Crew, Sue. (1997). Tests of weak form efficiency in the Australian and American futures market Master's Thesis, School of Business, The University of Queensland.

 0.30

51

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7129-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7129_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:25:19">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:300418</link><title>Control of a thermoelectric cold plate utilizing experimental design methods</title><description>Coleman, Darren (1999). Control of a thermoelectric cold plate utilizing experimental design methods B.Sc Thesis, School of Computer Science and Electrical Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.29

37

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7129-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7129_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:25:50">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:218083</link><title>Trade versus aid : the case of Papua New Guinea</title><description>Ravusiro, Rima. (1989). Trade versus aid : the case of Papua New Guinea Master's Thesis, School of Economics, The University of Queensland.

 0.28

60

3</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>