<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7142">Amsterdam museums</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:59:06" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7142-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7142_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:59:11">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:198273</link><title>Decontextualisation, autonomy and the neo-avant-garde: Institutional critique and museum criticism</title><description>Stead, Naomi (2006). Decontextualisation, autonomy and the neo-avant-garde: Institutional critique and museum criticism. In: Davidts Wouter, Kruk Vinca and Teresa Stoppani, Museum in ¿Motion? Conference Proceedings. Museum in ¿Motion?, Maastricht and Sittard, Limburg, Netherlands, (1-14). 12-13 November 2004.

 0.77

150</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7142-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7142_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:01:42">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158379</link><title>Hijacked Agenda: The National Museum of Australia and the Gallery of the First Australians</title><description>Dauber, Christine Louise (2007). Hijacked Agenda: The National Museum of Australia and the Gallery of the First Australians PhD Thesis, School of English, Media Studies and Art History, University of Queensland.

 0.75

523

39</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7142-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7142_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:03:01">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:198598</link><title>Dynamic interactions of marine ecosystems with wrecks in Chuuk Lagoon, Federated States of Micronesia</title><description>MacLeod, I. D., Beger, M., Richards, V., Jeffery, W. and Hengeveld, M. (2007). Dynamic interactions of marine ecosystems with wrecks in Chuuk Lagoon, Federated States of Micronesia. In: C. Ed Degrigny, B. Ankersmit, I. Yolanda and R. van Langh, Metal 07, Preprints of the ICOM-CC Metals Working Group meeting. International Council of Museums (ICOM) Metal 07, Amsterdam, Netherlands, (51-54). 17-22 September 2007.

 0.62

44</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7142-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7142_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:04:28">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:317957</link><title>Direct U-Th dating of vertebrate fossils with minimum sampling destruction and application to museum specimens</title><description>Price, Gilbert J., Feng, Yue-xing, Zhao, Jian-xin and Webb, Gregory E. (2013) Direct U-Th dating of vertebrate fossils with minimum sampling destruction and application to museum specimens. Quaternary Geochronology, 18 : 1-8.

 0.56

27

1

Cited 1 times in Scopus1

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7142-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7142_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:07:03">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:293217</link><title>Belonging in the mining museum: an examination of Chinese Australian identity and belonging in discourses of the Gold Rush</title><description>Han, Alan (2012). Belonging in the mining museum: an examination of Chinese Australian identity and belonging in discourses of the Gold Rush PhD Thesis, School of English, Media Studies and Art History, The University of Queensland.

 0.56

128

12</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7142-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7142_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:09:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158669</link><title>The perceptions and motivations of visitors attending special events in galleries</title><description>Axelsen, Megan (2007). The perceptions and motivations of visitors attending special events in galleries PhD Thesis, School of Tourism, University of Queensland.

 0.55

470

38</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7142-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7142_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:10:47">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:246614</link><title>Cultural heritage conventions and other instruments: A compendium with commentaries</title><description>O'Keefe, Patrick J. and Prott, Lyndel V. Cultural heritage conventions and other instruments: A compendium with commentaries. Crickadarn, UK: Institute of Art and Law, 2011.

 0.54

177

49</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7142-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7142_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:13:38">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:296907</link><title>In the moment: the timeliness of Tinguely</title><description>Holden, Susan (2012). In the moment: the timeliness of Tinguely. In Shakin: the contemporary kinetic aesthetic e-catalogue (pp. xx-xx) Surfers Paradise, QLD, Australia: Gold Coast City Gallery.

 0.50

24</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7142-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7142_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:17:00">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:321818</link><title>The economic valuation of culture in Singapore: case studies of the Singapore Arts Festivals, National Museum and the Esplanade-Theatres on the Bay</title><description>Chang, Sharon (2013). The economic valuation of culture in Singapore: case studies of the Singapore Arts Festivals, National Museum and the Esplanade-Theatres on the Bay PhD Thesis, School of Economics, The University of Queensland.

 0.48

34

8</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7142-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7142_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:20:09">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:328070</link><title>The role of anthropological exhibitions in museums</title><description>Allen, Lindy (). The role of anthropological exhibitions in museums Honours Thesis, School of Social Science, The University of Queensland.

 0.47

8</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>