<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7146">why do leaves fall</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:18:43" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7146-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7146_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:18:50">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:218046</link><title>Australia</title><description>Alexander, Michael, Whitehouse, Gillian and Brennan, Deborah (2009) Australia United Kingdom: Department for Business Enterprise and Regulatory Reform, UK

 0.56

53

3</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7146-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7146_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:20:24">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:241415</link><title>Falls prevention education for older people designed using the Health Belief Model</title><description>Anne-Marie Hill (2010). Falls prevention education for older people designed using the Health Belief Model PhD Thesis, School of Health &amp; Rehabilitation Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.53

542

12</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7146-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7146_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:21:11">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:276315</link><title>Paid parental leave evaluation: Phase 1</title><description>Martin, Bill, Hewitt, Belinda, Baird, Marian, Baxter, Janeen, Heron, Alexandra, Whitehouse, Gillian, Zadoroznyj, Maria, Xiang, Ning, Broom, Dorothy, Connelly, Luke, Jones, Andrew, Kalb, Guyonne, McVicar, Duncan, Strazdins, Lyndall, Walter, Margaret, Western, Mark and Wooden, Mark (2012) Paid parental leave evaluation: Phase 1. Occasional Papers Series, 44: .

 0.50

93

14</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7146-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7146_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:21:46">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:216320</link><title>Are tourists rational? Destination decisions and other results from a survey of visitors to a North Queensland natural site – Jourama Falls</title><description>Tisdell, Clem (2010). Are tourists rational? Destination decisions and other results from a survey of visitors to a North Queensland natural site – Jourama Falls. Working Papers on Economics, Ecology and Environment 164, School of Economics, University of Queensland.

 0.48

46

29</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7146-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7146_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:22:49">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:220319</link><title>Domiciliary versus centre-based rehabilitation of older community dwellers: Randomised trial with economic evaluation</title><description>Tracy Comans (2010). Domiciliary versus centre-based rehabilitation of older community dwellers: Randomised trial with economic evaluation PhD Thesis, School of Health &amp; Rehabilitation Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.47

109

7</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7146-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7146_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:23:55">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:310896</link><title>What are the drivers that lead women to leave a senior role in Finance in Australia? A mixed methods study</title><description>Neck, Carolyn Rosemarie (2013). What are the drivers that lead women to leave a senior role in Finance in Australia? A mixed methods study PhD Thesis, UQ Business School, The University of Queensland.

 0.46

44

7</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7146-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7146_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:25:06">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:159654</link><title>Clinimetric evaluation of current and novel methods for the assessment of fall and fracture risk in residential aged care.</title><description>Miss Anna Barker (2008). Clinimetric evaluation of current and novel methods for the assessment of fall and fracture risk in residential aged care. PhD Thesis, School of Health and Rehabilitation Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.46

301

72</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7146-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7146_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:26:53">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:223994</link><title>Families, Maternity leave and the Law: A Survey</title><description>Grant, Jane (1996) Families, Maternity leave and the Law: A Survey The University of Queensland:

 0.46

19

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7146-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7146_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:27:49">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:145662</link><title>Don't Blame Me</title><description>Durrell, L. R.. Don't Blame Me.

 0.45

37

37</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7146-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7146_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:30:48">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:295826</link><title>The call to go: why youth ministry must leave the building</title><description>Benson, David (2013) The call to go: why youth ministry must leave the building. St Mark's Review: A Journal of Christian Thought and Opinion, 224: 62-69.

 0.45

23

6</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>