<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7147">breast cancer review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:33:34" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7147-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7147_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:33:41">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:192407</link><title>Symptom control in women with advanced breast cancer</title><description>Hardy, J. (2003) Symptom control in women with advanced breast cancer. Trends in Urology, Gynaecology and Sexual Health, 8 3: 19-26.

 1.31

39</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7147-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7147_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:36:13">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:177969</link><title>Breast cancer and abortion: collaborative reanalysis of data from 53 epidemiological studies, including 83 000 women with breast cancer from 16 countries</title><description>Bain, Christopher J. and Collaborative Group on Hormonal Factors in Breast Cancer (2004) Breast cancer and abortion: collaborative reanalysis of data from 53 epidemiological studies, including 83 000 women with breast cancer from 16 countries. Lancet, 363 9414: 1007-1016.

 1.25

64

Cited 96 times in Scopus96

28</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7147-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7147_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:37:18">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:166495</link><title>Breast cancer stem cells: Implications for therapy of breast cancer</title><description>Morrison, Brian J., Schmidt, Chis W., Lakhani, Sunil, Reynolds, Brent A. and Alejandro, Lopez J. (2008) Breast cancer stem cells: Implications for therapy of breast cancer. Breast Cancer Research, 10 4: 210-1-210-14.

 1.18

87

36

Cited 43 times in Scopus43

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7147-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7147_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:39:48">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:116296</link><title>Can the stroma provide the clue to the cellular basis for mammographic density?</title><description>Warren, R and Lakhani, SR (2003) Can the stroma provide the clue to the cellular basis for mammographic density?. Breast Cancer Research, 5 5: 225-227.

 1.13

50

14

Cited 15 times in Scopus15

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7147-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7147_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:42:08">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:173458</link><title>Partial breast irradiation for early breast cancer</title><description>Lehman, Margot, Hickey, Brigid E. and Francis, Daniel P. (2008) Partial breast irradiation for early breast cancer. Cochrane Database of Systematic Reviews, 3 : CD007077.1-CD007077.9.

 1.12

76

Cited 0 times in Scopus0

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7147-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7147_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:44:23">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:70406</link><title>Children's and family needs of young women with advanced breast cancer: A review</title><description>Turner, J. (2004) Children's and family needs of young women with advanced breast cancer: A review. Palliative and Supportive Care, 2 1: 55-64.

 1.08

67

Cited 8 times in Scopus8

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7147-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7147_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:45:45">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:114819</link><title>Molecular genetics of solid tumours: translating research into clinical practice. What we could do now: breast cancer</title><description>Lakhani, SR (2001) Molecular genetics of solid tumours: translating research into clinical practice. What we could do now: breast cancer. Journal of Clinical Pathology-molecular Pathology, 54 5: 281-284.

 1.07

39

12</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7147-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7147_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:46:54">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:257463</link><title>The relative economics of screening for colorectal cancer, breast cancer and cervical cancer</title><description>Gyrd-Hansen, D (1999) The relative economics of screening for colorectal cancer, breast cancer and cervical cancer. Critical Reviews in Oncology Hematology, 32 2: 133-144.

 1.06

21

8

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7147-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7147_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:49:17">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:114413</link><title>The mammary myoepithelial cell - Cinderella or ugly sister?</title><description>Lakhani, SR and O'Hare, MJ (2001) The mammary myoepithelial cell - Cinderella or ugly sister?. Breast Cancer Research, 3 1: 1-4.

 1.05

48

70

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7147-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7147_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:50:20">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:59172</link><title>Pathologic features of breast cancers in women with previous benign breast disease</title><description>Jacobs, Timothy W., Byrne, Celia, Colditz, Graham A., Connolly, James L. and Schnitt, Stuart J. (2001) Pathologic features of breast cancers in women with previous benign breast disease. American Journal of Clinical Pathology, 115 3: 362-369.

 1.03

39

11</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>