<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7150">senior java developer</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:30:06" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7150-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7150_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:30:11">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:188382</link><title>Implementing a service-oriented architecture for earth resources information</title><description>Stilgoe, Gavin (2009). Implementing a service-oriented architecture for earth resources information. In: , Novotel Sydney Manly Pacific, (). 9 - 13 November.

 0.63

87

131</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7150-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7150_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:31:48">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:179975</link><title>Complex Adaptive Processes of Supply Chain Formation and Collapse: Two Case Studies of Mango Supply Chains in West and East Java, Indonesia</title><description>Trina Fizzanty (2009). Complex Adaptive Processes of Supply Chain Formation and Collapse: Two Case Studies of Mango Supply Chains in West and East Java, Indonesia PhD Thesis, School of Integrative Systems, The University of Queensland.

 0.56

248

27</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7150-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7150_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:34:10">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:241116</link><title>An evaluation of current industrialisation in East Java and its potential for future development</title><description>Singgih, Moses L. (1995). An evaluation of current industrialisation in East Java and its potential for future development PhD Thesis, School of Economics, The University of Queensland.

 0.55

52

3</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7150-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7150_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:36:38">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:172822</link><title>Pentecostalism in Urban Java: a Study of Religious Change, 1980-2006</title><description>Robinson, Mark (2008). Pentecostalism in Urban Java: a Study of Religious Change, 1980-2006 PhD Thesis, School of Languages and Comp Cultural Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.54

407

22</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7150-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7150_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:38:21">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:107359</link><title>Power, progress and the course of empire: British ruin sentiment in Southeast Asia in the late eighteenth and early nineteenth centuries</title><description>Tiffin, S. P. (2005). Power, progress and the course of empire: British ruin sentiment in Southeast Asia in the late eighteenth and early nineteenth centuries PhD Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion and Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.54

111

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7150-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7150_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:39:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:188867</link><title>Universal collaborative annotations with thin clients – supporting user feedback to the atlas of living Australia</title><description>Chernich, Ron, Crawley, Stephen and Hunter, Jane (2009). Universal collaborative annotations with thin clients – supporting user feedback to the atlas of living Australia. In: , eResearch Australasia 2009. eResearch Australasia 2009, Novotel Sydney Manly Pacific, (1-2). 9 - 13 November 2009.

 0.50

101

107</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7150-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7150_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:41:17">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158374</link><title>Poverty reduction monitoring and assessment : a planning strategy to pomote more sustainable development in East Java - Indonesia : Malang as a case study</title><description>Surjono. (2007). Poverty reduction monitoring and assessment : a planning strategy to pomote more sustainable development in East Java - Indonesia : Malang as a case study PhD Thesis, School of Geography, Planning and Architecture, University of Queensland.

 0.48

728

24</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7150-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7150_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:43:57">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:224605</link><title>A study of the Indonesian coal industry</title><description>Lockchart, Peter Barter (1985) A study of the Indonesian coal industry The University of Queensland:

 0.44

51

3</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7150-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7150_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:44:29">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:211732</link><title>Scavenging ducks and transmission of highly pathogenic avian influenza, Java, Indonesia</title><description>Henning, Joerg, Wibawa, Hendra, Morton, John, Usman, Tri Bhakti, Junaidi, Akhmad and Meers, Joanne (2010) Scavenging ducks and transmission of highly pathogenic avian influenza, Java, Indonesia. Emerging Infectious Diseases, 16 8: 1244-1250.

 0.44

46

1

17

Cited 17 times in Scopus17

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7150-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7150_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:47:09">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:294158</link><title>VLPC: a HTML5 pharmacology virtual laboratory</title><description>Chen, S., Zornig, J., Chester, N., Tregloan, P. A., Cody, A. and Cheesman, M. J. (2012). VLPC: a HTML5 pharmacology virtual laboratory. In: , 2012 9th International Conference on Remote Engineering and Virtual Instrumentation (REV). 2012 9th International Conference on Remote Engineering and Virtual Instrumentation (REV), Bilbao, Spain, (). 4-6 July 2012.

 0.43

91

3

Cited 0 times in Scopus0

0</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>