<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7153">pig latin help</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:23:49" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7153-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7153_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:23:54">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:263544</link><title>Economics of Feral Pig Control</title><description>David Smorfitt (2011). Economics of Feral Pig Control PhD Thesis, School of Economics, The University of Queensland.

 0.58

205

20</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7153-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7153_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:26:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:221593</link><title>Target-specific vertebrate pest control in complex faunal communities: feral pig baiting in the Wet Tropics of Queensland, Australia</title><description>Andrew Bengsen (2010). Target-specific vertebrate pest control in complex faunal communities: feral pig baiting in the Wet Tropics of Queensland, Australia PhD Thesis, School of Animal Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.55

151

14</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7153-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7153_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:28:56">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:256829</link><title>THE ROLE OF PROTEASE IN UNLOCKING THE NUTRITIVE VALUE OF SORGHUM GRAIN FOR PIGS</title><description>Avril Finn (2011). THE ROLE OF PROTEASE IN UNLOCKING THE NUTRITIVE VALUE OF SORGHUM GRAIN FOR PIGS PhD Thesis, School of Agriculture and Food Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.49

213

14</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7153-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7153_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:29:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:269465</link><title>Observations on mild Teschen disease in Australia</title><description>Watt, Dennis Alexander (1978). Observations on mild Teschen disease in Australia PhD Thesis, School of Veterinary Science, The University of Queensland.

 0.44

79

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7153-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7153_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:30:46">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:157875</link><title>Classical swine fever in the Lao Peoples' Democratic Republic : virological, epidemiological and clinical studies</title><description>Blacksell, S. D. (Stuart Dean) (2001). Classical swine fever in the Lao Peoples' Democratic Republic : virological, epidemiological and clinical studies PhD Thesis, School of Molecular and Microbial Sciences, University of Queensland.

 0.40

264

12</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7153-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7153_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:32:22">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106095</link><title>The colour and oxidative stability of cooked pork</title><description>Hay, Theresa Kathleen Clare. (2002). The colour and oxidative stability of cooked pork PhD Thesis, School of Land, Crop and Food Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.37

129

3</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7153-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7153_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:34:43">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:286414</link><title>Immunological and molecular studies on Japanese encephalitis virus with reference to the Australasian region</title><description>Williams, David Thomas (2001). Immunological and molecular studies on Japanese encephalitis virus with reference to the Australasian region PhD Thesis, School of Molecular and Microbial Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.36

82

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7153-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7153_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:37:43">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106919</link><title>The significance of enterotoxigenic E.coli as a cause of pre-weaning piglet diarrhoea in North Vietnam</title><description>Do, Ngoc Thuy (2004). The significance of enterotoxigenic E.coli as a cause of pre-weaning piglet diarrhoea in North Vietnam PhD Thesis, School of Veterinary Science, The University of Queensland.

 0.36

136

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7153-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7153_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:39:46">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:105912</link><title>The role of mosquitoes in the emergence of Japanese encephalitis virus in Australia</title><description>van den Hurk, Andrew Francis. (2002). The role of mosquitoes in the emergence of Japanese encephalitis virus in Australia PhD Thesis, School of Molecular and Microbial Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.35

147

6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7153-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7153_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:40:37">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:271446</link><title>Dietary protein level and glucose and insulin dynamics in mature geldings</title><description>Barton, K.D., Foote, C.E., Cawdell-Smith, A.J., Anderson, S.T., Boston, R.C. and Bryden, W.L. (2011). Dietary protein level and glucose and insulin dynamics in mature geldings. In: , Recent Advances in Animal Nutrition in Australia, Vol.18, 2011. Recent Advances in Animal Nutrition in Australia, UNE, Armidale, NSW, Australia, (96-97). July, 2011.

 0.35

62</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>