<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7154">stones satisfaction</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:43:41" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7154-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7154_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:43:47">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:105768</link><title>Group task satisfaction : the construct of job satisfaction applied to groups</title><description>Mason, Claire Marjorie. (2001). Group task satisfaction : the construct of job satisfaction applied to groups PhD Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.65

231

3</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7154-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7154_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:47:22">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:313081</link><title>A randomized controlled trial of group stepping stones triple P: A mixed-disability trial</title><description>Roux, Gemma, Sofronoff, Kate and Sanders, Matthew (2013) A randomized controlled trial of group stepping stones triple P: A mixed-disability trial. Family Process, 52 3: 411-424.

 0.65

18

2

Cited 2 times in Scopus2

4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7154-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7154_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:50:09">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:218505</link><title>Provider emotional competence and workgroup emotional climate as influences on customer and provider satisfaction with service encounters</title><description>Gough, Helen. (1998). Provider emotional competence and workgroup emotional climate as influences on customer and provider satisfaction with service encounters Honours Thesis, Graduate School of Management, The University of Queensland.

 0.63

59

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7154-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7154_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:51:06">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:174814</link><title>Stepping Stones Triple P: An RCT of a parenting program with parents of a child diagnosed with an Autism Spectrum Disorder</title><description>Whittingham, Koa, Sofronoff, Kate, Sheffield, Jeanie and Sanders, Matthew R. (2009) Stepping Stones Triple P: An RCT of a parenting program with parents of a child diagnosed with an Autism Spectrum Disorder. Journal of Abnormal Child Psychology, 37 4: 469-480.

 0.59

212

44

Cited 52 times in Scopus52

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7154-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7154_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:54:15">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:302600</link><title>Stepping Stones Triple P-Positive Parenting Program for children with disability: A systematic review and meta-analysis</title><description>Tellegen, Cassandra L. and Sanders, Matthew R. (2013) Stepping Stones Triple P-Positive Parenting Program for children with disability: A systematic review and meta-analysis. Research in Developmental Disabilities, 34 5: 1556-1571.

 0.55

26

1

Cited 1 times in Scopus1

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7154-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7154_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:57:32">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:279309</link><title>Parent satisfaction with a neonatal hearing screening program</title><description>Rafidah Mazlan (2005). Parent satisfaction with a neonatal hearing screening program MPhil Thesis, School of Health and Rehabilitation Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.53

84

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7154-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7154_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:00:03">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:291077</link><title>Life satisfaction across the retirement transition: a latent growth curve modeling approach</title><description>Heybroek, Lachlan (2012). Life satisfaction across the retirement transition: a latent growth curve modeling approach PhD Thesis, School of Social Science, The University of Queensland.

 0.53

145

17</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7154-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7154_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:00:38">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:275661</link><title>Does social support explain the link between attachment and adolescent wellbeing?</title><description>Collins, Gene (2011). Does social support explain the link between attachment and adolescent wellbeing? Honours Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.51

98

23</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7154-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7154_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:03:45">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158797</link><title>Implementation and Evaluation of the Parenting Program Stepping Stones Triple P for children with Autism Spectrum Disorders</title><description>Whittingham, Koa Lou (2007). Implementation and Evaluation of the Parenting Program Stepping Stones Triple P for children with Autism Spectrum Disorders PhD Thesis, School of Psychology, University of Queensland.

 0.50

638

48</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7154-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7154_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:06:43">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:178791</link><title>Scarring, Habituation and Job Flexibility: Work histories in Secure and Insecure Employment</title><description>Colin P. Green and Leeves, Gareth D. (2009) Scarring, Habituation and Job Flexibility: Work histories in Secure and Insecure Employment. Discussion Paper No. 385, School of Economics, The University of Queensland.

 0.47

61

142</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>