<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7168">fabric glue</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:00:25" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7168-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7168_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:00:28">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:312232</link><title>The viability of strengthening existing timber bridge girders using carbon fibre fabric and carbon fibre laminate</title><description>Devlin, Michael (2004). The viability of strengthening existing timber bridge girders using carbon fibre fabric and carbon fibre laminate B.Sc Thesis, School of Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.40

9</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7168-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7168_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:02:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:305263</link><title>Development of novel materials and scaffold fabrication methodologies for soft tissue engineering applications</title><description>Luckman, Paul Stuart Ballantine (2012). Development of novel materials and scaffold fabrication methodologies for soft tissue engineering applications PhD Thesis, Australian Institute for Bioengineering and Nanotechnology, The University of Queensland.

 0.31

74

7</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7168-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7168_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:03:00">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:159849</link><title>Novel Hydrophobic Dendritic Sensitisers for Use in Dye-sensitised Solar Cells: The Effect of Molecular Structure on Performance and Charge Transfer Dynamics</title><description>Mr. Michael G. Deceglie (2007). Novel Hydrophobic Dendritic Sensitisers for Use in Dye-sensitised Solar Cells: The Effect of Molecular Structure on Performance and Charge Transfer Dynamics MPhil Thesis, School of Physical Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.30

123

20</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7168-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7168_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:04:46">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:300144</link><title>Test rig design for Mars gravity entry, descent and landing system</title><description>Yeh, Chi-Wei Simon (2005). Test rig design for Mars gravity entry, descent and landing system B.Sc Thesis, School of Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.29

39</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7168-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7168_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:05:16">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:319819</link><title>Bio-architectural technology and the Dreamtime knowledge of spinifex grass</title><description>Memmott, Paul (2013). Bio-architectural technology and the Dreamtime knowledge of spinifex grass. In: Stephen Kajewski, Karen Manley and Keith Hampson, Proceedings of the 19th CIB World Building Congress, Brisbane 2013: Construction and Society. CIB WBC13: 19th World Building Congress 2013, Brisbane, QLD, Australia, (1-14). 5-9 May, 2013.

 0.28

51

6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7168-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7168_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:06:21">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:132068</link><title>Mechanical properties and removal characteristic of cemented tungsten carbide with fine microstructure studied by nanoindentation and nanoscratch</title><description>Irwan, R. and Huang, H. (2007). Mechanical properties and removal characteristic of cemented tungsten carbide with fine microstructure studied by nanoindentation and nanoscratch. In: Martin Veidt, Faris Albermani, Bill Daniel, John Griffiths, Doug Hargreaves, Ross McAree, Paul Meehan and Andy Tan, Proceedings of the 5th Australasian Congress on Applied Mechanics (ACAM 2007). 5th Australasian Congress on Applied Mechanics (ACAM 2007), Brisbane, Australia, (240-245). 10-12 December, 2007.

 0.28

193

448</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7168-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7168_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:08:13">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:273250</link><title>The Nitridation of Silicon in Ammonia and Nitrogen</title><description>Rene Chaustowski (2012). The Nitridation of Silicon in Ammonia and Nitrogen MPhil Thesis, School of Mechanical and Mining Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.28

57

9</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7168-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7168_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:09:31">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:279390</link><title>Electrochemically produced hydrogen bubble probes for gas evolution kinetics and force spectroscopy</title><description>Donose, Bogdan C., Harnisch, Falk and Taran, Elena (2012) Electrochemically produced hydrogen bubble probes for gas evolution kinetics and force spectroscopy. Electrochemistry Communications, 24 1: 21-24.

 0.28

36

1

2

Cited 2 times in Scopus2

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7168-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7168_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:10:32">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:219387</link><title>Ex Vivo Tissue Vascularisation</title><description>Lien Chau (2010). Ex Vivo Tissue Vascularisation PhD Thesis, Aust Institute for Bioengineering &amp; Nanotechnology, The University of Queensland.

 0.28

183

19</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7168-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7168_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:12:17">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:9589</link><title>A Prototype E.S.D. Home: Towards a Model for Practice in Solar Sustainable Design</title><description>Hyde, Richard and Watson, Steve (2002). A Prototype E.S.D. Home: Towards a Model for Practice in Solar Sustainable Design. In: 36th Annual Australia and New Zealand Architectural Science Association Conference, Geelong, Victoria, Australia, (). November, 2002.

 0.27

459

1028</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>