<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7173"> severed spinal cord</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:17:10" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7173-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7173_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:17:14">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:85939</link><title>Molecular control of cell type diversity in the developing spinal cord</title><description>Yamada, Toshiya, Karunaratne, Asanka and Hargrave, Murray (1999) Molecular control of cell type diversity in the developing spinal cord. Clinical and Experimental Pharmacology and Physiology, 26 9: 741-745.

 1.16

31

0

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7173-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7173_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:18:42">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:194008</link><title>Viral vector-mediated gene transfer of neurotrophins to promote regeneration of the injured spinal cord</title><description>Hendriks, William T.J., Ruitenberg, Marc J., Blits, Bas, Boer, Gerard J. and Verhaagen, Joost (2004). Viral vector-mediated gene transfer of neurotrophins to promote regeneration of the injured spinal cord. In Aloe, Luigi and Calzà, Laura (Ed.), NGF and related molecules in health and disease (pp. 451-476) Amsterdam , Netherlands: Elesevier.

 1.06

51

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7173-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7173_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:19:53">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:199112</link><title>Quantitative analysis of cellular inflammation after traumatic spinal cord injury: Evidence for a multiphasic inflammatory response in the acute to chronic environment</title><description>Beck, Kevin D., Nguyen, Hal X., Galvan, Manuel D., Salazar, Desireé L., Woodruff, Trent M. and Anderson, Aileen J. (2010) Quantitative analysis of cellular inflammation after traumatic spinal cord injury: Evidence for a multiphasic inflammatory response in the acute to chronic environment. Brain, 133 2: 433-447.

 1.02

57

76

Cited 84 times in Scopus84

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7173-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7173_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:21:20">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:9626</link><title>Demyelination and Nerve Conduction Abnormalities in Acute and Chronic Experimental Allergic Encephalomyelitis in the Lewis Rat</title><description>Pender, M. P., Nguyen, K. B., Stanley, G. P. and Yoong, G. (1990). Demyelination and Nerve Conduction Abnormalities in Acute and Chronic Experimental Allergic Encephalomyelitis in the Lewis Rat. In: Takeshi Yonezawa, Satellite Symposium (Demyelination: Mechanisms and Background) of the XIth International Congress of Neuropathology. XIth International Congress of Neuropathology, Kyoto, Japan, (50-55). 9-11 September, 1990.

 0.97

485

876</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7173-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7173_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:24:45">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:176709</link><title>Treatment of spinal cord injury with co-grafts of genetically modified Schwann cells and fetal spinal cord cell suspension in the rat</title><description>Feng, Shi-Qing, Kong, Xiao-Hong, Guo, Shi-Fu, Wang, Pei, Li, Li, Zhong, Jin-Hua and Zhou, Xin-Fu (2005) Treatment of spinal cord injury with co-grafts of genetically modified Schwann cells and fetal spinal cord cell suspension in the rat. Neurotoxicity Research, 7 1-2: 169-177.

 0.93

57

16

Cited 20 times in Scopus20

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7173-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7173_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:27:25">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:61043</link><title>The effects of pregnancy on myelin basic protein-induced experimental autoimmune encephalomyelitis in Lewis rats: Suppression of clinical disease, modulation of cytokine expression in the spinal cord inflammatory infiltrate and suppression of lymphocyte p</title><description>Harness, J. and McCombe, P. A. (2001) The effects of pregnancy on myelin basic protein-induced experimental autoimmune encephalomyelitis in Lewis rats: Suppression of clinical disease, modulation of cytokine expression in the spinal cord inflammatory infiltrate and suppression of lymphocyte p. American Journal of Reproductive Immunology, 46 6: 405-412.

 0.93

47

6

Cited 8 times in Scopus8

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7173-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7173_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:29:28">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:217688</link><title>Differential development of sensory hypersensitivity and a measure of spinal cord hyperexcitability following whiplash injury</title><description>Sterling, Michele (2010) Differential development of sensory hypersensitivity and a measure of spinal cord hyperexcitability following whiplash injury. Pain, 150 3: 501-506.

 0.92

62

23

Cited 25 times in Scopus25

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7173-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7173_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:30:10">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:140852</link><title>Extensive spinal meningioma in a young dog</title><description>Yeomans, S. M. (2000) Extensive spinal meningioma in a young dog. Journal of Comparative Pathology, 122 4: 303-306.

 0.92

45

6

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7173-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7173_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:31:57">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:216628</link><title>Labour market outcomes for people with a spinal cord injury</title><description>Rowell, David and Connelly, Luke (2010) Labour market outcomes for people with a spinal cord injury. Economics and Human Biology, 8 2: 223-232.

 0.92

26

2

Cited 2 times in Scopus2

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7173-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7173_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:34:11">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:10396</link><title>Rapid entry and downregulation of T Cells in the central nervous system During the reinduction of experimental autoimmune encephalomyelitis</title><description>Gordon, F. L., Nguyen, K. B., White, C. A. and Pender, M. P. (2001) Rapid entry and downregulation of T Cells in the central nervous system During the reinduction of experimental autoimmune encephalomyelitis. Journal of Neuroimmunology, 112 1-2: 15-27.

 0.91

443

335

21

Cited 22 times in Scopus22

0</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>