<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7180">blink reflex</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:07:27" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7180-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7180_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:07:32">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:34658</link><title>The effects of prepulse-blink reflex trial repetition and prepulse change on blink reflex modification at short and long lead intervals</title><description>Lipp, OV and Siddle, DAT (1998) The effects of prepulse-blink reflex trial repetition and prepulse change on blink reflex modification at short and long lead intervals. Biological Psychology, 47 1: 45-63.

 1.58

35

9

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7180-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7180_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:09:49">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:74528</link><title>Attentional blink reflex modulation in a continuous performance task is modality specific</title><description>Lipp, O. V. and Neumann, D. L. (2004) Attentional blink reflex modulation in a continuous performance task is modality specific. Psychophysiology, 41 3: 417-425.

 1.43

99

12

Cited 14 times in Scopus14

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7180-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7180_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:12:34">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:74532</link><title>The effects of lead stimulus and reflex stimulus modality on modulation of the blink reflex at very short, short, and long lead intervals</title><description>Neumann, D. L., Lipp, O. V. and Pretorius, N. R. (2004) The effects of lead stimulus and reflex stimulus modality on modulation of the blink reflex at very short, short, and long lead intervals. Perception &amp; Psychophysics, 66 1: 141-151.

 1.41

60

7

Cited 6 times in Scopus6

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7180-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7180_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:13:08">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:66481</link><title>The independent effects of attention and lead stimulus properties on the acoustic blink reflex</title><description>Neumann, DL and Lipp, OV (2003) The independent effects of attention and lead stimulus properties on the acoustic blink reflex. Journal of Psychophysiology, 17 3: 124-134.

 1.27

32

1

Cited 2 times in Scopus2

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7180-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7180_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:13:44">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:62285</link><title>Lead stimulus modality change and the attentional modulation of the acoustic and electrical blink reflex</title><description>Lipp, OV, Neumann, DL and McHugh, MJ (2002) Lead stimulus modality change and the attentional modulation of the acoustic and electrical blink reflex. Biological Psychology, 62 1: 27-48.

 1.25

39

10

Cited 11 times in Scopus11

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7180-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7180_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:15:27">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:248285</link><title>The Effect of Repeated Prepulse-Blink Reflex Trials On Blink Reflex Modulation At Short Lead Intervals</title><description>Lipp, OV, Arnold, SL, Siddle, Dat and Dawson, ME (1994) The Effect of Repeated Prepulse-Blink Reflex Trials On Blink Reflex Modulation At Short Lead Intervals. Biological Psychology, 38 1: 19-36.

 1.23

14

14

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7180-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7180_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:17:18">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:74527</link><title>The effect of stimulus modality and task difficulty on attentional modulation of blink startle</title><description>Neumann, DL, Lipp, OV and McHugh, MJ (2004) The effect of stimulus modality and task difficulty on attentional modulation of blink startle. Psychophysiology, 41 3: 407-416.

 1.21

41

9

Cited 9 times in Scopus9

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7180-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7180_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:17:57">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:130792</link><title>Startle blink facilitation during the go signal of a reaction time task is not affected by movement preparation or attention to the go signal</title><description>Lipp, OV, Alhadad, SS and Purkis, HM (2007) Startle blink facilitation during the go signal of a reaction time task is not affected by movement preparation or attention to the go signal. Neuroscience Letters, 427 2: 94-98.

 1.20

50

1

Cited 1 times in Scopus1

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7180-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7180_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:20:33">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:62378</link><title>Spontaneous and reflexive eye activity measures of mental workload</title><description>Neumann, DL and Lipp, OV (2002) Spontaneous and reflexive eye activity measures of mental workload. Australian Journal of Psychology, 54 3: 174-179.

 1.17

59

4

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7180-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7180_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:23:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:78430</link><title>The effects of affective picture stimuli on blink modulation in adults and children</title><description>Waters, A. M., Lipp, O. V. and Spence, S. H. (2005) The effects of affective picture stimuli on blink modulation in adults and children. Biological Psychology, 68 3: 257-281.

 1.16

56

15

Cited 15 times in Scopus15

0</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>