<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7185">constitution of italy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:16:36" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7185-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7185_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:16:41">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:206982</link><title>Musical ecologies: An examination of the mutually constitutive nature of cultural and individual processes in children's musical learning and development</title><description>Barrett, Margaret (2004). Musical ecologies: An examination of the mutually constitutive nature of cultural and individual processes in children's musical learning and development. In: Michele Biasutti, Psicologia e Educazione Musicale. Proceedings of: Simposio Internazionale Psicologia e Educazione Musicale. PME04: Simposio Internazionale Psicologia e Educazione Musicale (International Symposium on Psychology and Music Education), Padova, Italy, (). 29-30 November 2004.

 0.71

50</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7185-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7185_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:18:42">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:289660</link><title>Una società di società: why Australia is a Federation</title><description>Aroney, Nicholas (2012) Una società di società: why Australia is a Federation. Giornale Di Storia Constituzionale, 24 2: 23-33.

 0.61

75

3

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7185-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7185_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:21:32">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:104088</link><title>Environmentalism versus constitutionalism: A contest without winners</title><description>Ratnapala, A. S. (2006). Environmentalism versus constitutionalism: A contest without winners. In: , Environmentalism versus constitutionalism: A contest without winners. Joint Meeting of the Law and Economics Association of New Zealand and the New Zealand Association of Economists, Wellington, New Zealand, (1-37). 28 June 2006.

 0.59

65

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7185-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7185_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:22:58">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:177812</link><title>Environmentalism versus constitutionalism: A contest without winners</title><description>Ratnapala, Suri (2007) Environmentalism versus constitutionalism: A contest without winners. Resource Management Theory and Practice, 3 : 110-164.

 0.59

96</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7185-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7185_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:23:59">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:281089</link><title>Economics of collective choice-The missing dimension of constitutional theory</title><description>Ratnapala, Anura (2012) Economics of collective choice-The missing dimension of constitutional theory. Public Choice, 152 3: 461-466.

 0.57

23

0

Cited 0 times in Scopus0

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7185-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7185_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:26:35">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:236774</link><title>Patterns</title><description>Taylor, Mark (2010). Patterns. In Luca Basso Peressut, Imma Forino, Genaro Postiglione and Roberto Rizzi (Ed.), Interior Wor(l)ds * (pp. 228-233) Torino, Italy: Umberto Allemandi.

 0.56

62

3</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7185-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7185_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:28:19">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:187146</link><title>International perspectives on pedagogies of inclusion in music education : theorising practice</title><description>Saether, Eva, Ballantyne, Julie, Ruthmann, Alex, Dillon, Steven C. and Harrison, Scott (2008). International perspectives on pedagogies of inclusion in music education : theorising practice. In: International Society of Music Education (ISME) Symposium : International Perspectives on Pedagogies of Inclusion in Music Education : Theorising Practice, Bologna, Italy, (). July 2008.

 0.49

52</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7185-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7185_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:31:09">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158227</link><title>Soldiers and civilians in Italy AD 493-551</title><description>Fletcher, Maria Louise (2006). Soldiers and civilians in Italy AD 493-551 MPhil Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion, and Classics, University of Queensland.

 0.47

113

6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7185-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7185_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:33:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:228366</link><title>Distributed embedded Real-Time systems and beyond: A vision of future road vehicle management</title><description>Wedde, Horst F., Lehnhoff, Sebastian, Rehtanz, Christian and Krause, Olav (2008). Distributed embedded Real-Time systems and beyond: A vision of future road vehicle management. In: , Proceedings of the 34th Euromicro Conference on Software Engineering and Advanced Applications (SEAA'08). 34th Euromicro Conference on Software Engineering and Advanced Applications (SEAA'08), Parma, Italy, (401-408). 3-5 September 2008.

 0.45

39

0

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7185-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7185_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:34:40">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:177581</link><title>"Before everything, remain Italian": Fascism and the Italian population of Queensland 1910-1945</title><description>Brown, David (2008). "Before everything, remain Italian": Fascism and the Italian population of Queensland 1910-1945 PhD Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion and Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.45

443

2771</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>