<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7197">contraceptive diaphragm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:33:27" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7197-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7197_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:33:31">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:275449</link><title>Hormonal contraception and mate selection: Are non-ovulating women disadvantaged?</title><description>Auld, Catherine (2011). Hormonal contraception and mate selection: Are non-ovulating women disadvantaged? Honours Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.74

149

46</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7197-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7197_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:34:40">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:245876</link><title>The wandering mirena: Laparoscopic retrieval</title><description>Erian, Mark, McLaren, Glenda and Baartz, David (2011) The wandering mirena: Laparoscopic retrieval. Journal of the Society of Laparoendoscopic Surgeons, 15 1: 127-130.

 0.70

25

0

Cited 1 times in Scopus1

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7197-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7197_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:35:54">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:62540</link><title>Physiological responses to the menstrual cycle - Implications for the development of heat illness in female athletes</title><description>Marsh, S. A. and Jenkins, D. G. (2002) Physiological responses to the menstrual cycle - Implications for the development of heat illness in female athletes. Sports Medicine, 32 10: 601-614.

 0.54

70

10

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7197-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7197_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:38:24">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:219812</link><title>Birds, bees and birth control: a history of Family Planning in Queensland 1971-2001</title><description>Bannah, Sylvia (2010). Birds, bees and birth control: a history of Family Planning in Queensland 1971-2001 PhD Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion and Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.37

147

220</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7197-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7197_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:41:23">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:243717</link><title>Semper floreat</title><description>Semper floreat (1970) Volume 40 Issue 9

 0.35

31

593</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7197-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7197_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:42:06">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158798</link><title>Epidemiological Factors in the Development of Epithelial Ovarian and Related Cancers</title><description>Jordan, Susan J. (2007). Epidemiological Factors in the Development of Epithelial Ovarian and Related Cancers PhD Thesis, School of Population Health, University of Queensland.

 0.32

282

11</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7197-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7197_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:43:11">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:187061</link><title>A FEMINIST ANALYSIS OF THE EFFECTS OF CHANGING SOCIAL STRUCTURES ON THE RELIGIOUS BELIEFS AND PRACTICES OF WOMEN LIVING IN IRELAND AND IRISH FEMALE EMIGRANTS TO AUSTRALIA</title><description>Bridget Broadbent (2009). A FEMINIST ANALYSIS OF THE EFFECTS OF CHANGING SOCIAL STRUCTURES ON THE RELIGIOUS BELIEFS AND PRACTICES OF WOMEN LIVING IN IRELAND AND IRISH FEMALE EMIGRANTS TO AUSTRALIA PhD Thesis, School of Social Science, The University of Queensland.

 0.31

173

21</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7197-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7197_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:43:43">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:258963</link><title>Survival and prognostic factors in epithelial ovarian cancer : follow-up of an Australian case-control study</title><description>Nagle, C. M. (Christina Mary) (2003). Survival and prognostic factors in epithelial ovarian cancer : follow-up of an Australian case-control study PhD Thesis, School of Population Health, The University of Queensland.

 0.26

49

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7197-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7197_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:46:00">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:227862</link><title>Fertility and infertility: studies in reproductive epidemiology in Australia</title><description>Danielle Herbert (2011). Fertility and infertility: studies in reproductive epidemiology in Australia PhD Thesis, School of Population Health, The University of Queensland.

 0.26

989

73</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7197-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7197_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 06:47:16">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:157859</link><title>UNDERSTANDING AND PREVENTING HIV-RISK RELATED SEXUAL BEHAVIOURS: EXAMINATION OF THE UTILITY OF THE THEORIES OF REASONED ACTION AND PLANNED BEHAVIOUR</title><description>Johnston, Trisha Carol (2000). UNDERSTANDING AND PREVENTING HIV-RISK RELATED SEXUAL BEHAVIOURS: EXAMINATION OF THE UTILITY OF THE THEORIES OF REASONED ACTION AND PLANNED BEHAVIOUR PhD Thesis, Psychology, University of Queensland.

 0.24

338

1</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>