<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7207">earthquake</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:21:38" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7207-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7207_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:21:41">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:150850</link><title>Evolution of earthquake statistics and forecasting the earthquake hazard</title><description>Mora, P. R., Jaume, S. C. and Place, D. G. (1999). Evolution of earthquake statistics and forecasting the earthquake hazard. In: , The 10th Anniversary of the Newcastle Earthquake: Lessons Learnt. 1999 Australian Earthquake Engineering Society Conference, Sydney, Australia, ((13)1-(13)5). 29-30 September 1999.

 1.24

238</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7207-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7207_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:24:43">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:103216</link><title>The earthquake trend in Australia indicated by LURR method</title><description>Yin, Can (2005). The earthquake trend in Australia indicated by LURR method. In: , Earthquake Engineering in Australia - Conference 2005. Earthquake Engineering in Australia - Conference 2005, Albury, NSW, (). November, 2005.

 1.21

27</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7207-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7207_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:28:00">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:150842</link><title>Stress transfer, dynamic triggering and stress correlations: How earthquake occurences affects the timing and slip of subsequent earthquakes</title><description>Jaume, S. C. (1999). Stress transfer, dynamic triggering and stress correlations: How earthquake occurences affects the timing and slip of subsequent earthquakes. In: , APEC Cooperation for Earthquake Simulation (ACES) 1st ACES Workshop Proceedings. ACES Inaugural Workshop, Brisbane &amp; Noosa, Qld, Aust., (273-279). 31 Jan - 5 Feb 1999.

 1.21

34</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7207-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7207_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:28:47">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:104987</link><title>Coulomb stress changes due to Queensland earthquakes and the implications for seismic risk assessment</title><description>Weatherley, D K (2006). Coulomb stress changes due to Queensland earthquakes and the implications for seismic risk assessment. In: K. McCue and Sonja Lenz, Earthquake Engineering in Australia. Earthquake Engineering in Australia 2006, Canberra, ACT, (145-150). 24-26 November 2006.

 1.21

89</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7207-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7207_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:29:23">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:204864</link><title>Numerical investigation of earthquake trend around Sumatra region by a LURR method</title><description>Yin, C and Xing, H. L. (2008). Numerical investigation of earthquake trend around Sumatra region by a LURR method. In: , Eos Transactions AGU (American Geophysical Union). Supplement. Proceedings of: 2008 Western Pacific Geophysics Meeting. WP08: 2008 Western Pacific Geophysics Meeting, Cairns, QLD, Australia, (). 29 July-1 August 2008.

 1.17

48</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7207-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7207_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:31:33">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:194704</link><title>Mangroves and uplift:'Helpem Petu Fren': Responding to the impacts and consequences of the 2007 earthquake on mangrove areas of Ranongga Island, Solomon Islands</title><description>Duke, Norman C. (2007) Mangroves and uplift:'Helpem Petu Fren': Responding to the impacts and consequences of the 2007 earthquake on mangrove areas of Ranongga Island, Solomon Islands. , Centre for Marine Studies, The University of Queensland.

 1.09

41</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7207-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7207_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:33:16">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:149049</link><title>Earthquake forecasting: retrospective studies in Australia - The Newcastle and Burra earthquakes - and numberical simulation of the physical process</title><description>Mora, P. R., Place, D. G., Wang, Y., Peng, K. and Weatherley, D. (2000). Earthquake forecasting: retrospective studies in Australia - The Newcastle and Burra earthquakes - and numberical simulation of the physical process. In: V. H. Jensen and B. Butler, Dams, Fault Scarps and Earthquakes. 2000 Australian Earthquake Engineering Society Conference., Hobart, Tasmania, (Paper number 28). no date given.

 1.08

89</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7207-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7207_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:34:37">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:150855</link><title>Accelerating energy release prior to large events in simulated earthquake cycles: implications for earthquake forecasting</title><description>Mora, P. R. and Place, D. G. (1999). Accelerating energy release prior to large events in simulated earthquake cycles: implications for earthquake forecasting. In: , APEC Cooperation for Earthquake Simulation (ACES) 1st ACES Workshop Proceedings. ACES Inaugural Workshop, Brisbane &amp; Noosa, Qld, Aust., (513-519). 31 January - 5 February 1999.

 1.08

89</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7207-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7207_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:35:36">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:150845</link><title>Accelerating seismic energy release before moderate to large earthquakes</title><description>Jaume, S. C., Mora, P. R. and Bufe, C. G. (1999). Accelerating seismic energy release before moderate to large earthquakes. In: , The 10th Anniversary of the Newcastle Earthquake: Lessons Learnt. 1999 Australian Earthquake Engineering Society Conference, Sydney, Australia, ((16) 1-(16) 5). 29-30 September 1999.

 1.08

105</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7207-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7207_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:37:01">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:101670</link><title>Lattice Solid and Cellular automaton simulations: Implication to earthquake forecastability</title><description>Mora, P. R., Weatherley, D. K. and Place, D. (2004). Lattice Solid and Cellular automaton simulations: Implication to earthquake forecastability. In: , 4th ACES Workshop Abstract Volume. 4th APEC Cooperation for Earthquake Simulation Workshop, Beijing, China, (1-3). 9-14 July, 2004.

 1.07

33</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>