<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7211">punctuation guide</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:08:26" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7211-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7211_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:08:33">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:162362</link><title>The effects of lowering prey density on the growth, survival and foraging behaviour of larval fat snook (Centropomus parallelus poey 1860)</title><description>Temple, Shelby, Cerqueira, Vinicius Ronzani and Brown, Joseph A. (2004) The effects of lowering prey density on the growth, survival and foraging behaviour of larval fat snook (Centropomus parallelus poey 1860). Aquaculture, 233 1-4: 205-217.

 0.40

38

24

Cited 25 times in Scopus25

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7211-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7211_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:09:16">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:311552</link><title>Plain language in technical writing: The case of the Australian Taxation Office</title><description>Stewart, Johanna (2013). Plain language in technical writing: The case of the Australian Taxation Office PhD Thesis, School of English, Media Studies and Art History, The University of Queensland.

 0.39

109

8</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7211-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7211_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:10:58">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:287309</link><title>An integrated zircon geochronological and geochemical investigation into the Miocene plutonic evolution of the Cyclades, Aegean Sea, Greece: part 2-geochemistry</title><description>Bolhar, Robert, Ring, Uwe, Kemp, Anthony I. S., Whitehouse, Martin J., Weaver, Steve D., Woodhead, Jon D., Uysal, I. Tonguc and Turnbull, Rose (2012) An integrated zircon geochronological and geochemical investigation into the Miocene plutonic evolution of the Cyclades, Aegean Sea, Greece: part 2-geochemistry. Contributions to Mineralogy and Petrology, 164 6: 915-933.

 0.35

51

2

Cited 3 times in Scopus3

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7211-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7211_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:11:28">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:137133</link><title>Developing generic criteria and standards for assessment in law: processes and (by)products</title><description>Hughes, Clair and Cappa, Clare (2007) Developing generic criteria and standards for assessment in law: processes and (by)products. Assessment and evaluation in higher education, 32 4: 417-432.

 0.34

87

367

Cited 3 times in Scopus3

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7211-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7211_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:12:29">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:7704</link><title>A Computational Analysis of Literary Style: Comparison of Kawabata Yasunari and Mishima Yukio</title><description>Tomatsu, Reiko (2006). A Computational Analysis of Literary Style: Comparison of Kawabata Yasunari and Mishima Yukio. In: Bennett, Kate, Jamarani, Maryam and Tolton, Laura Rhizomes: Re-Visioning Boundaries, School of Languages and Comparative Cultural Studies, The University of Queensland, (). 24-25 February, 2006.

 0.34

736

2832</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7211-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7211_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:13:52">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:224710</link><title>Economic growth : evolutionary and self-organisation perspectives on the micro-foundations of knowledge and the process of technological change</title><description>Philip, Pradeep. (1998). Economic growth : evolutionary and self-organisation perspectives on the micro-foundations of knowledge and the process of technological change PhD Thesis, School of Economics, The University of Queensland.

 0.31

269

6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7211-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7211_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:15:32">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:234745</link><title>Why did many more diamond miners than gold miners die in South Africa during the 1918 influenza pandemic?</title><description>Shanks, G. Dennis, Brundage, John and Frean, John (2010) Why did many more diamond miners than gold miners die in South Africa during the 1918 influenza pandemic?. International Health, 2 1: 47-51.

 0.31

56

2

Cited 2 times in Scopus2

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7211-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7211_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:16:11">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:241839</link><title>Front matter including table of contents, lists of illustrations and maps, foreword and preface</title><description>Dalton, Brian James and Smith, Anne (1996). Front matter including table of contents, lists of illustrations and maps, foreword and preface. In Dalton, B. J. (Ed.), Lectures on North Queensland history. No. 5 (pp. i-ix) Townsville, Qld.: Dept. of History and Politics, James Cook University of North Queensland.

 0.31

29

148</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7211-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7211_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:18:41">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:12564</link><title>Movements of feral camels in central Australia determined by satellite telemetry</title><description>Grigg, G. C., Pople, A. R. and Beard, Lyn A. (1995) Movements of feral camels in central Australia determined by satellite telemetry. Journal of Arid Environments, 31 4: 459-469.

 0.31

302

595

13

Cited 15 times in Scopus15

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7211-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7211_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:21:37">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:218827</link><title>Time in groups : group development, time management, appraised structured use of time, and group effectiveness</title><description>Chang, Artemis C. F. (2001). Time in groups : group development, time management, appraised structured use of time, and group effectiveness PhD Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion, and Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.30

171

3</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>