<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7216">salmonella</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:32:52" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7216-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7216_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:32:59">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:254521</link><title>Use of Salmonella Spp Carrier Strains to Deliver Bordetella-Pertussis Antigens in Mice Using the Oral Route</title><description>Guzman, CA, Timmis, KN and Walker, MJ (1993). Use of Salmonella Spp Carrier Strains to Deliver Bordetella-Pertussis Antigens in Mice Using the Oral Route. In: , Biology of Salmonella. NATO Advanced Research Workshop on Biology of Salmonella, Portorosa Italy, (453-457). May 11-15, 1992.

 1.18

14

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7216-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7216_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:33:45">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:200445</link><title>Dynamic remodeling of the endosomal system during formation of Salmonella-induced filaments by intracellular Salmonella enterica</title><description>Rajashekar, Roopa, Liebl, David, Seitz, Arne and Hensel, Michael (2008) Dynamic remodeling of the endosomal system during formation of Salmonella-induced filaments by intracellular Salmonella enterica. Traffic, 9 12: 2100-2116.

 1.12

30

21

Cited 20 times in Scopus20

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7216-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7216_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:36:15">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:72273</link><title>Quantification and prevalence of Salmonella in beef cattle presenting at slaughter</title><description>Fegan, N., Vanderlinde, P., Higgs, G. and Desmarchelier, P. (2004) Quantification and prevalence of Salmonella in beef cattle presenting at slaughter. Journal of Applied Microbiology, 97 5: 892-898.

 1.09

60

22

Cited 23 times in Scopus23

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7216-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7216_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:39:11">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:254696</link><title>Specific Lung Mucosal and Systemic Immune-Responses After Oral Immunization of Mice with Salmonella-Typhimurium-Aroa, Salmonella-Typhi Ty21a, and Invasive Escherichia-Coli Expressing Recombinant Pertussis Toxin S1 Subunit</title><description>Walker, MJ, Rohde, M, Timmis, KN and Guzman, CA (1992) Specific Lung Mucosal and Systemic Immune-Responses After Oral Immunization of Mice with Salmonella-Typhimurium-Aroa, Salmonella-Typhi Ty21a, and Invasive Escherichia-Coli Expressing Recombinant Pertussis Toxin S1 Subunit. Infection and Immunity, 60 10: 4260-4268.

 1.04

5

38</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7216-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7216_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:40:34">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:197135</link><title>Salmonella ecological study, South Australia 2008</title><description>Fearnley, E., Raupach, J. and Cameron, S. (2008). Salmonella ecological study, South Australia 2008. In: OzFoodNet National Face to Face Meeting: Enhancing Surveillance of Foodborne Disease Across Australia, Adelaide, Australia, (). 12-13 June, 2008.

 0.98

31</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7216-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7216_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:42:11">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:107876</link><title>Live attentuated Salmonella dublin vaccine development</title><description>Mizuno, T., Bensink, J. C., Frost, A. J. and Trott, D. J. (2003). Live attentuated Salmonella dublin vaccine development. In: MicroNZ2003: Annual Scientific Meeting &amp; Exhibition, Auckland, New Zealand, (). 28 September - 2 October, 2003.

 0.98

107</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7216-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7216_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:43:48">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:114704</link><title>Meningoencephalomyelitis in a foal due to Salmonella agona infection</title><description>Patterson-Kane, JC, Bain, FT, Donahue, JM and Harrison, LR (2001) Meningoencephalomyelitis in a foal due to Salmonella agona infection. New Zealand Veterinary Journal, 49 4: 159-161.

 0.98

48

3

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7216-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7216_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:44:49">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:290541</link><title>Systemic and Mucosal Intestinal Antibody-Response of Sheep Immunized with Aromatic-Dependent Live or Killed Salmonella-Typhimurium</title><description>Mukkur, Tks, Walker, KH, Baker, P and Jones, D (1995) Systemic and Mucosal Intestinal Antibody-Response of Sheep Immunized with Aromatic-Dependent Live or Killed Salmonella-Typhimurium. Comparative Immunology Microbiology and Infectious Diseases, 18 1: 27-39.

 0.97

12

8

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7216-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7216_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:45:31">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:257350</link><title>An antimicrobial peptide that targets DNA repair intermediates in vitro inhibits Salmonella growth within murine macrophages</title><description>Su, Leo Y., Willner, Dana L. and Segall, Anca M. (2010) An antimicrobial peptide that targets DNA repair intermediates in vitro inhibits Salmonella growth within murine macrophages. Antimicrobial Agents and Chemotherapy, 54 5: 1888-1899.

 0.93

41

11

Cited 12 times in Scopus12

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7216-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7216_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:46:55">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:183556</link><title>Introduction of new multidrug-resistant Salmonella enterica strains into commercial dairy herds</title><description>Adhikari, B., Besser, T. E., Gay, J.M., Fox, L. K., Davis, M. A., Cobbold, R. N., Berge, A.C., McClanahan, R. and Hancock, D. D. (2009) Introduction of new multidrug-resistant Salmonella enterica strains into commercial dairy herds. Journal of Dairy Science, 92 9: 4218-4228.

 0.93

48

5

Cited 6 times in Scopus6

0</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>