<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7218">edward kennedy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:04:18" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7218-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7218_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:04:24">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:130851</link><title>Retailing and the mature consumer</title><description>Edwards, F. and McColl-Kennedy, J. R. (1990). Retailing and the mature consumer. In: , Conference papers. Australasian Marketing Educators Conference (2nd : 1990 : South Australian Institute of Technology), Adelaide, Australia, (). 7-9 February, 1990.

 0.89

73</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7218-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7218_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:06:47">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:144259</link><title>Old world famine, new world plenty: The career of Sir Arthur Edward Kennedy</title><description>Harrison, Jennifer (1999) Old world famine, new world plenty: The career of Sir Arthur Edward Kennedy. Journal of the Royal Historical Society of Queensland, 17 4: 155-171.

 0.87

73</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7218-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7218_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:08:59">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:146830</link><title>Old world famine, new world plenty: The career of Sir Arthur Edward Kennedy, 1810-1883</title><description>Harrison, J. (1999). Old world famine, new world plenty: The career of Sir Arthur Edward Kennedy, 1810-1883. In T. Parkhill (Ed.), Familia 15 ed. (pp. 68-86) Belfast: Ulster Historicala Foudnation.

 0.82

55</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7218-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7218_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:10:02">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:60691</link><title>Factors in the decline of coastal ecosystems</title><description>Boesch, Donald, Burreson, Eugene, Dennison, William, Houde, Edward, Kemp, Michael, Kennedy, Victor, Newell, Roger, Paynter, Kennedy, Orth, Robert and Ulanowicz, Robert (2001) Factors in the decline of coastal ecosystems. Science, 293 5535: 1589-1591.

 0.81

98

34

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7218-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7218_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:10:37">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:104055</link><title>Employee responses to organizational wrongdoing as coping strategies: A process model and integrative review</title><description>Edwards, M. S., Keeffe, D. A. and Ashkanasy, N. M. (2006). Employee responses to organizational wrongdoing as coping strategies: A process model and integrative review. In: J. Kennedy and L. di Milia, Proceedings of the 20th Annual Conference of the Australian and New Zealand Academy of Management. 20th Annual Conference of the Australian and New Zealand Academy of Management, Yeppoon, Australia, (). 6-9 December 2006.

 0.74

71</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7218-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7218_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:12:29">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:211534</link><title>The Kennedy Expedition</title><description>Pike, Glenville (1954) The Kennedy Expedition. Journal of the Royal Historical Society of Queensland, 5 2: 953-968.

 0.68

49

725</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7218-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7218_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:14:10">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:260879</link><title>Allogeneic stem cell transplantation with peripheral blood stem cells mobilized by pegylated G-CSF</title><description>Hill, Geoffrey R., Morris, Edward S., Fuery, Madonna, Hutchins, Cheryl, Butler, Jason, Grigg, Andrew, Roberts, Andrew, Bradstock, Ken, Szer, Jeffrey, Kennedy, Glen, Morton, James and Durrant, Simon (2006) Allogeneic stem cell transplantation with peripheral blood stem cells mobilized by pegylated G-CSF. Biology of Blood and Marrow Transplantation, 12 6: 603-607.

 0.56

58

22

Cited 21 times in Scopus21

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7218-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7218_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:16:54">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:311752</link><title>Group 7 Workshop Presentation. Bridge to bridge, ridge to river: an urban design workshop. Outcomes and key recommendations</title><description>Skinner, Peter R., Thompson, Shane, Loneragan, John, Bouman, Oscar, Clausen, Nathan, Cloake, Des, Edson, Naomi, Henma, Murray, Kennedy, Morgan, McKeown, Mike and Zietsman, Milton (2013). Group 7 Workshop Presentation. Bridge to bridge, ridge to river: an urban design workshop. Outcomes and key recommendations, , Urban Design Alliance of Queensland, UDAL, BDA, GU, AIA, UQ, QUT, Architectus.

 0.54

19</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7218-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7218_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:19:09">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106734</link><title>Jonathan Edwards' spiritual sense as as complement to Locke's everday sense experience</title><description>Ball, Carol Elaine (2004). Jonathan Edwards' spiritual sense as as complement to Locke's everday sense experience MPhil Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion, and Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.54

121

11</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7218-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7218_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:19:45">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:241808</link><title>Pioneer squatting in the Kennedy District</title><description>Allingham, A. (1975). Pioneer squatting in the Kennedy District. In Dalton, B. J. (Ed.), Lectures on north Queensland history. Second series (pp. 77-96) Townsville: James Cook University.

 0.53

70

530</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>