<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7222">route 666</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:55:37" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7222-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7222_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:55:43">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:240854</link><title>Constraint-based dogleg channel routing with via minimization</title><description>Tseng, I-Lun, Chen, Huan-Wen, Lee, Che-I and Postula, Adam (2010). Constraint-based dogleg channel routing with via minimization. In: Hamid R. Arabnia, David de la Fuente, Elena B. Kozerenko and Jose A. Olivas, Proceedings of the 2010 International Conference on Artificial Intelligence (ICAI'10). 2010 International Conference on Artificial Intelligence (ICAI'10), Las Vegas, Nevada, United States, (666-672). 12-15 July 2010.

 0.56

56

Cited 0 times in Scopus0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7222-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7222_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:58:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158332</link><title>MODELLING DRIVER BEHAVIOUR UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF TRAFFIC INFORMATION</title><description>Panwai, Sakda (2006). MODELLING DRIVER BEHAVIOUR UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF TRAFFIC INFORMATION PhD Thesis, School of Engineering, University of Queensland.

 0.52

516

7</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7222-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7222_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:00:27">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:192380</link><title>Intradermal influenza vaccine administered using a new microinjection system produces superior immunogenicity in elderly adults: A randomized controlled trial</title><description>Holland, David, Booy, Robert, De Looze, Ferdinandus, McDonald, James, Karrasch, Jeff, McKeirnan, Maureen, Salem, Hatem, Mills, Graham, Reid, Jim, Weber, Francoise and Saville, Melanie (2008) Intradermal influenza vaccine administered using a new microinjection system produces superior immunogenicity in elderly adults: A randomized controlled trial. Journal of Infectious Diseases, 198 5: 650-658.

 0.46

98

114

Cited 133 times in Scopus133

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7222-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7222_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:02:22">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:224394</link><title>Alternate routing in telephone networks and the evaluation of marginal capacities</title><description>Gentle, N. F. (1969). Alternate routing in telephone networks and the evaluation of marginal capacities Master's Thesis, School of Computer Science and Electrical Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.41

51

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7222-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7222_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:04:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:224118</link><title>Interactive graphics solution to the shortest route problem as applicable to the ready mix concrete industry</title><description>Ham, Ian Geoggrey (1989) Interactive graphics solution to the shortest route problem as applicable to the ready mix concrete industry The University of Queensland:

 0.38

77

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7222-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7222_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:05:16">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:220127</link><title>The effect of ambiguity and incongruence on end user query perforamce / by Michael Hung Kam Tse.</title><description>Tse, Michael Hung Kam. (1998). The effect of ambiguity and incongruence on end user query perforamce / by Michael Hung Kam Tse. Honours Thesis, School of Business, The University of Queensland.

 0.36

46</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7222-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7222_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:07:35">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:246126</link><title>Antecedents of Trust and Collaboration within the Context of Cultural Route Tourism</title><description>Zhuo Wang (2011). Antecedents of Trust and Collaboration within the Context of Cultural Route Tourism PhD Thesis, School of Tourism, The University of Queensland.

 0.35

170

16</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7222-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7222_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:10:14">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:234388</link><title>Age-Friendly Buses: Development, Evaluation and Occupational Therapy Theory</title><description>Kieran Broome (2010). Age-Friendly Buses: Development, Evaluation and Occupational Therapy Theory PhD Thesis, School of Health &amp; Rehabilitation Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.35

209

32</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7222-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7222_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:10:46">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:225953</link><title>Economies of Scale In Bus Transport</title><description>Nanutsathit, Chakkaphant (1980) Economies of Scale In Bus Transport The University of Queensland:

 0.34

17

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7222-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7222_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:12:37">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106975</link><title>Synthesis and characterisation of mesostructured titania for photoelectrochemical solar cells</title><description>Kartini, Indriana (2004). Synthesis and characterisation of mesostructured titania for photoelectrochemical solar cells PhD Thesis, School of Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.31

224

3</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>