<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7234">347 ford engines</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:57:58" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7234-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7234_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:58:03">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:300092</link><title>Ethanol &amp; internal combustion engines, issues &amp; Wear</title><description>Prout, Andrew (2005). Ethanol &amp; internal combustion engines, issues &amp; Wear B.Sc Thesis, School of Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.38

81</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7234-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7234_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:58:46">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:226704</link><title>"The motor vehicle assembly industry in Australia--an industry study"</title><description>O'Grady, Ronals W. (1995) "The motor vehicle assembly industry in Australia--an industry study" The University of Queensland:

 0.31

88

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7234-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7234_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:00:15">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106181</link><title>Plots and plotters : narrative, desire, and ideology in contemporary American historiographic metafiction</title><description>Thomas, Glen Joseph. (2002). Plots and plotters : narrative, desire, and ideology in contemporary American historiographic metafiction PhD Thesis, School of English, Media Studies and Art History, The University of Queensland.

 0.31

392

9</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7234-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7234_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 16:02:12">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:284155</link><title>An imported railway - the background to construction of Queensland's early railway</title><description>Buchanan, Robyn (2012). An imported railway - the background to construction of Queensland's early railway MPhil Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion &amp; Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.30

109

14</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7234-05"><link>http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:236655</link><title>Modelling the influence of droplet properties, formulation and plant canopy on spray distribution</title><description>Dorr, G. J. (2010). Modelling the influence of droplet properties, formulation and plant canopy on spray distribution. In: P. Balsari, P. I. Carpenter, S. E. Cooper, C. R. Glass, B. Magri, C. Mountford-Smith, T. H. Robinson, D. Stock, W. A. Taylor, E. W. Thornhill and J. van de Zande, International Advances in Pesticide Application 2010. International Advances in Pesticide Application 2010 conference, Cambridge, England, (341-350). 5-7 January 2010.

 0.30

73

6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7234-06"><link>http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:226238</link><title>Strategic audit and analysis of western star trucks</title><description>Shand, Douglas W. (1987) Strategic audit and analysis of western star trucks The University of Queensland:

 0.28

25

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7234-07"><link>http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:270688</link><title>Interactions of meniscal cells with extracellular matrix molecules Towards the generation of tissue engineered menisci</title><description>Tan, Guak-Kim and Cooper-White, Justin J. (2011) Interactions of meniscal cells with extracellular matrix molecules Towards the generation of tissue engineered menisci. Cell Adhesion &amp; Migration, 5 3: 220-226.

 0.28

41

1

2

Cited 2 times in Scopus2

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7234-08"><link>http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:275756</link><title>Simulating Dynamic Complexity in a Water Quality Trading Market: Insights for Design of Nutrient Trading Programs</title><description>Steven Arquitt (2012). Simulating Dynamic Complexity in a Water Quality Trading Market: Insights for Design of Nutrient Trading Programs PhD Thesis, School of Geography, Planning &amp; Env Management, The University of Queensland.

 0.28

118

13</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7234-09"><link>http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:219298</link><title>Personal liability under small business trading structures</title><description>Sinnott, Peter J. (1989). Personal liability under small business trading structures Master's Thesis, School of Business, The University of Queensland.

 0.27

34</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7234-10"><link>http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:278745</link><title>Revisiting damping performance of the Queensland network under wind power penetration</title><description>Modi, Nilesh and Saha, Tapan K. (2012). Revisiting damping performance of the Queensland network under wind power penetration. In: , 2012 IEEE Power and Energy Society General Meeting. 2012 IEEE Power and Energy Society General Meeting, San Diego, United States, (1-8). 22â26 July 2012.

 0.27

99

6

0

Cited 0 times in Scopus0

0</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>