<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7241">flight simulators</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:38:49" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7241-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7241_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:38:54">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:142684</link><title>The numerical and experimental simulation of hypervelocity flow around the HYFLEX vehicle forebody</title><description>Johnston, IA, Tuttle, SL, Jacobs, PA and Shimoda, T (1999) The numerical and experimental simulation of hypervelocity flow around the HYFLEX vehicle forebody. Shock Waves, 9 1: 57-67.

 0.91

41

1

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7241-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7241_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:38:55">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:35318</link><title>Flush air data system calibration using numerical simulation</title><description>Johnston, I., Jacobs, P. A. and Shimoda, T. (1999) Flush air data system calibration using numerical simulation. Journal of Spacecraft and Rockets, 35 6: 812-820.

 0.91

376

0

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7241-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7241_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:38:56">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:304993</link><title>Developing a Policy Flight Simulator at the Acute Aged Care Interface</title><description>Gray, L., McDonnell, G., Gibson, D. and Broe, G. A. (2005). Developing a Policy Flight Simulator at the Acute Aged Care Interface. In: , Australasian Journal On Ageing. , , (A14-A14). .

 0.81

14

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7241-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7241_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:38:56">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:255694</link><title>The SCRAMSPACE I Scramjet Flight Experiment â Scientific rationale and technical developments</title><description>Tirtey, S. C., Boyce, R. R., Brown, L., Creagh, M. and Ogawa, H. (2011). The SCRAMSPACE I Scramjet Flight Experiment â Scientific rationale and technical developments. In: L. Ouwehand, Proceedings of the 7th European Symposium on Aerothermodynamics. 7th Aerothermodynamics Symposium, Brugge, Belgium, (). 9-12 May 2011.

 0.79

117

6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7241-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7241_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:38:57">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:3067</link><title>Application of genetic algorithms to hypersonic flight control</title><description>Austin, K. J. and Jacobs, P. A. (2002). Application of genetic algorithms to hypersonic flight control. In: Michael H. Smith, William A. Gruver and Lawrence O. Hall, Proceedings of Joint 9th IFSA World Congress abnd 20th NAFIPS International Conference. 9th International Fuzzy Systems Association World Congress/20th North American Fuzzy Information Processing Society, International Conference, Vancouver, Canada, (2428-2433). 25-28 Jul 2001.

 0.72

74

8

0

Cited 10 times in Scopus10</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7241-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7241_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:38:58">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:243229</link><title>Subscale testing of the FIRE II vehicle in a superorbital expansion tube</title><description>Capra, B.R., Leyland, P. and Morgan, R.G. (2004). Subscale testing of the FIRE II vehicle in a superorbital expansion tube. In: , 42nd AIAA Aerospace Sciences Meeting and Exhibit Online Proceedings. 42nd AIAA Aerospace Sciences Meeting and Exhibit, Reno, Nevada, U.S.A., (10498-10506). 5 - 8 January 2004.

 0.71

47

Cited 1 times in Scopus1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7241-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7241_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:39:00">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:204220</link><title>Comparison of reference frames in the linearisation of flight dynamics for spinning vehicles</title><description>Creagh, Michael A and Lind, Rick (2009). Comparison of reference frames in the linearisation of flight dynamics for spinning vehicles. In: , AIAA Guidance, Navigation, and Control Conference and Exhibit - AIAA Atmospheric Flight Mechanics Conference - AIAA Modeling and Simulation Technologies Conference. AIAA Guidance, Navigation, and Control Conference, Chicago, IL, United States, (). 10 - 13 August 2009.

 0.71

67

Cited 1 times in Scopus1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7241-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7241_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:39:02">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:123989</link><title>Visual control of flight speed and height in the honeybee</title><description>Baird, E., Srinivasan, M.V., Zhang, S.W., Lamont, R. and Cowling, A. (2006). Visual control of flight speed and height in the honeybee. In: , Lecture Notes in Computer Science 4095. From Animals to Animats 9 9th International Conference on Simulation of Adaptive Behavior, SAB 2006,, Rome, Italy, (40-51). September 25-29, 2006.

 0.68

60

2

24

Cited 18 times in Scopus18</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7241-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7241_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:39:03">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:204221</link><title>H-infinity control for attitude manoeuvres of a spinning asymmetric vehicle</title><description>Creagh, Michael A and Lind, Rick (2009). H-infinity control for attitude manoeuvres of a spinning asymmetric vehicle. In: , AIAA Guidance, Navigation, and Control Conference and Exhibit - AIAA Atmospheric Flight Mechanics Conference - AIAA Modeling and Simulation Technologies Conference. AIAA Guidance, Navigation, and Control Conference, Chicago, Illinois, (). 10 - 13 August 2009.

 0.68

68

Cited 0 times in Scopus0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7241-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7241_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:39:05">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:231203</link><title>UAV attitude control using the visual horizon</title><description>Thurrowgood, Saul, Moore, Richard J. D., Bland, Daniel, Soccol, Dean and Srinivasan, Mandyam V. (2010). UAV attitude control using the visual horizon. In: Gordon Wyeth and Ben Upcroft, Proceedings of the 2010 Australasian Conference on Robotics &amp; Automation. Australasian Conference on Robotics and Automation 2010 (ACRA 2010), Brisbane, QLD, Australia, (). 1-3 December 2010.

 0.67

100

3

Cited 0 times in Scopus0</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>