<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7249">largest alligator on record</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:46:58" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7249-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7249_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:47:06">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:10080</link><title>Movements and Home Ranges of Radio-Tracked Crocodylus porosus in the Cambridge Gulf Region of Western Australia</title><description>Kay, Winston R. (2004) Movements and Home Ranges of Radio-Tracked Crocodylus porosus in the Cambridge Gulf Region of Western Australia. Wildlife Research, 31 5: 495-508.

 0.51

328

921

27

Cited 26 times in Scopus26

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7249-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7249_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:47:09">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:10239</link><title>The Sub-Pulmonary Conus And The Arterial Anastomosis As Important Sites Of Cardiovascular Regulation In The Crocodile Crocodylus porosus</title><description>Axelsson, Michael, Franklin, Craig E., Fritsche, Regina, Grigg, Gordon C. and Nilsson, Stefan (1997) The Sub-Pulmonary Conus And The Arterial Anastomosis As Important Sites Of Cardiovascular Regulation In The Crocodile Crocodylus porosus. Journal of Experimental Biology, 200 4: 807-814.

 0.47

986

394

7</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7249-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7249_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:47:10">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:77836</link><title>Comparison of beam theory and finite-element analysis with in vivo bone strain data from the alligator cranium</title><description>Metzger, K. A., Daniel, W. J. T. and Ross, C. F. (2005) Comparison of beam theory and finite-element analysis with in vivo bone strain data from the alligator cranium. The Anatomical Record. Part A: Discoveries in Molecular, Cellular, and Evolutionary Biology, 283A 2: 331-348.

 0.47

137

292

31

Cited 34 times in Scopus34

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7249-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7249_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:47:11">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:287137</link><title>Uranium in Northern Australia : with special reference to the ore bodies of the South Alligator River area, Northern Territory</title><description>Shepherd, John H (1968). Uranium in Northern Australia : with special reference to the ore bodies of the South Alligator River area, Northern Territory PhD Thesis, , The University of Queensland.

 0.38

69

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7249-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7249_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:47:12">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158003</link><title>Population ecology of Crocodylus porosus (Schneider 1801) in the Kimberley region of Western Australia</title><description>Kay, Winston (2005). Population ecology of Crocodylus porosus (Schneider 1801) in the Kimberley region of Western Australia PhD Thesis, School of Integrative Biology, University of Queensland.

 0.37

321

22</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7249-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7249_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:47:14">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:9640</link><title>Population Ecology Of Crocodylus porosus (Schneider 1801) In The Kimberley Region Of Western Australia</title><description>Kay, Winston R (2005). Population Ecology Of Crocodylus porosus (Schneider 1801) In The Kimberley Region Of Western Australia PhD Thesis, School of Integrative Biology, The University of Queensland.

 0.37

1070

3006</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7249-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7249_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:47:15">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:9162</link><title>Osmoregulatory Mechanisms of the Australian Freshwater Crocodile, Crocodylus johnstoni, in Creshwater and Estuarine Habitats</title><description>Taplin, L. E., Grigg, G. C., Beard, L. A. and Pulsford, T. (1999) Osmoregulatory Mechanisms of the Australian Freshwater Crocodile, Crocodylus johnstoni, in Creshwater and Estuarine Habitats. Journal of Comparative Physiology B: Biochemical, Systemic, and Environmental Physiology, 169 3: 215-223.

 0.36

879

1186

3

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7249-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7249_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:47:17">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:212661</link><title>Biology of Sex Determination and Sexual Development in the Cane Toad (Bufo marinus)</title><description>Oganes Abramyan (2010). Biology of Sex Determination and Sexual Development in the Cane Toad (Bufo marinus) PhD Thesis, Institute for Molecular Bioscience, The University of Queensland.

 0.33

341

16</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7249-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7249_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:47:18">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:9185</link><title>Plasma Homeostasis and Cloacal Urine Composition in Crocodylus porosus Caught Along a Salinity Gradient</title><description>Grigg, Gordon C. (1981) Plasma Homeostasis and Cloacal Urine Composition in Crocodylus porosus Caught Along a Salinity Gradient. Journal of Comparative Physiology B. Biochemical, Systematic and Environmental Physiology, 144 2: 261-270.

 0.31

484

463

37

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7249-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7249_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:47:19">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:10237</link><title>Crocodiles as dinosaurs: Behavioural thermoregulation in very large ectotherms leads to high and stable body temperatures</title><description>Seebacher, F., Grigg, G. C. and Beard, L. A. (1999) Crocodiles as dinosaurs: Behavioural thermoregulation in very large ectotherms leads to high and stable body temperatures. Journal of Experimental Biology, 202 1: 77-86.

 0.31

1156

813

80</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>