<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7250">collagen vascular disease</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:47:56" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7250-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7250_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:48:03">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:66314</link><title>Tumor progression in hepatocellular carcinoma: Relationship with tumor stroma and parenchymal disease</title><description>Lockwood, D. S. R, Yeadon, T. M., Clouston, A. D., Crawford, D. G., Fawcett, J., Callaghan, S. A. and Gotley, D. C. (2003) Tumor progression in hepatocellular carcinoma: Relationship with tumor stroma and parenchymal disease. Journal of Gastroenterology And Hepatology, 18 6: 666-672.

 0.80

85

16

Cited 18 times in Scopus18

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7250-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7250_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:48:05">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:127943</link><title>Development of tissue engineered vascular grafts</title><description>Campbell, G. R. and Campbell, J. H. (2007) Development of tissue engineered vascular grafts. Current Pharmaceutical Biotechnology, 8 1: 43-50.

 0.75

63

32

Cited 44 times in Scopus44

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7250-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7250_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:48:06">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:38673</link><title>Which factors mediate cardiac fibrosis following myocardial infarction? Role of TGF beta 1 &amp; CTGF in pathological collagen deposition post-MI</title><description>Krum, H, Yao, J, Lim, S and Tzanidis, A (2002) Which factors mediate cardiac fibrosis following myocardial infarction? Role of TGF beta 1 &amp; CTGF in pathological collagen deposition post-MI. Circulation, 106 19: 232-232.

 0.74

72

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7250-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7250_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:48:08">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:78794</link><title>Cardiac extracellular matrix: a dynamic entity</title><description>Brown, L (2005) Cardiac extracellular matrix: a dynamic entity. American Journal of Physiology-heart And Circulatory Physiology, 289 3: H973-H974.

 0.71

34

14

Cited 17 times in Scopus17

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7250-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7250_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:48:09">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:36069</link><title>Novel vascular graft grown within recipient's own peritoneal cavity</title><description>Campbell, J. H., Efendy, J. L. and Campbell, G. R. (1999) Novel vascular graft grown within recipient's own peritoneal cavity. Circulation Research, 85 12: 1173-1178.

 0.68

62

162</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7250-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7250_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:48:10">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:60630</link><title>Reversal of cardiovascular remodelling with candesart</title><description>Brown, Lindsay, Fenning, Andrew, Shek, Annie and Burstow, Darryl (2001) Reversal of cardiovascular remodelling with candesart. Journal of The Renin-angiotensin-aldosterone System, 2 1: S141-S147.

 0.65

90

4

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7250-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7250_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:48:11">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:64976</link><title>Vegfb gene knockout mice display reduced pathology and synovial angiogenesis in both antigen-induced and collagen-induced models of arthritis</title><description>Mould, Arne W., Tonks, Ian D., Cahill, Marian M., Pettit, Allison R., Thomas, Ranjeny, Hayward, Nicholas K. and Kay, Graham F. (2003) Vegfb gene knockout mice display reduced pathology and synovial angiogenesis in both antigen-induced and collagen-induced models of arthritis. Arthritis and Rheumatism, 48 9: 2660-2669.

 0.64

71

62

Cited 68 times in Scopus68

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7250-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7250_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:48:12">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:100163</link><title>Vascular remodelling in the internal mammary artery graft and association with elevated endothelin-1 expression</title><description>Sutherland, A., Nataatmadja, M., West, M., Garlick, B. and Walker, P. (2004). Vascular remodelling in the internal mammary artery graft and association with elevated endothelin-1 expression. In: J. W. Butany, Cardiovascular Pathology. XIII International Vascular Biology Meeting, Toronto, Canada, (S120-S121). 1-5 Jun, 2004.

 0.64

75

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7250-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7250_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:48:13">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:188222</link><title>Loss of renal microvascular integrity in postnatal Crim1 hypomorphic transgenic mice</title><description>Wilkinson, L, Gilbert, T, Sipos, A, Toma, I, Pennisi, D. J., Peti-Peterdi, J and Little, M. H. (2009) Loss of renal microvascular integrity in postnatal Crim1 hypomorphic transgenic mice. KIDNEY INTERNATIONAL, 76 11: 1161-1171.

 0.64

49

8

Cited 9 times in Scopus9

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7250-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7250_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:48:14">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:270688</link><title>Interactions of meniscal cells with extracellular matrix molecules Towards the generation of tissue engineered menisci</title><description>Tan, Guak-Kim and Cooper-White, Justin J. (2011) Interactions of meniscal cells with extracellular matrix molecules Towards the generation of tissue engineered menisci. Cell Adhesion &amp; Migration, 5 3: 220-226.

 0.63

44

1

2

Cited 2 times in Scopus2

0</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>