<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7258">swahili dishes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:56:07" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7258-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7258_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:56:09">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:105983</link><title>An ideological and discursive analysis of English language teaching in the Sultanate of Oman</title><description>Al-Issa, Ali Said Mohammed. (2002). An ideological and discursive analysis of English language teaching in the Sultanate of Oman PhD Thesis, Graduate School of Education, The University of Queensland.

 0.21

791

7</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7258-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7258_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:56:10">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:243901</link><title>Semper floreat</title><description>Semper floreat (1988) Issue 3

 0.16

56

87</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7258-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7258_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:56:11">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:151770</link><title>Wild Spirit: Halfway Through Africa</title><description>Annette Henderson (2008). Wild Spirit: Halfway Through Africa MPhil Thesis, School of English, Media Studies and Art History, The University of Queensland.

 0.15

202

132</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7258-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7258_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:56:12">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:238498</link><title>Political community and peace-building in East Timor</title><description>Brown, M. Anne and Gusmao, Alex (2010). Political community and peace-building in East Timor. In Michael Leach, Nuno Canas Mendes, Antero B. de Silva, Alarico da Costa Ximenes and Bob Boughton (Ed.), Hatene kona ba, Compreender, Understanding, Mengerti Timor-Leste (pp. 21-25) Hawthorn, VIC, Australia: Swinburne Press for Timor-Leste Studies Association.

 0.14

108

8</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7258-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7258_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:56:13">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:185403</link><title>A depth-study of the Thaayorr Language of the Edward River tribe Cape York Peninsula: Being a description of the phonology with a brief grammatical outline and samples of lexicon and oral literature</title><description>Hall, Allen Harry (1969). A depth-study of the Thaayorr Language of the Edward River tribe Cape York Peninsula: Being a description of the phonology with a brief grammatical outline and samples of lexicon and oral literature M.A. Thesis, School of English, Media Studies and Art History, The University of Queensland.

 0.14

144

543</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7258-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7258_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:56:14">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158192</link><title>The undead : an unnatural history of vampires and troublesome corpses in Western Europe from the medieval period to the twentieth century</title><description>Keyworth, Gordon David (2006). The undead : an unnatural history of vampires and troublesome corpses in Western Europe from the medieval period to the twentieth century PhD Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion, and Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.13

1955

48</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>