<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7259">radish root</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:57:12" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7259-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7259_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:57:16">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:9969</link><title>Inhibition Of Adventitious Rooting In Backhousia Citriodora F. Muell. Cuttings Correlate With The Concentration Of Essential Oil</title><description>Kibbler, H., Williams, C. M., Williams, R. R. and Johnston, M. E. (2002) Inhibition Of Adventitious Rooting In Backhousia Citriodora F. Muell. Cuttings Correlate With The Concentration Of Essential Oil.

 0.72

547

1063</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7259-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7259_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:57:17">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:330473</link><title>First report of Pythiogeton ramosum (Pythiales) in Australia</title><description>Le D.P., Smith M. and Aitken E. (2014) First report of Pythiogeton ramosum (Pythiales) in Australia. Australasian Plant Disease Notes, 9 1: .

 0.56

Cited 0 times in Scopus0

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7259-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7259_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:57:18">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:240309</link><title>Adventitious root formation in Backhousia citriodora F. Muell : the stock plant barriers</title><description>Kibbler, Harry. (2002). Adventitious root formation in Backhousia citriodora F. Muell : the stock plant barriers PhD Thesis, School of Land, Crop and Food Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.52

106

6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7259-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7259_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:57:19">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:119968</link><title>Toxic effects of Pb2+ on the growth and mineral nutrition of signal grass (Brachiaria decumbens) and Rhodes grass (Chloris gayana)</title><description>Kopittke, Peter M., Asher, Colin J., Blamey, F. P. C. and Menzies, Neal W. (2007) Toxic effects of Pb2+ on the growth and mineral nutrition of signal grass (Brachiaria decumbens) and Rhodes grass (Chloris gayana). Plant and Soil, 300 1-2: 127-136.

 0.43

195

560

22

Cited 25 times in Scopus25

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7259-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7259_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:57:20">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158367</link><title>Developing Healthier Banana roots with mycorrhizae and rhizobacteria</title><description>Smith, Linda Jane (2006). Developing Healthier Banana roots with mycorrhizae and rhizobacteria PhD Thesis, School of Land, Crop and Food Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.32

760

20</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7259-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7259_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:57:21">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106106</link><title>Responses of Australian native plants to metal toxicity</title><description>Reichman, Suzanne Maree. (2002). Responses of Australian native plants to metal toxicity PhD Thesis, School of Land, Crop and Food Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.32

312

12</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7259-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7259_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:57:22">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:105856</link><title>The role and regulation of glutamate dehydrogenase in higher plants</title><description>Purnell, Matthew Peter. (2002). The role and regulation of glutamate dehydrogenase in higher plants PhD Thesis, Department of Botany/School of Life Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.31

202

4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7259-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7259_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:57:23">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:233617</link><title>Some factors that may influence the invasiveness of Mikania micrantha Kunth. ex. H.B.K. in Fiji</title><description>Macanawai, A. R., Day, M. D., Tumaneng-Diete, T. and Adkins, S. W. (2010). Some factors that may influence the invasiveness of Mikania micrantha Kunth. ex. H.B.K. in Fiji. In: S. M. Zydenbos, Proceedings of the Seventeenth Australasian Weed Conference (2010) - New Frontiers in New Zealand: Together we can beat the weeds. Seventeenth Australasian Weeds Conference (2010), Christchurch, New Zealand., (95-98). 26-30 September 2010..

 0.30

53

26</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7259-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7259_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:57:24">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:292285</link><title>Evaluating the natural herbicide potential of some medicinal and allelopathic plants in southeast Queensland, Australia</title><description>Allan, Sally M. (2012). Evaluating the natural herbicide potential of some medicinal and allelopathic plants in southeast Queensland, Australia PhD Thesis, School of Agriculture and Food Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.29

175

13</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7259-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7259_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 22:57:25">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:261942</link><title>Effects of the rare earth elements, Lanthanum and Cerium, on the growth and nutrition of corn and mungbean</title><description>Diatloff, Eugene. (1998). Effects of the rare earth elements, Lanthanum and Cerium, on the growth and nutrition of corn and mungbean PhD Thesis, Dept. of Agriculture, The University of Queensland.

 0.29

172

3</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>