<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7263">hospital acquired pneumonia</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:01:22" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7263-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7263_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:01:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:77903</link><title>Disease risk and mortality prediction in intensive care patients with pneumonia. Australian and New Zealand practice in intensive care (ANZPIC II)</title><description>Boots, R. J., Lipman, J., Bellomo, R., Stephens, D. and Heller, R. E. (2005) Disease risk and mortality prediction in intensive care patients with pneumonia. Australian and New Zealand practice in intensive care (ANZPIC II). Anaesthesia And Intensive Care, 33 1: 101-111.

 1.09

223

15

Cited 18 times in Scopus18</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7263-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7263_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:01:31">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:77904</link><title>Australian and New Zealand practice in intensive care (ANZPIC II: The spectrum of practice in the diagnosis and management of pneumonia in patients requiring mechanical ventilation</title><description>Boots, R. J., Lipman, J., Bellomo, R., Stephens, D. and Heller, R. E. (2005) Australian and New Zealand practice in intensive care (ANZPIC II: The spectrum of practice in the diagnosis and management of pneumonia in patients requiring mechanical ventilation. Anaesthesia and Intensive Care, 33 1: 87-100.

 1.03

215

11

Cited 11 times in Scopus11</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7263-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7263_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:01:32">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:293224</link><title>Australasian respiratory and emergency physicians do not use the pneumonia severity index in community-acquired pneumonia</title><description>Serisier, David J., Williams, Sophie and Bowler, Simon D. (2013) Australasian respiratory and emergency physicians do not use the pneumonia severity index in community-acquired pneumonia. Respirology, 18 2: 291-296.

 0.95

25

3

Cited 5 times in Scopus5

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7263-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7263_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:01:34">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:137781</link><title>Effect of a simple educational intervention on the hospital management of community-acquired pneumonia</title><description>Serisier, D. J. and Bowler, S. (2007) Effect of a simple educational intervention on the hospital management of community-acquired pneumonia. Respirology, 12 3: 389-393.

 0.95

39

4

Cited 5 times in Scopus5

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7263-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7263_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:01:35">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:215931</link><title>Should third-generation cephalosporins be the empirical treatment of choice for severe community-acquired pneumonia in adults?</title><description>Paterson, D. L. and Playford, E. G. (1998) Should third-generation cephalosporins be the empirical treatment of choice for severe community-acquired pneumonia in adults?. Medical Journal of Australia, 168 7: 344-348.

 0.90

49

10

Cited 10 times in Scopus10</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7263-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7263_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:01:36">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:242322</link><title>Current management of community-acquired pneumonia in children: An algorithmic guideline recommendation</title><description>Steele, R. W., Thomas, M. P. and Kolls, J. K. (1999) Current management of community-acquired pneumonia in children: An algorithmic guideline recommendation. Infections in Medicine, 16 1: 46-52.

 0.89

35

1

Cited 6 times in Scopus6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7263-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7263_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:01:38">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:76839</link><title>Empiric management of community-acquired pneumonia in Australian emergency departments</title><description>Maxwell, D. J., McIntosh, K. A., Pulver, L. K., Easton, K. L., CAPTION Study Grp and Tett, S. E. (2005) Empiric management of community-acquired pneumonia in Australian emergency departments. Medical Journal of Australia, 183 10: 520-524.

 0.88

496

23

Cited 29 times in Scopus29</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7263-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7263_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:01:39">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:76218</link><title>Australian and New Zealand practice in intensive care (ANZPIC II): Predictors of physician confidence to diagnose pneumonia and determine illness severity in ventilated patients</title><description>Boots, R. J., Lipman, J., Bellomo, R., Stephens, D. and Heller, R. F. (2005) Australian and New Zealand practice in intensive care (ANZPIC II): Predictors of physician confidence to diagnose pneumonia and determine illness severity in ventilated patients. Anaesthesia and Intensive Care, 33 1: 112-119.

 0.86

224

5

Cited 5 times in Scopus5</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7263-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7263_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:01:41">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:237150</link><title>Antibiotics for community-acquired lower respiratory tract infections secondary to Mycoplasma pneumoniae in children (Review)</title><description>Mulholland, Selamawit, Gavranich, John B. and Chang, Anne B. (2010) Antibiotics for community-acquired lower respiratory tract infections secondary to Mycoplasma pneumoniae in children (Review). Cochrane Database of Systematic Reviews, 7 7: CD004875-1-CD004875 -34.

 0.86

103

4

13

Cited 8 times in Scopus8

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7263-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7263_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:01:42">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:104131</link><title>The CAPTION Project: Implementation of guidelines for management of community-acquired pneumonia in hospital emergency departments</title><description>Pulver, L, McIntosh, K.A., Maxwell, D and Wai, A (2006). The CAPTION Project: Implementation of guidelines for management of community-acquired pneumonia in hospital emergency departments. In: , Using Evidence Using Guidelines Symposium. Using Evidence Using Guidelines Symposium, Melbourne / Langham Hotel, (57-57). 19-20 October, 2006.

 0.84

199</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>