<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7265">grassland plants</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:03:22" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7265-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7265_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:03:24">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:62398</link><title>International Grassland Congress Outlook: An historical review and future expectations</title><description>Humphreys, L. R. (2002) International Grassland Congress Outlook: An historical review and future expectations. Tropical Grasslands, 36 4: 193-198.

 1.22

38

0

Cited 0 times in Scopus0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7265-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7265_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:03:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:161974</link><title>Impacts of Tree Invasion on Floristic Composition of Subtropical Grasslands on the Bunya Mountains, Australia</title><description>Butler, Don William, Fairfax , Russell James and Fensham, Roderick John (2006) Impacts of Tree Invasion on Floristic Composition of Subtropical Grasslands on the Bunya Mountains, Australia. Australian Journal of Botany, 54 3: 261-270.

 1.12

259

4

Cited 4 times in Scopus4

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7265-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7265_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:03:29">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:130689</link><title>A survey of graziers' perceptions of long-term productivity of leucaena pastures in Queensland</title><description>Radrizzani, A., Shelton, H. M., Dalzell, S. A. and Kravchuk, O. (2007). A survey of graziers' perceptions of long-term productivity of leucaena pastures in Queensland. In: , Tropical Grasslands. 7th Australian Tropical Pastures Conference, Dalby, Qld, (240-241). 11-12 April 2007.

 0.98

82

0

Cited 0 times in Scopus0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7265-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7265_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:03:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:130690</link><title>Understanding the mechanism behind invasion of African lovegrass</title><description>Firn, J. and Buckley, Y. (2007) Understanding the mechanism behind invasion of African lovegrass. Tropical Grasslands, 41 3: 243-244.

 0.97

80

0

Cited 0 times in Scopus0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7265-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7265_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:03:32">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:78406</link><title>Leucaena in northern Australia: a forage tree legume success story</title><description>Mullen, B. F., Shelton, H. M. and Dalzell, S. A. (2005) Leucaena in northern Australia: a forage tree legume success story. Tropical Grasslands, 39 4: 226-226.

 0.97

70

1

Cited 1 times in Scopus1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7265-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7265_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:03:33">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:78401</link><title>Sesbania grandiflora: a successful tree legume in Lombok, Indonesia</title><description>Hasniati, D and Shelton, M (2005) Sesbania grandiflora: a successful tree legume in Lombok, Indonesia. Tropical Grasslands, 39 4: 217-217.

 0.97

67

0

Cited 0 times in Scopus0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7265-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7265_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:03:34">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:78439</link><title>Adoption of tropical legume technology around the world: analysis of success</title><description>Shelton, H. M., Franzel, S. and Peters, M. (2005) Adoption of tropical legume technology around the world: analysis of success. Tropical Grasslands, 39 4: 198-209.

 0.97

100

8

Cited 11 times in Scopus11</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7265-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7265_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:03:35">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:282772</link><title>Invasion of grasslands by silver wattle, Acacia dealbata (Mimosaceae), alters beetle (Coleoptera) assemblage structure</title><description>Coetzee, B. W. T., van Rensburg, B. J. and Robertson, M. P. (2007) Invasion of grasslands by silver wattle, Acacia dealbata (Mimosaceae), alters beetle (Coleoptera) assemblage structure. African Entomology, 15 2: 328-339.

 0.93

28

10

Cited 10 times in Scopus10

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7265-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7265_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:03:36">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:274710</link><title>Plant secondary compounds; their impact on forage nutritive value and upon animal production</title><description>Barry, TN, McNeill, DM and McNabb, WC (2001). Plant secondary compounds; their impact on forage nutritive value and upon animal production. In: , Proceedings of the Xix International Grassland Congress. 19th International Grassland Congress, Sao Pedro Brazil, (445-452). Feb 11-21, 2001.

 0.93

22

43</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7265-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7265_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-22 23:03:37">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:81682</link><title>Habitat use by Darling Downs population of the grassland earless dragon: implications for conservation.</title><description>Starr, C. R. and Leung, K. (2006) Habitat use by Darling Downs population of the grassland earless dragon: implications for conservation.. Journal of Wildlife Management, 70 4: 897-903.

 0.91

424

1

Cited 1 times in Scopus1

0</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>