<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7348">map of the united states</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:26:14" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7348-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7348_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:26:20">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:279414</link><title>The role of pedigree information in combined linkage disequilibrium and linkage mapping of quantitative trait loci in a general complex pedigree</title><description>Lee, S. H. and Van der Werf, J. H. J. (2005) The role of pedigree information in combined linkage disequilibrium and linkage mapping of quantitative trait loci in a general complex pedigree. Genetics, 169 1: 455-466.

 0.78

26

15

Cited 15 times in Scopus15

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7348-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7348_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:26:21">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:234039</link><title>Genomics meets genetics: Towards a mutant map of the mouse</title><description>Wells, C. and Brown, S. D. M. (2000) Genomics meets genetics: Towards a mutant map of the mouse. Mammalian Genome, 11 7: 472-477.

 0.77

27

9

Cited 13 times in Scopus13

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7348-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7348_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:26:22">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:300498</link><title>Methods in geomorphology: mapping glacial features</title><description>Hyatt, O. M. and Shulmeister, J. (2013). Methods in geomorphology: mapping glacial features. In John F. Shroder, A. D. Switzer and D. M. Kennedy (Ed.), Treatise on geomorphology (pp. 92-104) San Diego, CA, United States: Academic Press.

 0.75

49

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7348-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7348_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:26:23">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:135359</link><title>Mapping the Australian PR state</title><description>Ward, Ian (2007). Mapping the Australian PR state. In Sally Young (Ed.), Government communication in Australia (pp. 3-18) New York, United States of America: Cambridge University Press.

 0.73

197

4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7348-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7348_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:26:24">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:258642</link><title>Development of a linkage map and mapping of phenotypic polymorphisms in a free-living population of Soay sheep (Ovis aries)</title><description>Beraldi, Dario, McRae, Allan F., Gratten, Jacob, Slate, Jon, Visscher, Peter M. and Pemberton, Josephine M. (2006) Development of a linkage map and mapping of phenotypic polymorphisms in a free-living population of Soay sheep (Ovis aries). Genetics, 173 3: 1521-1537.

 0.72

28

39

Cited 39 times in Scopus39

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7348-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7348_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:26:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:228820</link><title>Maps and movies: talking with Deepa Mehta</title><description>Khorana, Sukhmani (2009) Maps and movies: talking with Deepa Mehta. Bright Lights Film Journal, 63: .

 0.72

34</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7348-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7348_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:26:27">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:316237</link><title>The development of product microstructure "morphology maps" and their significance in describing the decomposition of solids</title><description>Hayes, P. C. (2010). The development of product microstructure "morphology maps" and their significance in describing the decomposition of solids. In: , Jim Evans Honorary Symposium - Held During TMS 2010 Annual Meeting and Exhibition. Jim Evans Honorary Symposium - TMS 2010 Annual Meeting and Exhibition, Seattle, WA, United States, (257-265). 14-18 February 2010.

 0.71

8

Cited 0 times in Scopus0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7348-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7348_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:26:29">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:74275</link><title>Application of remote sensing and GIS in mineral resource mapping - An overview</title><description>Rajesh, HM (2004) Application of remote sensing and GIS in mineral resource mapping - An overview. Journal of Mineralogical And Petrological Sciences, 99 3: 83-103.

 0.71

410

15

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7348-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7348_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:26:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:229027</link><title>Integrating field data with high spatial resolution multispectral satellite imagery for calibration and validation of coral reef benthic community maps</title><description>Roelfsema, Chris and Phinn, Stuart (2010) Integrating field data with high spatial resolution multispectral satellite imagery for calibration and validation of coral reef benthic community maps. Journal of Applied Remote Sensing, 4 1: 043527.1-043527.28.

 0.68

103

0

Cited 13 times in Scopus13

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7348-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7348_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 00:26:31">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:104971</link><title>Newly mapped Paleozoic stratigraphic units in the Huanuco region of Central Peru: Tectonic implications for the Maraon fold-thrust belt</title><description>Scherrenberg, A. F. and Jacay, Javier (2006). Newly mapped Paleozoic stratigraphic units in the Huanuco region of Central Peru: Tectonic implications for the Maraon fold-thrust belt. In: , Backbone of the Americas: Patagonia to Alaska GSA Special Meetings: Abstracts with Programs No. 1. Backbone of the Americas: Patagonia to Alaska, Mendoza, Argentina, (). 3 - 7 April 2006.

 0.67

52</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>