<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7404">kobe bryant</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:21:14" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7404-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7404_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:21:21">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:263540</link><title>Structural basis of disease resistance in flax against flax rust</title><description>Thomas Ve (2011). Structural basis of disease resistance in flax against flax rust PhD Thesis, School of Chemistry &amp; Molecular Bioscience, The University of Queensland.

 0.29

135

15</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7404-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7404_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:21:22">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:305349</link><title>Development of bioinformatics tools to analyse peptide-protein interactions: Immunoinformatics applications in next generation vaccine design</title><description>Oyarzun, Patricio Alejandro (2013). Development of bioinformatics tools to analyse peptide-protein interactions: Immunoinformatics applications in next generation vaccine design PhD Thesis, School of Chemistry &amp; Molecular Biosciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.24

122

13</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7404-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7404_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:21:23">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:207381</link><title>Extract interesting skyline points in high dimension</title><description>Fung, Gabriel Pui Cheong, Lu, Wei, Yang, Jing, Du, Xiaoyong and Zhou, Xiaofang (2010). Extract interesting skyline points in high dimension. In: Hiroyuki Kitagawa, Yoshiharu Ishikawa, Qing Li and Chiemi Watanabe, Database Systems for Advanced Applications, Proceedings, Part 2. 15th International Conference on Database Systems for Advanced Applications (DASFAA 2010), Tsukuba, Japan, (94-108). 1-4 April 2010.

 0.23

105

9

0

Cited 0 times in Scopus0

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7404-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7404_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:21:25">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:268901</link><title>Worldwide international trade and economic development with an emphasis on Australia</title><description>Kastelle, Tim and Liesch, Peter W. (2011). Worldwide international trade and economic development with an emphasis on Australia. In: Shige Makino and Tunga Kiyak, Proceedings of the 53rd Annual Meeting of the Academy of International Business. Academy of International Business, Nagoya, Japan, (142). 24-28 June, 2011.

 0.22

67

44</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7404-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7404_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:21:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:268902</link><title>A scientometric investigation of articles published in the Journal of International Business Studies revealing empirically the evolution of the field</title><description>Liesch, Peter W., McGaughey, Sara L., Middleton, Stuart and Cretchley, Julia (2011). A scientometric investigation of articles published in the Journal of International Business Studies revealing empirically the evolution of the field. In: Shige Makino and Tunga Kiyak, Proceedings of the 53rd Annual Meeting of the Academy of International Business. 53rd Annual Meeting of the Academy of International Business, Nagoya, Japan, (229-229). 24-28 June 2011.

 0.22

64

38</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7404-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7404_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:21:27">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:268892</link><title>N-culturals:Functional individuals with multicultural identities</title><description>Pekerti, Andre Anugerah (2011). N-culturals:Functional individuals with multicultural identities. In: Shige Makino and Tunga Kiyak, Proceedings of the 53rd Annual Meeting of the Academy of International Business. 53rd Annual Meeting of the Academy of International Business, Nagoya, Japan, (135-135). 24-28 June 2011.

 0.22

60

26</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7404-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7404_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:21:28">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:268890</link><title>Fostering organizational citizenship behavior in Asia: The mediating role of trust and satisfaction on OCB in China and Indonesia</title><description>Pekerti, Andre A. and Sendjaya, Sen (2011). Fostering organizational citizenship behavior in Asia: The mediating role of trust and satisfaction on OCB in China and Indonesia. In: Shige Makino and Tunga Kiyak, Proceedings of the 53rd Annual Meeting of the Academy of International Business. Academy of International Business, Nagoya, Japan, (34). 24-28 June 2011.

 0.22

78

54</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7404-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7404_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:21:29">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:268900</link><title>The impact of entrepreneurial behaviour, network structural properties and network actor attributes on SMEs' Commitment to offshore expansion</title><description>Chen, John Yen-Kuang Chen, Steen, John and Kastelle, Tim (2011). The impact of entrepreneurial behaviour, network structural properties and network actor attributes on SMEs' Commitment to offshore expansion. In: Shige Makino and Tunga Kiyak, Proceedings of the 53rd Annual Meeting of the Academy of International Business. 53rd Annual Meeting of the Academy of International Business, Nagoya, Japan, (69-69). 24-28 June 2011.

 0.22

67

43</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7404-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7404_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:21:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:268896</link><title>An empirical investigation into a subsidiary absorptive capacity process model</title><description>Schleimer, Stephanie and Pedersen, Torben (2011). An empirical investigation into a subsidiary absorptive capacity process model. In: Shige Makingo and Tunga Kiyak, Proceedings of the 53rd Annual Meeting of the Academy of International Business. Academy of International Business, Nagoya, Japan, (36-36). 24-28 June 2011.

 0.22

48

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7404-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7404_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:21:31">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:268899</link><title>Time orientation in Hofstede and Globe: Long term orientation versus future orientation</title><description>Venaik, Sunil, Zhu, Yunxia and Brewer, Paul (2011). Time orientation in Hofstede and Globe: Long term orientation versus future orientation. In: Shige Makino and Tunga Kiyak, Proceedings of the 53rd Annual Meeting of the Academy of International Business. 53rd Annual Meeting of the Academy of International Business, Nagoya, Japan, (64-64). 24-28 June 2011.

 0.22

200

83</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>