<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7405">light therapy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:22:12" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7405-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7405_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:22:15">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:181500</link><title>How do people with aphasia view their discharge from therapy?</title><description>Hersh, D (2009) How do people with aphasia view their discharge from therapy?. Aphasiology, 23 3: 331-350.

 0.73

47

15

Cited 15 times in Scopus15

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7405-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7405_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:22:17">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:129596</link><title>Changes in postural activity of the trunk muscles following spinal manipulative therapy</title><description>Ferreira, M. L., Ferreira, P. H. and Hodges, P. W. (2007) Changes in postural activity of the trunk muscles following spinal manipulative therapy. Manual Therapy, 12 3: 240-248.

 0.71

140

8

Cited 14 times in Scopus14

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7405-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7405_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:22:20">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:274467</link><title>The current status of low level laser therapy in dentistry .2. Hard tissue applications</title><description>Walsh, LJ (1997) The current status of low level laser therapy in dentistry .2. Hard tissue applications. Australian Dental Journal, 42 5: 302-306.

 0.69

16

30

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7405-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7405_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:22:23">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:9522</link><title>Use of traditional and complementary medical care by patients with Multiple Sclerosis in South-East Queensland</title><description>Hooper, Kaye D., Pender, Michael P., Webb, Penny M. and McCombe, Pam A. (2001) Use of traditional and complementary medical care by patients with Multiple Sclerosis in South-East Queensland. International Journal of MS Care, 3 1: .

 0.69

442

784</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7405-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7405_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:22:25">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:216969</link><title>Current trends in the diagnosis, therapy and monitoring of the monoclonal gammopathies</title><description>Mollee, Peter (2009) Current trends in the diagnosis, therapy and monitoring of the monoclonal gammopathies. Clinical Biochemist Reviews, 30 3: 93-103.

 0.67

47</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7405-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7405_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:22:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:35336</link><title>Patient matching in treatment for alcohol dependence: is the null hypothesis still alive and well?</title><description>Hall, Wayne (1999) Patient matching in treatment for alcohol dependence: is the null hypothesis still alive and well?. Addiction, 94 1: 52-54.

 0.64

98

5

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7405-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7405_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:22:27">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:306596</link><title>Treating youth depression and anxiety: a randomised controlled trial examining the efficacy of computerised versus face-to-face cognitive behaviour therapy</title><description>Sethi, Suvena (2013) Treating youth depression and anxiety: a randomised controlled trial examining the efficacy of computerised versus face-to-face cognitive behaviour therapy. Australian Psychologist, 48 4: 249-257.

 0.64

33

0

Cited 0 times in Scopus0

13</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7405-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7405_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:22:28">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:325222</link><title>An update on brain plasticity for physical therapists</title><description>Schabrun, Siobhan M., Ridding, Michael C. and Chipchase, Lucinda S. (2013) An update on brain plasticity for physical therapists. Physiotherapy Practice and Research, 34 1: 1-8.

 0.62

40

4

Cited 0 times in Scopus0

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7405-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7405_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:22:29">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:269115</link><title>Addressing the nonexercise part of the activity continuum: A more realistic and achievable approach to activity programming for adults with mobility disability?</title><description>Manns, Patricia J., Dunstan, David W., Owen, Neville and Healy, Genevieve N. (2012) Addressing the nonexercise part of the activity continuum: A more realistic and achievable approach to activity programming for adults with mobility disability?. Physical Therapy, 92 4: 614-625.

 0.61

66

8

Cited 9 times in Scopus9

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7405-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7405_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:22:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:206191</link><title>Dog-assisted Therapy for Older People with Dementia: A Randomised Controlled Trial in Residential Aged Care Facilities</title><description>Jacqueline Perkins (2008). Dog-assisted Therapy for Older People with Dementia: A Randomised Controlled Trial in Residential Aged Care Facilities PhD Thesis, School of Veterinary Science, The University of Queensland.

 0.60

1074

14</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>