<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7406">does my child have adhd</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:23:12" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7406-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7406_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:23:20">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:205730</link><title>Exploring the influence of perceptual and attentional load to unmask a spatially selective attention deficit in children with ADHD and unaffected siblings.</title><description>Miss Sarah Pollock (). Exploring the influence of perceptual and attentional load to unmask a spatially selective attention deficit in children with ADHD and unaffected siblings. Professional Doctorate, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.99

104

11</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7406-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7406_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:23:22">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158533</link><title>An examination of mothers' and fathers' adjustment to having a child with ADHD: An application of the Double ABCX Model of Family Adaptation</title><description>Lancaster, Jennifer Madeleine Charlotte (2007). An examination of mothers' and fathers' adjustment to having a child with ADHD: An application of the Double ABCX Model of Family Adaptation PhD Thesis, School of Psychology, University of Queensland.

 0.95

185

7</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7406-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7406_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:23:22">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:178030</link><title>Behavioural Inhibition in Children with ADHD: Does Stimulant Medication Eliminate Potential Deficits?</title><description>Caroline Johnson (2008). Behavioural Inhibition in Children with ADHD: Does Stimulant Medication Eliminate Potential Deficits? PhD Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.85

388

13</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7406-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7406_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:23:23">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:172956</link><title>A retrospective study of the combined effects of stimulant and low dose anticonvulsant medication on cognition and function in adults with ADHD</title><description>Mr Gabriel Roux (). A retrospective study of the combined effects of stimulant and low dose anticonvulsant medication on cognition and function in adults with ADHD Professional Doctorate, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.77

147

4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7406-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7406_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:23:24">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:216341</link><title>Adolescents with Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder: Case Studies of the Academic, Behavioural, and Social Differences Over Time of Five Young People in a Flexible Learning Centre</title><description>Linda Houston (2010). Adolescents with Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder: Case Studies of the Academic, Behavioural, and Social Differences Over Time of Five Young People in a Flexible Learning Centre MPhil Thesis, School of Education, The University of Queensland.

 0.72

285

21</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7406-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7406_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:23:25">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:151319</link><title>INVESTIGATION OF THE CONCURRENT AND PREDICTIVE CONTRIBUTION OF ADHD-LIKE BEHAVIOURS AND PHONOLOGICAL PROCESSING TO EARLY WORD READING DEVELOPMENT</title><description>Cassandra Dittman (2008). INVESTIGATION OF THE CONCURRENT AND PREDICTIVE CONTRIBUTION OF ADHD-LIKE BEHAVIOURS AND PHONOLOGICAL PROCESSING TO EARLY WORD READING DEVELOPMENT PhD Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.65

323

167</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7406-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7406_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:23:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158797</link><title>Implementation and Evaluation of the Parenting Program Stepping Stones Triple P for children with Autism Spectrum Disorders</title><description>Whittingham, Koa Lou (2007). Implementation and Evaluation of the Parenting Program Stepping Stones Triple P for children with Autism Spectrum Disorders PhD Thesis, School of Psychology, University of Queensland.

 0.55

650

48</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7406-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7406_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:23:27">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:276357</link><title>Parenting children with eczema: What are the challenges and why is it difficult?</title><description>Sillar, Katie (2011). Parenting children with eczema: What are the challenges and why is it difficult? Honours Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.52

64

9</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7406-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7406_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:23:29">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:292493</link><title>The association between parent factors and child eczema behaviour</title><description>Hughes, Brenda (2012). The association between parent factors and child eczema behaviour Honours Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.51

47

4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7406-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7406_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:23:29">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:276580</link><title>An evaluation of the efficacy of a brief radio podcast Triple P-Positive Parenting Program</title><description>Helen Tometzki (2011). An evaluation of the efficacy of a brief radio podcast Triple P-Positive Parenting Program Honours Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.50

101

20</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>