<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7408">tom cruise</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:25:15" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7408-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7408_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:25:19">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:205093</link><title>The Petrie family : building colonial Brisbane</title><description>Dornan, Dimity, 1945- and Cryle, Denis, 1949- The Petrie family : building colonial Brisbane. St. Lucia, Qld.: University of Queensland Press, 1991.

 0.33

236

792</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7408-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7408_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:25:20">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:237912</link><title>Bondi's underbelly: The 'gay gang murders'</title><description>Davis, Kristen (2007). Bondi's underbelly: The 'gay gang murders'. In: Naomi Stead, Conference Proceedings: Queer Space: Centres and Peripheries. Queer Space: Centres and Peripheries, Sydney, Australia, (). 20-21 February 2007.

 0.32

77

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7408-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7408_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:25:21">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:212739</link><title>Blackbirding : a brief history of the South Sea Islands labour traffic and the vessels engaged in it</title><description>Stevens, E. V. (Eric Vaughan), 1878-1960. (1950) Blackbirding : a brief history of the South Sea Islands labour traffic and the vessels engaged in it. Journal of the Royal Historical Society of Queensland, 4 3: 361-403.

 0.31

278

4099</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7408-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7408_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:25:22">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:207891</link><title>The Pacific Islands : their glamour and their tragedies</title><description>Davies, A. G. (1944) The Pacific Islands : their glamour and their tragedies. The Historical Society of Queensland Journal, 3 3: 143-174.

 0.31

53

417</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7408-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7408_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:25:24">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:319342</link><title>The last voyage, to India and Australia, in the "Sunbeam"</title><description>Brassey, Annie The last voyage, to India and Australia, in the "Sunbeam". London, UK: Longmans, Green, and Co, 1889.

 0.29

8</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7408-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7408_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:25:25">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:238608</link><title>The local gaze: Social inhibitors to engagement in the Maldivian tourism industry</title><description>Shakeela, Aishath, Ruhanen, Lisa and Breakey, Noreen (2011). The local gaze: Social inhibitors to engagement in the Maldivian tourism industry. In: Michael J. Gross, Tourism: Creating a Brilliant Blend: Proceedings of the 21st Annual CAUTHE Conference. CAUTHE 2011 - 21st CAUTHE National Conference, Adealide, SA, Australia, (1-13). 8-11 February 2011.

 0.29

71

225</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7408-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7408_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:25:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:244679</link><title>Is a consumer an ecotourist? A theoretical framework for empirical research on tourists’ behaviour as consumers</title><description>Yabuta, Masahiro and Scott, Noel (2011). Is a consumer an ecotourist? A theoretical framework for empirical research on tourists’ behaviour as consumers. In: Michael J. Gross, Tourism: Creating a Brilliant Blend: Proceedings of the 21st Annual CAUTHE Conference. Council of Australian University Tourism and Hospitality Educators National Conference, Adelaide, SA, Australia, (1-13). 8-11 February 2011.

 0.29

139

8</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7408-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7408_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:25:27">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:238564</link><title>Transformational benefits from a visit to a multicultural festival: The case of South Korea</title><description>Lee, Insun, Arcodia, Charles and Lee, Timothy J. (2011). Transformational benefits from a visit to a multicultural festival: The case of South Korea. In: Michael J. Gross, Tourism: Creating a Brilliant Blend: Proceedings of the 21st Annual CAUTHE Conference. Council of Australian University Tourism and Hospitality Educators National Conference, Adelaide, University of South Australia, (1-11). 8-11 February 2011.

 0.29

90

64</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7408-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7408_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:25:29">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:238122</link><title>Community-driven rural tourism development in suburban Beijing</title><description>Zou, Tongqian, Huang, Songshan and Ding, Peiyi (2011). Community-driven rural tourism development in suburban Beijing. In: Michael J. Gross, Tourism: Creating a Brilliant Blend: Proceedings of the 21st Annual CAUTHE Conference. Council of Australian University Tourism and Hospitality Educators National Conference, Adelaide, SA, Australia, (1-19). 8-11 February 2011.

 0.29

113

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7408-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7408_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:25:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:244678</link><title>Organic innovation in the informal tourism sector: The case of the Becak Wisata, Yogyakarta</title><description>Damayanti, Maya, Scott, Noel and Ruhanen, Lisa (2011). Organic innovation in the informal tourism sector: The case of the Becak Wisata, Yogyakarta. In: Michael J. Gross, Tourism: Creating a Brilliant Blend: Proceedings of the 21st Annual CAUTHE Conference. Council of Australian University Tourism and Hospitality Educators, Adelaide, SA, Australia, (1-10). 9-11 February 2011.

 0.29

111

3</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>