<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7413">alkan piano</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:30:17" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7413-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7413_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:30:20">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:255709</link><title>Stephen Yates: Watching the river flow (Stephen Yates: Valse Triste)</title><description>Zhukov, Katie (2011) Stephen Yates: Watching the river flow (Stephen Yates: Valse Triste). Ultimo, NSW, Australia, ABC Classic FM.

 0.35

66</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7413-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7413_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:30:21">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:266621</link><title>The pulse of power. Part 2: Brightest threads</title><description>Continuum Sax, Davidson, Robert and Nightingale, James (2010) The pulse of power. Part 2: Brightest threads. Joan Sutherland Performing Arts Centre, Penrith, NSW, Australia, International Society for Contemporary Music (ISCM).

 0.30

94

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7413-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7413_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:30:22">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:236870</link><title>Taste: Invertebrates</title><description>Reinhard, Judith (2010). Taste: Invertebrates. In Breed, M. D. and Moore, J. (Ed.), Encyclopedia of animal behaviour (pp. 379-393) Burlington, MA, U.S.A.: Elseiver.

 0.18

43

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7413-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7413_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:30:23">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:287555</link><title>Expansion and dissemination of the lexicon of Bislama : a study of user recognition and attitudes</title><description>Balzer, Trevor George William (2005). Expansion and dissemination of the lexicon of Bislama : a study of user recognition and attitudes PhD Thesis, School of Languages and Comp Cultural Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.14

45

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7413-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7413_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:30:24">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:253475</link><title>Theoretical and experimental analysis of the Non Markov Parameter to detect low frequency synchronisation in time series analysis</title><description>Varghese, J. J., Weegink, K. J., Bellette, P. A., Coyne, T., Silburn, P. A. and Meehan, P. A. (2011). Theoretical and experimental analysis of the Non Markov Parameter to detect low frequency synchronisation in time series analysis. In: Nigel Lovell, Proceedings of the 33rd Annual International Conference of the IEEE Engineering in Medicine and Biology Society. 33rd Annual International Conference of the IEEE Engineering in Medicine and Biology Society (EMBS), Boston, MA, United States, (). 30 August - 3 September 2011.

 0.13

117

7</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>