<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7415">most anticipated games of 2013</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:32:18" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7415-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7415_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:32:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:322295</link><title>Social versus individual gamers: Factors influencing game engagement</title><description>Yuen, Cindy (2013). Social versus individual gamers: Factors influencing game engagement Honours Thesis, UQ Business School, The University of Queensland.

 0.59

34

6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7415-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7415_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:32:27">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:312197</link><title>Training bots to play: Investigating interactive reinforcement learning for bot behaviours in shooter games</title><description>McPartland, Michelle (2012). Training bots to play: Investigating interactive reinforcement learning for bot behaviours in shooter games PhD Thesis, School of Information Technol and Elec Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.45

31

3</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7415-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7415_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:32:28">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:304881</link><title>Creating spaces in higher education for marginalised Australians: Principles for socially inclusive pedagogies</title><description>Gale, Trevor and Mills, Carmen (2013) Creating spaces in higher education for marginalised Australians: Principles for socially inclusive pedagogies. Enhanced Learning in the Social Sciences, 5 2: 7-19.

 0.41

25

1

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7415-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7415_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:32:29">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:307079</link><title>Philosophic inquiry in sport</title><description>Philosophic inquiry in sport. Edited by Morgan, William J., (William John) and Meier, Klaus V. Champaign, Ill.: Human Kinetics, 1995.

 0.41

291

5</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7415-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7415_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:32:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:205535</link><title>The Brisbane Broncos: The team to beat</title><description>Gallaway, Jack The Brisbane Broncos: The team to beat. St Lucia, Qld: University of Queensland Press, 2001.

 0.41

106

198</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7415-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7415_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:32:33">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:326086</link><title>The effects of gamification on student learning through the use of reputation and rewards within community moderated discussion boards</title><description>Smith, Elliot, Herbert, Jeremy, Kavanagh, Lydia and Reidsema, Carl (2013). The effects of gamification on student learning through the use of reputation and rewards within community moderated discussion boards. In: Charles Lemckert, Graham Jenkins and Susan Lang-Lemckert, Proceedings of the 24th Annual Conference of the Australasian Association for Engineering Education: AAEE2013 Proceedings. AAEE 2013: 24th Annual Conference of the Australasian Association for Engineering Education, Gold Coast, QLD, Australia, (1-9). 8-11 December, 2013.

 0.40

33

26</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7415-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7415_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:32:34">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:306803</link><title>Understanding expert recall and recognition of natural visual patterns of movement</title><description>Gorman, Adam D. (2013). Understanding expert recall and recognition of natural visual patterns of movement PhD Thesis, School of Human Movement Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.40

91

8</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7415-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7415_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:32:35">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:310949</link><title>Mumbai’s maidans: from fields of fire to non-places</title><description>Gosseye, Janina (2009). Mumbai’s maidans: from fields of fire to non-places. In Kelly Shannon and Janina Gosseye (Ed.), Reclaiming (the Urbanism of) Mumbai (pp. 120-131) Amsterdam, The Netherlands: SUN Academia.

 0.38

24

3</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7415-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7415_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:32:36">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:311745</link><title>A framework for categorising mobile applications in mathematics education</title><description>Handal, Boris, El-Khoury, Joe, Campbell, Chris and Cavanagh, Michael (2013). A framework for categorising mobile applications in mathematics education. In: , Proceedings of the Australian Conference on Science and Mathematics Education. Australian Conference on Science and Mathematics Education 2013, Canberra, ACT, Australia, (142-147). 19-21 September, 2013.

 0.36

29

6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7415-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7415_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:32:37">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:326644</link><title>Virtual worlds in Australian and New Zealand higher education: remembering the past, understanding the present and imagining the future</title><description>Gregory, Sue, Hillier, Mathew, Campbell, Chris, Garcia Salinas, Jamie, Farley, Helen, Steel, Caroline, Gregory, Brent, Reiners, Torsten, Fardinpour, Ali, Lee, Mark J. W., Jacka, Lisa, Butler, Des, Holloway, David, Grant, Scott, Hearns, Merle, Flintoff, Kim, Jegathesan, Jay Jay, Ellis, David, McDonald, Marcus, Stokes-Thompson, Frederick et al. (2013). Virtual worlds in Australian and New Zealand higher education: remembering the past, understanding the present and imagining the future. In: H. Carter, M. Gosper and J. Hedberg, Proceedings of the 30th Australasian Society for Computers in Learning in Tertiary Education Conference (ASCILITE 2013). Electric Dreams: 30th ascilite Conference, North Ryde, NSW, Australia, (312-324). 1-4 December 2013.

 0.35

33

7</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>