<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7423">postdoc jobs european university biotech</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:40:25" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7423-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7423_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:40:29">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106962</link><title>Stakeholder interactions in the process of biotechnology integration</title><description>Daniel, Lisa J. (2004). Stakeholder interactions in the process of biotechnology integration PhD Thesis, School of Biomedical Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.24

121

8</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7423-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7423_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:40:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:302774</link><title>Institutional entrepreneurship and the development of a new organisational field of science research infrastructure: the case of the 'Smart State Institutes'</title><description>Staggs, Jonathan (2013). Institutional entrepreneurship and the development of a new organisational field of science research infrastructure: the case of the 'Smart State Institutes' PhD Thesis, University of Queensland Business School, The University of Queensland.

 0.20

73

16</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7423-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7423_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:40:31">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:171091</link><title>Efforts to capture high amylose in rice</title><description>Butardo, Vito Jr. M., Fitzgerald, Melissa A., Rahman, Sadequr and Gidley, Michael J. (2008). Efforts to capture high amylose in rice. In: , Cereal Foods World: Diversity of Grains. AACC International Annual Meeting 2008, Hawaii Convention Centre, Honolulu, Hawaii, (A15-A15). 21-24 September, 2008.

 0.16

305

1449</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7423-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7423_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:40:32">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:224975</link><title>Managing creativity and its challenges: Case of the film industry</title><description>Wong, Caroline (2010). Managing creativity and its challenges: Case of the film industry. In: Tan Yigitcanlar, Peter Yates and Klaus Kunzmann, Proceedings of the 3rd Knowledge Cities World Summit: From theory to practice. The 3rd Knowledge Cities World Summit (KCWS 2010), Melbourne, Australia, (401-416). 16-20 November 2010.

 0.16

107

991</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7423-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7423_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:40:33">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:237378</link><title>What makes Australian IT industry companies go global?</title><description>Searle, Glen and O'Connor, Kevin (2010). What makes Australian IT industry companies go global?. In: Tan Yigitcanlar, Peter Yates and Klaus Kunzmann, Proceedings of: The Third Knowledge Cities World Summit. From Theory to Practice. KCWS 2010: Knowledge Cities World Summit, Melbourne, VIC, Australia, (864-874). 16-19 November 2010.

 0.16

117

4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7423-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7423_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:40:34">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:232440</link><title>Validating feathers for the field diagnosis of highly pathogenic avian influenza subtype H5N1</title><description>Nuradji, Harimurti, Wibawa, Hendra, Lowther, Sue, Payne, Jean, Rookes, Jennifer, Bingham, John and Meers, Joanne (2010). Validating feathers for the field diagnosis of highly pathogenic avian influenza subtype H5N1. In: Global Biosecurity 2010, Brisbane, QLD, Australia, (149-149). 28 February-3 March 2010.

 0.15

80</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7423-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7423_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:40:35">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:232369</link><title>Vectoring of avian influenza antigens using a recombinant avian herpes virus vector</title><description>Hartawan, Risza, Meers, Joanne, Mahony, Tim and Robinson, Karl (2010). Vectoring of avian influenza antigens using a recombinant avian herpes virus vector. In: , Global Biosecurity 2010: Safeguarding Agriculture and the Environment. Conference Handbook. Global Biosecurity 2010, Brisbane, QLD, Australia, (143-143). 28 February-3 March 2010.

 0.15

87

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7423-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7423_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:40:36">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:151742</link><title>Life History, Population Genetics and Sensory Biology of the White Spotted Eagle Ray Aetobatus narinari (Euphrasen, 1790) with Emphasis on the Relative Importance of Olfaction</title><description>Vera Schluessel (2008). Life History, Population Genetics and Sensory Biology of the White Spotted Eagle Ray Aetobatus narinari (Euphrasen, 1790) with Emphasis on the Relative Importance of Olfaction PhD Thesis, School of Biomedical Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.14

1327

160</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7423-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7423_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:40:37">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:270855</link><title>SNARE-Mediated Secretion and Late Endosomes in Macrophages</title><description>Carolin Offenh채user (2011). SNARE-Mediated Secretion and Late Endosomes in Macrophages PhD Thesis, Institute for Molecular Bioscience, The University of Queensland.

 0.13

148

13</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>