<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7433">747-8</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:50:27" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7433-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7433_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:50:33">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:258382</link><title>Nanosized anatase TiO2 single crystals with tunable exposed (001) facets for enhanced energy conversion efficiency of dye-sensitized solar cells</title><description>Wu, Xia, Chen, Zhigang, Lu, Gao Qing (Max) and Wang, Lianzhou (2011) Nanosized anatase TiO2 single crystals with tunable exposed (001) facets for enhanced energy conversion efficiency of dye-sensitized solar cells. Advanced Functional Materials, 21 21: 4167-4172.

 0.36

133

50

Cited 54 times in Scopus54

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7433-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7433_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:50:34">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:9606</link><title>Induction of defeasible logic theories in the legal domain</title><description>Johnston, Benjamin and Governatori, Guido (2003). Induction of defeasible logic theories in the legal domain. In: Giovanni Sartor, Proceedings of the 9th International Conference on Artificial Intelligence and Law. Proceedings of the 9th International Conference on Artificial Intelligence and Law (ICAIL-03), Edinburgh, Scotland, (204-213). 24 - 28 June 2003.

 0.28

189

1137

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7433-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7433_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:50:35">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:255709</link><title>Stephen Yates: Watching the river flow (Stephen Yates: Valse Triste)</title><description>Zhukov, Katie (2011) Stephen Yates: Watching the river flow (Stephen Yates: Valse Triste). Ultimo, NSW, Australia, ABC Classic FM.

 0.25

66</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7433-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7433_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:50:36">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:10391</link><title>Ciguatera Poisoning: A Global Issue with Common Management Problems</title><description>Ting, Joseph Y. S. and Brown, A. F. T. (2001) Ciguatera Poisoning: A Global Issue with Common Management Problems. European Journal of Emergency Medicine, 8 4: 295-300.

 0.24

1136

1960</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7433-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7433_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:50:37">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:9547</link><title>A Computationally Grounded Logic of Knowledge, Belief and Certainty</title><description>Su, K., Sattar, A., Governatori, G. and Chen, Q. (2005). A Computationally Grounded Logic of Knowledge, Belief and Certainty. In: S. Kraus, M. P. Singh, S. Koening, M. Wooldridge, F. Dignum and V. Dignum, Proceedings of the 4th International Joint Conference of Autonomous Agents and Multiagent Systems. 4th International Conference on Autonomous Agents and Multiagent Systems, Utrecht, The Netherlands, (149-156). 25-29 July, 2005.

 0.22

314

1203</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7433-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7433_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:50:38">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:312337</link><title>Sintering of γ-TiAl based alloys</title><description>Xia, Yang (2013). Sintering of γ-TiAl based alloys PhD Thesis, School of Mechanical and Mining Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.21

70

13</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7433-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7433_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:50:39">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:248894</link><title>Experience with high frequency oscillation ventilation during the 2009 H1N1 influenza pandemic in Australia and New Zealand</title><description>Boots, Robert J., Lipman, Jeffrey, Lassig-Smith, Melissa, Stephens, DP, Thomas, J., Shehabi, Y., Bass, F., Anthony, A., Long, D., Seppelt, I.M., Weisbrodt, L., Erickson, S., Beca, J., Sherring, C., McGuiness, S., Parke, R., Stachowski, E.R., Boyd, R. and Howe, B. (2011) Experience with high frequency oscillation ventilation during the 2009 H1N1 influenza pandemic in Australia and New Zealand. Anaesthesia and Intensive Care, 39 5: 837-846.

 0.21

89

2

2

Cited 4 times in Scopus4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7433-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7433_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:50:41">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:274146</link><title>Increased bone mineral density in Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander Australians: Impact of body composition differences</title><description>Maple-Brown, L. J., Hughes, J., Piers, L. S., Ward, L. C., Meerkin, J., Eisman, J. A., Center, J. R., Pocock, N. A., Jerums, G. and O'Dea, K. (2012) Increased bone mineral density in Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander Australians: Impact of body composition differences. Bone, 51 1: 123-130.

 0.21

47

3

2

Cited 1 times in Scopus1

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7433-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7433_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:50:42">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:259544</link><title>Diversity in work: The heterogeneity of women’s labour market participation patterns</title><description>Yerkes, Mara (2006). Diversity in work: The heterogeneity of women’s labour market participation patterns. AIAS Working paper 06/45, Amsterdam Institute for Advanced Labour Studies.

 0.20

27</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7433-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7433_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:50:43">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:298145</link><title>A detailed investigation of nominally 2-D radical-farming scramjet combustion</title><description>Lorrain, Philippe, Brieschenk, Stefan, Capra, Bianca and Boyce, Russell (2012). A detailed investigation of nominally 2-D radical-farming scramjet combustion. In: , Proceedings of the 18th International Spaceplanes and Hypersonic Systems and Technologies Conference. 18th AIAA International Spaceplanes and Hypersonic Systems and Technologies Conference, Tours, France, (). 24-28 September 2012.

 0.20

40

2

Cited 0 times in Scopus0</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>