<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7438">facebook privacy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:55:18" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7438-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7438_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:55:25">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:239715</link><title>The role of normative influence, risk, and trust in Facebook users' online privacy protection behaviour</title><description>Saeri, A. K. (2010). The role of normative influence, risk, and trust in Facebook users' online privacy protection behaviour Honours Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 1.15

292

39</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7438-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7438_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:55:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:278728</link><title>Using Facebook to engage students with social justice concepts in teacher education</title><description>Smala, Simone (2012). Using Facebook to engage students with social justice concepts in teacher education. In: Paul Resta, Proceedings of Society for Information Technology and Teacher Education International Conference 2012. SITE 2012: Society for Information and Technology Teacher Education 23rd International Conference, Austin, TX, United States, (916-920). 5 - 9 March 2012.

 0.92

69

3</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7438-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7438_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:55:27">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:287210</link><title>If I didn't want people to know, I wouldn't put it on Facebook: how privacy is changing in the age of social networking</title><description>Pomfret, Liam and Previte, Josephine (2012). If I didn't want people to know, I wouldn't put it on Facebook: how privacy is changing in the age of social networking. In: Richard Lee, Proceedings ANZMAC 2012. Australian and New Zealand Marketing Academy Conference (ANZMAC 2012), Adelaide, SA, Australia, (1-7). 3 - 5 December 2012.

 0.89

206

63</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7438-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7438_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:55:28">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:124191</link><title>Social Networking: never mind the students, what about us? Use of Social Networking Softwares for professional networking and development for library staff.</title><description>Jennifer Creese, Jacqueline Cribb and Joanne Spicer (2008). Social Networking: never mind the students, what about us? Use of Social Networking Softwares for professional networking and development for library staff.. In: Beyond The Hype: Web 2.0 Symposium, Queensland University of Technology, Brisbane, (). 1-2 February, 2008.

 0.82

975

807</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7438-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7438_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:55:29">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:284464</link><title>Contextual language learning: the educational potential of mobile technologies and social media</title><description>Al-shehri, Saleh (2012). Contextual language learning: the educational potential of mobile technologies and social media PhD Thesis, School of Education, The University of Queensland.

 0.73

269

25</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7438-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7438_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:55:31">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:230496</link><title>UNDERSTANDING JEALOUSY IN ROMANTIC RELATIONSHIPS: LINKS TO ATTACHMENT, FACEBOOK INVOLVEMENT, AND RELATIONAL OUTCOMES</title><description>Rachel Elphinston (2010). UNDERSTANDING JEALOUSY IN ROMANTIC RELATIONSHIPS: LINKS TO ATTACHMENT, FACEBOOK INVOLVEMENT, AND RELATIONAL OUTCOMES PhD Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.70

793

14</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7438-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7438_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:55:32">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:239170</link><title>Privacy invasive geo-mashups : Privacy 2.0 and the limits of first generation information privacy laws</title><description>Burdon, Mark (2010) Privacy invasive geo-mashups : Privacy 2.0 and the limits of first generation information privacy laws. University of Illinois Journal of Law, Technology and Policy, 2010 1: 1-50.

 0.60

75

4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7438-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7438_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:55:33">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:179720</link><title>Networking an evaluation of clinical literature searches: a preliminary report</title><description>Wearne, Joy (2009). Networking an evaluation of clinical literature searches: a preliminary report. In: Positioning the Profession: the Tenth International Congress on Medical Librarianship, Brisbane, Australia, (1-20). August 31-September 4, 2009.

 0.50

153

271</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7438-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7438_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:55:34">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:326402</link><title>Defining the Sensor Society</title><description>Andrejevic, Mark and Burdon, Mark (2015) Defining the Sensor Society. Television and New Media, : .

 0.47

168

212</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7438-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7438_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:55:35">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:264101</link><title>The seven-headed music machine</title><description>Topology, Davidson, Robert and Clocked Out (2007) The seven-headed music machine. New Farm, QLD, Australia, Brisbane Powerhouse.

 0.45

30</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>