<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7440">barcelona real madrid</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:57:15" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7440-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7440_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:57:22">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:291353</link><title>An improved quantitative mass spectrometry analysis of tumor specific mutant proteins at high sensitivity</title><description>Ruppen-Canas, Isabel, Lopez-Casas, Pedro P., Garcia, Fernando, Ximenez-Embun, Pilar, Munoz, Manuel, Pia Morelli, M., Real, Francisco X., Serna, Antonio, Hidalgo, Manuel and Ashman, Keith (2012) An improved quantitative mass spectrometry analysis of tumor specific mutant proteins at high sensitivity. Proteomics, 12 9: 1319-1327.

 0.65

46

4

Cited 4 times in Scopus4

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7440-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7440_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:57:23">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:276162</link><title>Vector-Borne Diseases - constant challenge for practicing veterinarians: recommendations from the CVBD World Forum</title><description>Baneth, Gad, Traub, Rebecca, Bourdeau, Patrick, Bourdoiseau, Gilles, Bowman, Dwight, Breitschwerdt, Edward, Capelli, Gioia, Cardoso, Luís, Dantas-Torres, Filipe, Day, Michael, Dedet, Jean-Pierre, Dobler, Gerhard, Ferrer, Lluís, Irwin, Peter, Kempf, Volkhard, Kohn, Babara, Lappin, Michael, Little, Susan, Maggi, Ricardo, Miro, Guadalupe et al. (2012) Vector-Borne Diseases - constant challenge for practicing veterinarians: recommendations from the CVBD World Forum. Parasites &amp; Vectors, 5 1: Article number 55.

 0.49

64

7

Cited 11 times in Scopus11

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7440-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7440_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:57:25">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:292958</link><title>Antoni Gaudi's expiatory temple of the Sagrada Familia, Barcelona, Catalonia, Spain : an exploration into the extent to which Antoni Gaudi's architecture is responsive to its context</title><description>Small, Kim (2005). Antoni Gaudi's expiatory temple of the Sagrada Familia, Barcelona, Catalonia, Spain : an exploration into the extent to which Antoni Gaudi's architecture is responsive to its context B.A. Thesis, School of Geography, Planning &amp; Env Management, The University of Queensland.

 0.49

131</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7440-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7440_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:57:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:173367</link><title>Changing sexual and gender paradigms</title><description>Martínez-Expósito, Alfredo (2008). Changing sexual and gender paradigms. In Altisent, M. E. (Ed.), A companion to the twentieth-century Spanish novel (pp. 174-185) Woodbridge, U.K.: Tamesis.

 0.32

79

323</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7440-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7440_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:57:27">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:321668</link><title>Feed preference in pigs: Relationship between cereal preference and nutrient composition and digestibility</title><description>Sola-Oriol D., Roura E. and Torrallardona D. (2014) Feed preference in pigs: Relationship between cereal preference and nutrient composition and digestibility. Journal of Animal Science, 92 1: 220-228.

 0.31

16

2

Cited 0 times in Scopus0

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7440-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7440_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:57:29">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:228476</link><title>Maintenance and Shift of Catalan and Spanish: Two Sets of Data from Barcelona</title><description>Margaret Jean Simmons (2010). Maintenance and Shift of Catalan and Spanish: Two Sets of Data from Barcelona PhD Thesis, School of Languages &amp; Comparative Cultural Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.30

135

25</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7440-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7440_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:57:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:162229</link><title>Agitators and Patriots: Cultural and Political Identity in Queensland's Spanish Communities, 1900-1975</title><description>Robert Mason (2008). Agitators and Patriots: Cultural and Political Identity in Queensland's Spanish Communities, 1900-1975 PhD Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion &amp; Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.30

233

18</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7440-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7440_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:57:31">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:279473</link><title>Bram Stoker (Abraham Stoker), 1847-1912 : a bibliography</title><description>Hughes, William. and University of Queensland. Victorian Fiction Research Unit. Bram Stoker (Abraham Stoker), 1847-1912 : a bibliography. St. Lucia, Qld.: Victorian Fiction Research Unit, Dept. of English, University of Queensland, 1997.

 0.29

75

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7440-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7440_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:57:32">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:240439</link><title>The use of the Spanish adverbs atrás and detrás: an underlying hierarchy of linguistic factors that determines the appropriate adverb</title><description>Baxter, Kristi Susan. (2002). The use of the Spanish adverbs atrás and detrás: an underlying hierarchy of linguistic factors that determines the appropriate adverb PhD Thesis, School of Languages and Comparative Cultural Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.27

87

3</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7440-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7440_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 01:57:33">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:157972</link><title>Lamentation settings by Manuel José Doyagüe (1755-1842) recently rediscovered in Manila : a contextual study and critical transcription</title><description>Irving, David Ronald Marshall (2004). Lamentation settings by Manuel José Doyagüe (1755-1842) recently rediscovered in Manila : a contextual study and critical transcription MPhil Thesis, School of Music, University of Queensland.

 0.27

185

6</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>