<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7445">marathon training</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:02:14" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7445-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7445_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:02:22">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:161323</link><title>Malignant melanoma in marathon runner</title><description>Ambros-Rudolph, Christina M., Hofmann-Wellenhof, Rainer, Richtig, Erika, M端ller-F端rstner, Manuela, Soyer, H. Peter and Kerl, Helmut (2006) Malignant melanoma in marathon runner. Archives of dermatology, 142 11: 1471-1474.

 0.81

61

18

Cited 22 times in Scopus22</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7445-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7445_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:02:23">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:312990</link><title>Organic Fitness: Physical Activity Consistent with Our Hunter-Gatherer Heritage</title><description>O'Keefe, James H., Vogel, Robert, Lavie, Carl J. and Cordain, Loren (2010) Organic Fitness: Physical Activity Consistent with Our Hunter-Gatherer Heritage. Physician and Sportsmedicine, 38 4: 11-18.

 0.66

15

3

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7445-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7445_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:02:24">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:67109</link><title>Tennis, incidence of URTI and salivary IgA</title><description>Novas, A. M. P., Rowbottom, D. G. and Jenkins, D. G. (2003) Tennis, incidence of URTI and salivary IgA. International Journal of Sports Medicine, 24 3: 223-229.

 0.52

131

43

Cited 46 times in Scopus46

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7445-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7445_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:02:27">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:76041</link><title>Exercise-induced muscle damage, plasma cytokines, and markers of neutrophil activation</title><description>Peake, J. M., Suzuki, K., Wilson, G., Hordern, M. D., Nosaka, K., Mackinnon, L. T. and Coombes, J. S. (2005) Exercise-induced muscle damage, plasma cytokines, and markers of neutrophil activation. Medicine and Science in Sports and Exercise, 37 5: 737-745.

 0.45

179

62

Cited 76 times in Scopus76

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7445-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7445_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:02:29">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106498</link><title>The role of glutamine in exercise-induced changes in immune function</title><description>Hiscock, Natalie. (2003). The role of glutamine in exercise-induced changes in immune function PhD Thesis, School of Human Movement Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.43

225

6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7445-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7445_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:02:31">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:76119</link><title>Carbohydrate supplementation and alterations in neutrophils, and plasma cortisol and myoglobin concentration after intense exercise</title><description>Peake, J, Wilson, G, Mackinnon, L and Coombes, JS (2005) Carbohydrate supplementation and alterations in neutrophils, and plasma cortisol and myoglobin concentration after intense exercise. European Journal of Applied Physiology, 93 5-6: 672-678.

 0.42

124

6

Cited 6 times in Scopus6

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7445-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7445_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:02:32">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:228693</link><title>Neuromuscular control and performance during the triathlon cycle-run transition</title><description>Jason Bonacci (2010). Neuromuscular control and performance during the triathlon cycle-run transition PhD Thesis, School of Health &amp; Rehabilitation Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.38

459

11</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7445-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7445_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:02:33">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158107</link><title>The role of immune disturbances in the pathology of heat stroke : the dual pathway model of heat stroke</title><description>Lim, Chin Leong (2006). The role of immune disturbances in the pathology of heat stroke : the dual pathway model of heat stroke PhD Thesis, School of Human Movement Studies, University of Queensland.

 0.38

870

4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7445-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7445_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:02:34">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106702</link><title>Ultra-endurance exercise, oxidative stress and arterial stiffness</title><description>Knez, Wade L. (2004). Ultra-endurance exercise, oxidative stress and arterial stiffness PhD Thesis, School of Human Movement Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.37

354

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7445-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7445_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:02:36">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:75541</link><title>Relationship between laboratory-measured variables and heart rate during an ultra-endurance triathlon</title><description>Laursen, Paul B., Knez, Wade L., Shing, Cecilia M., Langill, Robert H., Rhodes, Edward C. and Jenkins, David G. (2005) Relationship between laboratory-measured variables and heart rate during an ultra-endurance triathlon. Journal of Sports Sciences, 23 10: 1111-1120.

 0.36

105

13

Cited 14 times in Scopus14

0</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>