<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7449">Asics GT 2000</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:06:16" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7449-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7449_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:06:22">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:178671</link><title>The effects of caffeine on 2000 metre rowing performance</title><description>Skinner, T., Jenkins, D., Leveritt, M. and Coombes, J. (2009). The effects of caffeine on 2000 metre rowing performance. In: , 2008 ASICS Conference of Science and Medicine in Sport: Program and Abstracts. Asics Conference of Science and Medicine in Sport (ACSMS) 2008, Hamilton Island, QLD, Australia, (s71-s71). 16-18 October 2008.

 0.69

137

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7449-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7449_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:06:24">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:221539</link><title>The impact of the CLERP Act on IPO prospectus earnings forecasts</title><description>Peters, Christopher J. (2002). The impact of the CLERP Act on IPO prospectus earnings forecasts Honours Thesis, School of Business, The University of Queensland.

 0.35

94</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7449-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7449_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:06:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:261883</link><title>Navigating CEO appointments: do Australia's top male and female CEOs differ in how they made it to the top?</title><description>Fitzsimmons, Terrance William (2011). Navigating CEO appointments: do Australia's top male and female CEOs differ in how they made it to the top? PhD Thesis, UQ Business School, The University of Queensland.

 0.33

969

432</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7449-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7449_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:06:27">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:223002</link><title>Share buybacks, total returns and shareholder equity</title><description>Rathie, Alister. (2008). Share buybacks, total returns and shareholder equity Honours Thesis, School of Business, The University of Queensland.

 0.31

97

4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7449-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7449_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:06:28">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:298099</link><title>DSP processor design for reconfigurable system on chip</title><description>Al-tameemi, Ammar Abdul-Jabbar (2013). DSP processor design for reconfigurable system on chip PhD Thesis, School of Information Technology and Electrical Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.30

133

6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7449-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7449_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:06:29">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:159940</link><title>QUKU: A Mixed Grain Dynamically Reconfigurable Architecture for High Performance Computing</title><description>Shukla, Sunil (2008). QUKU: A Mixed Grain Dynamically Reconfigurable Architecture for High Performance Computing PhD Thesis, School of Information Technol and Elec Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.30

258

35</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7449-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7449_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:06:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:221544</link><title>The sectoral and macroeconomic implications of trade liberalisation in Australia : a CGE simulation</title><description>Nott, Ailsa. (1996). The sectoral and macroeconomic implications of trade liberalisation in Australia : a CGE simulation Master's Thesis, School of Economics, The University of Queensland.

 0.27

67

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7449-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7449_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:06:31">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:218835</link><title>Why do Australian takeover firms forecast earnings?</title><description>Hirst, Scott. (1998). Why do Australian takeover firms forecast earnings? Honours Thesis, School of Business, University of Queensland.

 0.26

53</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7449-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7449_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:06:32">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:269535</link><title>VLSI implementation for MPEG-1/Audio Layer III chip : bitstream processor - low power design</title><description>Lin, Li-Yang. (2005). VLSI implementation for MPEG-1/Audio Layer III chip : bitstream processor - low power design MPhil Thesis, School of Information Technology and Electrical Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.26

123

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7449-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7449_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:06:33">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:295057</link><title>An ASIC application for DNA sequencing by Smith-Waterman algorithm (DNASSWA)</title><description>Lin, Cheng-Hsien Kenny (2005). An ASIC application for DNA sequencing by Smith-Waterman algorithm (DNASSWA) MPhil Thesis, School of Information Technol and Elec Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.26

65

1</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>