<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7451">buy animal farm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:08:16" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7451-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7451_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:08:23">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:277539</link><title>Understanding animal welfare: An integrated approach</title><description>Eadie, Edward Norman (2012). Understanding animal welfare: An integrated approach MPhil Thesis, School of Veterinary Science, The University of Queensland.

 0.73

48

10</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7451-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7451_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:08:24">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:216356</link><title>Understanding of farm management decision making and factors influencing its processes in the Korean context</title><description>Jong-sun Kim (2010). Understanding of farm management decision making and factors influencing its processes in the Korean context PhD Thesis, School of Integrative Systems, The University of Queensland.

 0.61

1186

21</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7451-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7451_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:08:25">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:105607</link><title>The development of the Australian dairy industry with special reference to differences in the structure of dairy farms by state between 1983/84 and 1994/95</title><description>Berrevoets, Hendrik Willem. (2001). The development of the Australian dairy industry with special reference to differences in the structure of dairy farms by state between 1983/84 and 1994/95 MPhil Thesis, School of Social Science, The University of Queensland.

 0.57

120

5</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7451-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7451_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:08:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:151762</link><title>Influence of Culture and Stakeholders in Botswana's Dairy System</title><description>Tselaesele, Motlapele Nelson (2007). Influence of Culture and Stakeholders in Botswana's Dairy System PhD Thesis, School of Natural and Rural Systems Management, The University of Queensland.

 0.56

406

132</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7451-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7451_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:08:27">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:328179</link><title>Push and pull factors in rural Filipino youth's outmigration from agricultural communities</title><description>Manalo IV, Jaime A. and van de Fliert, Elske (2013) Push and pull factors in rural Filipino youth's outmigration from agricultural communities. Asian Journal of Agriculture and Development, 10 2: 59-73.

 0.56

19

13</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7451-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7451_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:08:28">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:188407</link><title>Most significant changes experienced by farmers from adopting rainforestation farming</title><description>Velarde, Genie Leen M., Gravoso, Rotacio S., Cagasan, Editha G. and Gabrillo, Christina A. (2007) Most significant changes experienced by farmers from adopting rainforestation farming. Annals of Tropical Research. Special Issue on Smallholder Forestry, 29 3: 109-122.

 0.54

86

275</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7451-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7451_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:08:29">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:135061</link><title>Going Organic: What factors influence the decisions of farmers and consumers to enter the organic industry and how can these be used to develop organic friendly policies?</title><description>Rahayu, Nur Hygiawati (2007). Going Organic: What factors influence the decisions of farmers and consumers to enter the organic industry and how can these be used to develop organic friendly policies? PhD Thesis, School of Natural and Rural Systems Management, The University of Queensland.

 0.53

697

190</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7451-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7451_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:08:30">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:233262</link><title>An international comparison of female and male students’ attitudes to the use of animals</title><description>Phillips, Clive, Izmirli, Serdar, Aldavood, Javid, Alonso, Marta, Choe, Bi, Hanlon, Alison, Handziska, Anastasija, Illmann, Gudrun, Keeling, Linda, Kennedy, Mark, Lee, Gwi, Lund, Vonne, Mejdell, Cecilie, Pelagic, Veselinas and Rehn, Therese (2010) An international comparison of female and male students’ attitudes to the use of animals. Animals, 1 1: 7-26.

 0.53

65

3

Cited 7 times in Scopus7

5</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7451-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7451_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:08:31">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:297467</link><title>Livestock and livelihoods: Trajectories in the production and marketing of large ruminants in the uplands of Northern Laos</title><description>Phonvisay, Aloun (2013). Livestock and livelihoods: Trajectories in the production and marketing of large ruminants in the uplands of Northern Laos PhD Thesis, School of Agriculture and Food Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.49

141

18</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7451-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7451_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:08:32">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:184849</link><title>Deregulating and developing dairy-food chain relationships: Implications for farm business management in south east Queensland</title><description>Parker, Amanda Jane (2003). Deregulating and developing dairy-food chain relationships: Implications for farm business management in south east Queensland PhD Thesis, School of Natural and Rural Systems Management, The University of Queensland.

 0.48

128

134</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>