<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7452">arizona game and fish homepage</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:09:11" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7452-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7452_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:09:15">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:314236</link><title>Partridges, quails, francolins, snowcocks, guineafowl and turkeys: status survey and conservation action plan 2000–2004</title><description>Partridges, quails, francolins, snowcocks, guineafowl and turkeys: status survey and conservation action plan 2000–2004. Edited by Richard A. Fuller, John P. Carroll and Philip J. K. McGowan Gland, Switzerland: International Union for Conservation of Nature and Natural Resources (IUCN), 2000.

 0.19

47

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7452-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7452_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:09:16">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:9529</link><title>The Application of In Situ Digital Networks to News Reporting and Delivery</title><description>Cokley, John (2004). The Application of In Situ Digital Networks to News Reporting and Delivery PhD Thesis, School of Film, Media &amp; Cultural Studies, Griffith University.

 0.19

937

1656</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7452-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7452_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:09:17">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:301881</link><title>Stakeholder engagement and collaboration: The case of the Monsoon Cup International Regatta</title><description>Abdullah, Nawal Hanim (2013). Stakeholder engagement and collaboration: The case of the Monsoon Cup International Regatta PhD Thesis, School of Tourism, The University of Queensland.

 0.18

135

9</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7452-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7452_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:09:18">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:107217</link><title>Typology of Periphrastic 'Do'-constructions</title><description>Jäger, Andreas (2005). Typology of Periphrastic 'Do'-constructions PhD Thesis, School of English, Media Studies and Art History, The University of Queensland.

 0.16

203

3</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7452-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7452_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:09:19">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:194356</link><title>Change in the Cultural Identity of German Settlers of the Logan and Maroochy Rivers, Queensland, 1860-1914</title><description>Jasmine Sommer (2009). Change in the Cultural Identity of German Settlers of the Logan and Maroochy Rivers, Queensland, 1860-1914 MPhil Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion &amp; Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.15

583

41</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7452-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7452_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:09:21">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:321778</link><title>Effects of matrix intensification on the distribution and condition of forest birds in South-West Ghana, West Africa</title><description>Deikumah, Justus (2013). Effects of matrix intensification on the distribution and condition of forest birds in South-West Ghana, West Africa PhD Thesis, School of Geography, Planning &amp; Env Management, The University of Queensland.

 0.15

24

8</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7452-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7452_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:09:22">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:246806</link><title>Social impact assessment documents : a manual of supporting documents for: A Community Guide to Social Impact Assessment January 2, 2003</title><description>Burdge, Rabel J Social impact assessment documents : a manual of supporting documents for: A Community Guide to Social Impact Assessment January 2, 2003. Bellingham, WA: Burdge, Rabel J., 2003.

 0.15

152

46</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7452-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7452_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:09:23">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:186330</link><title>Effective teacher attributes: Perceptions of early-career and pre-service music teachers</title><description>Harrison, Scott and Ballantyne, Julie (2005). Effective teacher attributes: Perceptions of early-career and pre-service music teachers. In: Cooper, Maxine, Proceedings of the 33rd Annual Australian Teacher Education Association Conference. Teacher Education: Local and Global: Australian Teacher Education Association Conference Proceedings, Surfers Paradise, Australia, (219-226). 6 - 9 July 2005.

 0.15

79

142</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7452-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7452_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:09:24">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:234995</link><title>Observations: Are they the link between university-based learning and informed practice for preservice teachers?</title><description>McCluskey, Kerryn (2010). Observations: Are they the link between university-based learning and informed practice for preservice teachers?. In: György Mészáros and Iván Falus, Responsibility, Challenge And Support In Teachers’ Life-Long Professional Development. ATEE 2010 Annual Conference Proceedings. 35th Annual Conference of the Association for Teacher Education in Europe, Budapest, Hungary, (). 26-30 August 2010.

 0.14

58

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7452-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7452_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:09:25">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:234988</link><title>Challenges for the teaching profession: How to cater for diversity in the workforce</title><description>McCluskey, Kerryn (2010). Challenges for the teaching profession: How to cater for diversity in the workforce. In: György Mészáros and Iván Falus, Responsibility, Challenge And Support In Teachers’ Life-Long Professional Development. ATEE 2010 Annual Conference Proceedings. 35th Annual Conference of the Association for Teacher Education in Europe, Budapest, Hungary, (). 26-30 August 2010.

 0.14

59

3</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>