<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7458">rice recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:15:00" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7458-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7458_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:15:09">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:256431</link><title>The more things change, the more they stay the same: rice and beans in modern Cuba</title><description>Pertierra, Anna Cristina (2012). The more things change, the more they stay the same: rice and beans in modern Cuba. In Richard Wilk and Livia Barbosa (Ed.), Rice and beans: a unique dish in a hundred places (pp. 35-60) London, U.K.: Berg Publishers.

 0.60

113

16</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7458-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7458_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:15:10">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:322257</link><title>Storied Palates: Narrative in Contemporary Cookbooks</title><description>Culver, Carody (2013). Storied Palates: Narrative in Contemporary Cookbooks PhD Thesis, School of English, Media Studies and Art History, The University of Queensland.

 0.52

20

7</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7458-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7458_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:15:11">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:193528</link><title>SPATIAL VARIATION IN WATER AVAILABILITY, SOIL NUTRIENT AND WATER CONSTRAINTS FOR RAINFED LOWLAND RICE PRODUCTION IN SAVANNAKHET PROVINCE, SOUTHERN LAO PDR</title><description>Thavone Inthavong (2009). SPATIAL VARIATION IN WATER AVAILABILITY, SOIL NUTRIENT AND WATER CONSTRAINTS FOR RAINFED LOWLAND RICE PRODUCTION IN SAVANNAKHET PROVINCE, SOUTHERN LAO PDR PhD Thesis, School of Land, Crop and Food Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.39

323

16</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7458-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7458_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:15:15">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:140575</link><title>Literary daughters' recipes: Food and female subjectivity in the writings of Mori Mari and Koda Aya</title><description>Aoyama Tomoko (2000) Literary daughters' recipes: Food and female subjectivity in the writings of Mori Mari and Koda Aya. Japanstudien, 12 : 91-116.

 0.38

98

21</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7458-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7458_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:15:17">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:296757</link><title>Can you really teach scientific inquiry online?</title><description>Johnton, Elizabeth, Elliott, Kristine, Boin, Anna, Irving, Helen and Galea, Victor (2009). Can you really teach scientific inquiry online?. In: , The proceedings of the Science Learning and Teaching Conference 2009. 3rd Science Learning and Teaching Conference 2009, Heriot-Watt University, Edinburgh, Scotland, (). 16-17 June 2009.

 0.34

26

3</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7458-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7458_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:15:17">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158208</link><title>'Food to go round' : negotiating healthy eating for management and prevention of type 2 diabetes among some urban indigenous Australians</title><description>Foley, Wendy L. (2006). 'Food to go round' : negotiating healthy eating for management and prevention of type 2 diabetes among some urban indigenous Australians PhD Thesis, School of Population Health, University of Queensland.

 0.34

619

40</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7458-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7458_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:15:19">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158210</link><title>Anyone for rice? : Australian food culture, multiculturalism and Asian-Australian identities</title><description>Widarsito, Sinta Jean (2006). Anyone for rice? : Australian food culture, multiculturalism and Asian-Australian identities PhD Thesis, School of English, Media Studies and Art History, University of Queensland.

 0.34

1096

57</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7458-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7458_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:15:20">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:245794</link><title>A community and laboratory-based assessment of natural food sources of vitamin A in the Federated States of Micronesia</title><description>Englberger, Lois. (2003). A community and laboratory-based assessment of natural food sources of vitamin A in the Federated States of Micronesia PhD Thesis, School of Population Health, The University of Queensland.

 0.32

279

6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7458-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7458_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:15:21">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:105638</link><title>Investigating methodologies for enhancing transgene expression in sorghum and rice</title><description>Able, Jason Alan (2001). Investigating methodologies for enhancing transgene expression in sorghum and rice PhD Thesis, School of Land, Crop and Food Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.31

101

6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7458-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7458_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:15:22">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:241635</link><title>Some factors influencing food consumption in selected Asian countries</title><description>Stroppiana, Ruth. (1999). Some factors influencing food consumption in selected Asian countries PhD Thesis, School of Economic, The University of Queensland.

 0.30

191

5</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>