<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7460">kobe bryant news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:17:00" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7460-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7460_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:17:11">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:268828</link><title>Women sharing a chemical moment in time</title><description>Garson, Mary (2011) Women sharing a chemical moment in time. Chemistry International, 33 2: 16-19.

 0.19

75

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7460-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7460_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:17:13">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:107335</link><title>'Kingdom-minded' people: Christian identity and the contributions of Chinese business Christians</title><description>Austin, Denise A. (2005). 'Kingdom-minded' people: Christian identity and the contributions of Chinese business Christians PhD Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion, and Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.18

328

4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7460-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7460_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:17:14">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:203523</link><title>Legitimation of violence against women in Colombia: A feminist critical discourse analytic study</title><description>Laura Tolton (2009). Legitimation of violence against women in Colombia: A feminist critical discourse analytic study PhD Thesis, School of Languages and Comp Cultural Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.18

515

66</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7460-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7460_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:17:14">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:243994</link><title>Semper floreat</title><description>Semper floreat (2003) Issue May Edition

 0.17

43

359</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7460-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7460_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:17:15">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:306103</link><title>Inertia and the change of state in the Uppsala internationalization process model</title><description>Dow, Douglas, Liesch, Peter W. and Welch, Lawrence (2013). Inertia and the change of state in the Uppsala internationalization process model. In: Patricia McDougall-Covin and Tunga Kiyak, Proceedings of the 55th Annual Meeting of the Academy of International Business: Bridging the Divide: Linking IB to Complementary Disciplines and Practice. 55th Annual Meeting of the Academy of International Business, Istanbul, Turkey, (165-165). 3-6 July 2013.

 0.17

65</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7460-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7460_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:17:16">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:306105</link><title>Marketing strategy in MNC subsidiaries: pure versus hybrid archetypes</title><description>Midgley, David and Venaik, Sunil (2013). Marketing strategy in MNC subsidiaries: pure versus hybrid archetypes. In: Patricia McDougall-Covin and Tunga Kiyak, Proceedings of the 55th Annual Meeting of the Academy of International Business: Bridging the Divide: Linking IB to Complementary Disciplines and Practice. 55th Annual Meeting of the Academy of International Business, Istanbul, Turkey, (215-216). 3-6 July 2013.

 0.17

41

14</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7460-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7460_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:17:17">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:319340</link><title>Wanderings, south and east : with 2 maps and 47 wood engravings executed under the direction of Edward Whymper, from sketches by the author, native drawings, etc.</title><description>Coote, Walter Wanderings, south and east : with 2 maps and 47 wood engravings executed under the direction of Edward Whymper, from sketches by the author, native drawings, etc.. London: Sampson Low, Marston, Searle &amp; Rivington, 1882.

 0.17

58

185</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7460-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7460_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:17:18">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:219698</link><title>Does more equal better? : an empirical examination of the impact of multiple celebrity endorsement on consumer advertisement evaluations</title><description>Stower, Penny A. L. (2006). Does more equal better? : an empirical examination of the impact of multiple celebrity endorsement on consumer advertisement evaluations Honours Thesis, School of Business, The University of Queensland.

 0.16

106

4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7460-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7460_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:17:21">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:189954</link><title>A loose partnership : business and the regional state in the development of Queensland's relations with Japan</title><description>O'Donnell, Fay Margaret (1994). A loose partnership : business and the regional state in the development of Queensland's relations with Japan PhD Thesis, School of Languages and Comparative Cultural Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.16

133

95</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7460-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7460_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:17:23">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:211307</link><title>Pugh's Almanac, Directory and gazetteer</title><description>Pugh's Almanac, Directory and gazetteer (1920)

 0.16

152

534</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>