<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7466">interconnects skin effect</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:22:55" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7466-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7466_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:23:00">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:172859</link><title>The accessibility and interconnectivity of the tubular system network in toad skeletal muscle</title><description>Edwards, Joshua N. and Launikonis, Bradley S. (2008) The accessibility and interconnectivity of the tubular system network in toad skeletal muscle. The Jounal of Physiology, 586 21: 5077-5089.

 0.62

266

11

Cited 11 times in Scopus11

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7466-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7466_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:23:02">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106275</link><title>Skin tales : epistemologies of skin and self</title><description>Winter, Alexandra Marie. (2003). Skin tales : epistemologies of skin and self PhD Thesis, School of English, Media Studies and Art History, The University of Queensland.

 0.62

86

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7466-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7466_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:23:03">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:157988</link><title>Modelling diffraction in optical interconnects</title><description>Petrovic, Novak S. (2004). Modelling diffraction in optical interconnects PhD Thesis, School of Information Technology and Electrical Engineering, University of Queensland.

 0.58

760

1372</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7466-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7466_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:23:04">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:223544</link><title>Factors that affect the transdermal penetration of glucocorticoids in dogs</title><description>Liisa Ahlstrom (2010). Factors that affect the transdermal penetration of glucocorticoids in dogs PhD Thesis, School of Veterinary Science, The University of Queensland.

 0.54

183

10</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7466-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7466_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:23:05">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:193553</link><title>Solute content and the tensile behavior of high pressure die cast Mg-Al alloys</title><description>Nagasekhar, A. V. and Cáceres, C. H. (2007). Solute content and the tensile behavior of high pressure die cast Mg-Al alloys. In: Chang, Young Won, Kim, Nack J. and Lee, Chong Soo, Materials Science Forum. The 6th Pacific Rim International Conference on Advanced Materials and Processing, Jeju Island, Korea, (333-336). 5-9 November, 2007.

 0.48

315

5

Cited 5 times in Scopus5</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7466-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7466_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:23:07">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:278151</link><title>The origin of the yield strength in thin sections of high pressure die castings</title><description>Yang, Kun (2012). The origin of the yield strength in thin sections of high pressure die castings PhD Thesis, School of Mechanical and Mining Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.48

137

23</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7466-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7466_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:23:08">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:296694</link><title>Determination of stress field caused by microprojection arrays contacting and impacting hyperelastic layered skin</title><description>Meliga, Stefano C., Flaim, Christopher, Veidt, Martin and Kendall, Mark A. F. (2012). Determination of stress field caused by microprojection arrays contacting and impacting hyperelastic layered skin. In: Andrei Kotousov, Raj Das and Stuart Wildy, Proceedings: the 7th Australasian Congress on Applied Mechanics (ACAM 7). 7th Australasian Congress on Applied Mechanics (ACAM 7), Adelaide, Australia, (331-340). 9-12 December 2012.

 0.46

153

9</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7466-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7466_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:23:09">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:291793</link><title>Surfactant protein B-based microemulsion as transdermal drug carrier for anti-acne agent</title><description>Ramli, Suria (2013). Surfactant protein B-based microemulsion as transdermal drug carrier for anti-acne agent PhD Thesis, School of Chemistry and Molecular Biosciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.41

168

11</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7466-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7466_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:23:10">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:267278</link><title>THE ROLE OF NMYC AND CMYC IN SKIN DEVELOPMENT AND IN HEDGEHOG PATHWAY-INDUCED TUMORIGENESIS</title><description>RHONDA HUI PING KAN (2011). THE ROLE OF NMYC AND CMYC IN SKIN DEVELOPMENT AND IN HEDGEHOG PATHWAY-INDUCED TUMORIGENESIS PhD Thesis, Institute for Molecular Bioscience, The University of Queensland.

 0.39

99

16</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7466-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7466_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:23:11">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158521</link><title>Endogenous Electrical Potential and Flow within and without the Human Body  With particular reference to the bioelectric processes of Acupuncture, Qi Gong and Yoga</title><description>Nicoll, Edwin Peter Carter (2007). Endogenous Electrical Potential and Flow within and without the Human Body  With particular reference to the bioelectric processes of Acupuncture, Qi Gong and Yoga PhD Thesis, School of Biomedical Sciences, University of Queensland.

 0.39

391

9</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>