<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7471">php foreach</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:28:07" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7471-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7471_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:28:09">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:83576</link><title>More bang for each health care buck</title><description>Brooks, Peter (2006) More bang for each health care buck. New Matilda, : .

 0.33

38</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7471-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7471_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:28:10">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:288072</link><title>Structural and evolutionary studies of backbone cyclised proteins</title><description>Mulvenna, Jason (2005). Structural and evolutionary studies of backbone cyclised proteins PhD Thesis, Institute for Molecular Bioscience, The University of Queensland.

 0.26

52

5</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7471-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7471_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:28:11">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:241842</link><title>Exploring small molecules and their drug-like properties using Semantic Web technologies</title><description>Joo Young Choi (2010). Exploring small molecules and their drug-like properties using Semantic Web technologies MPhil Thesis, Institute for Molecular Bioscience, The University of Queensland.

 0.18

107

12</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7471-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7471_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:28:12">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:268781</link><title>Accelerating the BLAST algorithm via parrallel computing</title><description>Calder, Mark. (2005). Accelerating the BLAST algorithm via parrallel computing MPhil Thesis, School of Information Technology and Electrical Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.17

173

7</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7471-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7471_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:28:13">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:174760</link><title>Investigations into Multiple-Element Smart Antenna Systems for Wireless Communications</title><description>Konstanty Bialkowski (2008). Investigations into Multiple-Element Smart Antenna Systems for Wireless Communications PhD Thesis, School of Information Technol and Elec Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.17

512

43</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7471-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7471_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:28:14">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:229141</link><title>A Distributed Quantum System Simulation Environment</title><description>Mr Simon Benson (2010). A Distributed Quantum System Simulation Environment PhD Thesis, School of Information Tech &amp; Elec Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.16

174

11</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7471-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7471_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:28:15">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:267589</link><title>Collaborative video indexing, annotation and discussion over high-bandwidth networks</title><description>Schroeter, Ronald. (2004). Collaborative video indexing, annotation and discussion over high-bandwidth networks MPhil Thesis, School of Information Technology and Electrical Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.16

63

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7471-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7471_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:28:16">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158766</link><title>DEVELOPING ONTOLOGIES IN THE BIOLOGICAL DOMAIN</title><description>Castro, Alexander Garcia (2007). DEVELOPING ONTOLOGIES IN THE BIOLOGICAL DOMAIN PhD Thesis, Institute for Molecular Bioscience , University of Queensland.

 0.16

200

6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7471-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7471_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:28:17">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:269569</link><title>The development and application of methods and tools for the assembly and analysis of second generation sequence data</title><description>Michael Imelfort (2011). The development and application of methods and tools for the assembly and analysis of second generation sequence data PhD Thesis, School of Agriculture and Food Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.14

130

38</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7471-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7471_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:28:18">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:261361</link><title>Functional Testing of GUI-Based Applications with the Action-Event Framework</title><description>Hoai Duc Nguyen (2011). Functional Testing of GUI-Based Applications with the Action-Event Framework PhD Thesis, School of Information Technology and Electrical Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.14

146

11</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>