<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7473">noise canceling head phones</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:30:05" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7473-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7473_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:30:13">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:9945</link><title>Multi-User Signal and Spectra Coordination for Digital Subscriber Lines</title><description>Cendrillon, Raphael (2004). Multi-User Signal and Spectra Coordination for Digital Subscriber Lines , Department of Electrical Engineering, Katholieke Universiteit Leuven, Belgium.

 0.43

394

1561</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7473-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7473_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:30:15">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:209256</link><title>A study of the production, character, and abatement of noise in pneumatic percussive drills.</title><description>Beiers, John Leonard (1966). A study of the production, character, and abatement of noise in pneumatic percussive drills. PhD Thesis, School of Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.38

134

8</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7473-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7473_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:30:15">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:290360</link><title>A consumer value theory of innovation in 3G mobile phones: a grounded theory approach</title><description>Ferrers, Richard Anthony (2012). A consumer value theory of innovation in 3G mobile phones: a grounded theory approach PhD Thesis, UQ Business School, The University of Queensland.

 0.34

378

11</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7473-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7473_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:30:17">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158247</link><title>Active Audition for Robots using Parameter-Less Self-Organising Maps</title><description>Berglund, Erik Johan (2006). Active Audition for Robots using Parameter-Less Self-Organising Maps PhD Thesis, School of Information Technology and Electrical Engineering, University of Queensland.

 0.32

416

191</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7473-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7473_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:30:18">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:185230</link><title>Accurate and efficient implementation of the time-frequency matched filter</title><description>O' Toole, John M., Mesbah, Mostefa and Boashash, Boualem (2009) Accurate and efficient implementation of the time-frequency matched filter.

 0.30

177

463</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7473-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7473_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:30:19">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158139</link><title>Electromagnetic analysis and design of high frequency coils for magnetic resonance</title><description>Xu, Bin (2006). Electromagnetic analysis and design of high frequency coils for magnetic resonance PhD Thesis, School of Information Technology and Electrical Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.30

484

9</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7473-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7473_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:30:20">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:223184</link><title>Performance investigation of multi-element antenna terminals for personal communications : TDMA LEOS system applications</title><description>Choy, Faith (2001). Performance investigation of multi-element antenna terminals for personal communications : TDMA LEOS system applications PhD Thesis, School of Computer Science and Electrical Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.29

98

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7473-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7473_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:30:21">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:152787</link><title>Rapid neonatal hearing screening using a modified maximum length sequences automated auditory brainstem response</title><description>Dzulkarnain, Ahmad Aidil Arafat (2008). Rapid neonatal hearing screening using a modified maximum length sequences automated auditory brainstem response PhD Thesis, School of Health and Rehabilitation Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.28

452

82</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7473-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7473_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:30:22">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:300164</link><title>Modulation technique for a mobile multimedia communication</title><description>Chan, Wei Leung Jude (1999). Modulation technique for a mobile multimedia communication B.Sc Thesis, School of Computer Science and Electrical Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.28

33</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7473-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7473_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:30:23">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158213</link><title>On the Edge of Their Seats: The Novel Manuscript 'Frantic', and the critical essay 'Suspense in Fiction: Its Operation and Techniques'</title><description>Howell, Katherine Leslie (2006). On the Edge of Their Seats: The Novel Manuscript 'Frantic', and the critical essay 'Suspense in Fiction: Its Operation and Techniques' MPhil Thesis, School of English, Media Studies and Art History, The University of Queensland.

 0.28

324

31</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>