<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7474">php convert special symbols to html</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:31:09" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7474-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7474_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:31:16">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:174760</link><title>Investigations into Multiple-Element Smart Antenna Systems for Wireless Communications</title><description>Konstanty Bialkowski (2008). Investigations into Multiple-Element Smart Antenna Systems for Wireless Communications PhD Thesis, School of Information Technol and Elec Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.29

512

43</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7474-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7474_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:31:18">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158683</link><title>Defining the Legal Contours of Academic Freedom of Educators in their Creation and Utilisation of Online Tools and Technologies in Higher E-Learning</title><description>Ramiscal, Noel (2007). Defining the Legal Contours of Academic Freedom of Educators in their Creation and Utilisation of Online Tools and Technologies in Higher E-Learning PhD Thesis, School of Law, University of Queensland.

 0.29

905

5</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7474-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7474_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:31:19">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:132740</link><title>Media And Political Change In Southeast Asia: Karaoke Culture And The Evolution Of Personality Politics</title><description>Woodier, Jonathan (2008). Media And Political Change In Southeast Asia: Karaoke Culture And The Evolution Of Personality Politics PhD Thesis, School of Political Science and International Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.27

539

200</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7474-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7474_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:31:20">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:259672</link><title>Indonesia and Post-New Order Reforms: Challenges and Opportunities for Promoting the Responsibility to Protect</title><description>Pohlman, Annie (2010) Indonesia and Post-New Order Reforms: Challenges and Opportunities for Promoting the Responsibility to Protect :

 0.26

57

40</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7474-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7474_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:31:21">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:177578</link><title>Imagining the Tree of Life: the language of trees in Renaissance literary and visual landscapes.</title><description>Bladen, Victoria (2008). Imagining the Tree of Life: the language of trees in Renaissance literary and visual landscapes. PhD Thesis, School of English, Media Studies and Art History, The University of Queensland.

 0.26

489

36</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7474-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7474_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:31:22">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:329569</link><title>An investigation into the potential for solar energy to succeed the fossil fuel super power</title><description>Burrows, Steven (2006). An investigation into the potential for solar energy to succeed the fossil fuel super power B.Sc Thesis, School of Mechanical and Mining Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.26

13</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7474-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7474_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:31:24">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:295922</link><title>Characteristics of Phonetics and Lexis of the Vietnamese language in Australia</title><description>Dao, Dich Muc (2012). Characteristics of Phonetics and Lexis of the Vietnamese language in Australia PhD Thesis, School of Languages and Comparative Cultural Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.26

219

10</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7474-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7474_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:31:25">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:159665</link><title>A socio-economic evaluation of the supervised cattle distribution program in the Philippines</title><description>Duthy, Stephen (Stephen W.) (2005). A socio-economic evaluation of the supervised cattle distribution program in the Philippines PhD Thesis, School of Economics, The University of Queensland.

 0.26

341

8</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7474-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7474_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:31:26">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:319400</link><title>Nature, environmental contests and the politics of indigeneity in Chile’s Northern Patagonia</title><description>Jones, Charmaine (2013). Nature, environmental contests and the politics of indigeneity in Chile’s Northern Patagonia PhD Thesis, School of Social Science, The University of Queensland.

 0.26

41

4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7474-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7474_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:31:27">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:294885</link><title>"Is less more": scientific approach to design analysis and evaluation</title><description>Sully, Hayden. (2004). "Is less more": scientific approach to design analysis and evaluation B.A. Thesis, School of Geography, Planning &amp; Env Management, The University of Queensland.

 0.25

29</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>