<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7475">software consultant work at home</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:32:09" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7475-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7475_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:32:16">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:269976</link><title>Telehealth business case, advice and options - Final report</title><description>Gray, Len C., Smith, Anthony C., Armfield, Nigel R., Travers, Catherine, Croll, Peter and Caffery, Liam J. (2011) Telehealth business case, advice and options - Final report St. Lucia, Qld., Australia: UniQuest

 0.55

65</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7475-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7475_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:32:17">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:224339</link><title>To a small international consulting company: The case of redwing international</title><description>Gillespie, Brian M (1996) To a small international consulting company: The case of redwing international The University of Queensland:

 0.55

23

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7475-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7475_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:32:18">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:106636</link><title>The impact of telework on work-family balance in Australia</title><description>Diamond, Christine. (2003). The impact of telework on work-family balance in Australia PhD Thesis, School of Political Science and International Studies, The University of Queensland.

 0.48

188

7</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7475-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7475_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:32:19">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:157886</link><title>Viable Software: the Intelligent Control Paradigm for Adaptable and Adaptive Architecture</title><description>Herring, Charles Edward (2002). Viable Software: the Intelligent Control Paradigm for Adaptable and Adaptive Architecture PhD Thesis, School of Information Technology and Electrical Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.47

970

9</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7475-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7475_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:32:20">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:301667</link><title>The review and application of mine design and optimisation softwares in the Australian minerals industry.</title><description>Monro, Kell (2001). The review and application of mine design and optimisation softwares in the Australian minerals industry. B.Sc Thesis, School of Engineering, The University of Queensland.

 0.47

43

4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7475-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7475_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:32:21">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:296269</link><title>Work-related discomfort in the optometry profession â whose responsibility?</title><description>Long, Jennifer, Burgess-Limerick, Robin and Staoleton, Fiona (2012) Work-related discomfort in the optometry profession â whose responsibility?. Ergonomics Australia, 10 6: .

 0.47

34

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7475-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7475_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:32:22">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:226702</link><title>A model to develop strategies for the support of End User computing</title><description>Stegeman, Rodney J. (1991) A model to develop strategies for the support of End User computing The University of Queensland:

 0.46

47

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7475-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7475_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:32:23">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:276128</link><title>Pharmacists in primary care multidisciplinary teams: How would you like your coffee?</title><description>Freeman, Chris (2012) Pharmacists in primary care multidisciplinary teams: How would you like your coffee?. Australian Pharmacist, 31 6: 450-450.

 0.46

79

3</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7475-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7475_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:32:24">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:225275</link><title>Entry strategies for the Japanese education software market</title><description>Watts, Robert T. (1996) Entry strategies for the Japanese education software market The University of Queensland:

 0.46

109

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7475-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7475_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:32:25">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:237276</link><title>Knowledge-based development and industry clustering: Spatial embeddedness of Sydney and Melbourne's software industry</title><description>Searle, Glen (2010) Knowledge-based development and industry clustering: Spatial embeddedness of Sydney and Melbourne's software industry. International Journal of Knowledge-Based Development, 1 1-2: 118-135.

 0.46

88

3

Cited 0 times in Scopus0

0</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>