<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7477">china bird flu</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:34:00" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7477-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7477_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:34:06">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:308090</link><title>Towards a better understanding of the novel avian-origin H7N9 influenza A virus in China</title><description>Wang, Yongbo, Dai, Zhangyan, Cheng, Han, Liu, Zexian, Pan, Zhicheng, Deng, Wankun, Gao, Tianshun, Li, Xiaotong, Yao, Yuangen, Ren, Jian and Xue, Yu (2013) Towards a better understanding of the novel avian-origin H7N9 influenza A virus in China. Scientific Reports, 3 : 2318.1-2318.10.

 0.49

13

2

1

Cited 2 times in Scopus2

15</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7477-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7477_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:34:07">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:121808</link><title>Asia's livestock industries : changes and environmental consequences.</title><description>Tisdell, C. A. (Clement Allan) (1998). Asia's livestock industries : changes and environmental consequences.. Working papers on economics, ecology and the environment. Working Paper No. 23, Department of Economics, University of Queensland.

 0.47

177

993</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7477-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7477_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:34:08">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:121810</link><title>Asia's (especially China's) livestock industries : changes and environmental consequences.</title><description>Tisdell, C. A. (Clement Allan) (1998). Asia's (especially China's) livestock industries : changes and environmental consequences.. Working papers on economics, ecology and the environment. Working Paper No. 25, Department of Economics, University of Queensland.

 0.40

226

886</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7477-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7477_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:34:09">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:179867</link><title>Managing emerging diseases and disasters in India</title><description>Chattopadhyay, Anjana (2009). Managing emerging diseases and disasters in India. In: Positioning the Profession: the Tenth International Congress on Medical Librarianship, Brisbane, Australia, (1-15). August 31-September 4, 2009.

 0.38

141

499</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7477-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7477_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:34:09">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:254351</link><title>Of rabbits, chickens and champagne - everything old is new again.</title><description>Petersen, A., Jaglic, Z., Bisgaard, M., Subaaharan, S., Blackall, P.J. and Christensen, H. (2010). Of rabbits, chickens and champagne - everything old is new again.. In: Australasian Veterinary Poultry Alliance Meeting, Gold Coast , QLD, Australia, (). 26th - 27th .

 0.35

37

380</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7477-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7477_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:34:10">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:268588</link><title>Australia’s Defence and Foreign Relations with Indonesia, 1997-2010</title><description>Gabrielle Le Grand (2011). Australia’s Defence and Foreign Relations with Indonesia, 1997-2010 MPhil Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion &amp; Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.34

300

15</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7477-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7477_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:34:11">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:297328</link><title>Aspects of the epidemiology and pathobiology of Indonesian H5N1 highly pathogenic avian influenza virus in domestic ducks</title><description>Wibawa, Hendra (2012). Aspects of the epidemiology and pathobiology of Indonesian H5N1 highly pathogenic avian influenza virus in domestic ducks PhD Thesis, School of Veterinary Science, The University of Queensland.

 0.33

80

9</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7477-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7477_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:34:12">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:325373</link><title>Analysis of the institutional arrangements for the management of Australia’s threatened birds</title><description>Holmes, Timothy Q. (2013). Analysis of the institutional arrangements for the management of Australia’s threatened birds PhD Thesis, School of Biological Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.31

38

47</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7477-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7477_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:34:13">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:304496</link><title>Feathers for diagnosis of highly pathogenic avian influenza (H5N1) in ducks and chickens</title><description>Nuradji, Harimurti (2012). Feathers for diagnosis of highly pathogenic avian influenza (H5N1) in ducks and chickens PhD Thesis, School of Veterinary Science, The University of Queensland.

 0.31

120

11</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7477-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7477_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:34:14">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:306757</link><title>Constraints to production of village chickens in Timor-Lesté</title><description>Serrao, Eduardo Aniceto (2012). Constraints to production of village chickens in Timor-Lesté PhD Thesis, School of Veterinary Science, The University of Queensland.

 0.30

86

6</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>