<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7481">worms nexus 7</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:37:47" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7481-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7481_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:37:55">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:292308</link><title>Chrysomya bezziana in pet dogs in Hong Kong: a potential threat to Australia</title><description>Chemonges-Nielsen, S (2003) Chrysomya bezziana in pet dogs in Hong Kong: a potential threat to Australia. Australian Veterinary Journal, 81 4: 202-205.

 0.32

52

4

6

Cited 7 times in Scopus7

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7481-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7481_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:37:58">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:273350</link><title>Amending and Defending Constitution</title><description>Tessa Jones (2011). Amending and Defending Constitution MPhil Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion &amp; Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.31

90

11</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7481-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7481_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:37:58">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:8581</link><title>A historical perspective on early progress of water fluoridation in Queensland 1945-1954: Sheep, climate and sugar</title><description>Akers, H. F. and Porter, S. A. T. (2004) A historical perspective on early progress of water fluoridation in Queensland 1945-1954: Sheep, climate and sugar. The Australian Dental Journal, 49 2: 61-66.

 0.24

309

776

1

Cited 3 times in Scopus3

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7481-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7481_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:38:00">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:132291</link><title>Cryptogonimidae Ward, 1917 (Platyhelminthes: Digenea), With Emphasis On Taxa Infecting Indo-West Pacific Lutjanidae And Haemulidae (Perciformes)</title><description>Miller, Terrence (2007). Cryptogonimidae Ward, 1917 (Platyhelminthes: Digenea), With Emphasis On Taxa Infecting Indo-West Pacific Lutjanidae And Haemulidae (Perciformes) PhD Thesis, School of Molecular and Microbial Sciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.24

169

214</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7481-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7481_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:38:01">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:324755</link><title>The greatest issue of all: Berlin, American national security, and the cold war</title><description>Coleman, David G. (2000). The greatest issue of all: Berlin, American national security, and the cold war PhD Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion &amp; Classics, University of Queensland.

 0.23

7</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7481-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7481_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:38:02">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:198858</link><title>The Brisbane episcopate of St. Clair Donaldson 1904-1921</title><description>Kidd, Alexander Philip (1996). The Brisbane episcopate of St. Clair Donaldson 1904-1921 PhD Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion, and Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.23

129

243</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7481-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7481_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:38:03">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:185950</link><title>Determinants of Schistosoma japonicum and soil-transmitted helminth infections, and associated morbidity in Hunan province, China: an epidemiological assessment</title><description>Julie Balen (2009). Determinants of Schistosoma japonicum and soil-transmitted helminth infections, and associated morbidity in Hunan province, China: an epidemiological assessment PhD Thesis, School of Population Health, The University of Queensland.

 0.23

239

9</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7481-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7481_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:38:04">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:276008</link><title>Patterns of trophic transmission of digenean trematodes through fishes of the Great Barrier Reef: host specificity or hoping for the best?</title><description>Abigail Downie (2011). Patterns of trophic transmission of digenean trematodes through fishes of the Great Barrier Reef: host specificity or hoping for the best? PhD Thesis, School of Chemistry &amp; Molecular Biosciences, The University of Queensland.

 0.21

174

20</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7481-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7481_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:38:05">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:224795</link><title>Dialectics of desire and danger : maidenhood, sexuality and modernity in Mataram, Eastern Indonesia</title><description>Bennett, Linda Rae. (2002). Dialectics of desire and danger : maidenhood, sexuality and modernity in Mataram, Eastern Indonesia PhD Thesis, Tropical Health Program, The University of Queensland.

 0.21

181

4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7481-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7481_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:38:06">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:314975</link><title>The scope of published population genetic data for Indo-Pacific marine fauna and future research opportunities in the region</title><description>Keyse, Jude, Crandall, Eric D., Toonen, Robert J., Meyer, Christopher P., Treml, Eric A. and Riginos, Cynthia (2014) The scope of published population genetic data for Indo-Pacific marine fauna and future research opportunities in the region. Bulletin of Marine Science, 90 1: 47-78.

 0.21

47

59

7

Cited 0 times in Scopus0

0</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>