<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7483">facebook paying?</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:39:54" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7483-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7483_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:39:58">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:240001</link><title>Face-to-Facebook: A comparison of the effects of ostracism in 21st century social environments</title><description>Samantha King (2010). Face-to-Facebook: A comparison of the effects of ostracism in 21st century social environments Honours Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.80

486

39</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7483-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7483_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:39:59">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:284464</link><title>Contextual language learning: the educational potential of mobile technologies and social media</title><description>Al-shehri, Saleh (2012). Contextual language learning: the educational potential of mobile technologies and social media PhD Thesis, School of Education, The University of Queensland.

 0.74

269

25</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7483-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7483_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:40:00">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:230496</link><title>UNDERSTANDING JEALOUSY IN ROMANTIC RELATIONSHIPS: LINKS TO ATTACHMENT, FACEBOOK INVOLVEMENT, AND RELATIONAL OUTCOMES</title><description>Rachel Elphinston (2010). UNDERSTANDING JEALOUSY IN ROMANTIC RELATIONSHIPS: LINKS TO ATTACHMENT, FACEBOOK INVOLVEMENT, AND RELATIONAL OUTCOMES PhD Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.74

793

14</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7483-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7483_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:40:01">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:287210</link><title>If I didn't want people to know, I wouldn't put it on Facebook: how privacy is changing in the age of social networking</title><description>Pomfret, Liam and Previte, Josephine (2012). If I didn't want people to know, I wouldn't put it on Facebook: how privacy is changing in the age of social networking. In: Richard Lee, Proceedings ANZMAC 2012. Australian and New Zealand Marketing Academy Conference (ANZMAC 2012), Adelaide, SA, Australia, (1-7). 3 - 5 December 2012.

 0.54

206

63</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7483-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7483_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:40:02">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:223911</link><title>Does Mind-Reading Matter for Adolescent Social Functioning? A Study of Theory of Mind, Social Anxiety and Social Acceptance</title><description>Klopper, Eve G. (2011). Does Mind-Reading Matter for Adolescent Social Functioning? A Study of Theory of Mind, Social Anxiety and Social Acceptance Professional Doctorate, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.54

309

93</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7483-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7483_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:40:03">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:293357</link><title>Ostracism in social networking</title><description>Verreynne, Marnize (2012). Ostracism in social networking Honours Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.48

177

14</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7483-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7483_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:40:04">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:290203</link><title>Privacy and identity management in social media: driving factors for identity hiding</title><description>Smala, Simone and Al-Shehri, Saleh (2013). Privacy and identity management in social media: driving factors for identity hiding. In Jared Keengwe (Ed.), Research perspectives and best practices in educational technology integration (pp. 304-320) Hershey, PA, United States: Information Science Reference.

 0.40

127

13

0

Cited 0 times in Scopus0

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7483-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7483_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:40:05">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:179787</link><title>Meeting the challenges in information service provision for rural health professionals</title><description>Keast, Don, O'Neill, Sandra and Morris, Jocelyn (2009). Meeting the challenges in information service provision for rural health professionals. In: , Proceedings of the 10th International Congress on Medical Librarianship. Positioning the Profession: the Tenth International Congress on Medical Librarianship, Brisbane, Australia, (1-19). 31 August - 4 September, 2009.

 0.37

311

513</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7483-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7483_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:40:07">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:179928</link><title>An investigation into the information behaviour of veterinary practitioners in South Africa</title><description>Nel, Marguerite (2009). An investigation into the information behaviour of veterinary practitioners in South Africa. In: Positioning the Profession: the Tenth International Congress on Medical Librarianship, Brisbane, Australia, (1-25). August 31-September 4, 2009.

 0.35

163

793</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7483-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7483_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:40:08">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:293095</link><title>Parenting support 2.0: social media as a parenting support tool</title><description>Tee, Amelia Hwei Ying (2012). Parenting support 2.0: social media as a parenting support tool Honours Thesis, School of Psychology, The University of Queensland.

 0.33

43

6</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>