<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7493">islam discussions social media</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:49:58" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7493-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7493_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:50:05">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:282660</link><title>Islam and education: conflict and conformity in Pakistan's madrassahs</title><description>Ali, Saleem H. Islam and education: conflict and conformity in Pakistan's madrassahs. Karachi, Pakistan: Oxford Univerisity Press, 2009.

 0.99

111</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7493-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7493_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:50:07">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:196965</link><title>The Islamic Publication Industry in Modern Indonesia: Intellectual Transmission, Ideology, and the Profit Motive</title><description>Akh Muzakki (2009). The Islamic Publication Industry in Modern Indonesia: Intellectual Transmission, Ideology, and the Profit Motive PhD Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion, and Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.95

444

22</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7493-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7493_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:50:08">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:281078</link><title>Embracing Sharia-compliant products through regulatory amendment to achieve parity of treatment</title><description>Sadiq, Kerrie and Black, Ann (2012) Embracing Sharia-compliant products through regulatory amendment to achieve parity of treatment. Sydney Law Review, 34 1: 189-211.

 0.90

48

3</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7493-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7493_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:50:09">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:184493</link><title>Sacred communication: Exploring the attributes of health promotion programs in the faith-based media</title><description>Ahmad, Mohd Khairie, Harrison, John and Lawe Davies, Christopher R. (2009). Sacred communication: Exploring the attributes of health promotion programs in the faith-based media. In: Conference on Media and Islamic Thinking (MIST'09), Bangi, Malaysia, (). 21-22 July 2009.

 0.89

172

472</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7493-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7493_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:50:10">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:238095</link><title>Islamic Studies and Islamic Education in Contemporary Southeast Asia</title><description>Islamic Studies and Islamic Education in Contemporary Southeast Asia. Edited by Kamaruzzaman Bustamam-Ahmad and Patrick Jory Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia: Yayasan Ilmuwan, 2011.

 0.89

225

35395</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7493-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7493_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:50:12">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:229665</link><title>Islamic Persuasive Communication: Concepts, Characteristics, and Impacts of Media Health Programs</title><description>Mohd Ahmad (2011). Islamic Persuasive Communication: Concepts, Characteristics, and Impacts of Media Health Programs PhD Thesis, School of Journalism and Communication, The University of Queensland.

 0.87

1072

20</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7493-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7493_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:50:13">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:184492</link><title>Cultural sensitivity in health promotion program: Islamic persuasive communication</title><description>Ahmad, Mohd Khairie, Harrison, John and Lawe Davies, Christopher (2008). Cultural sensitivity in health promotion program: Islamic persuasive communication. In: 6th International Conference on Communication and Mass Media, Athens, Greece, (1-11). 19-22 May 2008.

 0.83

331

552</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7493-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7493_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:50:15">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:184491</link><title>Untapped potential: Cultural sensitivity-Islamic persuasive communication in health promotion programs</title><description>Ahmad, Mohd Khairie and Harrison, John (2007). Untapped potential: Cultural sensitivity-Islamic persuasive communication in health promotion programs. In: , Proceedings of: The Global Communication and Development Conference. Global Communication and Development Conference, Shanghai, China, (1-21). 16-21 October 2007.

 0.81

285

563</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7493-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7493_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:50:16">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:194709</link><title>An analysis of Islamic conceptualisations of press freedom in Malaysia</title><description>Nerawi Sedu (2009). An analysis of Islamic conceptualisations of press freedom in Malaysia PhD Thesis, School of Journalism and Communication, The University of Queensland.

 0.79

650

52</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7493-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7493_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:50:18">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:240254</link><title>From “Patani Melayi” to “Thai Muslim</title><description>Jory, Patrick (2006) From “Patani Melayi” to “Thai Muslim. ISIM Review, 18 : 42-43.

 0.74

50

1</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>