<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7496">why IEEE member</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:52:56" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7496-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7496_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:53:02">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:235074</link><title>Symbolic analysis of tau cell log-domain filter using affine MOSFET models</title><description>Thanigaivelan, Balavelan, Postula, Adam, Jin, Craig, Schaik, Andre Van and Hamilton, Tara Julia (2010). Symbolic analysis of tau cell log-domain filter using affine MOSFET models. In: , Proceedings of the 2010 Asia Pacific Conference on Circuits And Systems. Asia Pacific Conference on Circuits And Systems (APCCAS2010), Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, (1095-1099). 6-9 December 2010.

 0.86

68

133</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7496-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7496_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:53:03">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:279517</link><title>Investigation of the impacts of three-phase photovoltaic systems on three-phase unbalanced networks</title><description>Roediger, Stephanie, Yan, Ruifeng and Saha, Tapan (2012). Investigation of the impacts of three-phase photovoltaic systems on three-phase unbalanced networks. In: , 2012 IEEE Power and Energy Society General Meeting. 2012 IEEE Power and Energy Society General Meeting, San Diego, United States, (1-8). 22-26 July 2012.

 0.49

101

3

0

Cited 0 times in Scopus0

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7496-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7496_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:53:04">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:9867</link><title>Investigation of Power Quality Categorisation and Simulating Its Impact on Sensitive Electronic Equipment</title><description>Thapar, A., Saha, T. K. and Dong, Z. Y. (2004). Investigation of Power Quality Categorisation and Simulating Its Impact on Sensitive Electronic Equipment. In: T. Weaver, Proceedings of the IEEE Power Engineering Society General Meeting 2004. IEEE Power Engineering Society General Meeting, Denver, Colorado, USA, (1-6). 6-10 June, 2004.

 0.49

533

1763</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7496-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7496_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:53:05">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:77915</link><title>Application of program packages EMTDC and matlab in the analysis of impact of neutral point operating regime on the magnitude of touch Voltage</title><description>Berbic, N., Memisevic, R. and Vorsic, J. (2005) Application of program packages EMTDC and matlab in the analysis of impact of neutral point operating regime on the magnitude of touch Voltage. IEEE Transactions on Power Delivery, 20 2: 838-843.

 0.48

86

94

0

Cited 4 times in Scopus4

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7496-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7496_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:53:06">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:294366</link><title>Investigation of LMP forecasting for congested power systems</title><description>Nappu, Muhammad Bachtiar, Arief, Ardiaty, Saha, Tapan Kumar and Bansal, Ramesh C. (2012). Investigation of LMP forecasting for congested power systems. In: , Proceedings Universities Power Engineering Conference (AUPEC), 2012 22nd Australasian. Universities Power Engineering Conference (AUPEC), 2012 22nd Australasian, Bali, Indonesia, (1-6). 26 – 29 September 2012.

 0.45

49

6

Cited 0 times in Scopus0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7496-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7496_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:53:08">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:8348</link><title>Optimal multi-user spectrum balancing for digital subscriber lines</title><description>Cendrillon, Raphael, Moonen, Marc, Verlinden, Jan and Bostoen, Tom (2006) Optimal multi-user spectrum balancing for digital subscriber lines. IEEE Transactions on Communications, 54 5: 922-933.

 0.45

340

858

159

Cited 227 times in Scopus227

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7496-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7496_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:53:09">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:9854</link><title>Investigating the impact of Powerformer on voltage stability by dynamic simulation</title><description>Aumuller, Craig and Saha, Tapan K. (2003) Investigating the impact of Powerformer on voltage stability by dynamic simulation. IEEE Transactions on Power Systems, 18 3: 1142-1148.

 0.45

851

1427

11

Cited 19 times in Scopus19

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7496-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7496_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:53:11">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:324879</link><title>Bayesian neural network and discrete wavelet transform for partial discharge pattern classification in high voltage equipment</title><description>Ma, Hui, Chan, Jeffery C. and Saha, Tapan K. (2013). Bayesian neural network and discrete wavelet transform for partial discharge pattern classification in high voltage equipment. In: , 2013 IEEE Power and Energy Society General Meeting (PES): Proceedings. PES-GM 2013: IEEE Power and Energy Society General Meeting, Vancouver, BC, Canada, (1-5). 21-25 July, 2013.

 0.44

111

25

0

Cited 0 times in Scopus0

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7496-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7496_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:53:12">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:9811</link><title>Analysis and Assessment of Large Scale Power System Voltage Stability by a Novel Sensitivity Based Method</title><description>Aumuller, Craig and Saha, Tapan K. (2002). Analysis and Assessment of Large Scale Power System Voltage Stability by a Novel Sensitivity Based Method. In: M. Proetto, Proceedings of the IEEE Power Engineering Summer Meeting 2002. IEEE Power Engineering Society Summer Meeting, Chicago, USA, (1-6). July, 2002.

 0.44

558

1196</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7496-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7496_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:53:13">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:309765</link><title>Preliminary results for dissolved gas levels in a vegetable oil-filled power transformer</title><description>Martin, Daniel, Lelekakis,Nick, Davydov, Valery and Odarenko, Yuriy (2010) Preliminary results for dissolved gas levels in a vegetable oil-filled power transformer. IEEE Electrical Insulation Magazine, 26 5: 41-48.

 0.43

25

1

5

Cited 7 times in Scopus7

0</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>