<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7503">uki</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 02:59:54" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7503-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7503_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:00:01">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:40525</link><title>There's a Woman in the House, A 1950's Journey</title><description>Jordan, D., Jordan, L. and Paddle, S. There's a Woman in the House, A 1950's Journey 1 ed. Uki, NSW: Nadroj Press, 2003.

 0.82

180</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7503-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7503_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:00:02">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:158428</link><title>Depth in the Floating World: Western Realism and the Transformation of Traditional Space in Late Ukiyo-e Landscape Prints</title><description>Hickey, Gary James (2007). Depth in the Floating World: Western Realism and the Transformation of Traditional Space in Late Ukiyo-e Landscape Prints PhD Thesis, School of English, Media Studies and Art History, University of Queensland.

 0.57

201

8</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7503-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7503_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:00:03">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:243612</link><title>Front matter</title><description>(1980) Front matter. John Oxley journal: a bulletin for historical research in Queensland, 1 2: -2.

 0.43

30

13</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7503-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7503_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:00:04">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:313395</link><title>Notes on the origin of altered macerals in the Ragged Edge of the Pennsylvanian (Asturian) Herrin coalbed, Western Kentucky</title><description>Valentim, Bruno, Hower, James C., O'Keefe, Jennifer M. K., Rodrigues, Sandra, Ribeiro, Joana and Guedes, Alexandra (2013) Notes on the origin of altered macerals in the Ragged Edge of the Pennsylvanian (Asturian) Herrin coalbed, Western Kentucky. International Journal of Coal Geology, 115 : 24-40.

 0.43

27

0

Cited 0 times in Scopus0

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7503-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7503_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:00:05">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:254529</link><title>Biology of plant rhabdoviruses</title><description>Jackson, Andrew O., Dietzgen, Ralf G., Goodin, Michael M., Bragg, Jennifer N. and Deng, Min (2005) Biology of plant rhabdoviruses. Annual Review of Phytopathology, 43 : 623-660.

 0.43

29

52

Cited 55 times in Scopus55

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7503-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7503_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:00:06">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:254144</link><title>Pheromone trap for the eastern tent caterpillar moth</title><description>Haynes, Kenneth F., Mclaughlin, John, Stamper, Shelby, Rucker, Charlene, Webster, Francis X., Czokajlo, Darek and Kirsch, Philipp (2007) Pheromone trap for the eastern tent caterpillar moth. Environmental Entomology, 36 5: 1199-1205.

 0.43

33

1

Cited 1 times in Scopus1

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7503-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7503_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:00:08">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:287015</link><title>In planta localization and interactions of impatiens necrotic spot tospovirus proteins</title><description>Dietzgen, Ralf G., Martin, Kathleen M., Anderson, Gavin and Goodin, Michael M. (2012) In planta localization and interactions of impatiens necrotic spot tospovirus proteins. Journal of General Virology, 93 PART 11: 2490-2495.

 0.43

33

1

Cited 2 times in Scopus2

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7503-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7503_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:00:09">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:260073</link><title>Re Made in Tokyo</title><description>Andrew P. Steen (2011). Re Made in Tokyo MPhil Thesis, School of Architecture, The University of Queensland.

 0.32

367

13</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7503-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7503_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:00:10">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:243614</link><title>The Gold Coast : it's first inhabitants</title><description>Longhurst, Robert (1980) The Gold Coast : it's first inhabitants. John Oxley journal: a bulletin for historical research in Queensland, 1 2: 15-24.

 0.28

55

275</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7503-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7503_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:00:12">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:320592</link><title>Structural characterisation of the nuclear import receptor importin alpha in complex with the bipartite NLS of Prp20</title><description>Roman, Noelia, Christie, Mary, Swarbrick, Crystall M. D., Kobe, Bostjan and Forwood, Jade K. (2013) Structural characterisation of the nuclear import receptor importin alpha in complex with the bipartite NLS of Prp20. PLoS One, 8 12: e82038.1-e82038.6.

 0.28

31

0

Cited 0 times in Scopus0

0</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>