<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7504">leiden schools</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:00:53" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7504-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7504_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:00:56">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:291604</link><title>Complement factor C5a as mast cell activator mediates vascular remodelling in vein graft disease</title><description>de Vries, Margreet R., Wezel, Anouk, Schepers, Abbey, van Santbrink, Peter J., Woodruff, Trent M., Niessen, Hans W. M., Hamming, Jaap F., Kuiper, Johan, Bot, Ilze and Quax, Paul H. A. (2013) Complement factor C5a as mast cell activator mediates vascular remodelling in vein graft disease. Cardiovascular Research, 97 2: 311-320.

 0.68

21

5

Cited 6 times in Scopus6

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7504-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7504_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:00:58">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:191025</link><title>Hiroshige</title><description>Hickey, Gary (2005). Hiroshige. In Amy Reigle Newland (Ed.), The Hotei encyclopedia of Japanese woodblock prints (pp. 504-504) Leiden, The Netherlands: Hotei Publishing.

 0.63

47</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7504-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7504_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:00:59">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:271690</link><title>Demetrios (852)</title><description>Wheatley, Pat and Collins, Andrew (2009). Demetrios (852). In Ian Worthington (Ed.), Brill's new Jacoby Online ed. (pp. x-x) Leiden, The Netherlands: Brill.

 0.63

46</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7504-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7504_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:01:00">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:220176</link><title>The reign of King Suriyavongsa</title><description>Stuart-Fox, Martin (2010). The reign of King Suriyavongsa. In Juliette Van Krieken-Pieters (Ed.), Van Wuysthoff and the Lan Xang Kingdom: A dutch merchant’s visit to Laos in 1641 (pp. 173-186) Leiden, Netherlands: Gingko Publishers.

 0.63

73

12</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7504-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7504_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:01:01">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:286130</link><title>God is the greatest: multiple forms of Muslim religiosity in Peninsular Malaysia</title><description>Hoffstaedter, Gerhard (2013). God is the greatest: multiple forms of Muslim religiosity in Peninsular Malaysia. In Thomas Reuter and Alexander Horstmann (Ed.), Faith in the future: understanding the revitalization of religions and cultural traditions in Asia (pp. 251-268) Leiden, Netherlands: Brill.

 0.63

120

5

0

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7504-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7504_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:01:03">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:190302</link><title>Hokusai</title><description>Hickey, Gary (2006) Hokusai in Amy Reigle Newland (eds.) The Hotei Encyclopedia of Japanese Woodblock Prints. Leiden: Hotei Publishing

 0.63

52</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7504-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7504_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:01:04">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:273939</link><title>How well do starlab and nbody compare? II. Hardware and accuracy</title><description>Anders, P., Baumgardt, H., Gaburov, E. and Zwart, S. Portegies (2012) How well do starlab and nbody compare? II. Hardware and accuracy. Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, 421 4: 3557-3569.

 0.57

29

1

Cited 1 times in Scopus1

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7504-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7504_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:01:06">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:305869</link><title>Relationship between Factor V Leiden mutation and venous thromboembolism in patients with breast cancer treated with tamoxifen</title><description>Onitilo, Adedayo A., Doi, Suhail A. R., Engel, Jessica M., Glurich, Ingrid and Berg, Richard (2013) Relationship between Factor V Leiden mutation and venous thromboembolism in patients with breast cancer treated with tamoxifen. Thrombosis Research, 131 6: 567-568.

 0.57

46

1

Cited 1 times in Scopus1

0</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7504-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7504_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:01:08">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:260185</link><title>A literary mirror: Balinese reflections on modernity and identity in the twentieth century</title><description>Putra, I Nyoman Darma A literary mirror: Balinese reflections on modernity and identity in the twentieth century. Leiden, Netherlands: KITLV Press, 2011.

 0.56

57

5</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7504-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7504_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:01:09">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:313258</link><title>Beyond cultural constraint: gender, security and participation in the Pacific Islands</title><description>George, Nicole (2013). Beyond cultural constraint: gender, security and participation in the Pacific Islands. In Sara E. Davies, Zim Nworka, Eli Stamnes and Sarah Teitt (Ed.), Responsibility to Protect and Women, Peace and Security: Aligning the Protection Agendas (pp. 155-180) Leiden, Holland: Martinus Nijhof Publishers.

 0.56

33

5

0</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>