<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7505">ethnic myanmar</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:01:50" name="UQ eSpace" id="FW14-e016"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e016-7505-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7505_01.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:01:55">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:311499</link><title>Biodiversity conservation in a changing climate: a review of threats and implications for conservation planning in Myanmar</title><description>Rao, Madhu, Htun, Saw, Platt, Steven G., Tizard, Robert, Poole, Colin, Myint, Than and Watson, James E. M. (2013) Biodiversity conservation in a changing climate: a review of threats and implications for conservation planning in Myanmar. Ambio, 42 7: 789-804.

 0.87

39

4

1

Cited 1 times in Scopus1

38</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7505-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7505_02.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:01:56">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:108368</link><title>Exploring the socio-economic situation of plantation villagers: A case study in Myanmar Bago Yoma</title><description>Maung, Tin Min and Yamamoto, Miho (2007). Exploring the socio-economic situation of plantation villagers: A case study in Myanmar Bago Yoma. In: Steve Harrison, Annerine Bosch and John Herbohn, Improving the Triple Bottom Line Returns from Small-scale Forestry: Proceedings from an International Conference. Improving the Triple Bottom Line Returns from Small-scale Forestry, Ormoc, the Philippines, (253-266). 18 - 21 June 2007.

 0.69

311

1854</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7505-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7505_03.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:01:59">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:256906</link><title>ASEAN-US strategic partnership in East Asia community building: Opportunities, risks and constraints</title><description>Morada, Noel M. (2011). ASEAN-US strategic partnership in East Asia community building: Opportunities, risks and constraints. In Mark Borthwick and Tadashi Yamamoto (Ed.), A Pacific nation : Perspectives on the US role in an East Asia community (pp. 103-132) Tokyo, Japan: Japan Center for International Exchange.

 0.51

152

29</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7505-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7505_04.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:02:00">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:178726</link><title>Women and power in Burmese history</title><description>Jessica Harriden (2008). Women and power in Burmese history PhD Thesis, School of History, Philosophy, Religion &amp; Classics, The University of Queensland.

 0.48

388

17</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7505-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7505_05.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:02:01">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:240254</link><title>From “Patani Melayi” to “Thai Muslim</title><description>Jory, Patrick (2006) From “Patani Melayi” to “Thai Muslim. ISIM Review, 18 : 42-43.

 0.46

50

1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7505-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7505_06.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:02:02">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:252590</link><title>Gender dimensions of malaria self-care in rural Myanmar ?</title><description>Tin-Oo (2003). Gender dimensions of malaria self-care in rural Myanmar ? PhD Thesis, School of Population Health, The University of Queensland.

 0.40

52

3</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7505-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7505_07.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:02:03">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:120453</link><title>Sustainability issues and socio-economic change in the Jingpo communities of China : governance, culture and land rights.</title><description>Zhuge, Ren and Tisdell, C. A. (Clement Allan) (1996). Sustainability issues and socio-economic change in the Jingpo communities of China : governance, culture and land rights.. Working papers on economics, ecology and the environment. Working Paper No. 4, Department of Economics, University of Queensland.

 0.38

305

502</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7505-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7505_08.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:02:04">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:310811</link><title>Australian Chinese legislative recruitment, political incorporation and representation in the global moment (1973-2012)</title><description>Kwok, Jen Tsen (2013). Australian Chinese legislative recruitment, political incorporation and representation in the global moment (1973-2012) PhD Thesis, History, Philosophy, Religion and Classics (HPRC), The University of Queensland.

 0.36

42

6</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7505-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7505_09.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:02:05">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:268504</link><title>Improving energy security in East Asia: Prospects for energy cooperation</title><description>Taylor, Monique (2011). Improving energy security in East Asia: Prospects for energy cooperation. In: , 2011 Australia-China Futures Dialogues, Emerging Leaders' Dialogue: Non-traditional Security Challenges and Regional Cooperation in Asia. Australia-China Futures Dialogues, Emerging Leaders' Dialogue: Non-Traditional Security Challenges and Regional Cooperation in East Asia (2011), Beijiing, China, (30-33). 28-29 July 2011.

 0.33

184

2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e016-7505-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e016/7505_10.html" timestamp="2014-05-23 03:02:07">http://espace.library.uq.edu.au/view/UQ:294224</link><title>Corporate social marketing, Petronas festival advertisements: nation building, brand building and identity</title><description>Abdullah, Rozita (2012). Corporate social marketing, Petronas festival advertisements: nation building, brand building and identity PhD Thesis, School of Journalism and Communication, The University of Queensland.

 0.33

550

16</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>