<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7207">earthquake</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:32:10" name="ESPN" id="FW14-e160"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e160-7207-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e160/7207_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:32:12">http://espnfc.com/euro2012/en</link><title>Rapids, Earthquakes finish goalless</title><description>#INSERT type:video END# COMMERCE CITY, Colo. -- Alan Gordon hit the crossbar in the opening minute for San Jose and that was as close as the Earthquakes and the Colorado Rapids got to scoring in their 0-0 draw Saturday. Chris Wondolowski's header c...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e160-7207-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e160/7207_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:33:17">http://grantland.com/hollywood-prospectus/beast-mode-the-return-of-greg-dulli-and-the-afghan-whigs/</link><title>'Beast' Mode: The Return of Greg Dulli and the Afghan W...</title><description>Millions in the Los Angeles area were woken up by a 4.4 earthquake before the dawn of March 18. Greg Dulli was not one of them. This is in a figurative sense; the Cincinnati-born Afghan Whigs front man has lived in L.A. for about 25 years, and one of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e160-7207-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e160/7207_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:33:58">http://espnfc.com/blog/_/name/thetoepoke/id/6691/gif-columbus-crew-defender-gonzalez-guilty-of-play-acting</link><title>GIF: Columbus Crew defender Gonzalez guilty of play-acting</title><description>The San Jose Earthquakes and the Columbus Crew drew 1-1 in Major League Soccer on Sunday, but the game all but ended on a sour note when, in the closing few minutes, Columbus defender Giancarlo Gonzalez stooped to produce a piece of truly abysmal pla...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e160-7207-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e160/7207_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:34:55">http://espnfc.com/blog/_/name/usnationalteam/id/1796/u-s-hot-list-mixed-bag-for-key-internationals</link><title>U.S. Hot List: Mixed bag for key internationals</title><description>It's safe to say that Saturday was full of mixed emotions for Jurgen Klinsmann. The U.S. coach was in attendance for an evening match between the Galaxy and Vancouver Whitecaps at StubHub Center just outside of Los Angeles, where he watched World Cup...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e160-7207-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e160/7207_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:35:32">http://espnfc.com/uk/en/report/384790/san-jose-draw-columbus</link><title>San Jose draw with Columbus</title><description>#INSERT type:video END# SANTA CLARA, Calif. -- Chris Wondolowski scored on a header in the 51st minute to help the San Jose Earthquakes tie the Columbus Crew 1-1 on Sunday. Wondolowski has three goals this season for San Jose (0-2-2). Federico Hig...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e160-7207-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e160/7207_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:36:26">http://espnfc.com/blog/_/name/soccerusa/id/4586/cascadia-chaos-understudies-step-up-pivotal-red-cards</link><title>Cascadia chaos, understudies step up, pivotal red cards</title><description>The opening game of the MLS weekend set an impossible standard for the rest of the schedule but it didn't mean there wasn't entertainment to come. Great goals and big performances, even in the absence of a host of stars, trickled out from across the ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e160-7207-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e160/7207_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:36:59">http://espnfc.com/news/story/_/id/1772021/concacaf-fines-toluca-taping-san-jose-earthquakes</link><title>CONCACAF fines Toluca for taping San Jose Earthquakes</title><description>San Jose Earthquakes news</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e160-7207-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e160/7207_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:37:39">http://espn.go.com/blog/boston/new-england-revolution/post/_/id/2805/defense-lifts-revs-past-earthquakes</link><title>Defense lifts Revs past Earthquakes</title><description>In the days leading up to Saturday's match at San Jose, Revolution center back A.J. Soares was well aware of the challenge he and his teammates would face at Buck Shaw Stadium. With Chris Wondolowski and Steven Lenhart forming one of the best forw...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e160-7207-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e160/7207_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:38:26">http://espn.go.com/blog/boston/new-england-revolution/post/_/id/2801/nguyens-late-goal-gives-revs-first-win</link><title>Nguyen's late goal gives Revs first win</title><description>The comeback kids took center stage on Saturday. But it wasn't the Earthquakes who came out on top at Buck Shaw Stadium. Lee Nguyen's stoppage-time strike delivered a late dagger to the hosts, who entered Saturday's match with 17 stoppage-time goa...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e160-7207-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e160/7207_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 15:39:30">http://espnfc.com/uk/en/report/384809/revs-beat-quakes-93rd-minute</link><title>Revs beat Quakes in 93rd minute</title><description>Lee Nguyen scored in the 93rd minute, and the New England Revolution beat the San Jose Earthquakes 2-1 on Saturday night for their first win of the season.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>