<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7503">uki</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:30:29" name="ESPN" id="FW14-e160"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e160-7503-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e160/7503_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:30:30">http://insider.espn.go.com/blog/colleges/usc/post/_/id/15886/roundtable-usc-spring-storylines</link><title>Roundtable: USC spring storylines</title><description>WeAreSC staffers give opinions on topics related to Trojans football: What storyline will you be most interested to follow in spring ball? Garry Paskwietz: I'll be watching to see how the defense begins to take shape under new coordinator Justi...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e160-7503-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e160/7503_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:31:23">http://insider.espn.go.com/blog/colleges/usc/post/_/id/15865/breakdown-trojans-at-the-nfl-combine</link><title>Breakdown: Trojans at the NFL combine</title><description>The 2014 NFL Scouting Combine gets underway this week in Indianapolis, and there will be seven Trojans in attendance to perform in front of league coaches, scouts and personnel men. Here's an alphabetical look at the former USC players and where t...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e160-7503-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e160/7503_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:32:27">http://espn.go.com/blog/detroit-lions/post/_/id/5448/lions-draft-outlook-defensive-tackles</link><title>Lions draft outlook: Defensive tackles</title><description>The all-star games are over. The combine, which is the next area for potential draftees to prove anything, is less than a month away. Many of the players selected in May's draft will come from these three all-star games or from underclassmen who d...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e160-7503-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e160/7503_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:32:59">http://espn.go.com/blog/pac10/post/_/id/68594/filling-early-entries-spots-in-the-pac-12-south</link><title>Replacing the Pac-12 South's early entries</title><description>The Pac-12 has 26 of the 98 early entrants in the NFL draft. That's impressive. Some players are locks to get drafted. Others might have jumped the gun a bit and find themselves on practice squads or brushing up on their Canadian. We'll see. What ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e160-7503-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e160/7503_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:33:38">http://espn.go.com/blog/pac10/post/_/id/68299/sarkisian-focuses-on-building-trust-at-usc</link><title>Sarkisian focuses on building trust at USC</title><description>When USC defensive back Josh Shaw learned Steve Sarkisian would be the Trojans' new head coach, it was as if a four-year-old wish was finally granted. During the recruiting process, Shaw, a Southern California native, developed a strong bond with ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e160-7503-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e160/7503_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:34:47">http://espn.go.com/blog/pac10/post/_/id/68237/24-pac-12-players-entering-nfl-draft-early</link><title>25 Pac-12 players entering NFL draft early</title><description>While a number of big-name players opted to stick around for another year of Pac-12, most notably Oregon QB Marcus Mariota, UCLA QB Brett Hundley and Oregon State QB Sean Mannion, the conference was hit hard by early defections. Here's the complet...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e160-7503-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e160/7503_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:35:40">http://insider.espn.go.com/blog/colleges/usc/post/_/id/15172/five-stay-five-go-departures-still-sting</link><title>Five stay, five go; departures still sting</title><description>The Trojans have the decisions of all the NFL draft-eligible players and it was a mixed bag of results, with five players choosing to stay and five players choosing to leave. It was a strong finish to the process in recent days when Hayes Pullard,...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e160-7503-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e160/7503_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:36:42">http://espn.go.com/blog/pac10/post/_/id/68133/mailbag-enough-with-the-graham-hate</link><title>Mailbag: Enough with the Graham hate</title><description>Welcome to the mailbag, which nine out of 10 dentists agree has no bearing on your oral health. Bobby in Phoenix writes: Mark May said the following yesterday: "I heard through the grapevine, not publicly, but privately, Todd Graham was lobbying l...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e160-7503-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e160/7503_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:37:32">http://insider.espn.go.com/blog/colleges/usc/post/_/id/15064/roundtable-trojans-leaving-for-the-nfl-draft</link><title>Roundtable: Trojans opting for NFL draft</title><description>The Trojans have lost five underclass players to the NFL draft this year with more announcements coming. The WeAreSC staffers give their thoughts on the following topics: 1. Does Hayes Pullard stay or go? Garry Paskwietz: I've gone back and for...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e160-7503-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e160/7503_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:38:24">http://insider.espn.go.com/blog/colleges/usc/post/_/id/15059/getting-a-line-on-the-trojans-defense</link><title>Getting a line on the Trojans defense</title><description>LOS ANGELES -- After watching both Florida State and Auburn slug it out in a BCS classic final, USC Trojans fans are reminded that if they're going to once again challenge for a national title, much less a Pac-12 South Division crown, it will probabl...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>