<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7042">bmw c1</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:54:17" name="Kickass jokes" id="FW14-e083"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e083-7042-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e083/7042_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:54:18">http://kickasshumor.com/funny-joke/575/a-man-in-his-mid-forties-bought-a-new-bmw-and-was-</link><title>Long Joke</title><description>A man in his mid forties bought a new BMW and was out on the interstate for a nice evening drive. 
The top was down, the breeze was blowing through what was left of his hair and he decided to see what the engine had. As the needle jumped up to 80 mph, he suddenly saw flashing red and blue lights behind him. 
There's no way they can catch a BMW, he thought to himself and opened her up further. The needle hit 90, then 100, and finally reality hit him and he knew he shouldn't run from the police, so he slowed down and pulled over. 
The cop came up to him, took his license without a word and examined it and the car. It's been a long day, this is the end of my shift and it's Friday the 13th. I don't feel like more paperwork, so if you can give me an excuse for your driving that I haven't heard before, you can go. 
The guy thinks for a second and says, "Last week my wife ran off with a cop. I was afraid you were trying to give her back." 
"Have a nice weekend." Said the officer and he walked away.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e083-7042-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e083/7042_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:55:51">http://kickasshumor.com/funny-joke/9174/qwhats-the-difference-between-a-bmw-and-a-porcup</link><title>Short Joke</title><description>Q.What's the difference between a BMW and a porcupine. 
A. With a porcupine the pricks on the outside.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e083-7042-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e083/7042_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:56:39">http://kickasshumor.com/funny-joke/9840/boy-marry-me-girl-do-you-have-a-house</link><title>Short Joke</title><description>Boy : Marry me.. ? 
Girl: Do you have a house..? 
Boy : No.. 
Girl: Do you have a BMW car.. ? 
Boy : No.. 
Girl: How much is your salary.. ? 
Boy : No salary.. but,.. 
Girl: No but. You have nothing.. How can i 
marry you.?? 
Leave please.! 
Boy: (talk to himself) I have one villa, 3 
property lands, 3 Ferrari, 2Porsche.. Why I 
still need to buy BMW.?! How can I get the 
salary when actually I am the BOSS</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>