<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7402">little johnny</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:42:38" name="Kickass jokes" id="FW14-e083"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e083-7402-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e083/7402_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:42:39">http://kickasshumor.com/funny-joke/616/little-johnny-sat-in-the-classroom-the-teacher-sa</link><title>Long Joke</title><description>little johnny sat in the classroom. the teacher says class if you can tell me who said these quotes, ill let you leave early. who said four score and seven years ago? nancy beats johnny to it and shouts abe lincoln! the teacher says nancy you can leave. who said ask not what your country can do for you but what you can do for you? john kennedy shouts out susan. the teacher says very good susan you can leave. johnny says i wish these bitches would keep their mouths shut. the teacher says WHO SAID THAT?! johnny said tiger woods! can i leave now?</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e083-7402-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e083/7402_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:44:03">http://kickasshumor.com/funny-joke/686/little-johnny-attended-a-horse-auction-with-his-fa</link><title>Long Joke</title><description>Little Johnny attended a horse auction with his father. He watched as his father moved from horse to horse, running his hands up and down the horse's legs, rump, and chest. After a few minutes, Johnny asked, "Dad, why are you doing that?" His father replied, "Because when I'm buying horses, I have to make sure that they are healthy and in good shape before I buy. Johnny, looking worried, said, "Dad, I think the UPS guy wants to buy Mom."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e083-7402-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e083/7402_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:45:16">http://kickasshumor.com/funny-joke/722/one-day-a-man-lied-down-on-a-nude-beach-little-jo</link><title>Dirty Joke</title><description>One day a man lied down on a nude beach. Little Johnny comes up to the man, points to his penis and asks what it was. "Oh, that's my birdie." said the man. "Oh." little Johnny replies. The man fell asleep. When the man woke up, he found himself in the hospital. He looked around to find little Johnny at his bedside. "Hey kid, what happened?", asked the man. "Oh," says little Johnny. "I tried to pet your birdie. It tried to spit water at me, so I cracked it's eggs and burnt it's nest."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e083-7402-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e083/7402_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:46:54">http://kickasshumor.com/funny-joke/1522/fred-and-mary-get-married-but-cant-afford-a-honey</link><title>Dirty Joke</title><description>Fred and Mary get married but can't afford a honeymoon, so they go back to mom and dads for the night. 

In the morning, little Johnny gets up and has his breakfast. 
As he is going out of the door to go to school, he asks his mum if Fred and Mary are up yet. 
She replies, "No". 
Johnny asks, "Do you know what I think?" His mom replies, "Never mind what you think! Just go to school." 

Johnny comes home for lunch and asks his mom, "Is Fred and Mary up yet?" 
She replies, "No." 
Johnny says, "Do you know what I think?" 
His mom replies, "Never mind what you think! Eat your lunch and go back to school." 

After school, he comes home and asks, "Is Fred and Mary up yet?" 
His mom says, "No." 
Johnny asks, "Do you know what I think?" 
His mom replies, "OK! What do you think?" 
He says, "Well, last night Fred came in for Vaseline and I think I gave him my airplane glue."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e083-7402-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e083/7402_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:48:14">http://kickasshumor.com/funny-joke/1609/little-johnny-is-outside-in-the-back-yard-playing-</link><title>Long Joke</title><description>Little Johnny is outside in the back yard playing with his toy airplane. He takes it up in the air "rrrrrrrrrr" and brings it down for a landing, at which point he yells real loud "All you motherfuckers that wanna get off, get off. All you motherfuckers that wanna get on, get on." Well Johnnys mom is in the kitchen and hears him yell this. Shocked, Johnnys mom runs outside and tells Johnny to go to his room for 3 hours and think about what he's said. Pouting, johnny stomps to his room. 3 hours later Johnny comes out of his room and goes straight for his toy airplane in the back yard. He picks it up, flys it around a little and lands it. With mom listening closely from the window Johnny says "all you nice people that want to get off, get off. All you nice people that wanna get on, get on......and all you motherfuckers complaining about the 3 hour time delay, talk to the bitch in the kitchen.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e083-7402-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e083/7402_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:49:34">http://kickasshumor.com/funny-joke/1827/one-day-little-johnny-saw-his-grandpa-smoking-his</link><title>Dirty Joke</title><description>One day, Little Johnny saw his grandpa smoking his cigarettes. Little Johnny asked, "Grandpa, can I smoke some of your cigarettes?" His grandpa replied, "Can your penis reach your asshole?" "No", said Little Johnny. His grandpa replied, "Then you're not old enough." 

The next day, Little Johnny saw his grandpa drinking beer. He asked, "Grandpa, can I drink some of your beer?" His grandpa replied, "Can your penis reach your asshole?" "No" said Little Johhny. "Then you're not old enough." his grandpa replied. 

The next day, Little Johnny was eating cookies. His grandpa asked, "Can I have some of your cookies?" Little Johnny replied, "Can your penis reach your asshole?" His grandpa replied, "It most certainly can!" Little Johnny replied, "Then go fuck yourself. These are my cookies!"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e083-7402-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e083/7402_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:50:27">http://kickasshumor.com/funny-joke/1988/little-johnnys-chemistry-teacher-wanted-to-teach-</link><title>Long Joke</title><description>Little Johnny's Chemistry teacher wanted to teach his class a lesson about the evils of liquor, so he set up an experiment that involved a glass of water, a glass of whiskey, and two worms. 

"Now, class. Observe what happens to the two the worms," said the professor putting the first worm in the glass of water. The worm in the water moved about, twisting and seemingly unharmed. 

He then dropped the second work in the whiskey glass. It writhed in pain for a moment, then quickly sank to the bottom and died. "Now kids, what lesson can we derive from this experiment?" he asked. 

Little Johnny raised his hand and wisely responded, "Drink whiskey and you won't get worms!"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e083-7402-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e083/7402_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:51:53">http://kickasshumor.com/funny-joke/2089/teacher-anyone-who-thinks-hes-stupid-may-stand-</link><title>Short Joke</title><description>Teacher: "Anyone who thinks he's stupid may stand up!" 
*Nobody stands up* 
Teacher: "Im sure there are some stupid students over here!!" 
*Little Johnny stands up* 
Teacher: "Ohh, Johnny you think you're stupid?" 
Little Johnny: "No... i just feel bad that you're standing alone..."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e083-7402-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e083/7402_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:53:33">http://kickasshumor.com/funny-joke/2222/if-there-are-3-apples-and-johnny-takes-3-how-many</link><title>Anti-Humor Joke</title><description>If there are 3 apples and johnny takes 3, how many does johnny have? It doesn't matter, he was hit by a train</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e083-7402-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e083/7402_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 22:54:09">http://kickasshumor.com/funny-joke/2345/a-teacher-asks-her-class-if-there-are-5-birds-si</link><title>Long Joke</title><description>A teacher asks her class, "If there are 5 birds sitting on a fence and you shoot one of them, how many will be left?" She calls on little Johnny. 

"None, they all fly away with the first gunshot." 

The teacher replies, "The correct answer is 4, but I like your thinking." 

Then Little Johnny says, 
"I have a question for YOU.There are three women sitting on a bench having ice cream. One is delicately licking the sides of the triple scoop of ice cream. The second is gobbling down the top and sucking the cone. The third is biting off the top of the ice cream. Which one is married?" 

The teacher, blushing a great deal, replies, 
"Well I suppose the one that's gobbled down the top and sucked the cone." 

"The correct answer is the one with the wedding ring on... 

.....but I like your thinking."</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>