<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7001">LHC collision publications</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:32:41" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7001-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7001_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:32:43">http://lifeandphysics.wordpress.com/2010/08/17/into-the-unknown/</link><title>Into the unknown</title><description>Into the unknown

17 Aug 2010 by Jon Butterworth on Life and Physics lifeandphysics.wordpress.com/2010/08/17/into-the-unknown/

…  morning the first LHC paper to really probe for new physics was submitted by ATLAS to the …  There are also numerous preliminary results from all the LHC experiments. However, this ATLAS paper is the first to be sent for …

Topics: Particle Physics, Science, Atlas, cern, Nobel Prize</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7001-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7001_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:33:18">http://ukspacestore.wordpress.com/2013/05/18/lhc-news-lhc-creates-tiny-drops-of-big/</link><title>LHC NEWS: LHC Creates Tiny Drops of Big</title><description>LHC NEWS: LHC Creates Tiny Drops of Big

18 May 2013 by ukspacestore on UK Space Place ukspacestore.wordpress.com/2013/05/18/lhc-news-lhc-creates-tiny-drops-of-big/

LHC NEWS: LHC Creates Tiny Drops of Big Bang 'Blood Spatter'! The Large Hadron Collider (LHC) has recreated the world’s tiniest droplets of a primordial state of …

Topics: Space News</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7001-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7001_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:33:50">http://blogs.canada.com/2010/11/26/jet-quenching-and-the-big-bang-machine/</link><title>Jet Quenching and the Big Bang Machine</title><description>Jet Quenching and the Big Bang Machine

26 Nov 2010 by Jennifer Moreau on canada.com blogs.canada.com/2010/11/26/jet-quenching-and-the-big-bang-machine/

…  found that much. Click here. PR22.10 - 26.11.2010 LHC experiments bring new insight into primordial universe Geneva, 26 …  of nuclear matter, quarks and gluons, fly away from the collision point. In proton collisions, jets usually appear in pairs, emerging …

Topics: Burnaby_News</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7001-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7001_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:34:33">http://thedailyomnivore.net/2012/09/03/international-linear-collider/</link><title>International Linear Collider</title><description>International Linear Collider

4 Sep 2012 by partialmotionvideo on The Daily Omnivore thedailyomnivore.net/2012/09/03/international-linear-collider/

…  accelerator to succeed the Large Hadron Collider (LHC), the world's largest and highest-energy particle accelerator. The ILC is planned to have a collision energy of 500 GeV initially, with the possibility for a later upgrade …

Topics: Science, World, technology</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7001-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7001_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:34:55">http://makezine.com/2009/11/23/two-circulating-beams-bring-first-c/</link><title>Two circulating beams bring first collisions in the LHC</title><description>Two circulating beams bring first collisions in the LHC

23 Nov 2009 by Phillip Torrone on MAKE makezine.com/2009/11/23/two-circulating-beams-bring-first-c/

…  Two circulating beams bring first collisions in the LHC. Every time we have a post about the LHC the crazy comes out of the woodwork proclaiming the world is going to end …

Topics: Science</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7001-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7001_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:35:09">http://thingsbreak.wordpress.com/2008/09/11/media-lhc-doomsday-reporting/</link><title>Media LHC doomsday reporting</title><description>Media LHC doomsday reporting

11 Sep 2008 by thingsbreak on The Way Things Break thingsbreak.wordpress.com/2008/09/11/media-lhc-doomsday-reporting/

…  Dangerous Events During Heavy-Ion Collisions at the LHC: Report of the LHC Safety Study Group (2003) CERN Scientific Policy Committee (SPC) Report …

Topics: media, cern, Grumble Grumble, LHC, xkcd, hysteria, woo, Irrationality</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7001-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7001_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:36:16">http://sciencesprings.wordpress.com/2013/05/15/from-symmetry-whats-the-next-step-in-particle-colliders/</link><title>From Symmetry: "What’s the next step in particle colliders"</title><description>From Symmetry: "What’s the next step in particle colliders"

15 May 2013 by richardmitnick on Science Springs sciencesprings.wordpress.com/2013/05/15/from-symmetry-whats-the-next-step-in-particle-colliders/

…  from the linear Collider Collaboaration], to study the LHC’s discoveries in more detail. So what’s the difference between the LHC and the proposed ILC? Why do we need both? LHC Linear Collider. For …

Topics: LHC, High Energy Physics, particle accelerators, Particle Physics, Basic Research, LCC-Linear Collider Collaboration</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7001-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7001_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:38:54">http://physicsforme.com/2011/04/30/the-first-year-of-the-large-hadron-collider-a-brief-review/</link><title>The First Year of the Large Hadron Collider: A Brief Review</title><description>The First Year of the Large Hadron Collider: A Brief Review

30 Apr 2011 by physicsgg on physics4me physicsforme.com/2011/04/30/the-first-year-of-the-large-hadron-collider-a-brief-review/

…  first year of LHC data taking provided an integrated luminosity of about 35/pb in …  in the first months the LHC experiments reached the design performance. In more than hundred publications and conference notes tests of the Standard Model and searches for …

Topics: High Energy Physics, LHC</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7001-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7001_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:40:03">http://bbzippo.wordpress.com/2010/03/30/7-tev-collisions-why-not-antiprotons/</link><title>7 TeV collisions: why not antiprotons?</title><description>7 TeV collisions: why not antiprotons?

30 Mar 2010 by bbzippo on Drawing Blanks bbzippo.wordpress.com/2010/03/30/7-tev-collisions-why-not-antiprotons/

…  been wondering for a while why the LHC is designed for proton-proton collisions, and not proton-antiproton like …  the same set of magnets to circulate both beams, and the LHC needs two sets. First of all, apparently, it's very difficult to …  attraction dramatically increases the probability of collision. And at the LHC energies the virtual quarks (and antiquarks) and …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7001-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7001_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:41:47">http://manusuniverse.wordpress.com/2013/06/05/back-to-the-future-with-hera/</link><title>Back to the Future with HERA</title><description>Back to the Future with HERA

5 Jun 2013 by ManuG on Manu's Universe manusuniverse.wordpress.com/2013/06/05/back-to-the-future-with-hera/

…  quarks point the way for science at LHC Over a time span of 15 years, DESY’s particle accelerator HERA served …  are traces of particles emerging from a positron-proton collision at HERA. The red and gray traces are identified as the fragments of a …  collision events at the state-of-the-art accelerator LHC (Large Hadron Collider, CERN, Switzerland) greatly improves the precision …

Topics: Science, desy, Hera, LHC, Higgs boson, H1, Zeus, Proton, Z boson, W boson, charm quark, Partons, parton density function</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>