<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7010">manchester united FC football</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:17:39" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7010-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7010_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:17:40">http://myfootballshirtcollection.wordpress.com/2010/11/02/shirt-wish-list-4-%e2%80%93-fc-united-of-manchester-home-and-away-jersey/</link><title>Shirt Wish List #4 – FC United of Manchester Home and Away Jersey</title><description>Shirt Wish List #4 – FC United of Manchester Home and Away Jersey

2 Nov 2010 by myfootballshirtcollection on Myfootballshirtcollection's Blog myfootballshirtcollection.wordpress.com/2010/11/02/shirt-wish-list-4-–-fc-united-of-manchester-home-and-away-jersey/

…  a Manchester United fan I follow the team religiously and am aware of all the politics of …  . Well this has made some fans start their own club, FC United of Manchester and by the sounds of it they doing extremely well. …

Topics: Shirts Wish list, Manchester United, fc united of manchester, Home, away, Jersey, wishlist</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7010-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7010_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:19:26">http://watchstreamnflfreeliveonlinetv.wordpress.com/2013/11/02/watch-fulham-fc-vs-manchester-united-live-stream-soccer-online-tv/</link><title>Watch Fulham FC vs Manchester United Live stream soccer Online Tv</title><description>Watch Fulham FC vs Manchester United Live stream soccer Online Tv

2 Nov 2013 by dmmit01 on watchstreamnflfreeliveonlinetv watchstreamnflfreeliveonlinetv.wordpress.com/2013/11/02/watch-fulham-fc-vs-manchester-united-live-stream-soccer-online-tv/

…  here Fulham FC vs Manchester United SOCCER Football Online Fulham FC vs Manchester United. …

Topics: Sports Live!, Soccer, Fulham FC vs Manchester United highlights, Fulham FC vs Manchester United live free, Fulham FC vs Manchester United live Free feed, Fulham FC vs Manchester United live free Internet TV Co, Fulham FC vs Manchester United live free Online, Fulham FC vs Manchester United live free online coverag, Fulham FC vs Manchester United Live free online TV, Fulham FC vs Manchester United Live free Sopcast HD TV, Fulham FC vs Manchester United live free telecast, Fulham FC vs Manchester United live free TV link, Fulham FC vs Manchester United Live Free video, Fulham FC vs Manchester United recap, Fulham FC vs Manchester United streaming Free, Watch Fulham FC vs Manchester United live free</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7010-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7010_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:21:38">http://richardfrosty.com/2013/07/14/premier-league-twitter-table-2013-14/</link><title>Premier League Twitter Table 2013-14</title><description>Premier League Twitter Table 2013-14

14 Jul 2013 by Richard Frost on richardfrosty - Richard Frost - Manchester richardfrosty.com/2013/07/14/premier-league-twitter-table-2013-14/

…  Wednesday, 10 July 2013, the new Manchester United FC Twitter account @ManUtd announced its arrival with the tweet "New era, …

Topics: Richard Frost, manchester, social media marketing, Manchester United FC, manutd, Premier League Twitter Table, Manchester City FC, fc united of manchester, Liverpool FC, Arsenal FC, Chelsea FC</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7010-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7010_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:23:25">http://nakedsecurity.sophos.com/2008/06/05/want-to-invest-in-manchester-united/</link><title>Want to invest in Manchester United?</title><description>Want to invest in Manchester United?

5 Jun 2008 by SophosLabs on Naked Security nakedsecurity.sophos.com/2008/06/05/want-to-invest-in-manchester-united/

…  emails supposedly from Sir Alex Ferguson himself.  Dear Manchester United Fan, We are please to inform you that, you have been given the …

Topics: Spam, SophosLabs, General</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7010-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7010_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:28:00">http://ukmerchandise.wordpress.com/2013/01/15/manchester-united-football-club-hard-case-for-apple-ipod-touch-4g/</link><title>MANCHESTER UNITED FOOTBALL CLUB HARD CASE FOR APPLE IPOD TOUCH 4G</title><description>MANCHESTER UNITED FOOTBALL CLUB HARD CASE FOR APPLE IPOD TOUCH 4G

15 Jan 2013 by Admin on UK Football Club Merchandise ukmerchandise.wordpress.com/2013/01/15/manchester-united-football-club-hard-case-for-apple-ipod-touch-4g/

MANCHESTER UNITED FOOTBALL CLUB HARD CASE FOR APPLE IPOD TOUCH 4G Technical Details \- Stylish "Manchester United FC" Design \- Top Quality &amp; Durable Material \- The Best Protection …

Topics: Man Utd fc, Manchester United, MU, EEEEAA3683, MANCHESTER UNITED HARD CASE FOR APPLE IPOD TOUCH 4G, HARD CASE FOR APPLE IPOD TOUCH 4G</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7010-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7010_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:30:41">http://careersinfootball.com/work-in-football/jobs/</link><title>Jobs in football</title><description>Jobs in football

13 Feb 2014 by tobyr123 on Careers in football careersinfootball.com/work-in-football/jobs/

…  - America Scores Bay Area Human Resources Generalist - United States Soccer Federation Technical Director - Premier League …  Manager County Football Development Manager - Manchester FA Press and Communications Officer - West Riding FA Academy …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7010-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7010_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:33:26">http://stevehynd.com/2010/03/12/manchester-united-must-change/</link><title>Manchester United MUST change.</title><description>Manchester United MUST change.

12 Mar 2010 by steve4319 on Hynd's Blog stevehynd.com/2010/03/12/manchester-united-must-change/

…  are now owned by their supporters include: AFC Telford United, AFC Wimbledon, Bramley Buffaloes (RL), Brentford, Cambridge City, …  (Scotland), Enfield Town, Exeter City, FC United of Manchester, Gretna (Scotland), Merthyr Tydfil, Newport (IW) FC, Rochdale …

Topics: Football, Economics, Sport, Manchester United FC, must ..., Glazier, AFC Wimbledon, Supporters Direct, David Beckham</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7010-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7010_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:37:49">http://gangsofmanchester.com/2008/12/01/slice-of-scuttler-anyone/</link><title>Let them eat cake?</title><description>Let them eat cake?

1 Dec 2008 by andrewmarkdavies on Gangs of Manchester gangsofmanchester.com/2008/12/01/slice-of-scuttler-anyone/

…  has been plenty of discussion of the Gangs of Manchester on the various Manchester football message boards, not least on Blue …  Ric) and Red Issue. An extract has already appeared in United We Stand, and hopefully the King of the Kippax will be following …  Saturday, I was invited to speak at a pre-match social at FC United of Manchester, ahead of the game against Hednesford Town. It was …

Topics: gangs, manchester, Scuttlers, Mike Duff, Salford, cake, FC United, Manchester United, Manchester City, angel meadow, Football, Red Issue, Blue Moon, United We Stand, king of the kippax, Halle, Choir, Andrew Davies, Andrew Davies</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7010-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7010_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:41:37">http://footballinsights.wordpress.com/2007/11/14/ownership-of-football-clubs/</link><title>Ownership Of Football Clubs</title><description>Ownership Of Football Clubs

14 Nov 2007 by rajiv on Football Insights footballinsights.wordpress.com/2007/11/14/ownership-of-football-clubs/

…  website MyFootballClub are to acquire 51% of Ebbsfleet United for £700,000. A shrewd move by Ebbsfleet chairman Jason Botley, one …  of matches involving Milton Keynes Dons. FC United of Manchester were formed by disgruntled fans of Manchester United for whom the …

Topics: English Clubs, Football finances &amp; business, football-history, Sociology &amp; community</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7010-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7010_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:42:17">http://watchlivesoccertv.wordpress.com/2008/09/13/watch-live-video-liverpool-v-manchester-united-premier-league-football/</link><title>[Watch LIVE Video] LIVERPOOL v MANCHESTER UNITED \- Premier League Football</title><description>[Watch LIVE Video] LIVERPOOL v MANCHESTER UNITED \- Premier League Football

13 Sep 2008 by http://www.googootv.com on VER , TELEVISION , DIRECTO , VER , TV , VIVO , ONLINE watchlivesoccertv.wordpress.com/2008/09/13/watch-live-video-liverpool-v-manchester-united-premier-league-football/

…  Streaming Video Watch Football Soccer Live Liverpool FC vs Manchester United Online Free Video Streaming | Liverpool - Manchester United, Premier …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>