<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7014">Asian culture</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:49:21" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7014-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7014_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:49:22">http://mgrmmydiary.wordpress.com/2013/06/06/mydiary-edition-4-ultimate-culture-asian-culture-2/</link><title>Asian Culture</title><description>Asian Culture

6 Jun 2013 by mgrmmydiary on MyDiary Blog mgrmmydiary.wordpress.com/2013/06/06/mydiary-edition-4-ultimate-culture-asian-culture-2/

…  align="alignright" width="300"] Asian Culture[/caption] Asian Culture is the distinctive behavior of people in …

Topics: Ultimate Culture, Culture, Asian Culture, mydiaryedition4, Asia, Asian values, asian people, asian</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7014-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7014_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:52:29">http://kingdomrice.wordpress.com/about/</link><title>What is a "New Kind of Asian-Amercian?"</title><description>What is a "New Kind of Asian-Amercian?"

8 Aug 2013 by steveafterepic on Kingdom Rice kingdomrice.wordpress.com/about/

…  is now a US Marshall. After I described that I  build up Asian-Americans to be more confident in who they are as individuals, my friend …  represent growth areas for Asians. In traditional Asian culture, sense of worth comes from not from self, as is more common in the …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7014-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7014_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:55:21">http://engl134transasam.wordpress.com/2013/01/14/hannah-kim/</link><title>Hannah Kim</title><description>Hannah Kim

15 Jan 2013 by hanna98110 on ENGL 134: Lit &amp; Media of Transnational Asian America engl134transasam.wordpress.com/2013/01/14/hannah-kim/

…  class is my first class that is related with Asian American study. I thought taking this course will help me to earning Asian American literature and culture which seemed quite important to my Asian American identity. When I read …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7014-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7014_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:58:02">http://yellowinawhitemansworld.wordpress.com/2013/12/16/the-lindsey-lohan-effect-are-asian-women-easier-to-court/</link><title>The Lindsey Lohan effect: Are Asian women easier to court?</title><description>The Lindsey Lohan effect: Are Asian women easier to court?

16 Dec 2013 by yellowlovestory on Yellow In A White Man's World yellowinawhitemansworld.wordpress.com/2013/12/16/the-lindsey-lohan-effect-are-asian-women-easier-to-court/

…  not saying Asian women are 'easy' but the stark contrast between AMWF (Asian male, White female) relationships is damningly polar to the amount of …  less maintenance than white women because they come from a culture where they have the right to make familial decisions. In many Chinese …

Topics: Love Story, Australia, Lindsey Lohan, Lindsay Lohan, white people, Chelsea Lately, Oprah Winfrey, Asia, Race-Ethnic-Religious Relations, mean girls, Interracial Relationships</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7014-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7014_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:59:22">http://blogzillatheasiancultureinthemedia.wordpress.com/2014/03/15/asian-influence-in-american-society/</link><title>Asian Influence in American society</title><description>Asian Influence in American society

15 Mar 2014 by cookieapple on Blogzilla blogzillatheasiancultureinthemedia.wordpress.com/2014/03/15/asian-influence-in-american-society/

Asian Americans are not the only ones taking a stance in America today. Native born asians are having a major influence in American culture as of today. Ranging from Korean pop music, sports, and even in terms …  today is technology. Companies such as Samsung, Sony, any asian car companies, and etc have been gaining a strong foundation in American …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7014-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7014_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:01:00">http://culturaldilemmas.wordpress.com/2014/03/07/how-to-talk-to-asian-kids-about-their-different-appearance/</link><title>How To Talk To Asian Kids About Their Different Appearance?</title><description>How To Talk To Asian Kids About Their Different Appearance?

7 Mar 2014 by navjotgrewal on Cultural Dilemmas culturaldilemmas.wordpress.com/2014/03/07/how-to-talk-to-asian-kids-about-their-different-appearance/

…  align="alignright" width="300"] An Asian kid with an American child in school[/caption] It is not just about …  Educate your children about the good things in your culture, things that they can feel proud of. Repeated positive reinforcement …

Topics: asian moms, asian kids, Different Cultures, Cultures</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7014-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7014_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:03:02">http://asuiu.wordpress.com/about-2/</link><title>About</title><description>About

5 Feb 2014 by asuiu on Asian Student Union asuiu.wordpress.com/about-2/

…  Asian Student Union is a non-profit, non-partisan and secular organization …  in 2012 for the purpose of: Promoting awareness of Asian culture and heritage within the Indiana University community Fostering …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7014-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7014_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:04:51">http://woosubin01.wordpress.com/2014/03/13/analysis/</link><title>Analysis</title><description>Analysis

13 Mar 2014 by woosubin01 on One ASEAN 2015 woosubin01.wordpress.com/2014/03/13/analysis/

…  cultures by understanding and even assimilating one culture to another. It aims to create a region where people would distinguish …  really mean we should adapt Thai or any other Southeast Asian nations’ culture. It doesn’t mean that we should forget our own …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7014-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7014_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:07:26">http://amaziannews.wordpress.com/2014/03/16/asian-culture/</link><title>Asian Culture</title><description>Asian Culture

16 Mar 2014 by amaziannews on The Amazian News amaziannews.wordpress.com/2014/03/16/asian-culture/

…  Johnedel ChanecoIn asian culture there has always been more of a patriarchy within households. This …  has westernization changed the patriarchal system within asian …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7014-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7014_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:08:53">http://asam118summer13.wordpress.com/2013/06/28/hello-all/</link><title>Hello all!</title><description>Hello all!

28 Jun 2013 by Qua Nguyen on Asian American Pop Culture asam118summer13.wordpress.com/2013/06/28/hello-all/

…  name is Qua Nguyen. I am a returning senior majoring in Asian American Studies with a minor in Education. After achieving my degree, I …  Planning. My favorite example of Asian American Popular Culture is Far East Movement. In my opinion, Far East Movement was the first …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>