<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7029">best buy store closings</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:37:33" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7029-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7029_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:37:34">http://boston.cbslocal.com/2012/03/29/best-buy-to-close-50-stores-nationwide/</link><title>Best Buy To Close 50 Stores Nationwide</title><description>Best Buy To Close 50 Stores Nationwide

29 Mar 2012 by KC Downey on CBS Boston boston.cbslocal.com/2012/03/29/best-buy-to-close-50-stores-nationwide/

…  (AP) — Best Buy Co. said it plans to close 50 U.S. big box stores and open 100 small mobile …  partly due to restructuring charges. Despite the loss, Best Buy's adjusted results for the quarter topped Wall Street's …

Topics: News, Business, Best Buy, store closings, Left Middle Feature, Newsletters</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7029-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7029_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:38:38">http://chicago.cbslocal.com/2012/04/16/best-buy-to-close-1-chicago-store-5-in-suburbs/</link><title>Best Buy To Close 1 Chicago Store, 5 In Suburbs</title><description>Best Buy To Close 1 Chicago Store, 5 In Suburbs

16 Apr 2012 by Adam Harrington on CBS Chicago chicago.cbslocal.com/2012/04/16/best-buy-to-close-1-chicago-store-5-in-suburbs/

…  04/16/12 8:24 a.m. CHICAGO (CBS) -- Best Buy \-- the nation's largest consumer electronics retailer -- is announcing …  retailer says the South Side store at 87th Street and the Dan Ryan Expressway will be closing. The other …

Topics: News, Local, Business, Heard On WBBM 780, Best Buy, Dan Ryan Expressway, Deerfield, Matteson, Mundelein, Stores, west dundee, Addison, closing, 87th Street, Syndicated Local, John Waelti, Consumer Electronics, Main Feature</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7029-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7029_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:39:22">http://chicago.cbslocal.com/2012/03/29/expert-coming-best-buy-closings-reflect-move-away-from-big-box-model/</link><title>Expert: Coming Best Buy Closings Reflect Move Away From Big-Box Model</title><description>Expert: Coming Best Buy Closings Reflect Move Away From Big-Box Model

29 Mar 2012 by Adam Harrington on CBS Chicago chicago.cbslocal.com/2012/03/29/expert-coming-best-buy-closings-reflect-move-away-from-big-box-model/

…  (CBS) -- A local expert says the planned closings of 50 Best Buy stores is reflective of an evolution of the consumer retail market from big …

Topics: News, Local, Business, Noon Business Hour, Best Buy, Morningstar, Syndicated Local, stores closing, Consumer Electronics, Big-Box Model, R.J. Hottovy, watch &amp; listen, Seen On CBS 2, Heard On WBBM 780</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7029-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7029_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:40:05">http://atlanta.cbslocal.com/2012/04/15/best-buy-closing-stores-in-metro-atlanta/</link><title>Best Buy Closing Stores In Metro Atlanta</title><description>Best Buy Closing Stores In Metro Atlanta

15 Apr 2012 by vac872 on CBS Atlanta atlanta.cbslocal.com/2012/04/15/best-buy-closing-stores-in-metro-atlanta/

…  (AP/WAOK) - Best Buy has announced the locations of 50 stores that it is closing this …  Atlanta are located in Fayetteville and Loganville. Best Buy says it will try to find other jobs in the company for the …

Topics: News, Business, best buy closes georgia stores, best buy closing, Main Feature</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7029-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7029_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:40:52">http://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2012/04/14/another-minnesota-best-buy-store-closing/</link><title>Another Minnesota Best Buy Store Closing</title><description>Another Minnesota Best Buy Store Closing

14 Apr 2012 by Jeff Wald on CBS Minnesota minnesota.cbslocal.com/2012/04/14/another-minnesota-best-buy-store-closing/

…  (WCCO) – Officials with Best Buy announced Saturday that 42 more stores are closing nation-wide, and one of …  Buy location in Rochester will close as early as May 12. Store employees were given the news on Saturday. It's the Rochester South …

Topics: News, Best Buy, Rochester, Local, Consumer News, Business, Store closing, Left Middle Feature</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7029-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7029_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:42:07">http://fox8.com/2012/04/14/local-best-buy-set-to-permanently-close/</link><title>Steelyard Commons Store Set to Permanently Close</title><description>Steelyard Commons Store Set to Permanently Close

14 Apr 2012 by Bliss Davis on FOX8.com fox8.com/2012/04/14/local-best-buy-set-to-permanently-close/

Best Buy has unveiled which stores around the country it plans to permanently close …  set to close its doors. The tech chain announced 50 store closings in March. Since then one location in Missouri and another in …

Topics: News, blissdavisfox8, steelyard commons, Best Buy</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7029-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7029_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:42:54">http://consumerist.com/2012/01/31/best-buy-to-employees-at-closing-stores-dont-worry-were-opening-stores-in-china/</link><title>Best Buy To Employees: "Don't Worry About Stores Being Closed. We're Opening Stores In China"</title><description>Best Buy To Employees: "Don't Worry About Stores Being Closed. We're Opening Stores In China"

31 Jan 2012 by Chris Morran on Consumerist consumerist.com/2012/01/31/best-buy-to-employees-at-closing-stores-dont-worry-were-opening-stores-in-china/

…  in January, Best Buy CEO Brian "Brooks and" Dunn confirmed reports that the …  two examples from the memo: Is this the beginning of more closings? While we are closing this location, Best Buy has opened 106 …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7029-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7029_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:43:29">http://247wallst.com/retail/2012/03/29/best-buys-psychological-death-from-store-closures-bby/</link><title>Best Buy's Psychological Death From Store Closures (BBY)</title><description>Best Buy's Psychological Death From Store Closures (BBY)

29 Mar 2012 by Jon C. Ogg on 24/7 Wall St. 247wallst.com/retail/2012/03/29/best-buys-psychological-death-from-store-closures-bby/

Best Buy Co. Inc. (NYSE: BBY) is not just down because the company's earnings …  that it is transforming some stores to its new Connected Store format.  Rather than closing these 50 big box stores, Best Buy should …

Topics: Consumer Electronics, Retail, BBY, Best Buy store closures</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7029-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7029_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:44:50">http://q104.cbslocal.com/2012/03/29/best-buy-to-close-50-stores/</link><title>Best Buy To Close 50 Stores</title><description>Best Buy To Close 50 Stores

29 Mar 2012 by anastasios67 on Q104 Cleveland q104.cbslocal.com/2012/03/29/best-buy-to-close-50-stores/

…  a cost cutting move, Best Buy is closing 50 big box stores in the US.  A list of the stores to be …  Best Buy "We will announce details about specific store locations and timing for closings once they are finalized." Here is …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7029-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7029_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:46:25">http://crosbierealestategroup.wordpress.com/2012/04/16/denver-business-journal-best-buy-to-close-aurora-store-as-part-of-50-store-nationwide-shutdown/</link><title>Denver Business Journal | Best Buy to close Aurora store as part of 50-store nationwide shutdown</title><description>Denver Business Journal | Best Buy to close Aurora store as part of 50-store nationwide shutdown

16 Apr 2012 by Crosbie Real Estate Group on crosbierealestategroup crosbierealestategroup.wordpress.com/2012/04/16/denver-business-journal-best-buy-to-close-aurora-store-as-part-of-50-store-nationwide-shutdown/

Best Buy Co. -- grappling with competition from online retailers -- said Saturday it is closing a store in south Aurora as part of a nationwide closure of 50 full-sized …

Topics: Crosbie Real Estate Group, Commercial Real Estate, Denver Business Journal, Best Buy, Colorado, Retail, Real Estate, Store closing, retail real estate, Aurora, Best Buy to close Aurora store as part of 50-store nati, Mark Harden, 15800 E Briarwood Circle</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>