<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7037">how to write journalistic review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:39:06" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7037-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7037_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:39:07">http://allbettsareoff.wordpress.com/2013/01/04/writing-a-book-review/</link><title>Writing a Book Review</title><description>Writing a Book Review

4 Jan 2013 by allbettsareoff on allbettsareoff allbettsareoff.wordpress.com/2013/01/04/writing-a-book-review/

…  is important to learn how to write a good book review. Today I am featuring an article that provides helpful …

Topics: Writing Tips</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7037-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7037_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:39:41">http://awritingrose.wordpress.com/2013/01/09/writing-book-reviews/</link><title>Writing Book Reviews</title><description>Writing Book Reviews

9 Jan 2013 by awritingrose on A Writing Rose awritingrose.wordpress.com/2013/01/09/writing-book-reviews/

…  is important to know how to write a book review. Many bloggers read books and write a review of the book …

Topics: writing</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7037-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7037_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:40:21">http://gamebias.wordpress.com/about/</link><title>Purpose</title><description>Purpose

13 Feb 2014 by Jed Pressgrove on Game Bias gamebias.wordpress.com/about/

…  reviews, media analysis, or satire, Game Bias* seeks to examine how we think and write about video games. This blog intends to answer a broad …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7037-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7037_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:40:54">http://txpaladin.wordpress.com/2008/09/02/to-blog-podcast-is-the-real-question/</link><title>To blog &amp; podcast is the real question</title><description>To blog &amp; podcast is the real question

2 Sep 2008 by robowerks on TXPaladin on Live txpaladin.wordpress.com/2008/09/02/to-blog-podcast-is-the-real-question/

…  was listening to the replay of the PAX08: Gamercast Network - Podcasting The New Media Panel, …  more keep coming all the time. So the real challenge is how to gain more exposure and to make sure you know why your doing it. Some of …  do. My only thought is that someone might see something I write or listen to one of my podcasts and perhaps value my opinion. In the end …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7037-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7037_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:41:31">http://mrrosentel.wordpress.com/2011/12/01/flex-enrichment-school-newspaper-groundwork-20-points/</link><title>FLEX Enrichment: School Newspaper Groundwork (30 Points)</title><description>FLEX Enrichment: School Newspaper Groundwork (30 Points)

1 Dec 2011 by mrrosentel on Mr. Rosentel's Website mrrosentel.wordpress.com/2011/12/01/flex-enrichment-school-newspaper-groundwork-20-points/

…  deadline to complete the final draft of your School Newspaper assignment is Thursday, …  newspaper) Example of Online High School Newspaper How to Write a Newspaper Article How to Write a Sports Story How to Write an …

Topics: FLEX Enrichment</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7037-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7037_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:42:10">http://yarrethplysier.wordpress.com/work/</link><title>WORK</title><description>WORK

12 Nov 2013 by yarrethplysier on Yarreth Plysier yarrethplysier.wordpress.com/work/

…  under the concerning tab. In 2013, I was invited to be a co-writer of the Knack Studiewijzer, an one-time attachment to the …  human-interest articles, and one more serious report about how everyone is free to choose what they will study in our education …  written every article in Dutch. Nevertheless, I prefer to write this portfolio in English. The main reason for this will be found under …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7037-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7037_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:42:41">http://wordlily.com/2009/06/14/a-bridge-between-lit-blogs-and-book-blogs/</link><title>A bridge between lit blogs and book blogs?</title><description>A bridge between lit blogs and book blogs?

14 Jun 2009 by Word Lily on Word Lily wordlily.com/2009/06/14/a-bridge-between-lit-blogs-and-book-blogs/

…  bloggers flaunt their amateur status and enjoy not having to fit any pre-conceived mold for what they do and how they present themselves. [Many words have been used to attempt to …

Topics: Newspapering, Books, Internet, media, Journalism, Blogging, WordLily</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7037-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7037_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:43:35">http://mrkitching.wordpress.com/informative/</link><title>Informational</title><description>Informational

1 Aug 2011 by mrkitching on English 8th grade mrkitching.wordpress.com/informative/

…  texts such as newspapers and magazines. We will discuss how perspective can change the way different newspapers cover the same news …  Review Show:   The first thing you need to do is to choose an informational text to read from this list (all of which …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7037-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7037_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:44:10">http://musicscenempls.wordpress.com/2012/06/16/850/</link><title>A Better Way to Review Music: twistedwire</title><description>A Better Way to Review Music: twistedwire

16 Jun 2012 by gjmseal on Music Scene MPLS musicscenempls.wordpress.com/2012/06/16/850/

…  Scene MPLS is great! It provides a voice to the Twin Cities show-goers and is the area’s first cooperative live music review site. But, it does require you to know how to use WordPress and be at least semi-comfortable with the pressure of longer, more journalistic(ish) write-ups. Music Scene MPLS appeals to the every-day reader, but not so much to …

Topics: Live Music, mpls, Music Review, twistedwire</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7037-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7037_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:44:41">http://smudigitaljournalism.wordpress.com/2010/02/05/weekend-reading-and-practice-blog-item/</link><title>Weekend Reading and Practice Blog Item</title><description>Weekend Reading and Practice Blog Item

6 Feb 2010 by smudigitaljournalism on Digital Journalism @ SMU smudigitaljournalism.wordpress.com/2010/02/05/weekend-reading-and-practice-blog-item/

…  practice blog. Before you write your blog item, be sure to look over the blog item gradesheet on Blackboard to familiarize yourself …  I'll be looking for. Next week we will focus on how news organizations are using social media for journalistic purposes. For …

Topics: Class Links</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>