<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7045">Natural Parks America</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:40:00" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7045-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7045_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:40:02">http://bythelevel.com/2014/02/22/new-balance-national-parks-pack/</link><title>New Balance 'National Parks' Pack</title><description>New Balance 'National Parks' Pack

22 Feb 2014 by bythelevel on The Level bythelevel.com/2014/02/22/new-balance-national-parks-pack/

…  Balance take inspiration from the National Parks of America in a pack dedicated to the States natural surroundings. The National Parks pack sees classic New Balance …

Topics: Brand Updates, Streetwear, Trainers, Sneakers, pack, Footwear, New Balance, street wear blog, Streetwear Blog, National Parks, New Balance National Parks Pack, N.B.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7045-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7045_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:41:13">http://mukeshbalani.wordpress.com/2014/04/18/celebrate-national-parks-week-with-crowdsourced-artwork/</link><title>Celebrate National Parks Week With Crowdsourced Artwork</title><description>Celebrate National Parks Week With Crowdsourced Artwork

18 Apr 2014 by mukeshbalani on [ mukeshbalani.com ] mukeshbalani.wordpress.com/2014/04/18/celebrate-national-parks-week-with-crowdsourced-artwork/

…  its use of art to inspire tourism to the U.S. National Parks. Along with Max Slavkin, Perry-Zucker is co-founder of the Creative Action Network (CAN), the force behind the See America project, which encourages artists to submit works that celebrate the …  artists in the 1930s and 1940s to illustrate the natural landscapes of the United States. Read more...More about Travel, …

Topics: general info, Mashable</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7045-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7045_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:42:37">http://andrewmanske.com/productions/</link><title>Recent Productions</title><description>Recent Productions

14 Apr 2013 by Andrew Manske on ANDREW MANSKE andrewmanske.com/productions/

…  Americas wins Best Natural History film at Banff CBC: The Nature of Things- Billion Dollar …  Alberta: The Willmore Legacy Wolves of Labrador Parks Canada: Wapusk National Park  Kluane National Park &amp; Reserve - …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7045-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7045_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:43:34">http://summitcountyvoice.com/2013/04/17/environment-longleaf-pine-grove-bunchgrass-prairie-designated-as-national-natural-landmarks/</link><title>Environment: Longleaf pine grove, bunchgrass prairie designated as national natural landmarks</title><description>Environment: Longleaf pine grove, bunchgrass prairie designated as national natural landmarks

17 Apr 2013 by Bob Berwyn on Summit County Citizens Voice summitcountyvoice.com/2013/04/17/environment-longleaf-pine-grove-bunchgrass-prairie-designated-as-national-natural-landmarks/

…  Voice SUMMIT COUNTY — Designation of two new national natural landmarks will preserve examples of two ecosystems that have nearly …  the best example of bunchgrass prairie remaining in North America.  This large, high-quality natural area also contains aspen groves, …

Topics: Environment, public lands, national park service, forests, National Natural Landmarks, Zumwalt Prairie, longleaf pines</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7045-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7045_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:44:35">http://bryanemcnamara.wordpress.com/2014/04/15/la-garganta-del-diablo-the-devils-throat-in-iguazu-falls/</link><title>La Garganta del Diablo - "The Devil's Throat" in Iguazu Falls</title><description>La Garganta del Diablo - "The Devil's Throat" in Iguazu Falls

15 Apr 2014 by bryanemcnamara on Bryan McNamara bryanemcnamara.wordpress.com/2014/04/15/la-garganta-del-diablo-the-devils-throat-in-iguazu-falls/

…  Iguazu National Park with one of the palest kids South America has ever seen! No, we are not sweating and it is not raining. That is …  (Iguazu water falls), recently claimed as one of the seven natural modern wonders of the …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7045-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7045_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:46:10">http://mechanicalpencil13.wordpress.com/2014/04/11/geography/</link><title>Geography</title><description>Geography

11 Apr 2014 by mechanicalpencil13 on Mechanical Pencils, Narnia, Et Cetera mechanicalpencil13.wordpress.com/2014/04/11/geography/

…  spectacular photo from Lexington, KY- On top of the Natural Bridge. How was I to know there was so much to do in central Kentucky? Keeneland, KY horse Park, Natural Bridge, Daniel Boone National Forest, Red River Gorge ziplining, Ashland (Henry Clay estates), first Toyota factory in America, MegaCaverns …

Topics: Spring Break, Lexington, Natural Arch, Geography, Kentucky</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7045-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7045_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:47:39">http://ohioreadingcorpsbookroom.wordpress.com/2013/06/27/jaguar-attack-p/</link><title>Jaguar Attack! P.</title><description>Jaguar Attack! P.

27 Jun 2013 by ohioreadingcorpsbookroom on ohioreadingcorpsbookroom ohioreadingcorpsbookroom.wordpress.com/2013/06/27/jaguar-attack-p/

…  of a team of scientists traveling down a river in South America.  Although a jaguar attack is part of the story, the book mainly deals with the devastation of natural areas. TAGS: Highland Park, P, Global Warming, Expeditions, South …

Topics: animals, P, level p+, Scientists, Adventures, Papa, Highland Park, highland park-p, rainforests, Cool Jobs, Global Warming, Expeditions, South American, rainforest creatures, Non-Fiction</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7045-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7045_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:48:43">http://houston.cbslocal.com/top-lists/top-natural-wonders-in-the-usa/</link><title>Top Natural Wonders In The USA</title><description>Top Natural Wonders In The USA

15 Oct 2013 by cbsexaminer on CBS Houston houston.cbslocal.com/2013/10/15/top-natural-wonders-in-the-usa/

America is blessed with an abundance of natural wonders, from pristine lakes and mighty rivers to natural sandstone …  ranges featuring several American and Canadian national parks. With an elevation of 14,433 feet, Mount Elbert is the highest point of …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7045-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7045_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:50:17">http://natureedmonton.com/2013/08/14/edmontons-natural-area-parks-2/</link><title>Edmonton's Natural Area Parks</title><description>Edmonton's Natural Area Parks

15 Aug 2013 by Edmonton Master Naturalists on Nature Edmonton natureedmonton.com/2013/08/14/edmontons-natural-area-parks-2/

…  width="337"] Map of Edmonton's natural area parks from the City of Edmonton website.[/caption] As Edmontonians, we are …  with the largest stretch of river valley parkland in North America. But did you know that Edmonton also has many natural areas outside of …

Topics: Edmonton's Natural Area Parks</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7045-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7045_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:51:23">http://fox13now.com/2013/10/21/boy-scout-leaders-dismissed-after-goblin-valley-incident/</link><title>Boy Scout leaders dismissed after Goblin Valley incident</title><description>Boy Scout leaders dismissed after Goblin Valley incident

21 Oct 2013 by McKoye Mecham on FOX13Now.com fox13now.com/2013/10/21/boy-scout-leaders-dismissed-after-goblin-valley-incident/

…  Read more about the incident here. The Utah National Parks Council released this statement regarding the incident: Based on the …  of America. “Leave No Trace” teaches the value of natural areas and the methods we can use to help protect and conserve these …

Topics: News, Boy Scouts</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>