<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7051">dinosaur names</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:34:12" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7051-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7051_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:34:13">http://playinginprep.wordpress.com/2011/08/07/the-dinosaur-museum/</link><title>The Dinosaur Museum</title><description>The Dinosaur Museum

7 Aug 2011 by playinginprep on Playing in Prep playinginprep.wordpress.com/2011/08/07/the-dinosaur-museum/

…  want to build a dinosaur museum" said the children and from those few words an exciting …  role of curators in museums and the children selected a dinosaur so they could curate their own exhibit. To solve the issue of who …  other information.      They copied the names of their dinosaurs to make signs for the …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7051-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7051_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:35:27">http://dineabite.wordpress.com/2011/03/14/dinosaur-names/</link><title>Dinosaur Names</title><description>Dinosaur Names

14 Mar 2011 by dineabite on Dine-a-Bite dineabite.wordpress.com/2011/03/14/dinosaur-names/

…  is the literal English translation of the word “Dinosaur.” The name was coined by an 18th century Comparative Anatomist named …  Owen. It was also him who came up with different dinosaur names during his time. Other soon followed suit and created more names as more …

Topics: Informational</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7051-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7051_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:35:57">http://misssarahstorytimes.wordpress.com/2011/02/25/dinosaur-roar/</link><title>Dinosaur ROAR!</title><description>Dinosaur ROAR!

24 Feb 2011 by misssarahstorytime on Miss Sarah's Storytime misssarahstorytimes.wordpress.com/2011/02/25/dinosaur-roar/

…  Dinosaurs” by Byron Barton shows all kinds of dinosaur; big and small dinosaurs, dinosaurs with horns on their heads, spikes …  waaay more knowledgeable about how to pronounce dinosaur names than me. Thankfully this book has the pronunciation of the dinosaur’s …

Topics: Toddler Time</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7051-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7051_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:36:37">http://thechildrensnook.wordpress.com/2011/03/07/marchs-pick-stomp-dinosaur-stomp-review-giveaway/</link><title>March's Pick: Stomp, Dinosaur, Stomp! Review &amp; Giveaway</title><description>March's Pick: Stomp, Dinosaur, Stomp! Review &amp; Giveaway

8 Mar 2011 by childrensnook thechildrensnook.wordpress.com/2011/03/07/marchs-pick-stomp-dinosaur-stomp-review-giveaway/

…  month I have a book for you that will thrill little dinosaur lovers as well as intrigue those who know very little about dinosaurs. …  Dinosaur, Stomp! also helps you pronounce the dinosaur names correctly by listing the phonetic spelling of each of the dinosaur's …

Topics: Giveaways, Reviews</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7051-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7051_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:37:52">http://rainbowsabbots.wordpress.com/2013/09/23/some-learning-through-play/</link><title>Some learning through play...</title><description>Some learning through play...

23 Sep 2013 by miss.c.tottman on Cottontails rainbowsabbots.wordpress.com/2013/09/23/some-learning-through-play/

…  boys worked together to make the dinosaur puzzle and then discussed the dinosaurs different names. Following an adults suggestion they found a dinosaur book and tried to match the pictures to those in their puzzle. With …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7051-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7051_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:38:25">http://alexisv.wordpress.com/2013/11/22/dinosaurs-and-names/</link><title>Dinosaurs and Names</title><description>Dinosaurs and Names

22 Nov 2013 by alexisv on a web a word a world alexisv.wordpress.com/2013/11/22/dinosaurs-and-names/

…  kidnap a toddler.  RadioLab had just about the coolest dinosaur puppets I’ve ever seen, and the comedian who opened the whole thing …  la vie. As we walked out we started talking about names. I love how many people I know have given themselves their names, and it …

Topics: Friends, names, RadioLab, Gorse, doe bay, Orcas Island</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7051-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7051_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:39:03">http://carrosam000.wordpress.com/2014/02/28/mom-dad-i-want-to-be-a-digger/</link><title>"Mom, Dad, I want to be a digger"</title><description>"Mom, Dad, I want to be a digger"

28 Feb 2014 by carrosam000 on Let's Go Carrolling carrosam000.wordpress.com/2014/02/28/mom-dad-i-want-to-be-a-digger/

…  tons of different types of dinosaurs and I could spell the names of these dinosaurs. I loved dinosaurs. I had books on dinosaurs, movies …  amazed me and I had heard about people who search for old dinosaur bones. However, I did not know the name of these people who were lucky …

Topics: Meaningful, Smile</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7051-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7051_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:39:39">http://abadmommyblog.wordpress.com/2009/09/09/347/</link><title>Dinosaurs Go {RAWR}</title><description>Dinosaurs Go {RAWR}

9 Sep 2009 by ExMi on A Bad Mommy's Blog abadmommyblog.wordpress.com/2009/09/09/347/

…  with dinosaurs. Little figurines, big ones, fluffy dinosaur toys, big battery-operated ones. He has dinosaurs of every single …  on TV, he'll watch it. He is starting to learn the names too: Triceratops: he says "seratops" Stegasaurus: he says …

Topics: Parenting, Mommyhood, Toys, toddler, Dinosaurs, Learning to Talk, Obsessions</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7051-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7051_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:40:30">http://theknittingsailor.com/2012/09/02/im-a-dinosaur/</link><title>I'm a Dinosaur</title><description>I'm a Dinosaur

2 Sep 2012 by knittingsailor on The Knitting Sailor theknittingsailor.com/2012/09/02/im-a-dinosaur/

…  Dinosaur is apparently a “terrible lizard”. I feel like a terrible lizard …  to cheer up your day courtesy of the tinterweb. 1\. The dinosaur with the longest name was Micropachycephalosaurus meaning "tiny …   It is the most fun you can have (there are lots of other names too - have a look here.  And if you want to join my Dino-gang add it to …

Topics: the Captains Cabin, knitting, wool, dinosaur, wingspan</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7051-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7051_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:41:08">http://jirehjetaime.wordpress.com/2009/12/31/dinosaurs/</link><title>Dinosaurs!!</title><description>Dinosaurs!!

31 Dec 2009 by agapelove15 on Jireh &amp; Je t'aime jirehjetaime.wordpress.com/2009/12/31/dinosaurs/

…  out books on dinosaurs and insisted that mummy read the names of the dinosaurs to me. As the names are mostly long and difficult to pronouce, mummy replied that she …

Topics: Jireh</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>