<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7054">yarra valley sightseeing</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:59:40" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7054-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7054_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:59:41">http://peters365photos.wordpress.com/2012/12/16/melbourne-australia/</link><title>Melbourne - Australia</title><description>Melbourne - Australia

16 Dec 2012 by flyingkakapo on A Photo a Day peters365photos.wordpress.com/2012/12/16/melbourne-australia/

…  width="640"] Melbourne CBT and Yarra River, Victoria, Australia[/caption] Today Farida's cousins, Ailina and Mahathir, took us into Melbourne city for some sightseeing and lunch. My last visit to Melbourne was in 1983 and obviously …  taken as we were walking across the bridge spanning the Yarra river near the Crown casino looking towards the central business …

Topics: Travel and Tourism, Nikon, Australia, Victoria, Melbourne, nikon 1 series</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7054-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7054_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:00:23">http://jipaoverseas.wordpress.com/2009/03/08/lotsa-pics/</link><title>Lotsa pics...</title><description>Lotsa pics...

8 Mar 2009 by jipa on Jipa's working holiday blog jipaoverseas.wordpress.com/2009/03/08/lotsa-pics/

…  but ended up heading to the city. There are two major sightseeing towers in the city, the newer of which, Eureka, being the highest …  event that also included water ski-long jumping on the Yarra-river. Again, I shot so many frames I'd be surprised to see no good …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7054-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7054_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:00:48">http://southerncrossings2013.wordpress.com/2013/04/19/our-bikes-arrived/</link><title>Our Bikes Arrived!</title><description>Our Bikes Arrived!

19 Apr 2013 by marjirob on Southern Crossings 2013 southerncrossings2013.wordpress.com/2013/04/19/our-bikes-arrived/

…  Earlier in the week, when I went for a walk along the Yarra River in the morning I was amazed at the steady stream of bikers heading …  animals and then we will go to some of the famous Yarra Valley wineries. Should be a fun day! Thanks to those of you who have left …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7054-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7054_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:01:51">http://bradnlisasbigadventure.wordpress.com/2011/01/21/colonial-tram-car-restaurant/</link><title>Colonial Tram Car Restaurant</title><description>Colonial Tram Car Restaurant

21 Jan 2011 by Brad n Lisa's Big Adventure on Brad n Lisa's Big Adventure Blog bradnlisasbigadventure.wordpress.com/2011/01/21/colonial-tram-car-restaurant/

…  21 day tour. We get on the private bus and go out on a sightseeing tour of the city.  We see  St. Patrick's Cathedral, the …  I walked back through the botanic gardens and along the Yarra River. It is a HOT day.  We take a quick shower and meet everyone for …

Topics: Travels</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7054-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7054_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:02:25">http://melbournetouristguide.wordpress.com/2014/04/16/yarra-valley-victoria-australia/</link><title>Yarra Valley Victoria Australia</title><description>Yarra Valley Victoria Australia

16 Apr 2014 by melbournetouristguide on Melbourne Tourist Guide melbournetouristguide.wordpress.com/2014/04/16/yarra-valley-victoria-australia/

…  Yarra Valley Region Want to know more about the Yarra Valley Region? Discover this wine region, the Yarra Valley region is …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7054-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7054_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:03:03">http://vicandpaminoz.wordpress.com/2013/01/17/wednesday-16-january/</link><title>Wednesday 16 January</title><description>Wednesday 16 January

17 Jan 2013 by vicquayle on Vic and Pam in Oz vicandpaminoz.wordpress.com/2013/01/17/wednesday-16-january/

…  morning. The complex is alongside the main river, the Yarra, and across the road from the Melbourne Cricket Ground (MCG), and very …  way through. Vic took himself into the city to do some sightseeing. The Old Gaol was where Ned Kelly (Australian bushranger ie outlaw) …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7054-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7054_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:03:41">http://travelphotos1.wordpress.com/2013/06/17/yarra-valley-vineyard-australia/</link><title>Yarra Valley Vineyard, Australia</title><description>Yarra Valley Vineyard, Australia

17 Jun 2013 by elsyflaig47 on Travel photos travelphotos1.wordpress.com/2013/06/17/yarra-valley-vineyard-australia/

Source: Yarra Valley Vineyard, Australia

Topics: Articles, Travel, trips, turistic, @ vacation, Journey, Jaunt, Holiday, photos, Pictures]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7054-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7054_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:04:08">http://thepaperbackfortress.wordpress.com/2013/01/28/escape/</link><title>Escape!</title><description>Escape!

28 Jan 2013 by Anna thepaperbackfortress.wordpress.com/2013/01/28/escape/

…  beach, we tried a different approach and drove into the Yarra Ranges to visit the Boy's mum in Warburton. It's a lovely place …  more in 2013 is get out of the city for some walking and sightseeing. There are so many beautiful places within an hour or so's …

Topics: Wanderings, Planning, Plans, wandering, Travel, warburton, 2013</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7054-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7054_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:04:40">http://sophiewhitman.wordpress.com/2013/12/16/yarra-valley-adventure/</link><title>Yarra Valley Adventure</title><description>Yarra Valley Adventure

16 Dec 2013 by sophiewhitman on from Steph sophiewhitman.wordpress.com/2013/12/16/yarra-valley-adventure/

…  and I decided to hop on board and head to the spectacular Yarra Valley. We started our trip by visiting the lovely and uber modern, …

Topics: Food, Culture, Travel, Out and About, Melbourne, adventure, Yarra Valley, Victoria, Black Spur, Great Dividing Range, Healesville Victoria, Narbathong, cheese, Dairy, Trees, casper, Driving, RoadTrip, walking, Nature, outdoors</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7054-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7054_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:07:54">http://wineyarravalley.wordpress.com/wineries/</link><title>Wineries</title><description>Wineries

4 Feb 2011 by Wine Yarra Valley wineyarravalley.wordpress.com/wineries/

…  of the Yarra Valley The Yarra Valley is internationally recognised as one of Australia's leading …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>