<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7061">startup advisors chicago</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:49:29" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7061-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7061_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:49:30">http://bipeblawg.com/2014/04/11/fourth-chicago-based-ipo-to-over-a-billion-in-valuation-are-startup-and-tech-deals-coming-back-to-chicago/</link><title>Fourth Chicago Based IPO to over a Billion in Valuation! Are Startup and Tech Deals Coming back to Chicago?</title><description>Fourth Chicago Based IPO to over a Billion in Valuation! Are Startup and Tech Deals Coming back to Chicago?

11 Apr 2014 by viharp on The BIPE Blawg: Business, Intellectual Property and Employment Law Journal. bipeblawg.com/2014/04/11/fourth-chicago-based-ipo-to-over-a-billion-in-valuation-are-startup-and-tech-deals-coming-back-to-chicago/

…  of LinkedIn, Groupon, Envestment's IPOs, the Chicago startup, GrubHub went public on April 4, 2014, with shares soaring to over $40 …  a local tech startup that produces software for financial advisors has led to a current valuation of $1.35 billion dollars. All this …

Topics: This Weeks Update, ip lawyer, Tech Lawyer, Mergers and Acquisitions, IPOs, intial public offerings, startup community, Chicago, Grubhub, LinkedIn, Groupon, envestment, intellectual property lawyers, technology lawyers, chicago technoly startups, chicago entrepreneurship community, EEBC, EEBC-It's Just Brunch! Quarterly Startup Competition, Seed Money for Entrepreneurs, Seed money for Startups, Chicago Entrepreneurs Attorney, Chicago Startup Attorney, Patent Law Updates, General Business, Trademark Lawyer, chicago trademark lawyer, chicago trademark attorney, Trademark Attorney, chicago patent attorney</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7061-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7061_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:50:52">http://startupseven.com/about/</link><title>About Joe</title><description>About Joe

23 Jan 2010 by Joe on Startup Seven: Confessions of a Repeat Entrepreneur startupseven.com/about/

…  his grandfather and father run a successful restaurant in Chicago for over 50 years. Since graduating from M.I.T. with a degree in …  was the founder and CEO of Presto, a venture-backed startup in partnership with Hewlett-Packard, and served as founder and Vice …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7061-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7061_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:51:20">http://venturebeat.com/2008/10/17/partnerups-weekly-opportunities-22/</link><title>PartnerUp's Weekly Opportunities</title><description>PartnerUp's Weekly Opportunities

17 Oct 2008 by Contributor on VentureBeat venturebeat.com/2008/10/17/partnerups-weekly-opportunities-22/

…  their businesses, such as co-founders, business partners, advisors, board members, and skilled technical people. In addition, PartnerUp …  for their businesses. The PartnerUp team blogs on the StartUp Blog, an up-and-coming blog about entrepreneurship, small business, and …

Topics: Business and Technology</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7061-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7061_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:52:24">http://thebestnextthing.com/about/about-david-schonthal/</link><title>David Schonthal</title><description>David Schonthal

4 Apr 2014 by carteranddavid on The Best Next Thing thebestnextthing.com/about/about-david-schonthal/

…  where he’s helped launch initiatives such as the Startup-in-Residence program as well as developing new offers around corporate …  in new venture creation. He also serves as a member of Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel’s technology, innovation, and entrepreneurship …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7061-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7061_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:52:58">http://wearemstech.wordpress.com/2013/07/20/failbias-ms-tech-fireside-chat-at-bellycard-offices/</link><title>#FailBias: Fireside Chat at BellyCard Offices</title><description>#FailBias: Fireside Chat at BellyCard Offices

20 Jul 2013 by Nicole Yeary on #mstech wearemstech.wordpress.com/2013/07/20/failbias-ms-tech-fireside-chat-at-bellycard-offices/

…  Chicago startup failing? No, really.  Name 2.  Startups …  be speaking to two very talented leaders in the technology startup community.  This event emphasizes our mission at Ms.Tech --we don’t …

Topics: event, MStech, panel, Chicago, Women, Illinois, Startups, womenintech, david kadavy, Craig Ulliott, mana ionescu, bellycard, Failure, Entrepreneurs, Idea, Letting Go, failbias, Fireside Chats</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7061-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7061_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:53:29">http://people.loopmeetings.com/2014/04/16/deepak-goel/</link><title>Deepak Goel, CTO of Packback</title><description>Deepak Goel, CTO of Packback

16 Apr 2014 by @getLaura people.loopmeetings.com/2014/04/16/deepak-goel/

…  company unless you get promoted every year. Go work for a startup instead." Name: Deepak Goel Education: Indian Institute of …  marketing and engineering teams. I just moved to Chicago last year and currently I am the CTO of Packback. What is your …

Topics: Entrepreneurship, Marketing, technology, Featured Loop Member, networking, Chicago, Loop Member of the Week, Product Management, Product Manger, packback books</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7061-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7061_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:54:06">http://finance.fortune.cnn.com/2012/12/13/venture-capital-deals-257/</link><title>Venture capital deals</title><description>Venture capital deals

13 Dec 2012 by Dan Primack on Fortune Finance: Hedge Funds, Markets, Mergers &amp; Acquisitions, Private Equity, Venture Capital, Wall Street, Washington finance.fortune.cnn.com/2012/12/13/venture-capital-deals-257/

…  from Silicon Valley Bank. www.whiptail.com SpotHero, a Chicago-based parking garage reservation startup, has raised $2.5 million in VC funding. Battery Ventures led the round, …  Group. Other investors included Advancit Capital, Code Advisors, Allen DeBevoise (Machinima) and Juan Cristóbal Ferrer (Ferrer …

Topics: Term Sheet, Venture Capital, venture capital deals</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7061-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7061_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:54:55">http://abrewingthought.com/2013/07/02/crafted-in-chicago/</link><title>Crafted in Chicago</title><description>Crafted in Chicago

2 Jul 2013 by abrewingthought on a brewing thought abrewingthought.com/2013/07/02/crafted-in-chicago/

…  story behind my excitement for tech in Chicago and a new startup directory, set to launch next week “It is hopeless for the …  entrepreneurs are being supported by a growing network of advisors, angels, and institutional money. They’re building great teams …

Topics: Business 2, technology, Chicago, startups</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7061-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7061_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:55:43">http://philcastello.com/2013/11/07/why-my-startup-would-never-leave-chicago/</link><title>Why my startup would never leave Chicago.</title><description>Why my startup would never leave Chicago.

7 Nov 2013 by Phil Castello on PhilCastello.Com philcastello.com/2013/11/07/why-my-startup-would-never-leave-chicago/

…  I check out AngelList and I can't help but feel like Chicago is neglected. It appears that if your not in CA or NY you don't …  not sure how your spouse will react. But the size of your startup shouldn't matter. RentSpek has gained 22 users in it's 7 days …

Topics: Chicago, mayor, startups, RentSpek, Local H, Rahm, Business, Raham Emanuel, Web, Mobile, AngelList, New York, Silicon Valley, California, Chicago Cubs, Chicago White Sox, MLB, Baseball</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7061-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7061_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:56:27">http://hanhaiventure.wordpress.com/2013/09/03/angel-laoma-on-entry-to-chinas-market/</link><title>Angel LaoMa on Entry to China’s Market</title><description>Angel LaoMa on Entry to China’s Market

3 Sep 2013 by Hanhai Investment on Hanhai Investment hanhaiventure.wordpress.com/2013/09/03/angel-laoma-on-entry-to-chinas-market/

…  should know the answers to: 1\. How do I prepare my startup for expansion in China? 2\. Which city should I start my business in to …  500 company. He has also worked for Deloitte Touche in Chicago. Last but not least, he founded his first Chinese company in 1997 and …

Topics: Highlights</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>