<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7063">Spanish unemployment</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:03:11" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7063-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7063_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:03:13">http://portuguesepundit.wordpress.com/2013/01/03/unemployment-raises-in-portugal-and-spain/</link><title>Unemployment raises in Portugal and Spain</title><description>Unemployment raises in Portugal and Spain

3 Jan 2013 by O. Braga on Portuguese Pundit portuguesepundit.wordpress.com/2013/01/03/unemployment-raises-in-portugal-and-spain/

…  Spanish unemployment climbed up to 4,8 million people at the end of last year — the highest unemployment level since 1996. During 2012, the Spanish economy has destroyed 790,000 jobs. The official Spanish …

Topics: Portugal, Spain</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7063-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7063_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:03:53">http://presbiteriohannes.wordpress.com/2014/01/02/the-strange-case-of-spanish-unemployment/</link><title>The strange case of Spanish unemployment</title><description>The strange case of Spanish unemployment

2 Jan 2014 by presbiter iohannes on presbiter iohannes presbiteriohannes.wordpress.com/2014/01/02/the-strange-case-of-spanish-unemployment/

…  are unemployed. Picture that: As you read this, the unemployment rate in Spain is the 26 %. If you think that’s incredible, wait …  and a PhD student) in this article, compare French and Spanish unemployment rates and say: Behind their apparently similar employment …

Topics: stats, statistics, Economy, social issues, Politics, Spain, Unemployment, Econometrics, Europe</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7063-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7063_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:04:25">http://yseatoli.wordpress.com/2014/01/03/spanish-unemployment-shrinks/</link><title>Spanish unemployment shrinks</title><description>Spanish unemployment shrinks

3 Jan 2014 by yseatoli on mexico yseatoli.wordpress.com/2014/01/03/spanish-unemployment-shrinks/

THE number of people registered as out of work in Spain in December shrank by 107,570, to about 4.7 million. Spanish unemployment shrinks

Topics: Spanish unemployment shrinks</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7063-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7063_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:04:59">http://tribulationpress.info/2012/04/27/bbc-news-spanish-unemployment-hits-record-5-64-million/</link><title>BBC News - Spanish unemployment hits record 5.64 million</title><description>BBC News - Spanish unemployment hits record 5.64 million

27 Apr 2012 by lester on TribPress News tribulationpress.info/2012/04/27/bbc-news-spanish-unemployment-hits-record-5-64-million/

Spanish unemployment has hit a new record high, official figures have shown. The …  people reached 5,639,500 at the end of March, with the unemployment rate hitting 24.4%, the national statistics agency said. via BBC News - Spanish unemployment hits record 5.64 …

Topics: Economy</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7063-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7063_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:05:35">http://mybuwcsea.com/2012/05/03/spanish-unemployment/</link><title>Spanish Unemployment</title><description>Spanish Unemployment

3 May 2012 by mindingyourbusiness2 on Minding Your Business mybuwcsea.com/2012/05/03/spanish-unemployment/

…  unemployment rate passed the 5 million mark at the end of 2011. Standing at a 22.8% unemployment rate this is over double the Eurozone’s unemployment rate and is …  rates increased along with repossession rates of Spanish properties, as it rose 32% in the previous year. This was caused by the …

Topics: Europe, Government, European economic crisis</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7063-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7063_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:06:09">http://internationalguy.wordpress.com/2009/04/09/spanish-unemployment/</link><title>Spanish Unemployment</title><description>Spanish Unemployment

9 Apr 2009 by internationalguy on Internationalguy's Blog internationalguy.wordpress.com/2009/04/09/spanish-unemployment/

…  and a worse case one. On the moderate scenario, total unemployment will now hit 4.5 million by December, and 6 million by December …  (Jean Claude Trichet simply said what he had to to the Spanish journalist who questioned him on the Spanish banking system in …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7063-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7063_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:06:42">http://juancarlosnavanava.wordpress.com/2012/01/27/euro-crisis-spain-s-unemployment-rate-rises-to-22-9/</link><title>EURO CRISIS : SPAIN 'S UNEMPLOYMENT RATE RISES TO 22.9% !</title><description>EURO CRISIS : SPAIN 'S UNEMPLOYMENT RATE RISES TO 22.9% !

27 Jan 2012 by juancarlosnavanava on JUAN CARLOS NAVA'S BLOG juancarlosnavanava.wordpress.com/2012/01/27/euro-crisis-spain-s-unemployment-rate-rises-to-22-9/

Spanish Unemployment Rises to 22.9% via Spanish Unemployment Rises to 22.9% - Bloomberg.

Topics: Spain, united states, Brazil, Economía, India, Poland, Chile, France, Euro, Japan, Australia, Canada, Economy, world crisis, Business, economie, Markets, Russia, Finance, New Zealand, united kingdom, South Africa, China, Germany, Euro zone, Money, Italy, Colombia, european union</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7063-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7063_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:07:13">http://juancarlosnavanava.wordpress.com/2010/04/30/euro-spain-unemployment-tops-20/</link><title>EURO: SPAIN UNEMPLOYMENT TOPS 20% !</title><description>EURO: SPAIN UNEMPLOYMENT TOPS 20% !

30 Apr 2010 by juancarlosnavanava on JUAN CARLOS NAVA'S BLOG juancarlosnavanava.wordpress.com/2010/04/30/euro-spain-unemployment-tops-20/

Spanish Unemployment Rate Tops 20%, Undermining Deficit Fight via Spanish Unemployment Rate Tops 20%, Undermining Deficit Fight - Bloomberg.com.

Topics: Spain, united states, Brazil, dolar, peso mexicano, Economía, India, France, Euro, Japan, Australia, Canada, Economy, world crisis, Business, economie, Russia, Real, Dollar, Yen, yuan, Pound, Mexican peso, Swiss Franc, Finance, united kingdom, South Africa, Ruble, China</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7063-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7063_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:07:42">http://juancarlosnavanava.wordpress.com/2011/10/28/euro-crisis-spain-s-unemployment-rises-to-highest-in-15-years/</link><title>EURO CRISIS : SPAIN 'S UNEMPLOYMENT RISES TO HIGHEST IN 15 YEARS !</title><description>EURO CRISIS : SPAIN 'S UNEMPLOYMENT RISES TO HIGHEST IN 15 YEARS !

28 Oct 2011 by juancarlosnavanava on JUAN CARLOS NAVA'S BLOG juancarlosnavanava.wordpress.com/2011/10/28/euro-crisis-spain-s-unemployment-rises-to-highest-in-15-years/

Spanish Unemployment Rises to Highest in 15 Years, Undermining Recovery via Spanish Unemployment Rises to Highest in 15 Years, Undermining Recovery - Bloomberg.

Topics: Spain, united states, Brazil, Economía, India, France, Euro, Japan, Canada, Economy, world crisis, Business, economie, Markets, Russia, Finance, united kingdom, China, Germany, Euro zone, Money, Italy, european union, WORLD CRISIS, Financial Markets, euro area, Europe, mex, G-7, BRIC</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7063-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7063_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:08:16">http://juancarlosnavanava.wordpress.com/2009/07/24/spanish-unemployment-rate-rises-to-decade-high-17-9-may-reach-22-in-2010/</link><title>SPANISH UNEMPLOYMENT RATE RISES TO DECADE-HIGH 17.9%, MAY REACH 22% IN 2010</title><description>SPANISH UNEMPLOYMENT RATE RISES TO DECADE-HIGH 17.9%, MAY REACH 22% IN 2010

24 Jul 2009 by juancarlosnavanava on JUAN CARLOS NAVA'S BLOG juancarlosnavanava.wordpress.com/2009/07/24/spanish-unemployment-rate-rises-to-decade-high-17-9-may-reach-22-in-2010/

Spanish Unemployment Rate Rises to Decade-High 17.9 Percent via Spanish Unemployment Rate Rises to Decade-High 17.9 Percent - Bloomberg.com.

Topics: Spain, united states, Economía, France, Euro, Japan, Australia, Canada, Economy, world crisis, Business, economie, Finance, united kingdom, Germany, Euro zone, Money, Italy, european union, WORLD CRISIS, Financial Markets, euro area, World Depression, G7, Europe</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>