<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7065">disney easter dessert recipes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:15:04" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7065-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7065_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:15:05">http://nightowlkitchenblog.wordpress.com/2014/03/20/springing-around/</link><title>Springing Around...</title><description>Springing Around...

20 Mar 2014 by Night Owl Kitchen on Night Owl Kitchen nightowlkitchenblog.wordpress.com/2014/03/20/springing-around/

…  and sad. And I've been gathering ideas for our Easter menu, being of German descent I like to incorporate that into our …  Break Snacks from Snack Girl 20 Spring Break Treats from Disney Baby 20 Best Snacks for Kids from Parents.com School Parties: Snack …

Topics: Recipes, fun with family, Just For Fun, Crafts, Eggs, party food, Snacks, spring crafts, Spring recipes, kid crafts, school snacks, spring fun, First Day of Spring, Easter, Easter Crafts, Easter snacks, Bunnies, Ducks</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7065-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7065_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:15:53">http://cupcakesonstmarks.wordpress.com/2013/04/19/delicious-disney-desserts-italian-lemon-tart/</link><title>Delicious Disney Desserts: Italian Lemon Tart</title><description>Delicious Disney Desserts: Italian Lemon Tart

19 Apr 2013 by CupcakesOnStMarks on Cupcakes on St Marks cupcakesonstmarks.wordpress.com/2013/04/19/delicious-disney-desserts-italian-lemon-tart/

…  two weeks, yikes) but it is worth it, believe me. For Easter my mother surprised me with the Delicious Disney Desserts book that I had been drooling over the entire time I was in …

Topics: baking, Student, Photography, cooking, recipe, treat, Dessert, Yummy!, del.icio.us, Lemon, Raspberry, Disney, Fruit, Crust, Food, cook, Cruise Line, delicious disney desserts, Bake, Tart</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7065-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7065_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:16:33">http://rebeccawoodblog.wordpress.com/2010/03/31/easter-dessert-recipes/</link><title>Easter Dessert Recipes</title><description>Easter Dessert Recipes

31 Mar 2010 by Rebecca W on It Is What It Is rebeccawoodblog.wordpress.com/2010/03/31/easter-dessert-recipes/

…  last big push to gather recipes for Easter on Sunday. We are not having the usual Ham/Potato dinner …  week I have been trying to think of something to have for dessert and whether I should attempt to make something fancy or simply go buy a …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7065-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7065_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:17:05">http://wnep.com/2014/04/15/stadt-house-bakery-facebook/</link><title>Easter Recipe Ideas For Desserts</title><description>Easter Recipe Ideas For Desserts

15 Apr 2014 by Mike Vojtko on WNEP.com wnep.com/2014/04/15/stadt-house-bakery-facebook/

To see the recipe ideas to help you deck out your Easter deserts as featured on Newswatch 16 from Stadt House Bakery, click here!

Topics: Websites mentioned</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7065-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7065_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:17:54">http://savoringsimplicity.wordpress.com/2011/03/31/32-easter-dessert-recipes/</link><title>32 Easter Dessert Recipes</title><description>32 Easter Dessert Recipes

31 Mar 2011 by Savoring Simplicity on Savoring Simplicity savoringsimplicity.wordpress.com/2011/03/31/32-easter-dessert-recipes/

…  may be going out with a roar rather than a baabaa, but Easter is still on its way. I found some delightful desserts that are perfect for celebrating Easter or simply the arrival of springtime. Some require more determination …

Topics: Desserts, Spring desserts, easter desserts, cupcakes, Easter cupcakes, Easter cakes</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7065-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7065_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:18:42">http://booksforbelle.wordpress.com/2014/03/23/sunday-sweets-rock-candy/</link><title>Sunday Sweets - Rock Candy</title><description>Sunday Sweets - Rock Candy

23 Mar 2014 by booksforbelle on booksforbelle booksforbelle.wordpress.com/2014/03/23/sunday-sweets-rock-candy/

…  when I found some at the Main Street Confectionery at Walt Disney World.  As I was planning my Easter dinner for this year, I stumbled across a recipe on Pinterest for Rock …

Topics: check it off the list, Pinterest, Disney, recipe, Dessert, Sugar, snack!, walt disney world, Directions, candy, Sunday Sweets, treat, Main Street USA, Rock Candy, Kitchen Science, experiment, sugar substitute, Main Street Confectionery, Crystals</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7065-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7065_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:19:21">http://carofranck.wordpress.com/2010/03/17/chocolate-flavoured-article/</link><title>Chocolate-flavoured Article</title><description>Chocolate-flavoured Article

17 Mar 2010 by thalounette on Food: freestyle experiences carofranck.wordpress.com/2010/03/17/chocolate-flavoured-article/

…  on certain holidays now! Right now we can see that Easter will be here soon as we see the ‘phenomenon’ when we go to the …  or chocolate bars to chocolate fountains to serve dessert fondue for instance, dark, milk and white chocolate are everywhere …  seen there, like Don Quijote, Salvador Dali, Lucky Luke, Disney animated characters or famous buildings… Chocolate likeness of …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7065-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7065_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:19:46">http://organizedstyles.wordpress.com/2014/04/07/angel-food-cake/</link><title>Angel Food Cake</title><description>Angel Food Cake

7 Apr 2014 by courtneybragg organizedstyles.wordpress.com/2014/04/07/angel-food-cake/

…  morning! Spring is here and Easter is near! Since Easter is almost upon us I decided to share my very favorite Spring …  few years ago I was staying with my Aunt and Uncle for Easter and I wanted to contribute to our Easter meal, so I decided to make …

Topics: Recipes, Recipes 2, Food, Dessert, Easter</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7065-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7065_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:20:46">http://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2011/04/20/ranias-recipes-easter-breakfast-dessert/</link><title>Rania's Recipes: Easter Breakfast &amp; Dessert</title><description>Rania's Recipes: Easter Breakfast &amp; Dessert

20 Apr 2011 by hlang84 on CBS Pittsburgh pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2011/04/20/ranias-recipes-easter-breakfast-dessert/

…  April, Rania Harris has been showing off recipes for a special Easter holiday meal! This week, she's back with recipes for two family favorites at her home - Easter morning breakfast and dessert. Sour Cream Waffles with Strawberry Syrup 3 eggs – …

Topics: Rania Harris, Recipes, Rania's Recipes, Cooking With Rania, Easter, lemon meringue pie, Sour Cream Waffles, strawberry syrup</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7065-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7065_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:21:35">http://glutenfreegal.com/2014/04/19/gluten-free-easter-recipes-from-dinner-to-dessert/</link><title>Gluten Free Easter Recipes from Dinner to Dessert</title><description>Gluten Free Easter Recipes from Dinner to Dessert

19 Apr 2014 by Kirsten Berman - GlutenFree Gal on GlutenFreeGal glutenfreegal.com/2014/04/19/gluten-free-easter-recipes-from-dinner-to-dessert/

…  Weekend All… Enjoy these healthy, delectable recipes and tasty eats!   Roast Leg of Lamb with Garlic Herb Crust and …  Eggs and Ham Deviled Eggs  courtesy of My Recipes     Strawberry, Cucumber, and Basil Salad  courtesy of …  of The Urban Poser     Hidden Rainbow Easter Egg Cake from Boulder …

Topics: glutenfree recipes, Living Without, Gluten Free Food, gluten free Easter recipes, boulder lacavore, my recipes, Martha Stewart, Divine Health, tasty yummies, Delis, Urban Poser, Gluten-Free Holiday</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>