<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7068">Speech and Language Processing: An Introduction to Natural Language Processing, Computational Linguistics, and Speech Recognition</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:36:06" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7068-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7068_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:36:07">http://modusvivendi2013.wordpress.com/2014/03/04/fbk-hlt/</link><title>FBK | HLT</title><description>FBK | HLT

4 Mar 2014 by modusvivendi2013 on biology sociology modusvivendi2013.wordpress.com/2014/03/04/fbk-hlt/

…  particular, our research unit focuses on automatic speech recognition, machine translation, and content processing. HLT draws on several disciplines, such as computational …

Topics: Organisations</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7068-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7068_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:36:42">http://androidspeechbook.wordpress.com/web-page/chapter-1/</link><title>Chapter 1</title><description>Chapter 1

24 Oct 2013 by ZC on Voice application development for Android androidspeechbook.wordpress.com/web-page/chapter-1/

Speech on Android Devices Exercises: Familiarize yourself with the capabilities …  the voice features. Usually this is under Settings &gt; Language &amp; Input. You can play with the different configurations of the device's language, voice search options and text-to-speech options. Watch this video and try some Google voice …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7068-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7068_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:37:11">http://columbialinguistics.wordpress.com/2008/11/24/computer-science-courses/</link><title>Computer Science courses</title><description>Computer Science courses

24 Nov 2008 by columbialinguistics on Columbia Linguistics Society columbialinguistics.wordpress.com/2008/11/24/computer-science-courses/

…  Computational approaches to natural language generation and understanding. Recommended preparation: some previous or concurrent …  machine translation, dialogue systems, and emotional speech. Particular attention is given to robust techniques that can handle …

Topics: Courses, Computer Science</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7068-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7068_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:37:39">http://silviasevilla.wordpress.com/2006/12/26/computational-linguistics/</link><title>Computational linguistics</title><description>Computational linguistics

26 Dec 2006 by silviasevilla on Silvia's blog silviasevilla.wordpress.com/2006/12/26/computational-linguistics/

…  is an interdisciplinary field dealing with the statistical and logical modeling of natural language from a computational perspective. This …  language (parsing) or creating language (generation). Speech recognition and speech synthesis deal with how spoken language can be …

Topics: Language Resources</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7068-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7068_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:38:16">http://lauraandres1987.wordpress.com/2007/03/19/european-research-centre/</link><title>European Research Centres</title><description>European Research Centres

19 Mar 2007 by Laura Andrés on Perdida lauraandres1987.wordpress.com/2007/03/19/european-research-centre/

…  Technology Group: Language Technology (LT) forms a major research area at the Austrian Research …  its inception in 1984. We conduct research in modelling and processing human languages, especially for German. This includes …  (such as morphological components, parsers, generators, speech synthesizers, discourse processing components), and application …

Topics: -ist, littera, HTL</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7068-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7068_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:39:00">http://iraya.wordpress.com/2009/03/08/q1-hlt-and-research-centres-for-human-language-technology-in-europa/</link><title>(Q.1) HLT and Research Centres for Human Language Technology in Europa</title><description>(Q.1) HLT and Research Centres for Human Language Technology in Europa

8 Mar 2009 by iraya on IrAyA iraya.wordpress.com/2009/03/08/q1-hlt-and-research-centres-for-human-language-technology-in-europa/

…  wikipedia says Human Language Technology (hlt) or Natural Language Processing (nlp) consists of …  of natural language from a computational perspective, and also consists of speech technology. HLT is connected with computer sciences and …

Topics: HLT, littera</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7068-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7068_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:39:34">http://englishrep.org/2013/05/20/computational-linguistics/</link><title>Computational Linguistics</title><description>Computational Linguistics

20 May 2013 by floradebora on English Repository englishrep.org/2013/05/20/computational-linguistics/

…  Linguistics is devoted exclusively to the design and analysis of natural language processing systems. From this highly-regarded quarterly, university …  intelligence investigators, cognitive scientists, speech specialists, and philosophers get information about computational …

Topics: Free e-Journal, Linguistics, Computational</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7068-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7068_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:40:01">http://columbialinguistics.wordpress.com/2009/11/08/upcoming-events/</link><title>Upcoming Events</title><description>Upcoming Events

9 Nov 2009 by columbialinguistics on Columbia Linguistics Society columbialinguistics.wordpress.com/2009/11/08/upcoming-events/

…  pm Dinner at the Columbia Cottage. Join us for food and conversation - all are welcome! RSVP on Facebook. Friday, 11/20/09 3 pm …  including training language models for automatic speech recognition, text-to\- speech generation, and so on. We present here a …

Topics: Linguistics, Cottage, Speakers, Club-Events, Lectures, translation, Natural Language Processing, Computer Science</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7068-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7068_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:40:28">http://jenniferisasi.wordpress.com/2008/03/24/european-research-centres-for-human-language-technologies-q1/</link><title>European research centres for Human Language Technologies (Q1)</title><description>European research centres for Human Language Technologies (Q1)

24 Mar 2008 by Jennifer Isasi on My computer ♥ literature jenniferisasi.wordpress.com/2008/03/24/european-research-centres-for-human-language-technologies-q1/

…  Edinburgh Language Technology Group (LTG) is a research and development group that has been working in the area of natural language …  the processing of human language by computers, such as speech recognition and synthesis, machine translation, human-computer …

Topics: littera, HLT, littera, HLT</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7068-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7068_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:41:15">http://rhetoricked.com/2013/01/03/mla13_presentation/</link><title>Expanding Access: Building Bridges within DH</title><description>Expanding Access: Building Bridges within DH

3 Jan 2013 by Brian Larson on Rhetoricked rhetoricked.com/2013/01/03/mla13_presentation/

…  text of my prepared remarks for a roundtable at the Modern Language Association convention in January 2013. (This version is slightly …  that focus almost exclusively on the United States and English-language projects. This roundtable will bring together digital …  proper names of people, places, and things; part-of-speech tagging, which entails assigning a probable part of speech to each …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>