<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7080">lord of the rings hobbits theme</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:56:05" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7080-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7080_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:56:06">http://catholicbookreport.wordpress.com/2013/11/13/bilbos-journey-joseph-pearce/</link><title>Bilbo's Journey (Joseph Pearce)</title><description>Bilbo's Journey (Joseph Pearce)

14 Nov 2013 by Aaron on Catholic Book Report catholicbookreport.wordpress.com/2013/11/13/bilbos-journey-joseph-pearce/

…  the movie. (By the way, what are you waiting for?!) For Lord of the Rings fans, the book will be an even more welcome addition to your …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7080-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7080_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:56:46">http://pushtotalk.spl.org/2013/06/04/music-review-the-hobbit-soundtrack/</link><title>Teen Review: The Hobbit Soundtrack (music)</title><description>Teen Review: The Hobbit Soundtrack (music)

4 Jun 2013 by pushtotalkteens on Push to Talk pushtotalk.spl.org/2013/06/04/music-review-the-hobbit-soundtrack/

…  anybody who has seen The Lord of the Rings films will recall that the music was probably one of the …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7080-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7080_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:57:34">http://davehershey.wordpress.com/2012/06/04/the-hobbit-vs-les-miserables/</link><title>The Hobbit vs. Les Miserables</title><description>The Hobbit vs. Les Miserables

4 Jun 2012 by davehershey on Hershey's Writing davehershey.wordpress.com/2012/06/04/the-hobbit-vs-les-miserables/

…  is going to be fantastic as two film adaptations of great stories are set to hit theaters. First, The Hobbit. [youtube=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G0k3kHtyoqc] Second, …  books and Peter Jackson's adaptation of Lord of the Rings.  In terms of Les Miserables, the book was a long, tough and …

Topics: Ponderings, Random, Movies, Les Miserables, The Hobbit, lord of the rings</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7080-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7080_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:58:13">http://catholichomeschoolaustralia.com/2011/08/24/the-lord-of-the-rings-the-fellowship-of-the-ring/</link><title>The Lord of the Rings</title><description>The Lord of the Rings

24 Aug 2011 by Catholic Homeschool Australia on Catholic Homeschool Australia catholichomeschoolaustralia.com/2011/08/24/the-lord-of-the-rings-the-fellowship-of-the-ring/

The Fellowship of the Ring. An ancient Ring thought lost for centuries has been found, and …  discovers the Ring is in fact the One Ring of the Dark Lord Sauron, Frodo must make an epic quest to Mount Doom in order to destroy …

Topics: Movie Reviews, fellowship of the ring, Legolas, boromir, one ring, Mount Doom, Hobbit, lord of the rings</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7080-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7080_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:58:49">http://theologyofgames.wordpress.com/2013/04/02/what-news-from-the-shire/</link><title>What News From the Shire?</title><description>What News From the Shire?

2 Apr 2013 by jeremiahi on Theology of Games theologyofgames.wordpress.com/2013/04/02/what-news-from-the-shire/

…  last year's release of the first film installment of the Hobbit, the world of gaming rejoices—and of …  a short (if not completely inclusive) list of them: The Lord of the Rings Living Card Game Saga expansions - Fantasy Flight released …

Topics: News, Fantasy Flight Games, Lotr, The Hobbit, WizKids Games, Tolkien, J. R. R. Tolkien, Middle Earth, The Lord of the Rings, Cryptozoic Games, An Unexpected Journey</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7080-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7080_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:59:37">http://hcslearningcommons.org/2012/12/14/tolkien-experts-talk-about-his-christian-themes/</link><title>Tolkien Experts Talk About His Christian Themes</title><description>Tolkien Experts Talk About His Christian Themes

14 Dec 2012 by hcslearningcommons on HCS Learning Commons hcslearningcommons.org/2012/12/14/tolkien-experts-talk-about-his-christian-themes/

…  on Scoop.it - Christianity in Education In advance of The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey hitting theaters, Crosswalk.com talks with …  faith and how it comes across in The Hobbit and The Lord of the Rings. Pippa Davies @PippaDavies's insight: Video …

Topics: Tolkien, Hobbit, Fantasy, lord of rings, J. R. R. Tolkien, crosswalk.com, Christianity, Bilbo Baggins, Peter Jackson, Authors</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7080-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7080_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:00:20">http://inspiremakers.wordpress.com/2012/07/13/check-out-legos-hobbit-an-unexpected-gathering/</link><title>Check Out LEGO's Hobbit An Unexpected Gathering</title><description>Check Out LEGO's Hobbit An Unexpected Gathering

13 Jul 2012 by Christian Rivera on Inspire Me! inspiremakers.wordpress.com/2012/07/13/check-out-legos-hobbit-an-unexpected-gathering/

…  Diego Comic-Con booth all weekend, including a "theme of the day" roster that will spotlight a different franchise each day, including The Hobbit/Lord of the Rings, Star Wars, DC and Marvel Super Heroes and Ninjago. But also …

Topics: IGN All, News, Check Out LEGO's Hobbit An Unexpected Gathering, Check Out LEGO's Hobbit An Unexpected Gathering IGN All</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7080-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7080_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:01:02">http://abum190.wordpress.com/2012/04/05/the-hobbit/</link><title>The Hobbit</title><description>The Hobbit

6 Apr 2012 by abum190 on Coulda Been a Contender abum190.wordpress.com/2012/04/05/the-hobbit/

…  to me a long time ago, but it honestly always seemed sort of boring to me when I would try to read it, so I never got outside …   Strangely, I later devoured the much heavier and drier Lord of the Rings trilogy, loving every page.  What with The Hobbit movie …

Topics: Entertainment, pop culture, Books, J. R. R. Tolkien, The Hobbit, lord of the rings, Frodo, bilbo, Baggins, Peter Jackson</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7080-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7080_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:01:34">http://goodnewsnow.wordpress.com/2013/02/04/j-r-r-tolkien-legend-of-middle-earth/</link><title>J. R. R. Tolkien--Legend of Middle Earth</title><description>J. R. R. Tolkien--Legend of Middle Earth

4 Feb 2013 by papapound on The Good News goodnewsnow.wordpress.com/2013/02/04/j-r-r-tolkien-legend-of-middle-earth/

…  J. R. R. Tolkien created Middle Earth. Some of you may be interested. This info is not directly related to the Lord of the Rings themes I am focusing on this …

Topics: World Events, Tolkien, J.R.R. Tolkien</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7080-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7080_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:02:23">http://senfilmreviews.wordpress.com/2014/02/11/the-hobbit-an-unexpected-journey/</link><title>The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey</title><description>The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey

11 Feb 2014 by senfilmreviews on Sen film reviews senfilmreviews.wordpress.com/2014/02/11/the-hobbit-an-unexpected-journey/

…  without its faults… By Seneer Asif My rating: 4 out of 5 The first part into the three part Hobbit saga revolves around a young …  called Smaug. The Hobbit is a prequel to the famous Lord of the Rings trilogy, also directed by Peter Jackson. In a way we could …

Topics: film, The Hobbit, An Unexpected Journey, lord of the rings, Peter Jackson, Martin Freeman, Richard Armitage, Fantasy, Action, adventure, Epic, Book Adaptation, 2012, Ian McKellen</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>