<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7083">I'm on the road again</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:15:25" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7083-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7083_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:15:26">http://thebeautifulpath.org/2009/07/27/im-on-the-road-again/</link><title>I'm on the road again...</title><description>I'm on the road again...

27 Jul 2009 by Padre on The Beautiful Path thebeautifulpath.org/2009/07/27/im-on-the-road-again/

…  for a funeral. They say it might rain but for now the skies look clear and in less than an hour I should be away.The person …  dead.Regardless in less then a half hour I'll be on the road again and since I've never been to Boscobel before it will be …

Topics: Archival</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7083-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7083_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:15:59">http://samirchopra.com/2012/07/31/im-on-the-road-again/</link><title>I'm On The Road Again</title><description>I'm On The Road Again

1 Aug 2012 by Samir Chopra on Samir Chopra samirchopra.com/2012/07/31/im-on-the-road-again/

An old-fashioned road-trip still has its charms especially if it involves the gorgeous southwest. This month I am on the road, heading for desert, forest, and mountain. I will not be blogging other than posting daily photos. Hope you like 'em.

Topics: General, Travel (2), US-Southwest, Road Trip</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7083-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7083_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:16:34">http://alanbell.me.uk/2005/06/27/im-on-the-road-again/</link><title>I'm on the road again</title><description>I'm on the road again

27 Jun 2005 by Alan Bell on Alan's Place alanbell.me.uk/2005/06/27/im-on-the-road-again/

…  a little late for me, and the sun is shining brightly giving me a chance to try out the Caberg sun visor - very space age - The ride was great. No quicker than …  which I mean that I always feel more aware of conditions on a bike - it's amazing how you notice all the pot holes and drain covers …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7083-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7083_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:17:11">http://pauljsmith.wordpress.com/2009/12/01/im-on-the-road-again/</link><title>I'm On The Road Again</title><description>I'm On The Road Again

1 Dec 2009 by paul2413 on The Life and Times of a Texas Country Trial Lawyer pauljsmith.wordpress.com/2009/12/01/im-on-the-road-again/

…  on the road again,, moving. I am not sure exactly where I will stay, but it's not …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7083-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7083_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:17:52">http://adamrozanas.com/2010/12/30/on-the-road-again-no-literally-im-cleared-to-be-on-the-road-again/</link><title>On the Road Again...No, literally - I'm Cleared to be on the Road Again!</title><description>On the Road Again...No, literally - I'm Cleared to be on the Road Again!

30 Dec 2010 by asrozanas on Adam Rozanas adamrozanas.com/2010/12/30/on-the-road-again-no-literally-im-cleared-to-be-on-the-road-again/

…  the gray hairs set in, I'm beginning to realize that the older you get, …  white under-shirt, striped long-sleeved collared shirt on the outside, my best-looking tennis shoes...after all, I spent, like, 6 …  cause if the photo was any bigger you would have seen me on my Illinois license wearing a bright blue T-shirt with an outline of …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7083-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7083_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:18:22">http://shondratasha.wordpress.com/2007/11/17/im-on-the-road-again/</link><title>I'm on the road again....</title><description>I'm on the road again....

17 Nov 2007 by shondratasha on Just So you Know shondratasha.wordpress.com/2007/11/17/im-on-the-road-again/

…  week was Spokane Washington. So I flew into Pasco, stayed the night and did my first meeting, then drove 50 miles to my second meeting in …  I also started and finished The Jane Austen Book Club on CD. I think it would have made more sense if I was familiar with …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7083-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7083_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:18:59">http://fwhytecrosshaven.wordpress.com/2013/10/24/on-the-road-again-or-why-im-in-a-choir/</link><title>On The Road Again or Why I'm In A Choir</title><description>On The Road Again or Why I'm In A Choir

24 Oct 2013 by fionatwhyte on Fiona Whyte blog fwhytecrosshaven.wordpress.com/2013/10/24/on-the-road-again-or-why-im-in-a-choir/

…  on the road again. My partner and I are finalising arrangements for our trip to Derry this …

Topics: Music, Fiona Whyte, Cantabile Vocal Ensemble, Derry International Choral Festival, Londonderry, Limerick Choral Festival, Derry, Choirs, St Columb's Hall</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7083-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7083_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:19:35">http://reidcoolsaet.com/2011/08/08/im-on-the-road-again/</link><title>I'm on the road again</title><description>I'm on the road again

9 Aug 2011 by reidcoolsaet on FLOAT ON reidcoolsaet.com/2011/08/08/im-on-the-road-again/

…  km (running), 1 wedding. A few hours before I set off on the road trip I did my second workout of the week which consisted of almost …

Topics: Running</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7083-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7083_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:20:32">http://tripirate.wordpress.com/2010/10/03/offroad/</link><title>I'm Off the Road Again</title><description>I'm Off the Road Again

3 Oct 2010 by Twitchdoctor on Alchemy tripirate.wordpress.com/2010/10/03/offroad/

…  still no Ironman report.  The woman who is doing the leather-binding says that she's having trouble finding enough gilt to do all the lettering on the cover.  Plus I'm still in negotiation about film rights and I want …  Forest Park.  I'd put the mountain bike wheels back on the Cannondale and was pleased to discover that the Scorpions hadn't …

Topics: philosophical musings, Life, and Other Ephemera, Mountain Biking, marine corps, iraq, Iraq War, Afghanistan, National Museum of the Marine Corps, War, Suicide</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7083-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7083_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:21:07">http://richbeyondbills.wordpress.com/2011/08/21/im-on-the-road-again/</link><title>I'm on the road, again...</title><description>I'm on the road, again...

22 Aug 2011 by RichBeyondBills richbeyondbills.wordpress.com/2011/08/21/im-on-the-road-again/

…  not up to par each day with writing as of late due to the freedom known as "life". I wrote about being single a few posts …  a little ride to Banff just to enjoy the open road, sun on our face, wind on our bodies and the joy it is to hear the roar of our …

Topics: Personal</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>