<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7092">How much was a gallon of gas during depression</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:11:35" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7092-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7092_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:11:36">http://zdeaconblue.wordpress.com/2010/06/14/if-this-is-true-bp-may-lead-the-united-states-into-depression/</link><title>If this is true, BP may lead the United States into Depression</title><description>If this is true, BP may lead the United States into Depression

14 Jun 2010 by zdeaconblue on Zdeaconblue's Blog zdeaconblue.wordpress.com/2010/06/14/if-this-is-true-bp-may-lead-the-united-states-into-depression/

…  of Sciences as saying that the Gulf of Mexico leak is much worse than we have been told.  In fact the report suggests that the well …  inflict upon the ecosystems of the Gulf of Mexico and how long will they take to recover?  On the economic front, should the blast …

Topics: Environment, oil spill, Haliburton, BP, Transocean, Economy, dystopian times, european union, recession, Depression, Oil, Louisiana, Barack Obama, Tony Hayward, Anatoly Sagalevich, nuke, Nuclear weapon, well, CAP, catastraphe, Tuna, Russia, Russian Academy of Sciences, Mississippi, Alabama, Florida, Euro, financial crisis</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7092-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7092_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:12:12">http://newsdeskinternational.wordpress.com/2012/10/20/obama-explains-why-gas-price-are-high-but-is-it-the-truth/</link><title>Obama explains why gas price are high, but is it the truth?</title><description>Obama explains why gas price are high, but is it the truth?

20 Oct 2012 by Janet on Newsdesk International newsdeskinternational.wordpress.com/2012/10/20/obama-explains-why-gas-price-are-high-but-is-it-the-truth/

…  costs,  commodities speculation and oil supply all play a much bigger role in how much a  gallon of regular costs drivers, they said. The issue came up when …

Topics: Politics, Mitt Romney, President Barack Obama wrong on why gas is high, Analysts, Jonathan Lesser, an energy economist and president of the consulting fir</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7092-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7092_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:12:59">http://reclaimingthetitle.wordpress.com/2009/01/08/rising-gas-prices-the-lamest-reason-to-be-emo-ever/</link><title>Rising gas prices the lamest reason to be emo ever?</title><description>Rising gas prices the lamest reason to be emo ever?

8 Jan 2009 by Slick Diaz on Reclaiming the Title reclaimingthetitle.wordpress.com/2009/01/08/rising-gas-prices-the-lamest-reason-to-be-emo-ever/

…  part. Apparently there's a gas scene. You know, like how 209Vibe covered the music scene, Fitzy covers the affluent white folk …  one of his main campaign issues, it shouldn't be too much of a stretch to think that maybe the business/health care reporter should …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7092-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7092_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:13:35">http://mindset30.wordpress.com/2008/05/22/gas-prices-may-reach-500-per-gallon-sooner-than-we-think/</link><title>Gas Prices May Reach $5.00 per Gallon Sooner than We Think</title><description>Gas Prices May Reach $5.00 per Gallon Sooner than We Think

22 May 2008 by lhowell on Mindset 3.0 mindset30.wordpress.com/2008/05/22/gas-prices-may-reach-500-per-gallon-sooner-than-we-think/

…  there, I went a bit further and polled a few people on how much it costs to operate their automobile for a month. You ready? People …

Topics: Gas, government bail-out, Detroit, Depression, Marketing, mindset 3.0, Economy</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7092-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7092_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:14:01">http://science.time.com/2012/02/21/gasbag-why-no-president-can-bring-us-2-gasoline/</link><title>Gasbag: Why No President Can Bring Us $2 Gasoline</title><description>Gasbag: Why No President Can Bring Us $2 Gasoline

21 Feb 2012 by Bryan Walsh on Science &amp; Space science.time.com/2012/02/21/gasbag-why-no-president-can-bring-us-2-gasoline/

…  pain at the pump. But does a President really have that much control over how much it costs for you to fill your car? (MORE: Why Michele …

Topics: Oil, Oil, obama, oil sands, Gas prices, Keystone XL, Campaign</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7092-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7092_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:14:45">http://tree63fan.wordpress.com/2009/08/31/it-costs-what/</link><title>It Costs What?</title><description>It Costs What?

31 Aug 2009 by tree63fan on The Deliberate Ruminator tree63fan.wordpress.com/2009/08/31/it-costs-what/

…  fun digging into my bills and trying to figure out just how these various bills add up to the final bottom line numbers.  No, I'm …  250% of the cost of the gas itself. There's not much to do to adjust this bill other than to keep the house cooler in winter, …

Topics: Detailed Thoughts, Thoughts, Life, humor, water, Television, Utilities, Natural Gas, electricity, Bills, Gasoline, Shopping, energy savings, energy cost, Environment, cable tv, Dish TV, Eating Out</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7092-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7092_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:15:09">http://girlfriendsguide2homeschooling.wordpress.com/2011/05/09/what-happened-to-the-original-intent-of-meatless-monday/</link><title>What Happened to the Original Intent of Meatless Monday?</title><description>What Happened to the Original Intent of Meatless Monday?

9 May 2011 by boodlesmom on Girlfriend's Guide 2 Homeschooling girlfriendsguide2homeschooling.wordpress.com/2011/05/09/what-happened-to-the-original-intent-of-meatless-monday/

…  and I wonder if my family can do it and how much money would we save?  I'd love to know if anyone else does it. The original intent of Meatless Monday was due to food rationing to help with the war efforts and then during the …

Topics: Political Rants, Home cooking, Meatless Monday, Vegetarianism, homeschool and meatless monday, meatless monday history</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7092-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7092_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:16:07">http://totallygroovygirlfriday.wordpress.com/2008/10/16/implosion-of-world-wide-banking/</link><title>Implosion of World-wide Banking</title><description>Implosion of World-wide Banking

16 Oct 2008 by totallygroovygirlfriday on muses of the moment totallygroovygirlfriday.wordpress.com/2008/10/16/implosion-of-world-wide-banking/

…  most of the US under the age of 95 does not understand how this might affect them on a personal level and what to do to prepare for …  Purchase a bike. Violence rises. Secure your home as much as possible. High unemployment. Reduce debt, have six months …

Topics: Inflation</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7092-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7092_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:16:37">http://mikemadden59.wordpress.com/2011/05/09/a-tale-of-two-gas-prices/</link><title>A tale of two gas prices</title><description>A tale of two gas prices

9 May 2011 by The Working Class Conservative on The Working Class Conservative! mikemadden59.wordpress.com/2011/05/09/a-tale-of-two-gas-prices/

…  in some three years later.  Let's have a look at how the price of gas was handled by the Bush administration. Bush sees no …  more drilling.  To date drilling in the Gulf has pretty much become stagnant and there are no new drilling permits anywhere on the …

Topics: President Obama, main stream media, Gasoline, President Bush, Oil, 4, Crisis</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7092-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7092_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:17:01">http://coyotesblog.wordpress.com/2013/10/07/1970s-vs-today/</link><title>1970s vs Today</title><description>1970s vs Today

7 Oct 2013 by dstcoyote22 on DesertCoyote22's Blog coyotesblog.wordpress.com/2013/10/07/1970s-vs-today/

…  this is not my job, this a side hobby of mine, and pretty much a journalistic outlet for my writing. I am happy to see that people …  oil without having to directly affect the land. Look at how stinking wealthy these Oil rich countries are nowadays, it's almost a …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>