<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7093">What do i need to go fly fishing?</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:17:32" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7093-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7093_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:17:33">http://shskrjournal.wordpress.com/2013/09/28/starting-out-fishing-for-beginners/</link><title>Start Out Fishing for Beginners</title><description>Start Out Fishing for Beginners

28 Sep 2013 by shskr on SHSKR JOURNAL shskrjournal.wordpress.com/2013/09/28/starting-out-fishing-for-beginners/

…  beginners start asking themselves where do I start? Well, it depends on what outdoor activity you are interested in. If fishing is what you are …

Topics: outdoors, Fishing, Outdoor, Recreation, Flyfishing, tying flies, gear, Bait, boat, Casting, Fly, Freshwater, saltwater, spey, speyfishing, Spinning, Tackle, Fish, Fishing Tackle, Shopping, fishing lure, fishing rod</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7093-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7093_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:18:02">http://eveningsecret.wordpress.com/2010/04/29/evening-secret-blog-fly-fishing-trip-faqs-3/</link><title>Evening Secret Blog - Fly Fishing Trip FAQs</title><description>Evening Secret Blog - Fly Fishing Trip FAQs

29 Apr 2010 by eveningsecret on The Evening Secret Fishing Blog eveningsecret.wordpress.com/2010/04/29/evening-secret-blog-fly-fishing-trip-faqs-3/

…  and lighter than those used for ordinary fishing.Q. How do I choose a fly rod?A. To know what fly rod you should use, visit your local fly shop. They will help you …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7093-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7093_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:18:29">http://idreamofbrewery.wordpress.com/2012/06/30/fly-fishing-where-to-start/</link><title>Fly Fishing, where to start?</title><description>Fly Fishing, where to start?

30 Jun 2012 by koongara on idreamofbrewery idreamofbrewery.wordpress.com/2012/06/30/fly-fishing-where-to-start/

…  all the while camping and having a few beers. So where do I start? do I get lessons? what kind of gear do I need? do I need one of those hats or vests that I put my …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7093-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7093_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:19:03">http://hydroflynamics.wordpress.com/2013/02/26/fly-fishing-log-part-1/</link><title>Fly Fishing Log - Part 1 - Performance Measurement</title><description>Fly Fishing Log - Part 1 - Performance Measurement

27 Feb 2013 by hydroflynamic on hydroflynamics hydroflynamics.wordpress.com/2013/02/26/fly-fishing-log-part-1/

…  to get better. But this is a fly fishing blog.  Why do I need motion capture devices, or a coach?  You don't. You could go …  my slingpack or vest, and I carry it every time I fish. What do I need to measure?  I keep track of the following points; what river, …

Topics: Fly Fishing, Fly fishing, Fish, Performance Analysis, Performance, measurement, outdoors, Recreation, LOG, Journal, Weather, water</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7093-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7093_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:19:34">http://amandasjourneyintoflyfishing.wordpress.com/2014/04/24/on-my-way-to-the-river-2/</link><title>On my way to the River</title><description>On my way to the River

24 Apr 2014 by amandasjourneyintoflyfishing on amandasjourneyintoflyfishing amandasjourneyintoflyfishing.wordpress.com/2014/04/24/on-my-way-to-the-river-2/

…  totally out of my element today. I really didn’t know what to expect from this whole fishing thing. So off I go to work to face my …  fishing rod and a bag of stuff that I’m not sure what to do with. 7 pm comes and myrtle is out there waiting. I go out in the rain and …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7093-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7093_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:20:08">http://uplandways.com/2010/05/22/the-best-thirty-dollars-i-ever-spent/</link><title>THE BEST THIRTY DOLLARS I EVER SPENT</title><description>THE BEST THIRTY DOLLARS I EVER SPENT

22 May 2010 by Andrew Wayment on Upland Ways uplandways.com/2010/05/22/the-best-thirty-dollars-i-ever-spent/

…  natural resources that make Eastern Idaho so special. They do so through entering into conservation easements with private landowners. …  put all of your names in for a drawing on this fly rod. What do you say?" asked Babette, as she pointed to a nice looking fly rod …

Topics: Albright Fly Rod for a Barbie Fishing Pole.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7093-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7093_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:20:49">http://eveningsecret.wordpress.com/2010/05/20/evening-secret-blog-are-you-ready-for-a-peacock-bass-fishing-adventure-2/</link><title>Evening Secret Blog - Are You Ready for a Peacock Bass Fishing Adventure?</title><description>Evening Secret Blog - Are You Ready for a Peacock Bass Fishing Adventure?

20 May 2010 by eveningsecret on The Evening Secret Fishing Blog eveningsecret.wordpress.com/2010/05/20/evening-secret-blog-are-you-ready-for-a-peacock-bass-fishing-adventure-2/

…  and dangerous sports fishing game in the world. What makes it difficul... \- What facts about largemouth bass do I need to know before I go fishing? What facts about largemouth bass do I …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7093-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7093_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:21:18">http://fliesovernebraska.wordpress.com/2012/06/26/urban-fishing/</link><title>Urban Fishing?</title><description>Urban Fishing?

26 Jun 2012 by fliesovernebraska on Flies Over Nebraska fliesovernebraska.wordpress.com/2012/06/26/urban-fishing/

…  that I intend to catch on the fly... it's part of what keeps fly fishing fresh and interesting for me. Currently next on that …  How long before she can cast a fly?! Now all I need to do is tie some of those nylon rope flies I have been reading about on the …

Topics: Fly Fishing, Fishing, Nebraska, Nature, Antelope Creek, GAR</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7093-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7093_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:22:11">http://hydroflynamics.wordpress.com/2013/03/08/fly-fishing-log-2-use-analysis-to-change-the-way-you-fish/</link><title>Fly Fishing Log 2 - Use analysis to change the way you fish.</title><description>Fly Fishing Log 2 - Use analysis to change the way you fish.

8 Mar 2013 by hydroflynamic on hydroflynamics hydroflynamics.wordpress.com/2013/03/08/fly-fishing-log-2-use-analysis-to-change-the-way-you-fish/

…  review of observations data or other feedback, and you can do this yourself. The method that I learned early in my career is the PDCA …  This can help when fish are fussy, especially if you know what worked during similar conditions last year. I find that this is a very …

Topics: Fly Fishing, fly tying, Fly fishing, Fish, Performance Analysis, Performance, outdoors, Recreation, Weather, fly fishing method, fly selection, Fly, fly selection, PDCA</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7093-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7093_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:22:33">http://losthackle.wordpress.com/2012/04/18/simplificate-part3-what-i-now-carry-how/</link><title>Simplificate Part3: What I now carry &amp; how</title><description>Simplificate Part3: What I now carry &amp; how

18 Apr 2012 by losthackle on losthackle losthackle.wordpress.com/2012/04/18/simplificate-part3-what-i-now-carry-how/

…  what do I find I need? A rigged up rod and reel (the tenkara boys and girls will have a …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>