<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7094">calculate inertia sphere</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:23:13" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7094-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7094_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:23:14">http://antiarchit.wordpress.com/2010/10/27/dont-integrate/</link><title>Don’t Integrate!</title><description>Don’t Integrate!

27 Oct 2010 by antiarchit on Peeving Pedantry! antiarchit.wordpress.com/2010/10/27/dont-integrate/

…  to integrate to find out the center of mass and moment of inertia of a body. Firstly, we deal with the problem of finding the center …  axis, the arc length which are together sufficient to calculate the center of mass, by using the equation above. Just to get a …

Topics: Physics, integrate, physics, Mechanics, center of mass, Moment of Inertia</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7094-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7094_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:23:47">http://vsilvestriphysics.wordpress.com/2013/04/03/april-3-2013/</link><title>April 3, 2013</title><description>April 3, 2013

3 Apr 2013 by vsilvestri on Mr. Silvestri's Blog vsilvestriphysics.wordpress.com/2013/04/03/april-3-2013/

…  Rotational Equilibrium Discuss How Moment of Inertia Affects Rotational Motion Calculate Moment of Inertia of Various Shapes State Newton's Second Law …  How Moment of Inertia Affects Rotational Motion Calculate Moment of Inertia of Various Shapes State Newton's Second Law …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7094-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7094_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:24:14">http://keterehsky.wordpress.com/2010/04/15/chapter-5-rotation-of-rigid-body/</link><title>Chapter 5 Rotation Of Rigid Body</title><description>Chapter 5 Rotation Of Rigid Body

15 Apr 2010 by amimo5095 on keterehsky keterehsky.wordpress.com/2010/04/15/chapter-5-rotation-of-rigid-body/

…  of 4.0 rads-1 . The total angular displacement is 18 rad. Calculate: (a) The angular velocity. (b) The duration for the movement.  …  5.2 Rotational Dynamics &gt; Definition Moment of inertia is define as the resistance of a body to change to its rotational …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7094-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7094_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:24:38">http://wpf.2000things.com/2013/02/01/747-implementing-inertia-during-touch-manipulation/</link><title>#747 - Implementing Inertia during Touch Manipulation</title><description>#747 - Implementing Inertia during Touch Manipulation

1 Feb 2013 by Sean on 2,000 Things You Should Know About WPF wpf.2000things.com/2013/02/01/747-implementing-inertia-during-touch-manipulation/

…  talked about how to calculate a value for inertial deceleration.  Once you know what deceleration value that you want, you can implement inertia during touch manipulation by handling the ManipulationInertiaStarting …  event handler, if you specify a deceleration value, the inertia will be modeled and the object will continue to move after the user …

Topics: WPF, Events, Touch Input, Manipulation, ManipulationInertiaStarting</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7094-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7094_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:24:59">http://gasstationwithoutpumps.wordpress.com/2012/03/27/physics-homework-chapter-9/</link><title>Physics homework chapter 9</title><description>Physics homework chapter 9

27 Mar 2012 by gasstationwithoutpumps on Gas station without pumps gasstationwithoutpumps.wordpress.com/2012/03/27/physics-homework-chapter-9/

…  I had difficulty doing problem 8p35, which asks one to calculate the quantum energy levels for vibrations of HCl, making the …  would also have liked to have the moments of inertia for cylinders and spheres derived, rather than just stated as formulas …  I'm a little confused, though why moment of inertia is introduced in Chapter 9, but angular momentum is held off until …

Topics: Physics, Matter and Interactions, AP Physics, Home School</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7094-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7094_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:25:14">http://vsilvestriphysics.wordpress.com/2013/03/19/march-19-2013/</link><title>March 19, 2013</title><description>March 19, 2013

19 Mar 2013 by vsilvestri on Mr. Silvestri's Blog vsilvestriphysics.wordpress.com/2013/03/19/march-19-2013/

…  Equilibrium Relate Rotational Motion to Moment of Inertia Homework - No Labs - No Quiz - No Test - Through Course …  Equilibrium Relate Rotational Motion to Moment of Inertia Homework - No Labs - No Quiz - No Test - Through Course …  Rotational Motion to Moment of Inertia Calculate the Moment of Inertia for Various Shapes Homework - No Labs - …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7094-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7094_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:25:49">http://nateholt.wordpress.com/2009/07/05/melting-glaciers-and-not-enough-hours-in-the-day/</link><title>Melting glaciers and not enough hours in the day</title><description>Melting glaciers and not enough hours in the day

5 Jul 2009 by nateholt on Nate Holt's Blog nateholt.wordpress.com/2009/07/05/melting-glaciers-and-not-enough-hours-in-the-day/

…  out above her head. In this pose, her "moment of inertia" is small and the spin rate is very high. Her fixed angular …  7x10^16 kg. Moment of Inertia calculations for a solid sphere (full earth) and a spherical shell (the 2 inches of water) are here and …

Topics: musings</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7094-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7094_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:26:17">http://vsilvestriphysics.wordpress.com/2013/04/08/april-5-2013/</link><title>April 5, 2013</title><description>April 5, 2013

8 Apr 2013 by vsilvestri on Mr. Silvestri's Blog vsilvestriphysics.wordpress.com/2013/04/08/april-5-2013/

…  Homework Assignment Define and Calculate Angular Momentum Examine How Moment of Inertia Affects Angular Momentum Homework - No Labs - "Weighing an …  Homework Assignment Define and Calculate Angular Momentum Examine How Moment of Inertia Affects Angular …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7094-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7094_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:26:42">http://vsilvestriphysics.wordpress.com/2013/10/29/october-29-2013/</link><title>October 29, 2013</title><description>October 29, 2013

29 Oct 2013 by vsilvestri on Mr. Silvestri's Blog vsilvestriphysics.wordpress.com/2013/10/29/october-29-2013/

…  Newton's First Law of Motion in Terms of Inertia Calculate Net External Force Using Newton's First Law of Motion …  Newton's First Law of Motion in Terms of Inertia Calculate Net External Force Using Newton's First Law of Motion and …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7094-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7094_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:27:32">http://vsilvestriphysics.wordpress.com/2013/10/30/october-30-2013/</link><title>October 30, 2013</title><description>October 30, 2013

30 Oct 2013 by vsilvestri on Mr. Silvestri's Blog vsilvestriphysics.wordpress.com/2013/10/30/october-30-2013/

…  Newton's First Law of Motion in Terms of Inertia Calculate Net External Force Using Newton's First Law of Motion …  Newton's First Law of Motion in Terms of Inertia Calculate Net External Force Using Newton's First Law of Motion and …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>