<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7095">iron in water supply</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:28:07" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7095-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7095_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:28:08">http://theplumbinginfo.wordpress.com/2013/10/15/dealing-with-rusty-water/</link><title>Dealing with Rusty Water</title><description>Dealing with Rusty Water

15 Oct 2013 by theplumbinginfo on The Plumbing Info theplumbinginfo.wordpress.com/2013/10/15/dealing-with-rusty-water/

…  issue is more common for homes with private wells, high iron content is not limited to rural areas. Many suburban communities with a …  and cooking. Before we go into ways of treating iron in your water let’s get a little background on the different types of iron. …

Topics: Plumbing, Troubleshooting, rust, water</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7095-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7095_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:28:42">http://kirstynbarnett.wordpress.com/2014/01/10/chlorinated-water-supplies/</link><title>Chlorinated water supplies</title><description>Chlorinated water supplies

10 Jan 2014 by Kirstyn Barnett on Kirstyn Barnett kirstynbarnett.wordpress.com/2014/01/10/chlorinated-water-supplies/

…  from Pegasus residents about chlorine/metallic tastes in their water, I asked our Utilities &amp; Roading Manager for advice on what …  supplies.  The chlorine is used to remove manganese and iron in the raw water and is dosed into the water as it enters the plant.  The …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7095-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7095_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:29:05">http://drinkingwateradvisor.com/2011/08/13/iron-fortified-drinking-water-studies-for-the-prevention-of-childrens-anemia-in-developing-countries/</link><title>Iron-Fortified Drinking Water Studies for the Prevention of Children's Anemia in Developing Countries</title><description>Iron-Fortified Drinking Water Studies for the Prevention of Children's Anemia in Developing Countries

13 Aug 2011 by drinkingwateradvisor on The Drinking Water Advisor drinkingwateradvisor.com/2011/08/13/iron-fortified-drinking-water-studies-for-the-prevention-of-childrens-anemia-in-developing-countries/

…  is an interesting review article that discusses adding iron to drinking water to prevent childhood anemia in different situations, including preschool children in a day care center, …

Topics: health effects, Brazil, Iron, Anemia</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7095-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7095_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:29:32">http://luminouswatersolutions.wordpress.com/water-softeners-meadville-erie-pa/</link><title>Water Softeners</title><description>Water Softeners

9 Mar 2012 by luminouswater on Luminous Water Solutions luminouswatersolutions.wordpress.com/water-softeners-meadville-erie-pa/

Water Softeners remove iron (ferrous iron), hardness and Manganese in your water. The Kinetico series are sized by your water compensation, comes …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7095-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7095_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:29:57">http://corrosionmanagementsurvey.in/case-histories/</link><title>Case Histories</title><description>Case Histories

23 Aug 2010 by mvalliappan on Corrosion Management Survey in India corrosionmanagementsurvey.in/case-histories/

…  leaks pose contamination threat in Coimbatore, India COIMBATORE, JAN. 30. Leaks in drinking water and borewell water lines pose threat of contamination in the city. What …  took a bold decision and replaced their existing cast iron raw water rising main from the Mettur Dam reservoir with a stainless steel …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7095-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7095_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:30:23">http://picturestocktonarchive.wordpress.com/2012/12/04/the-town-house-stockton-c1865/</link><title>Stockton Town House c1865</title><description>Stockton Town House c1865

4 Dec 2012 by Picture Stockton Team on Picture Stockton Archive picturestocktonarchive.wordpress.com/2012/12/04/the-town-house-stockton-c1865/

…  civic building. The veranda was later replaced with a cast iron structure which has also been removed. Under this are the trestles for use in the market. The water pump seen in the foreground was part of the towns …

Topics: Stockton High Street</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7095-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7095_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:30:52">http://lgpynwzr.wordpress.com/2013/03/04/inexpensive-sunbeam-steam-master-iron-with-auto-sut-off-reviews/</link><title>Inexpensive Sunbeam Steam Master Iron with Auto Sut Off Reviews</title><description>Inexpensive Sunbeam Steam Master Iron with Auto Sut Off Reviews

4 Mar 2013 by lgpynwzr on lgpynwzr lgpynwzr.wordpress.com/2013/03/04/inexpensive-sunbeam-steam-master-iron-with-auto-sut-off-reviews/

…  Steam Master Iron with Auto Sut OffCLICK TO VIEW PRICES &gt;&gt;Sunbeam Steam Master Iron …  Value Successful? This posting seems to be at the ways in which you can improve your property with forged iron radiators. It focuses …  micro organism, mildew, and fungus on surfaces. Iron Water Filters Acquire Out Odor And Tint Inconveniences Drinking water …

Topics: Appliances, Travel (2)</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7095-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7095_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:31:19">http://archivesofmichigan.wordpress.com/2007/07/06/michigamme-reservoir/</link><title>Michigamme Reservoir</title><description>Michigamme Reservoir

6 Jul 2007 by Mark Harvey archivesofmichigan.wordpress.com/2007/07/06/michigamme-reservoir/

…  RESERVOIR (IRON COUNTY, MICHIGAN) Way Dam built in late 1930’s or early 1940’s. Wisconsin-Michigan Power Company, Mr. …  of the Brule and the Michigamme are discussed in the water power report in the Tenth Census of the United States (Vol. XVII) and …

Topics: Conservation</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7095-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7095_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:31:44">http://lgpynwzr.wordpress.com/2013/03/04/are-you-seeking-for-10-x-10-biosponge-plus-air-filter-refill-6-pack-one-year-supply-deals/</link><title>Are You Seeking for 10 x 10 BioSponge plus air filter refill (6 pack) One year supply Deals</title><description>Are You Seeking for 10 x 10 BioSponge plus air filter refill (6 pack) One year supply Deals

4 Mar 2013 by lgpynwzr on lgpynwzr lgpynwzr.wordpress.com/2013/03/04/are-you-seeking-for-10-x-10-biosponge-plus-air-filter-refill-6-pack-one-year-supply-deals/

…  air filter refill (6 pack) One year supply Selecting an Iron Filter is Just 50 % the Resolution As is apparent from the name, an iron …  H2o purification plays a incredibly vital element in maintain your well being. Folks have developed health acutely aware today …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7095-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7095_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:32:10">http://blog.precisionfiltration.com/2012/01/03/how-to-remove-bacteria-and-metal-hardness-from-your-water-supply/</link><title>How We Removed Bacteria and Metal from Water at a Funeral Home</title><description>How We Removed Bacteria and Metal from Water at a Funeral Home

3 Jan 2012 by Charlie Dinan at PFP on Precision Filtration Products blog.precisionfiltration.com/2012/01/03/how-to-remove-bacteria-and-metal-hardness-from-your-water-supply/

…  width="200" caption="EasyWater Iron Shield"][/caption] Have you ever had contaminated well-water at your home? How about "hard" public city water at the office? …  funeral home who had an issue with water contamination in his well-water supply. After a brief discussion, I learned that the well …

Topics: Filtration, water contamination, Water Filtration, water filtration, Liquid Filtration, Commercial &amp; Home Applications, funeral home, coliform, bacteria, Water Conditioning, public water, Well water, City Water, Water Testing, hard water, bacterial contamination, pipe scale, Iron</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>