<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7104">How to go from New York to Montreal</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:15:17" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7104-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7104_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:15:18">http://ilovebrunchandboots.org/2011/06/06/my-past-life-in-pictures-3/</link><title>My Past Life in Pictures 3</title><description>My Past Life in Pictures 3

6 Jun 2011 by DianaChristina7 on i love brunch &amp; boots ilovebrunchandboots.org/2011/06/06/my-past-life-in-pictures-3/

…  is for the Montreal Canadians. Go Habs. Go How a Chanel Bag is Made Pamphlet Gramercy Park Hotel Rooftop View of the Empire State Building from 230 5th Yankee Game Oysters from Flex Mussels Wine Barrels Sunflowers …

Topics: New York, Pictures]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7104-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7104_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:15:39">http://hardballtalk.nbcsports.com/2013/09/09/the-jays-and-mets-to-play-two-exhibition-games-in-montreal-next-spring/</link><title>The Jays and Mets to play two exhibition games in Montreal next spring</title><description>The Jays and Mets to play two exhibition games in Montreal next spring

9 Sep 2013 by Craig Calcaterra on HardballTalk hardballtalk.nbcsports.com/2013/09/09/the-jays-and-mets-to-play-two-exhibition-games-in-montreal-next-spring/

…  in Olympic Stadium in Montreal next spring: The contests, to be held right at the end of the pre-season, will bring big-league baseball …  been hearing lately. Which, no, I don't think will  go anywhere any time soon, but if you're the Jays you're better off …  happens. As for Montreal: I'm curious as to how Olympic Stadium is doing these …

Topics: Top Posts</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7104-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7104_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:17:01">http://foxlabjed.wordpress.com/2014/04/10/montreal-canadiens-vs-new-york-islanders-live/</link><title>Montreal Canadiens vs New York Islanders Live</title><description>Montreal Canadiens vs New York Islanders Live

10 Apr 2014 by foxlabjed on IT"S SHOW TIME foxlabjed.wordpress.com/2014/04/10/montreal-canadiens-vs-new-york-islanders-live/

…  installation process with thousands of sports channels to choose. Click here to Watch Watch this important match and enjoy …  additionally real against the Steelers, and look exactly how that turned out.There are a number of interesting creases in below. The …

Topics: Montreal Canadiens vs New York Islanders Live NHL Ice H, FOX, NBC, ESPN.Montreal Canadiens vs New York Islanders live stre, april 10, 2014 Kick Off Time : 7:30 pm (ET) live02 Don’t Miss t, live NHL Ice Hockey, NHL Live, nhl live online, watch NHL online So Watch and enjoy the Live Stream NHL, Montreal Canadiens vs New York Islanders basketballl, Montreal Canadiens vs New York Islanders live, Montreal Canadiens vs New York Islanders live online tv, See all the big matchs of the basketballl, abc, All events are showing Montreal Canadiens vs New York I, and if you want to watch the match on your TV and not y, android, Animal Planet, Apple, atdhe, AXN, Baseball, women's college basketball, BBC, Big Ten Network, Bing!, BTN, BTN2 TV here available. NHL Ice Hockey League 2014 seri</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7104-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7104_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:17:29">http://snyrangersblog.com/rangers/read-winning-in-montreal/</link><title>Read: Winning In Montreal</title><description>Read: Winning In Montreal

16 Jan 2012 by Adam Rotter on SNY Rangers Blog snyrangersblog.com/rangers/read-winning-in-montreal/

…  coverage.” Ryan Callahan told the NY Post, “We get to running around and don’t seem to be able to play the way we want to play.” Before the game, Brad Richards talked about how Montreal is his favorite building to play in. Lundqvist on his &amp; #NYR …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7104-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7104_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:18:03">http://brownscene.wordpress.com/2005/03/14/mont-real/</link><title>Mont REAL</title><description>Mont REAL

14 Mar 2005 by Leonard on BrownScene - Urban Filipino Cool brownscene.wordpress.com/2005/03/14/mont-real/

…  dieu. Je suis tres fatigue! On Saturday, I drove to Montreal to go see THIS. I was lucky enough to feel the stage and drop one …  to think that I want to step it up even another level, but how? The night ended off with a pleasant phone conversation about travelling, …

Topics: Stuff</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7104-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7104_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:18:25">http://foodanthro.com/2011/11/15/montreal-smoked-meat/</link><title>Montreal: Smoked Meat!</title><description>Montreal: Smoked Meat!

15 Nov 2011 by foodanthro on FoodAnthropology foodanthro.com/2011/11/15/montreal-smoked-meat/

…  obvious follow-up question, “where’s the best place to eat smoked meat?” “When you’re in Montreal, you must go to …  a final steaming before slicing and serving. Oh – and how is it different from pastrami? Let me turn to Montreal food writer and …

Topics: Anthropology, AAA meeting, anthropology, Culture, Heritage, AAA 2011 Montreal, montreal, smoked meat, Pastrami</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7104-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7104_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:18:57">http://offthemike.com/2011/04/22/comedy-business-talk-with-jeff-singer/</link><title>Comedy Business Talk with Jeff Singer</title><description>Comedy Business Talk with Jeff Singer

22 Apr 2011 by Mike Bobbitt on Off the Mike offthemike.com/2011/04/22/comedy-business-talk-with-jeff-singer/

…  my mind Jeff Singer has the dream job.  He gets to travel the country scouting comedy.  A lot of times he’s hitting …  bit to do with guests. Is your background performing or how did you get into this? JS: Well, I’m from Montreal as you know.  Did …

Topics: mike bobbitt, Comedy, comedian, off the mike, Jeff Singer, Just For Laughs, Interviews, Festivals</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7104-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7104_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:19:26">http://thresholdgirl.wordpress.com/2010/09/17/spin-on-immigration-1910/</link><title>Spin on Immigration 1910</title><description>Spin on Immigration 1910

17 Sep 2010 by Dorothy Nixon on My Montreal Stories - by Dorothy Nixon thresholdgirl.wordpress.com/2010/09/17/spin-on-immigration-1910/

Isle of Lewis Immigrants to Quebec (my husband's kin) Not quite sure who.Well, well, well. In 1911, …  journalist, but they only come to Canada to save money to go back home 'to their vinyards.' (Editor's note: Can I …  1910 article from Technical World Magazine, revealing how the Canadian Government was actively seeking Americans to immigrate to …

Topics: 1908 election results Canada; 1904 election results Can, Immigration Policy</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7104-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7104_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:20:00">http://themodelscoach.com/2013/07/15/strike-a-pose-there-is-nothing-to-it/</link><title>"Strike a Pose There is Nothing to it!</title><description>"Strike a Pose There is Nothing to it!

15 Jul 2013 by Naïad International on The Models' Coach - Naïad International themodelscoach.com/2013/07/15/strike-a-pose-there-is-nothing-to-it/

…  a Pose There is Nothing To It! Exactly like how the title states, I recently had the pleasure of …  Jérôme Bel’s critically-acclaimed run of The Show Must Go On, in Vienna.   That is wonderful, truly making you well experienced in …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7104-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7104_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:20:31">http://ongoalanalysis.wordpress.com/2013/05/02/nhl-predictive-playoff-analysis-2-may/</link><title>NHL Predictive Playoff Analysis – 2 May</title><description>NHL Predictive Playoff Analysis – 2 May

3 May 2013 by The Colonel on The OGA Blogs ongoalanalysis.wordpress.com/2013/05/02/nhl-predictive-playoff-analysis-2-may/

…  Conference team calls and the Conference rollup. So how does OGA do this? On 1 May, we provided one half of the Eastern …  forget –it’s the chase for “3.” The first team to it wins the vast majority of the time. No. 2 Montreal Versus No. 7 …  Pittsburgh, and Toronto at Montreal Kinda makes you go Hmmmm… Doesn’t it? We will see. Periodic updates come as the Round …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>