<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7108">renting car seattle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:38:48" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7108-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7108_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:38:49">http://speakterence.wordpress.com/2011/11/15/500/</link><title>500</title><description>500

15 Nov 2011 by speakterence on Terence at Work speakterence.wordpress.com/2011/11/15/500/

…  weekend in Vancouver, Seattle, and Victoria. Had to rent a car for the time there and Michelle had this fascination about renting a Fiat so here it is, our dope ass rental. After a bit …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7108-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7108_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:39:24">http://notjustseattle.wordpress.com/2007/10/02/local-news-no-rental-tax-for-flexcar-for-now-seattle-times-newspaper/</link><title>Local News | No rental tax for Flexcar — for now | Seattle Times Newspaper</title><description>Local News | No rental tax for Flexcar — for now | Seattle Times Newspaper

2 Oct 2007 by Carl on Not Just Seattle - Old Site notjustseattle.wordpress.com/2007/10/02/local-news-no-rental-tax-for-flexcar-for-now-seattle-times-newspaper/

…  Times NewspaperThe notion that Flexcar is in the rental car business is similar to saying a condominium is in the rental house …  difference. With Flexcars, they're timesharing, not renting. I'm surprised that this critical difference hasn't been …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7108-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7108_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:39:51">http://mahaslaztelevision.com/2014/02/27/mashariki-rent-a-car-seattle/</link><title>MASHARIKI RENT A CAR \- SEATTLE</title><description>MASHARIKI RENT A CAR \- SEATTLE

27 Feb 2014 by MAHASLAZ TEAM on MAHASLAZ TV mahaslaztelevision.com/2014/02/27/mashariki-rent-a-car-seattle/

…  interview with the Founder and C.E.O of Mashariki Rent A Car. A car renting business that is based in Seattle Washington. Get to know how he got …

Topics: the scope, GROWTH OF BUSINESS IN KENYA, the scope, thescope, mahaslaz</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7108-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7108_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:40:28">http://eigenblogger.com/2009/02/27/post1034/</link><title>UBC</title><description>UBC

27 Feb 2009 by Claudia on Eigenblogger eigenblogger.com/2009/02/27/post1034/

…  in Canada, bitches! After flying to Seattle and then renting a car to drive to Vancouver (weather problems were a factor, which is why we …

Topics: grad school, Canada, School1, UBC</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7108-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7108_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:40:55">http://canadianveggie.wordpress.com/car-free-weekend-trips/</link><title>Car-Free Weekend Trips</title><description>Car-Free Weekend Trips

28 May 2011 by canadianveggie on Canadian Veggie canadianveggie.wordpress.com/car-free-weekend-trips/

…  non car owners, Emily and I are always trying to find weekend trips we can take that can be done car-free. We don't mind renting vehicles, or using Modo vehicles, but it's cheaper and greener to …  Island Salt Spring Island Victoria Portland Seattle More ideas at Car-Free Vancouver [googlemaps …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7108-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7108_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:41:27">http://chrissopa.wordpress.com/2010/04/17/journey-west/</link><title>Journey West</title><description>Journey West

17 Apr 2010 by Chris Sopa International, Inc. on Chris Sopa's Blog chrissopa.wordpress.com/2010/04/17/journey-west/

…  May 9th.  I will be flying into Grand Junction, Colorado, renting a car and then driving (taking my time, of course) west to Seattle, WA where I …

Topics: Journey West</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7108-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7108_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:42:00">http://internexcanada.wordpress.com/2012/07/05/smartsaver-vancouver-zipcar/</link><title>SmartSaver Vancouver - Zipcar</title><description>SmartSaver Vancouver - Zipcar

5 Jul 2012 by Katie on INTERNeX Canada internexcanada.wordpress.com/2012/07/05/smartsaver-vancouver-zipcar/

…  if we wanted to make it to Seattle 3 days. We decided that renting a car would be the best option. All of us expected that renting a car would be …

Topics: INTERNeX, Fun, Vancouver, Canada, summer, Seattle, experience?, Music, Night, fireworks, 2012, Independence Day</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7108-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7108_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:42:41">http://invisibletracks.wordpress.com/2012/09/07/packing-to-go-south-for-the-winter/</link><title>Packing to go south for the winter</title><description>Packing to go south for the winter

7 Sep 2012 by Larry on Invisible Tracks invisibletracks.wordpress.com/2012/09/07/packing-to-go-south-for-the-winter/

…  are renting a place in Boise, ID this winter so we contacted Alaska Marine …  facility. Then they put our container on a railroad car to Whittier where was it then put on this huge 450 ft long and 100 ft …  Arctic Titan, here next to the barge, will tow it to Seattle.  The barge carries large truck shipping containers on the top level …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7108-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7108_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:43:26">http://literaryitinerary.wordpress.com/2010/09/20/my-epic-road-trip/</link><title>My Epic Road Trip</title><description>My Epic Road Trip

20 Sep 2010 by literaryitinerary on intentionally living literaryitinerary.wordpress.com/2010/09/20/my-epic-road-trip/

…  had a dream of driving the entire length of I-90 from Seattle, WA to Boston, MA. At just over three thousand miles, it is the …  course, I wouldn't want to drive my own car for this trip as that would mean putting over six thousand miles on it by …  time all was said and done. Instead, I would look in to renting a car here in Seattle and returning it to a rental car facility in …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7108-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7108_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:43:55">http://rascaljain44.wordpress.com/2014/01/17/3-advantages-of-renting-a-charter-bus-during-your-trip-to-seattle/</link><title>3 Advantages of Renting a Charter Bus during Your Trip to Seattle</title><description>3 Advantages of Renting a Charter Bus during Your Trip to Seattle

17 Jan 2014 by rascaljain Blogs on Rascal jain Blogs rascaljain44.wordpress.com/2014/01/17/3-advantages-of-renting-a-charter-bus-during-your-trip-to-seattle/

…  the city by public transportation or you prefer to rent a car or other form of transport.Seattle is a great base for day trips to the beautiful natural attractions of the region, so renting a form of transport can be a great idea if you want to enjoy …

Topics: seattle charter bus company</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>