<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7109">best place to eat pho in new york</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:44:21" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7109-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7109_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:44:22">http://foodiesuztravels.wordpress.com/2011/10/23/where-i-eat-in-edmonton/</link><title>where i eat in edmonton</title><description>where i eat in edmonton

24 Oct 2011 by sue robins on foodie suz travels foodiesuztravels.wordpress.com/2011/10/23/where-i-eat-in-edmonton/

…  where I'd direct folks from out-of-town to eat... Best breakfast with friends – New York Bagel Cafe Best place to take teenage kids – Sugarbowl Best family friendly burger joint …

Topics: Edmonton</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7109-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7109_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:44:42">http://twickerati.wordpress.com/2012/04/20/best-chinese-thai-in-twickenham/</link><title>Best Chinese or Thai in Twickenham. You tell us.</title><description>Best Chinese or Thai in Twickenham. You tell us.

20 Apr 2012 by twickerati on twickerati twickerati.wordpress.com/2012/04/20/best-chinese-thai-in-twickenham/

…  is required. We’ve previously established Twickenham’s best Indian restaurant, where the best Italian food is to be found and which is …  “your personal favourite”) but what about the best place for crispy duck pancakes, or pad thai or pho? Whether it’s eat in or …

Topics: Twickenham, Twickenham Green, Reviews, Reviews of Reviews, Food &amp; Drink, Food &amp; Drink</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7109-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7109_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:45:25">http://carloscuisine.com/2013/07/30/eat-pho-or-else/</link><title>Eat Phở Or Else!</title><description>Eat Phở Or Else!

30 Jul 2013 by carloscuisine on Carlos Cuisine carloscuisine.com/2013/07/30/eat-pho-or-else/

…  you walk into a Vietnamese restaurant to pick up a menu, and the cover says "Hungry in South Florida? Eat Phở or else!", you know you just have to go back and try it.  A …  of nước chấm, or nuoc cham) was perhaps one of the best ones I've had in South Florida - the combination of fish sauce, lime, …

Topics: Florida, Broward, sunrise, Vietnamese Cuisine, vietnamese, bun bo hue, pho, pho 78, Banh Mi, salted plum soda</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7109-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7109_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:45:57">http://literarylotus.com/2010/09/07/food-spotting-what-hawaii-chefs-eat/</link><title>Food Spotting: What Hawai'i Chefs Eat</title><description>Food Spotting: What Hawai'i Chefs Eat

7 Sep 2010 by literarylotus on LITERARY LOTUS literarylotus.com/2010/09/07/food-spotting-what-hawaii-chefs-eat/

…  asks Melanie Kosaka is where do Hawai'i's chefs eat? After talking with good friend and Hawai'i’s master sommelier …  the What Chefs Eat iPhone app. "We don’t need to know the 50 pizza places close to us, we want to know the top three, …  users have to do is choose a chef or category, like best late night spot, and up pops their photo and brief, geo-targeted …

Topics: hawaii people, Food</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7109-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7109_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:46:28">http://voxxi.com/2013/09/25/best-places-to-eat-in-new-york-city-in-2013/</link><title>Best places to eat in New York City in 2013</title><description>Best places to eat in New York City in 2013

25 Sep 2013 by lavoxfbeccaglia on Voxxi voxxi.com/2013/09/25/best-places-to-eat-in-new-york-city-in-2013/

…  you visiting New York with a strong desire to taste the best bites of this international culinary mecca? If so, and …  to choose from. And if you like small plates, this is your place. Order the traditional way or a few mezze and try it …

Topics: Culinary, restaurant reviews</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7109-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7109_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:47:13">http://reddylive.wordpress.com/2009/09/20/the-50-best-things-to-eat-in-the-world-and-where-to-eat-them/</link><title>The 50 best things to eat in the world, and where to eat them</title><description>The 50 best things to eat in the world, and where to eat them

20 Sep 2009 by reddylive on hanmi reddy journal reddylive.wordpress.com/2009/09/20/the-50-best-things-to-eat-in-the-world-and-where-to-eat-them/

…  PriceThe 50 best things to eat in the world, and where to eat them1. Best place to eat: Oysters.Strangfor Lough, Northern IrelandOysters over ice Richard …

Topics: The 50 best things to eat in the world, and where to eat them</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7109-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7109_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:47:41">http://eatclub.wordpress.com/2008/08/05/pho-viet-huong-072908/</link><title>Pho Viet Huong - 07.29.08</title><description>Pho Viet Huong - 07.29.08

6 Aug 2008 by Bruce Lee on EATCLUB eatclub.wordpress.com/2008/08/05/pho-viet-huong-072908/

…  and sour chicken) The Short and Sweet Probably the best (and only) pho I had in Chinatown.  Due to diet restrictions, I had to …  tastes pretty good. Sophia gives a "9.2 as a pho place." [vimeo 1475107] "Mphrawhahgq" means roll this spring …

Topics: Meetings, vietnamese, chinatown, pho</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7109-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7109_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:48:26">http://1000dinnersnyc.com/2011/11/01/54-baoguette-cafe-pho-is-the-new-chicken-noodle/</link><title>#54 - Baoguette Cafe - Pho is the new chicken noodle</title><description>#54 - Baoguette Cafe - Pho is the new chicken noodle

1 Nov 2011 by 1000dinners on 1000dinners 1000dinnersnyc.com/2011/11/01/54-baoguette-cafe-pho-is-the-new-chicken-noodle/

…  containing tomato sauce. Enter Baoguette Cafe, and the best soup for a cold gross day. Pho. Pronounced Fuh! It’s meal worthy in … =s_q&amp;hl=en&amp;geocode=&amp;q=Baoguette,+37+Saint+Marks+Place,+New+York,+NY+10003&amp;aq=0&amp;sll=40.730187,-74.000408&amp;sspn=0.01941 …

Topics: east village, Baoguette Cafe, St. Marks, Asiany Noodles, $</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7109-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7109_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:49:10">http://btypes.com/2012/11/08/the-pho-guide/</link><title>The Pho Guide</title><description>The Pho Guide

8 Nov 2012 by btypes on btypes btypes.com/2012/11/08/the-pho-guide/

…  of this post trying to come up with a catchy title: Best Pho Pho-Real Pho-bulous Pho Pho-king Awesome Pho Un-Pho-gettable …  pho or who may have been wondering where the best new place to go might be, I have ranked and described my favorite places to get …

Topics: Food, Drinks, RVA, restaurant reviews, Richmond, VA, Community, Pho So 1, Vietnam - 1, Tay Do, pho tay do, Mekong, mekong rva, hyunh's, pho, vietnamese richmond, vietnamese food richmond va</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7109-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7109_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:50:11">http://areyouchasingamy.com/2013/01/06/hong-kongs-insatiable-appetite/</link><title>Food Glorious Food - Hong Kong's insatiable appetite</title><description>Food Glorious Food - Hong Kong's insatiable appetite

6 Jan 2013 by amylouisepeel on Chasing Amy areyouchasingamy.com/2013/01/06/hong-kongs-insatiable-appetite/

…  the corners for the good places, people waiting to get the best Vietnamese pho or Japanese Ramen, dumplings in demand and people pining …  and visitor, to eat, to indulge, to find the new trendy place, the traditional favourite and I wanted to try as many as I could.  For …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>