<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7111">what is the starting salary for a recruiter</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:56:06" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7111-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7111_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:56:07">http://jefflipschultz.wordpress.com/2011/09/27/negotiating-your-starting-salary/</link><title>Negotiating Your Starting Salary</title><description>Negotiating Your Starting Salary

27 Sep 2011 by jefflipschultz on Jeff Lipschultz's Blog jefflipschultz.wordpress.com/2011/09/27/negotiating-your-starting-salary/

…  an employer asks you what your salary expectations are during the early stages of the interviewing process, you are trained to say you are …  When working with an external recruiter, the process is slightly different.  Read this article I wrote for Job-Hunt.org to …

Topics: Job Search, Interviewing 101, Job-Hunt.org article, working with recruiters</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7111-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7111_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:56:30">http://equalpaynegotiations.com/2012/10/02/the-players-in-the-game-of-salary-negotiations/</link><title>The Players in the Game of Salary Negotiations</title><description>The Players in the Game of Salary Negotiations

2 Oct 2012 by Katie Donovan on Equal Pay Negotiations LLC equalpaynegotiations.com/2012/10/02/the-players-in-the-game-of-salary-negotiations/

…  paid by the companies not be candidates.  Their payment is based on a percentage of the first year salary of the candidate hired by the …  final decision. The hiring manager ultimately decides what to offer as the starting salary as well.   This is because more often …

Topics: women negotiating</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7111-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7111_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:57:00">http://enstructive.wordpress.com/2013/12/23/salary/</link><title>Salary</title><description>Salary

23 Dec 2013 by enstructive on enstructive enstructive.wordpress.com/2013/12/23/salary/

…  the end of his job interview, the personal recruiter asked the young engineer fresh out of college, “And, what starting salary were you looking for?” The engineer said, “In the …

Topics: Engineers</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7111-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7111_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:57:39">http://idseye.com/2013/05/23/graduate-recruitment-rises-pay-remains-flat/</link><title>Graduate recruitment rises, pay remains flat</title><description>Graduate recruitment rises, pay remains flat

23 May 2013 by Adam Cohen on IDS eye - blog from Incomes Data Services idseye.com/2013/05/23/graduate-recruitment-rises-pay-remains-flat/

…  there will be more demand for graduates this year, this is not being translated into significantly improved starting salaries. Our …  average year-on-year increases at individual companies. What we found  was that 72 per cent of employers are not planning to increase …

Topics: Graduates, Graduate recruitment, graduate pay</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7111-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7111_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:58:07">http://topcareergurublog.wordpress.com/2013/11/20/negotiating-salary/</link><title>The Interviewer is Not Your Mum!</title><description>The Interviewer is Not Your Mum!

20 Nov 2013 by topcareerguru on Find a Job - Create A Great CV - Be Prepared for Tough Interview Questions - Find a Job You Love!! topcareergurublog.wordpress.com/2013/11/20/negotiating-salary/

…  and Job Hunting Tips[/caption] The recruiter is not your mum...so if your house hold costs are too high for the job you are …  disaster could hit at any point, so it's best to do what you can and control the things you can control, be as well prepared as you …

Topics: Career Tips, interview skills, Dealing With Tough Interview Questions, Great Career Advice, Recruitment, Find a Job!, Interviewing Skills, Interview, find job, job interview, Interview preparation, Salary</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7111-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7111_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:58:36">http://mastrheadhunter.wordpress.com/2013/10/14/the-value-added-services-of-a-professional-executive-recruiter/</link><title>The Value Added Services of a Professional Executive Recruiter</title><description>The Value Added Services of a Professional Executive Recruiter

14 Oct 2013 by coreylewis3369 on MastrHeadHunter mastrheadhunter.wordpress.com/2013/10/14/the-value-added-services-of-a-professional-executive-recruiter/

…  questions and/or make the following statements… What is your fee? You’re fee is too high. You are an expensive recruiter, I …

Topics: odds &amp; ends</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7111-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7111_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:59:22">http://getalegup.wordpress.com/2010/12/09/how-to-handle-the-salary-question/</link><title>How to handle "The Salary Question"</title><description>How to handle "The Salary Question"

9 Dec 2010 by Charlie Anderson on Get a Leg Up getalegup.wordpress.com/2010/12/09/how-to-handle-the-salary-question/

…  some point during the interview process, the recruiter will ask either "What's your current salary?" or "What are your salary …  no great way to answer this question.  Honesty is the best policy, but there are shades of grey, especially if asked the …

Topics: Tips &amp; Tricks, All posts, Interviewing, Job Search, Compensation</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7111-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7111_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:59:44">http://deltadallas.wordpress.com/2011/03/16/salary-negotiation-mwah-ah-ah-ah/</link><title>Salary Negotiation [Mwah-ah-ah-ah!]</title><description>Salary Negotiation [Mwah-ah-ah-ah!]

16 Mar 2011 by deltadallas on Delta Dallas deltadallas.wordpress.com/2011/03/16/salary-negotiation-mwah-ah-ah-ah/

…  a win-win situation between candidates and employers. What do you do, though, if you don’t have a recruiter working on your behalf? What if the offer made to you is a little low? Do you just take it and hope for a raise at your yearly …

Topics: Salary, Business, Employment - Finding a Job, interviews, Personal Responsibility, Compensation, Employer, Interview, Salary Negotiation, salary, salary requirement, Pay, New Job</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7111-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7111_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:00:25">http://fecak.com/recruiting/</link><title>Recruiting</title><description>Recruiting

30 Mar 2012 by fecak on Fecak.com fecak.com/recruiting/

…  them build great teams. We want to find the candidate that is not only a fit for your technical environment, but also the one that will …  and we feel our competitive advantage is insight into what technologists truly want. What is Engaged Search? Most recruiters work …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7111-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7111_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:01:01">http://chrispgtimedia.wordpress.com/2013/01/15/unreal-starting-salaries-just-one-more-kick-in-the-teeth/</link><title>Unreal starting salaries just one more kick in the teeth</title><description>Unreal starting salaries just one more kick in the teeth

15 Jan 2013 by Chris Phillips on Chris Phillips - GTI Media chrispgtimedia.wordpress.com/2013/01/15/unreal-starting-salaries-just-one-more-kick-in-the-teeth/

…  I could go on but you get the point. It's what I have learnt to call a challenging recruitment market for the thousands …  can see why they do this at least.What really gets my goat is the public parading of 'facts' about the market as though they …

Topics: graduate jobs, Recruitment, recruitment, graduate recruitment, Discrimination, starting salaries</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>