<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7116">pumpkin pie recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:22:11" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7116-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7116_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:22:13">http://keitochansays.com/2013/11/14/10-holiday-pumpkin-recipes/</link><title>10 Holiday Pumpkin Recipes</title><description>10 Holiday Pumpkin Recipes

14 Nov 2013 by Keitochan Says: on Keitochan Says: keitochansays.com/2013/11/14/10-holiday-pumpkin-recipes/

…  Spicy Pumpkin Hummus This tasty Spicy Pumpkin Hummus is sure to be a hit this fall, …  pepper if you want it even spicier; as with any hummus recipe, the ingredients can be adjusted until you get the flavor you …  always gets me if the fall mood and tastes like a pumpkin pie in a cup. Yum! Breakfast 3\. Pumpkin Waffles Pumpkin Waffles are the …

Topics: Food &amp; Drinks, Spices, Lunch &amp; Dinner, breakfast, beverages, Appetizers, Holidays, Fall, pumpkin, Miscellaneous, Food, Sides, Desserts, Bread, winter, pumpkin pie, canned pumpkin, more Holidays, Salads, Soup, spice, Dinner, lunch, Spicy Pumpkin Hummus, Soup, pumpkin spice latte, Holiday, pumpkin recipe, Beverages (2), sides</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7116-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7116_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:22:54">http://petalsblog.com/2013/09/26/pumpkin-spice-custard-pie-oh-my/</link><title>Pumpkin Spice Custard Pie \- Oh My!</title><description>Pumpkin Spice Custard Pie \- Oh My!

26 Sep 2013 by bspetals on petalsblogdotcom petalsblog.com/2013/09/26/pumpkin-spice-custard-pie-oh-my/

…  saying the name of this recipe gets us excited about Fall!  We are fortunate in Kansas City to be able …  recipe does not fall short!  With three easy steps, this pie can be whipped up for your next Sunday …  what you will need:1 Pumpkin Pumpkin Pie Cheeseball Mix3 eggs, beaten1 cup sugar2 tbs. flour1/2 cup …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7116-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7116_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:23:21">http://fatcrabcrafts.wordpress.com/2013/09/19/pumpkin-pie-cake-recipe/</link><title>Pumpkin Pie Cake Recipe</title><description>Pumpkin Pie Cake Recipe

19 Sep 2013 by Fat Crab Crafts on Fat Crab Crafts fatcrabcrafts.wordpress.com/2013/09/19/pumpkin-pie-cake-recipe/

…  on the horizon I could not wait to dive into something pumpkin.  I  found this recipe on Pinterest and I followed the pic to SixSistersStuff who I am giving …  recipes.  http://www.sixsistersstuff.com/2013/09/pumpkin-pie-cake-recipe.html Here is the recipe as copied from their …

Topics: pumpkin, cake, pie, recipe, cooking, Fall, Thanksgiving, desert, sweets, Dinner, Recipes, fall thanksgiving, pumpkin pie, evaporated milk, Teaspoon, splenda, Pinterest</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7116-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7116_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:23:55">http://granniesrecipebox.wordpress.com/2013/10/02/pecan-pumpkin-pie-recipe/</link><title>Pecan Pumpkin Pie Recipe</title><description>Pecan Pumpkin Pie Recipe

2 Oct 2013 by margielynn on Grannies Recipe Box granniesrecipebox.wordpress.com/2013/10/02/pecan-pumpkin-pie-recipe/

Pecan Pumpkin Pie is a great meeting of pumpkin and pecans. It is a little different from the traditional pumpkin pie, but different is good sometimes. This is a very easy pie to make, especially if you buy your pie crust, like I do! Enjoy.

Topics: Food, Dessert, pie, Pecan, Pecan Pumpkin Pie, pumpkin recipe</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7116-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7116_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:24:15">http://granniesrecipebox.wordpress.com/2013/12/14/pumpkin-custard-pie-recipe/</link><title>Pumpkin Custard Pie Recipe</title><description>Pumpkin Custard Pie Recipe

14 Dec 2013 by margielynn on Grannies Recipe Box granniesrecipebox.wordpress.com/2013/12/14/pumpkin-custard-pie-recipe/

Pumpkin Custard Pie is always a requested dessert at our house at Thanksgiving and Christmas. It is my son and husband's favorite pie. This recipe calls for allspice and ginger, but I do not put it in my pies. I just dump some extra cinnamon in!

Topics: recipe, Food, Dessert, pie, pumpkin custard pie, pumpkin pie</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7116-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7116_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:24:38">http://sarahtrumbley.wordpress.com/2013/10/09/pumpkin-pie-recipe/</link><title>Pumpkin Pie Recipe</title><description>Pumpkin Pie Recipe

9 Oct 2013 by sarahtrumbley on Adventures in Sugarland sarahtrumbley.wordpress.com/2013/10/09/pumpkin-pie-recipe/</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7116-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7116_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:25:10">http://news.health.com/2013/11/27/5-recipes-for-pumpkin-pie-pumpkin-cheesecake-and-more/</link><title>5 Recipes for Pumpkin Pie, Pumpkin Cheesecake, and More</title><description>5 Recipes for Pumpkin Pie, Pumpkin Cheesecake, and More

27 Nov 2013 by Ashley Macha on Health News / Tips &amp; Trends / Celebrity Health news.health.com/2013/11/27/5-recipes-for-pumpkin-pie-pumpkin-cheesecake-and-more/

…  thought so. This Thanksgiving just make sure you sneak a pumpkin dessert in there somewhere. (That's not too tough, is …  to puddings and more. Pumpkin and Carmelized-Pecan Pie Add some crunch (and protein) to a classic pumpkin pie by adding …  322. Fat: 22 grams. Fiber: 3 grams. Try this recipe: Pumpkin and Carmelized-Pecan Pie Pumpkin Cheesecake with Glazed …

Topics: News &amp; Views, Recipes, Thanksgiving, Dessert, pumpkin</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7116-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7116_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:25:58">http://healthstaging.wordpress.com/2008/11/21/most-delicious/</link><title>Most Delicious Time of the Year</title><description>Most Delicious Time of the Year

21 Nov 2008 by Health Editor on Health.com Staging healthstaging.wordpress.com/2008/11/21/most-delicious/

…  bring some kind of dessert.  Apparently they have a pumpkin pie recipe that they're bringing back into the dessert rotation, one with …

Topics: Holidays</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7116-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7116_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:26:36">http://hunttherecipe.wordpress.com/2008/11/05/pumpkin-bars/</link><title>Pumpkin Pie Bars</title><description>Pumpkin Pie Bars

5 Nov 2008 by Parsnip on Hunt the Recipe hunttherecipe.wordpress.com/2008/11/05/pumpkin-bars/

…  never made pumpkin pie before, what with my fear of pie crust and because someone has always made …  some for an election night party Cauli and I went to. This recipe calls for a shortbread-type crust, rather than a typical pie crust …

Topics: Dessert</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7116-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7116_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:27:06">http://lilyphotography-blog.com/2013/11/21/thanksgiving-recipes/</link><title>{Thanksgiving Recipes}</title><description>{Thanksgiving Recipes}

21 Nov 2013 by lilyphoto on Lily Photography by Elizabeth Chandler | Twin Falls, Idaho lilyphotography-blog.com/2013/11/21/thanksgiving-recipes/

…  align="aligncenter" width="360"] {Pumpkin Pie Recipes (Toffee-Almond Crunch Pumpkin Pie)}[/caption] [caption …  {Tastes Like Thanksgiving Casserole ~ This recipe is: Contest Winning}[/caption] [caption id="" …

Topics: Inspiration, Recipes, Holiday Inspiration</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>