<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7123">raleigh bike</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:59:16" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7123-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7123_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:59:17">http://raleighuk.wordpress.com/2012/08/09/raleigh-shortlisted-for-bikebiz-awards/</link><title>Raleigh shortlisted for Bikebiz awards</title><description>Raleigh shortlisted for Bikebiz awards

9 Aug 2012 by raleighuk on Raleigh News raleighuk.wordpress.com/2012/08/09/raleigh-shortlisted-for-bikebiz-awards/

Raleigh UK has been shortlisted in two categories at this year's Bikebiz bicycle industry awards - Bike Distributor (Marketing) and Bike Brand. In the Bike Distributor (Marketing) category Raleigh highlighted two successful campaigns, its 125th year anniversary …

Topics: cycling, Cycling, Raleigh, raleigh bikes, Raleigh Chopper, bikebiz, award, Marketing, manager, Birmingham, NEC, 125 Years</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7123-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7123_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:59:55">http://raleighuk.wordpress.com/2012/03/22/cycling-weeklys-top-50/</link><title>Cycling Weekly's Top 50</title><description>Cycling Weekly's Top 50

22 Mar 2012 by raleighuk on Raleigh News raleighuk.wordpress.com/2012/03/22/cycling-weeklys-top-50/

…  featuring the 50 Greatest Bikes of All Time in which our Raleigh bikes feature a remarkable SEVEN times! From the 1950s we have Red Harris' 1954 track bike and Ray Booty's Raleigh Record Ace from 1956. Then we have Carlton …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7123-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7123_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:00:25">http://raleighuk.wordpress.com/2012/02/22/raleigh-celebrates-125-years-with-the-launch-of-me-my-raleigh-photo-gallery/</link><title>Raleigh celebrates 125 years with the launch of Me &amp; My Raleigh photo gallery</title><description>Raleigh celebrates 125 years with the launch of Me &amp; My Raleigh photo gallery

22 Feb 2012 by raleighuk on Raleigh News raleighuk.wordpress.com/2012/02/22/raleigh-celebrates-125-years-with-the-launch-of-me-my-raleigh-photo-gallery/

Raleigh is marking its status as one of the world’s oldest bike companies by launching an online image gallery – Me &amp; My Raleigh – designed to celebrate the illustrious history of the iconic Raleigh …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7123-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7123_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:00:56">http://casbahcicloclub.com/2011/07/18/luciano/</link><title>luciano</title><description>luciano

18 Jul 2011 by casbahcicloclub on casbahcicloclub casbahcicloclub.com/2011/07/18/luciano/

…  raleigh Luciano portrayed with his Raleigh we don't know much about Raleigh bikes, we aren't that …  of residence: Milano occupation: craftsman bike model: legendary Raleigh bike, I think is a women one... likely the model …

Topics: bikes, Peoples, Bike, Raleigh, MiLan</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7123-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7123_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:01:36">http://raleighuk.wordpress.com/2014/01/17/new-raleigh-motus-electric-bikes-land-in-nottingham/</link><title>New Raleigh Motus electric bikes land in Nottingham</title><description>New Raleigh Motus electric bikes land in Nottingham

17 Jan 2014 by raleighuk on Raleigh News raleighuk.wordpress.com/2014/01/17/new-raleigh-motus-electric-bikes-land-in-nottingham/

…  into the Raleigh UK office this week comes the sleek and sophisticated Raleigh Motus electric bike. Raleigh has joined forces with e-bike technology front-runners Bosch …

Topics: cycling, ebike, Raleigh Motus electric bike, e-bike</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7123-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7123_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:02:08">http://bottombracket.wordpress.com/2008/03/14/_15/</link><title>_15</title><description>_15

14 Mar 2008 by withoutthought on bottombracket bottombracket.wordpress.com/2008/03/14/_15/

…  Cranks One of the most noted features of the original Raleigh bikes is talked about in Gregory Bowden's book 'Raleigh Cycles'. The 'tubular fork-crown' owed itself to new …  The tubular crown fork may have meant that a Raleigh bike could easily be singled out in a group of similar looking black …

Topics: History, raleigh cranks, tubular fork-crown, Gregory H. Bowden</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7123-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7123_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:02:39">http://raleighuk.wordpress.com/2012/08/08/gold-medal-discounts-on-raleigh-bikes/</link><title>Gold medal discounts on Raleigh bikes</title><description>Gold medal discounts on Raleigh bikes

8 Aug 2012 by raleighuk on Raleigh News raleighuk.wordpress.com/2012/08/08/gold-medal-discounts-on-raleigh-bikes/

…  recent gold medal success by British athletes in London, Raleigh is offering 30% off selected bikes in its touring and leisure …  off. These exclusive offers are only available through www.raleigh.co.uk while stocks last. Raleigh Urban range Raleigh Urban …

Topics: cycling, Raleigh, 2012, gold medal discounts, bike sale, summer, Olympics</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7123-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7123_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:03:07">http://centcotoli.wordpress.com/2013/11/18/raleigh-chill-mountain-bike/</link><title>Raleigh Chill Mountain Bike</title><description>Raleigh Chill Mountain Bike

18 Nov 2013 by centcotoli on Bangladeshi Khanki Magi Photo centcotoli.wordpress.com/2013/11/18/raleigh-chill-mountain-bike/

Raleigh Chill Mountain BikeRaleigh Chill Mountain Bike Savings! Save every month on your cable billfind everything. And free …  absolutely beautiful custom humidors, display, large and raleigh chill mountain bike. Represent consumer interests in congress, the …

Topics: Raleigh Chill Mountain Bike</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7123-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7123_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:03:17">http://raleighuk.wordpress.com/2012/09/27/raleigh-at-the-nec-cycle-show-day-1/</link><title>Raleigh at the NEC Cycle Show - day 1</title><description>Raleigh at the NEC Cycle Show - day 1

27 Sep 2012 by raleighuk on Raleigh News raleighuk.wordpress.com/2012/09/27/raleigh-at-the-nec-cycle-show-day-1/

Raleigh branded entrance way with Team Raleigh-GAC car? Check. Massive Raleigh stand near the entrance way? …  all looking great? Check. Most of the top independent bike shops in the country passing through our stand and our presentation rooms? …

Topics: cycling</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7123-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7123_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:03:42">http://raleighuk.wordpress.com/2013/09/12/raleigh-celebrates-cycle-to-work-day/</link><title>Raleigh celebrates Cycle To Work Day</title><description>Raleigh celebrates Cycle To Work Day

12 Sep 2013 by raleighuk on Raleigh News raleighuk.wordpress.com/2013/09/12/raleigh-celebrates-cycle-to-work-day/

…  Cycle To Work day and it's a cause that we at Raleigh UK think is worth championing. [caption id="" …  width="625"] Cycle commuters at Raleigh's Nottingham site...[/caption] At Raleigh we see Cycle to Work …  To Work day, to offer a fantastic Raleigh Revenio 2 road bike as a prize for pledging to ride today. We're also offering a special …

Topics: Cycling, Raleigh, bikes, cycling, Nottingham, cycle to work day</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>