<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7125">psychological effects of obesity in children</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:09:49" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7125-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7125_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:09:50">http://obesityprevention.wordpress.com/2008/01/13/the-effects-of-childhood-obesity-can-be-traumatic/</link><title>The Effects Of Childhood Obesity Can Be Traumatic</title><description>The Effects Of Childhood Obesity Can Be Traumatic

13 Jan 2008 by naekokori on Obesity and Prevention obesityprevention.wordpress.com/2008/01/13/the-effects-of-childhood-obesity-can-be-traumatic/

…  in children is a very serious issue. The effects of childhood obesity can have health and social consequences that continue into …  The effects of childhood obesity range from major psychological problems to serious health issues and chronic social …

Topics: health, Children, obesity, causes of obesity, Treatment, Nutrition, Family, Food, Fast Food, Coffee, Kitchen, parent, young children, Child, Baby, healthy</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7125-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7125_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:10:19">http://psuec.wordpress.com/2012/02/04/psychological-causes-of-childhood-obesity/</link><title>Psychological Causes of Childhood Obesity</title><description>Psychological Causes of Childhood Obesity

4 Feb 2012 by psuec on psuec psuec.wordpress.com/2012/02/04/psychological-causes-of-childhood-obesity/

…  is debatable whether psychological issues suffered by obese children are factors of their obesity or symptoms of it. While it is widely thought that genetics are a …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7125-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7125_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:10:45">http://oakridgeinternational.wordpress.com/2012/11/16/childhood-obesity-becoming-a-mental-dilemma-for-kids/</link><title>Childhood Obesity, Becoming a Mental Dilemma for Kids.</title><description>Childhood Obesity, Becoming a Mental Dilemma for Kids.

16 Nov 2012 by oakridgeint on Oakridge international schools oakridgeinternational.wordpress.com/2012/11/16/childhood-obesity-becoming-a-mental-dilemma-for-kids/

…  so dramatically in the last 20 years, but regardless of whatever combination of factors contribute to the problem, the resulting effects wreck havoc on these children's lives. In addition to the …  The effects of childhood obesity range from major psychological problems to serious health issues and chronic social problems. …

Topics: Education, Largest International Schools in Bangalore, Top International Schools in Bangalore, best international schools in bangalore, Schools in Bangalore, CBSE Schools in Bangalore, IGCSE schools in bangalore, International Schools in Bangalore</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7125-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7125_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:11:20">http://jan34marie.wordpress.com/2014/04/25/health-facts-on-childhood-obesity/</link><title>Health Facts on Childhood Obesity</title><description>Health Facts on Childhood Obesity

25 Apr 2014 by jan34marie on jan34marie jan34marie.wordpress.com/2014/04/25/health-facts-on-childhood-obesity/

  Health Effects of Childhood Obesity Childhood obesity has both immediate and long-term …  for bone and joint problems, sleep apnea, and social and psychological problems such as stigmatization and poor …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7125-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7125_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:11:35">http://photosatriani.wordpress.com/2011/12/11/junk-food-gourmet/</link><title>Junk Food Gourmet</title><description>Junk Food Gourmet

10 Dec 2011 by photosatriani on photosatriani photosatriani.wordpress.com/2011/12/11/junk-food-gourmet/

…  heavy consequences for public health as well as negative psychological effects both in the future adults (now obese children) and their families. I …

Topics: Work in progress, Childhood Obesity, Junk Food, gourmet</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7125-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7125_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:11:56">http://soedradjat.wordpress.com/2010/07/24/%e2%80%9cobesity-risk-factors-and-effects%e2%80%9d/</link><title>“Obesity: Risk Factors and Effects”</title><description>“Obesity: Risk Factors and Effects”

24 Jul 2010 by Agung Sudrajat on soedradjat soedradjat.wordpress.com/2010/07/24/“obesity-risk-factors-and-effects”/

…  this undesirable state is by knowing its risk factors and effects. Some of Obesity’s risk factors are as followings; poor diets, lack …  are less in productivity. Obesity as well as affects to psychological aspect. Current research literature, published in the last 5 …

Topics: sanwacana</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7125-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7125_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:12:30">http://publichealthstories.wordpress.com/2014/03/14/should-we-be-concerned-about-child-obesity/</link><title>Should We Be Concerned About Child Obesity?</title><description>Should We Be Concerned About Child Obesity?

15 Mar 2014 by Student Contributor on Public Health Stories publichealthstories.wordpress.com/2014/03/14/should-we-be-concerned-about-child-obesity/

…  that I searched for this blog post. By examining the effects of education on health choices, including social and psychological, and marketing prospectives, I will explore how these factors …

Topics: Child, Food, food, Childhood Obesity, Children, advertising, Social, Environment, Stigma, Weight</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7125-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7125_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:12:55">http://volron.wordpress.com/2011/03/20/child-obesity/</link><title>Child Obesity</title><description>Child Obesity

20 Mar 2011 by volron on Volron's Point volron.wordpress.com/2011/03/20/child-obesity/

…  &amp; Dale, 2004, pp. 44-5). Other factor involved is psychological factor, where children eating behaviour is caused by stress or …  to obesity in a child (Wikipedia contributors, 2007). Effects Several studies have pointed out that obese children are more likely …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7125-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7125_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:13:15">http://obesitynwpctl.wordpress.com/2011/04/26/tackling-childhood-overweight-treating-parents-exclusively-is-effective/</link><title>Tackling childhood overweight: treating parents exclusively is effective.</title><description>Tackling childhood overweight: treating parents exclusively is effective.

26 Apr 2011 by jowhitcombe on Obesity Horizon Scanning obesitynwpctl.wordpress.com/2011/04/26/tackling-childhood-overweight-treating-parents-exclusively-is-effective/

…  Journal of Obesity, 2011, 35, p. 501-509. Follow this link for abstract. Date of …  in the treatment group, both groups displayed positive psychological effects related to taking part in the study. Length of publication: 9 …

Topics: Diet, Nutrition, Children, obesity, Quantitative Research, Adults, Intervention, Parents, Health promotion, Education, bmi, body mass index, Health education, Volume 3, Issue 1, Therapy, Health education, Psychology</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7125-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7125_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:13:44">http://freshstart231.wordpress.com/2014/04/10/child-obesity-statistics-information/</link><title>Child Obesity Statistics Information</title><description>Child Obesity Statistics Information

10 Apr 2014 by freshstart231 on Fre$h Start freshstart231.wordpress.com/2014/04/10/child-obesity-statistics-information/

…  Purpose: Call on awareness of Childhood Obesity with facts and provide some preventions 1\. Childhood Obesity has …  for bone and joint problems, sleep apnea, and social and psychological problems such as stigmatization and poor self-esteem. 4. …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>