<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7128">where to donate clothes in nyc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:25:46" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7128-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7128_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:25:48">http://theorderobsessed.com/2010/08/22/clothing-recycling/</link><title>where to recycle clothing in nyc</title><description>where to recycle clothing in nyc

22 Aug 2010 by laura theorderobsessed.com/2010/08/22/clothing-recycling/

…  have clothes that aren't in good enough condition to donate (stained, damaged). Instead of throwing them out, you can recycle …  are a number of locations around Manhattan and Brooklyn where you can drop off clothing, shoes, hats, and belts. While they also accept …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7128-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7128_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:26:05">http://katastrophicthoughts.wordpress.com/2012/06/22/what-really-happens-when-you-donate-clothes/</link><title>What Really Happens When you Donate Clothes</title><description>What Really Happens When you Donate Clothes

22 Jun 2012 by kathleenerindavis on Katastrophic Thoughts katastrophicthoughts.wordpress.com/2012/06/22/what-really-happens-when-you-donate-clothes/

…  church sales are family outings (even now when I fly back to Michigan to visit my family there is both a pile of clothes on the guest bed …  they seem to be in the corner of the Midwest where I grew up), since New York is such a fashionable and expensive it follows …

Topics: Thrift Stores, used stuff, recycling, Sewing, Stuff, waste</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7128-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7128_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:26:34">http://twentyteneightyfour.wordpress.com/2010/01/07/waste-not-want-not-the-ugly-side-of-hm/</link><title>Waste not, want not: The ugly side of H&amp;M</title><description>Waste not, want not: The ugly side of H&amp;M

7 Jan 2010 by Nneoma Ulu on twentyteneightyfour twentyteneightyfour.wordpress.com/2010/01/07/waste-not-want-not-the-ugly-side-of-hm/

…  Spring, H&amp;M have released a new collection to help ease the conscience of most of us avid shoppers and our love for …  transportation of those clothes to name but a few. So where does that leave us? Is vintage the answer or should we buy from high end …

Topics: Hm......, New York Times, the garden collection, Sustainable Clothing, destroying clothes, Sweatshops, mass clothing production</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7128-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7128_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:27:06">http://whatwouldkmdo.wordpress.com/2012/02/12/day-42-what-i-would-have-done-if-i-won-the-320-million-powerball-drawing-last-night/</link><title>DAY 42 - What I would have done if I won the $320 million powerball drawing last night...</title><description>DAY 42 - What I would have done if I won the $320 million powerball drawing last night...

12 Feb 2012 by A Girl Named Spark on What Would Kate Middleton Do? whatwouldkmdo.wordpress.com/2012/02/12/day-42-what-i-would-have-done-if-i-won-the-320-million-powerball-drawing-last-night/

…  Buy my brother-in-law and brother Porsche's \- Donate $1 million to Austism research \- Put $1 million into a trust for my niece with Rett …  much but I really do owe that College a lot as it's where I met all of my good friends. \- Open a joint account for me and my …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7128-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7128_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:27:25">http://sweetstudioblog.com/2014/04/09/cleaning-out-your-closet-and-where-to-donate-clothes-in-nyc/</link><title>cleaning out your closet, and where to donate clothes in nyc</title><description>cleaning out your closet, and where to donate clothes in nyc

9 Apr 2014 by sweetstudioblog on sweet studio sweetstudioblog.com/2014/04/09/cleaning-out-your-closet-and-where-to-donate-clothes-in-nyc/

…  i first moved to new york, i shopped at goodwill and salvation army quite a bit. i was on …  once brought me joy a second chance at happiness? why not donate them to someone who might need them? who might love them? who might put …  to local animal shelters. here in new york, kittykind (where i volunteer every so often) repurposes old sheets and towels as padding …

Topics: spring, Personal, Charity</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7128-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7128_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:27:53">http://deaconjohnspace.wordpress.com/2014/01/16/from-the-friars-eletter-a-stable-becomes-home/</link><title>From The Friars eLetter: A Stable Becomes Home . . .</title><description>From The Friars eLetter: A Stable Becomes Home . . .

16 Jan 2014 by deaconjohn1987 on Deacon John's Space deaconjohnspace.wordpress.com/2014/01/16/from-the-friars-eletter-a-stable-becomes-home/

…  line from Pope Francis and my heart was honestly moved to tears: “Mary was able to turn a stable into a home for Jesus, with poor …  table next to me sits a beautiful little ceramic crèche where the familiar scene of Joseph and Mary gazing on the Christ child draws me …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7128-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7128_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:28:26">http://runthisapple.com/2014/03/30/treadmill-misery-the-first-rooftop-of-the-season/</link><title>Treadmill misery &amp; the first rooftop of the season.</title><description>Treadmill misery &amp; the first rooftop of the season.

30 Mar 2014 by Shawna on Run this Apple runthisapple.com/2014/03/30/treadmill-misery-the-first-rooftop-of-the-season/

…  any other kind? it's nice when you don't have to pretend to look good. :) i also discovered a new favorite gym apparatus: …  by summer, and part wonderful, super padded resting bench where i let the blood rush to my head while staring at my feet in-between reps. …

Topics: Running, NYC, Hell's Kitchen, Wine, Fitness, refinery hotel</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7128-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7128_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:29:03">http://grandcentraltransplant.wordpress.com/2013/11/07/moving-to-new-york-city/</link><title>Moving to New York City</title><description>Moving to New York City

7 Nov 2013 by chuckthursby on How To Make It In NYC While Being a Transplant grandcentraltransplant.wordpress.com/2013/11/07/moving-to-new-york-city/

…  you've decided to move to New York City? Congratulations, you've cleared one of the …  be taking with me to NYC. For items you can’t sell, donate! Friends probably need or want some of the junk you've collected …  you've done some research and have a rough idea of where you want to live. Ideally you know a few people in the city and can crash …

Topics: Getting There, Important Information, NYC, Moving, Donate</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7128-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7128_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:29:23">http://naturalflygirl.wordpress.com/2014/01/27/3-cleaning-house/</link><title>3\. Cleaning House</title><description>3\. Cleaning House

27 Jan 2014 by naturalflygirl on Natural Fly Girl naturalflygirl.wordpress.com/2014/01/27/3-cleaning-house/

…  All. Firstly, thanks so much to all of the InstaLove @naturalflygirl is receiving on …  have come at a better time, it's time to donate clothes, sell shoes, and consolidate to only the necessary. When you …  (Which it isn't for me.) We don't know where our home base is until 2-3 weeks before earning our wings: current home …

Topics: flight attendant, Delta Airlines, American Airlines, how to be a flight attendant, United Airlines, Flight crew, Flight Attendant Training, Saying Gooodbye, Life before</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7128-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7128_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:29:59">http://onegooddeedbook.com/2012/11/02/how-to-help-post-sandy-november-2/</link><title>How to Help, Post-Sandy - November 2</title><description>How to Help, Post-Sandy - November 2

2 Nov 2012 by erinmchughwrites on ONE GOOD DEED onegooddeedbook.com/2012/11/02/how-to-help-post-sandy-november-2/

…  when Superstorm Sandy was still raging, I listed a number to text to give $10 immediately for aid to the Red Cross (see October 30). …  blankets, flashlights, batteries--whatever anyone can donate will be accepted at these sites. St. Christopher’s Church Community …  needs your help to recover from #Sandy. When &amp; where you can volunteer: http://tmout.us/eXbmL (with thanks to …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>