<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7131">golf games</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:39:59" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7131-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7131_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:39:59">http://larry50.wordpress.com/2008/02/27/golf-discount-shops/</link><title>Golf discount shops</title><description>Golf discount shops

27 Feb 2008 by larry50 on Larry's View larry50.wordpress.com/2008/02/27/golf-discount-shops/

Golf is a game which is known as the game of business tycoons or the rich people. It is regarded as one of the very few leisure games. The general concept of the golf is that people play the game after their retirement. This is the only game …

Topics: Blogroll, Airline Tickets</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7131-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7131_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:40:20">http://thegamerwithkids.com/2011/04/27/tgwks-picks-for-most-unique-casual-golf-games-par-out-golf-flick-golf-super-stickman-golf-ios/</link><title>TGWK's Picks For Most Unique Casual Golf Games \- Par Out Golf, Flick Golf, Super Stickman Golf (iOS)</title><description>TGWK's Picks For Most Unique Casual Golf Games \- Par Out Golf, Flick Golf, Super Stickman Golf (iOS)

27 Apr 2011 by samversionone on The Gamer With Kids thegamerwithkids.com/2011/04/27/tgwks-picks-for-most-unique-casual-golf-games-par-out-golf-flick-golf-super-stickman-golf-ios/

Golf is one of those sports where you either love it or hate it. It's definitely …  exactly make it the easiest sport to pick up. Video game golf however is a bit easier to play, but the time it takes to play a round of …  put together a little list of my personal favorite golf games. I chose these because they are very different from other golf games …

Topics: Editorial, Gaming &amp; App News, iPhone, iPod Touch, &amp; iPad (iOS), iPad, ipod touch, Apple, app store, IOS, iPhone, par out golf, golf games, Flick Golf, super stickman golf</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7131-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7131_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:40:53">http://mitthalf.wordpress.com/golf-course-cornhole-game-set/</link><title>~ ++ Golf Course Cornhole Game Set</title><description>~ ++ Golf Course Cornhole Game Set

14 Dec 2012 by mitthalf on mitthalf mitthalf.wordpress.com/golf-course-cornhole-game-set/

Golf Course Cornhole Game Set - Golf Course Cornhole Game Set Read more For Golf Course Cornhole Game Golf Course Cornhole Game Set Detail Golf Course Cornhole Game Set ==&gt;Check Detail Golf Course&lt;==</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7131-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7131_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:41:21">http://1000thingstobegratefulfor.wordpress.com/2011/01/22/9-be-grateful-for-golf/</link><title>#9 Be Grateful for Golf</title><description>#9 Be Grateful for Golf

22 Jan 2011 by stepstoyourdream on 1000 Things to be grateful for 1000thingstobegratefulfor.wordpress.com/2011/01/22/9-be-grateful-for-golf/

…  Golf Golf is a amazing way to do business, meet and enjoy a long walk with great friends and meet great people. The game of golf has a lot of great rules and also teaches us a lot about things like to …

Topics: Gratitude #1-100, be grateful, 1000 gratitudes, I AM GRATEFUL, live with gratitude, grateful, "1000 Things", john thore stub sneisen, Everyday Gratitude, be grateful for today, Golf, love golf, I love golf</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7131-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7131_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:41:47">http://r4ccoon.wordpress.com/2009/03/08/the-power-exercise-in-the-golf-swing/</link><title>The Power Exercise In The Golf Swing</title><description>The Power Exercise In The Golf Swing

8 Mar 2009 by r4ccoon on R4ccoon's Weblog r4ccoon.wordpress.com/2009/03/08/the-power-exercise-in-the-golf-swing/

…  exercise will have a tremendous impact in a persons’ golf swing and golf game in general. In fact any strength exercise will have an impact on the …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7131-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7131_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:42:15">http://r4ccoon.wordpress.com/2009/03/08/golf-nutrition-is-not-an-oxymoron%e2%80%a6listen-up/</link><title>Golf Nutrition Is Not An Oxymoron…Listen Up</title><description>Golf Nutrition Is Not An Oxymoron…Listen Up

8 Mar 2009 by r4ccoon on R4ccoon's Weblog r4ccoon.wordpress.com/2009/03/08/golf-nutrition-is-not-an-oxymoron…listen-up/

Golf nutrition is still a relatively new concept. However, everybody knows that …  to help them perform at their peak. The reasons who golf nutrition is still in it’s’ infancy in the golf game is easy to see. To start with nutrition in sports goes hand in hand …

Topics: Golf</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7131-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7131_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:42:39">http://r4ccoon.wordpress.com/2009/03/08/golf-stretching-secrets-to-improve-performance/</link><title>Golf Stretching Secrets to Improve Performance</title><description>Golf Stretching Secrets to Improve Performance

8 Mar 2009 by r4ccoon on R4ccoon's Weblog r4ccoon.wordpress.com/2009/03/08/golf-stretching-secrets-to-improve-performance/

…  and therefore heavier club heads in recent years has made golf stretching secrets even more important to acquire. To make matters worse for golfers not interested in embracing golf stretching secrets, golf is a game unlike other sports where continuous …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7131-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7131_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:43:03">http://everygame.wordpress.com/2010/02/19/pga-european-tour/</link><title>PGA European Tour</title><description>PGA European Tour

19 Feb 2010 by Adam Redsell on EVERY GAME... EVER everygame.wordpress.com/2010/02/19/pga-european-tour/

Golf games are an abusive husband. No matter how many times I've been burned, …  but sort of happy, in a sick kind of way to report that GOLF GAMES STILL SUCK. This may in fact have something to do with the fact …

Topics: Games, SNES, Review, Golf, PGA, golf games, Tiger Woods, MotionPLUS, PGA European Tour Golf</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7131-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7131_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:43:42">http://bitesize-golf.com/about/</link><title>About</title><description>About

19 Aug 2011 by bitesizegolf on Bitesize Golf bitesize-golf.com/about/

…  is Bitesize Golf?" Bitesize Golf is aiming to become a central resource for all things junior golf. What does this mean? Getting young players into golf might be a bit …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7131-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7131_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:44:18">http://superdoodadsblog.wordpress.com/2012/05/04/how-to-improve-your-golf-game/</link><title>How To Improve Your Golf Game</title><description>How To Improve Your Golf Game

4 May 2012 by Charlotte's Doodad Blog on Charlotte Doodads Blog superdoodadsblog.wordpress.com/2012/05/04/how-to-improve-your-golf-game/

…  reason so many people enjoy golf is because it is a fun, relaxing way to spend the day outside, exercising …  and again and is unhappy with the way they are playing, golf can cease being fun and can instead be stressful! There are a few simple things you can do, however, to improve your golf game. If you start to do these things regularly, you will see your golf …

Topics: Hobbies, General</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>