<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7142">Amsterdam museums</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:38:09" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7142-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7142_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:38:10">http://thebleedingtomato.wordpress.com/2012/05/26/preview-stedelijk-museum/</link><title>Preview Stedelijk Museum</title><description>Preview Stedelijk Museum

26 May 2012 by The Bleeding Tomato on The Bleeding Tomato thebleedingtomato.wordpress.com/2012/05/26/preview-stedelijk-museum/

…  A new government in the Netherlands, a new Stedelijk in Amsterdam. The tide begins to turn. Stedelijk Museum Amsterdam \- preview (May 2012). Stedelijk Museum Amsterdam \- preview …

Topics: History, Art, art 2, Photography, Design, technology, Culture, Events, Inspiration, News, holland, Amsterdam, City Branding, Architecture, Security, Public Space, Painting, Stedelijk Museum, Benthem Crouwel Architekten, jan benthem, Mels Crouwel, naked, Mike Leigh</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7142-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7142_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:39:25">http://museumoftheday.wordpress.com/2014/01/11/amsterdam-museum/</link><title>Amsterdam Museum</title><description>Amsterdam Museum

11 Jan 2014 by John the Museum Guy on Museum of the Day museumoftheday.wordpress.com/2014/01/11/amsterdam-museum/

…  museum stands out as one of the best interpretive museums I've ever visited. It's been several years since my visit to Amsterdam, but I still recall how wonderful and robust the exhibits were at …

Topics: museum of the day, History, museum, city, holland, Amsterdam, amssterdam, Holland (2), City Museum, History 2</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7142-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7142_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:39:56">http://5and33blog.wordpress.com/2013/09/09/foam-museum-amsterdam/</link><title>FOAM - Photography Museum of Amsterdam</title><description>FOAM - Photography Museum of Amsterdam

9 Sep 2013 by 5&amp;33 5and33blog.wordpress.com/2013/09/09/foam-museum-amsterdam/

…  in Amsterdam, you'd be missing out if you didn't visit at least one …  reopened Rijksmuseum, or the classic Van Gogh museum, Amsterdam hosts a range of wacky, quirky, hidden and avant-garde museums and galleries to suit even the most offbeat tastes. Located in a …

Topics: Around Amsterdam, Art Happenings, what to do in Amsterdam, Art galleries in Amsterdam, Phootgraphy in Amsterdam, Foam museum, Rijksmuseum</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7142-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7142_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:40:23">http://gindunscombe.wordpress.com/2012/09/23/stedelijk-museum-amsterdam-reopening/</link><title>Stedelijk Museum Amsterdam reopening</title><description>Stedelijk Museum Amsterdam reopening

23 Sep 2012 by gindunscombe on Artworks and actions gindunscombe.wordpress.com/2012/09/23/stedelijk-museum-amsterdam-reopening/

…  Museum Amsterdam – re-opened 23 September 2012. Historic moment. I’m at Schiphol about to leave Amsterdam after a very full-on culture weekend – UNSEEN a huge photographic …  for the Stedelijk becoming one of the top modern art museums in the world. He was open to new art movements and saw the necessity of …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7142-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7142_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:41:37">http://eurolade.wordpress.com/2013/02/26/diamant-museum-amsterdam/</link><title>Diamant Museum Amsterdam</title><description>Diamant Museum Amsterdam

26 Feb 2013 by clubfashionista2 on clubfashionista2 eurolade.wordpress.com/2013/02/26/diamant-museum-amsterdam/

…  Nerina H.Amsterdam is well known for its diamond trade which dates back to the 16th …  Sephardic Jews left Portugal and Spain and immigrated to Amsterdam.  Diamond trade and crafts was a profession that was open to …  jobs in this industry. A couple of centuries later, Amsterdam evolved into an international center for diamond trade. Although …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7142-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7142_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:42:34">http://introissuesideas.wordpress.com/2014/02/09/red-light-secrets-museum-explores-the-prostitution-industry-of-amsterdam/</link><title>Red Light Secrets Museum explores the prostitution industry of Amsterdam</title><description>Red Light Secrets Museum explores the prostitution industry of Amsterdam

10 Feb 2014 by graciegolden on Introduction to the Museum: Issues and Ideas introissuesideas.wordpress.com/2014/02/09/red-light-secrets-museum-explores-the-prostitution-industry-of-amsterdam/

…  new Red Light Secrets Museum in the Red Light District of Amsterdam. The museum aims to educate tourists who want more information on the …  brothel, the museum details the history of prostitution in Amsterdam and the state of prostitution in the city. Focusing on the industry …

Topics: Hot Off The Press, museum opening, History Museum</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7142-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7142_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:42:57">http://burnblog.net/2014/01/30/amsterdam/</link><title>Amsterdam</title><description>Amsterdam

30 Jan 2014 by tartufoo on BURNBLOG burnblog.net/2014/01/30/amsterdam/

Amsterdam is one of the greatest small cities in the world. From its canals to world-famous museums and historical sights, Amsterdam is one of the most romantic and beautiful cities in …

Topics: Home, Travel, Tourism, history architecture, Holiday, Burnblog, Amsterdam, Rijksmuseum, Van Gogh Museum, Stedelijk Museum, Netherlands</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7142-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7142_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:43:17">http://flavorwire.com/444987/amazing-historical-tattoo-photos-from-taschens-25th-anniversary-edition-of-1000-tattoos/</link><title>Amazing Historical Tattoo Photos From Taschen's 25th Anniversary Edition of '1000 Tattoos'</title><description>Amazing Historical Tattoo Photos From Taschen's 25th Anniversary Edition of '1000 Tattoos'

12 Mar 2014 by donnellyflavorwire on Flavorwire flavorwire.com/444987/amazing-historical-tattoo-photos-from-taschens-25th-anniversary-edition-of-1000-tattoos/

…  1000 Tattoos, art historian Burkhard Riemschneider and Amsterdam-based tattoo-world legend Henk Schiffmacher (who also runs the Amsterdam Tattoo Museum) explore the history, lives, and stories behind …

Topics: Photography, Taschen, 1000 Tattoos, tattoo history, Burkhard Riemschneider, henk schiffmacher, The Amsterdam Tattoo Museum, zzz-mailer-ready-feature</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7142-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7142_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:44:09">http://tripelonia.wordpress.com/2014/03/14/a-little-trip-to-amsterdam/</link><title>A little trip to Amsterdam</title><description>A little trip to Amsterdam

14 Mar 2014 by Tripelonia on tripelonia tripelonia.wordpress.com/2014/03/14/a-little-trip-to-amsterdam/

Amsterdam is the official capital of the Netherlands and has an impressive architecture, …  and to have some gratuities, is necessary to buy the Amsterdam card, which includes free public transport, during the card validity …  free boat ride on the canals and a few discounts at museums. Amsterdam Card for 24 hours - 40 EUR Amsterdam Card for 48 hours - …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7142-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7142_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:44:34">http://ahgk1999.wordpress.com/2014/04/14/description/</link><title>Description Of Amsterdam</title><description>Description Of Amsterdam

14 Apr 2014 by amaros1232 on ahgk1999 ahgk1999.wordpress.com/2014/04/14/description/

Amsterdam in holland, is a loud city with great architecture and beautiful houses, …  is a good means of transport. This big city has beautiful museums like Rijks museum, Ana Frank's museum, Van gogh museum and Amsterdam art museum. I liked pretty much Amsterdam because is big, …

Topics: Ana Frank, Art Museum, Amsterdam</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>