<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7144">can headphones cause hearing loss</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:50:40" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7144-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7144_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:50:42">http://oneseventeenmedia.wordpress.com/2010/08/18/can-you-hear-me-now-earbuds-high-volume-music-cause-teen-hearing-loss/</link><title>Can You Hear Me Now?: Earbuds, high volume music cause teen hearing loss</title><description>Can You Hear Me Now?: Earbuds, high volume music cause teen hearing loss

19 Aug 2010 by Beth Carls on OneSeventeen Media Blog oneseventeenmedia.wordpress.com/2010/08/18/can-you-hear-me-now-earbuds-high-volume-music-cause-teen-hearing-loss/

…  loss among adults who ought to know better something we can smirk at, a study released on Tuesday (as show on CBS News) is just plain  …  suspect the primary cause is the use of using earbuds or headphones to listen to portable music. The authors of the report in the …

Topics: OneSeventeen Media, kids, Parents, technology, tweens, Social Media, Research, KidThrive.org</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7144-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7144_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:51:01">http://newyork.cbslocal.com/2013/12/03/nyc-ad-campaign-aims-to-cut-volume-on-headphones/</link><title>NYC Ad Campaign Aims To Cut Volume On Headphones</title><description>NYC Ad Campaign Aims To Cut Volume On Headphones

3 Dec 2013 by rmchatelain on CBS New York newyork.cbslocal.com/2013/12/03/nyc-ad-campaign-aims-to-cut-volume-on-headphones/

…  YORK (CBSNewYork) -- Blaring your headphones can cause irreversible hearing loss, city officials warn in a new ad …

Topics: News, health news, Local, health, Hearing Loss, Headphones, NY News, Dr. Thomas Farley, Syndication, Radio.com - News, Syndicated Local, NEW YORK CITY HEALTH DEPARTMENT</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7144-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7144_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:51:59">http://liupostpioneer.com/2012/03/28/the-not-so-silent-killer/</link><title>The Not-So-Silent Killer</title><description>The Not-So-Silent Killer

28 Mar 2012 by PostPioneer liupostpioneer.com/2012/03/28/the-not-so-silent-killer/

…  aware that smoking, drinking alcohol and eating junk food can have a negative effect on their health. However, the thought of listening …  habits. They are almost everywhere you go. People with headphones on, zoned out in another world, bobbing their heads to their …

Topics: features</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7144-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7144_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:52:36">http://zedie.wordpress.com/2014/01/27/will-headphones-damage-my-hearing/</link><title>Will headphones damage my hearing?</title><description>Will headphones damage my hearing?

27 Jan 2014 by zedie on someone somewhere zedie.wordpress.com/2014/01/27/will-headphones-damage-my-hearing/

…  often thought that listening to loud music on headphones damages hearing, though evidence is inconclusive. A new survey may …  straight to the sensitive inner ear through earphones can't be a good idea. Can it? The solution A review of the research in …

Topics: Medicine, News</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7144-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7144_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:53:10">http://mcntalk.com/2012/08/29/earphones-as-damaging-as-jet-engine-noise/</link><title>Earphones As Damaging As Jet Engine Noise?</title><description>Earphones As Damaging As Jet Engine Noise?

29 Aug 2012 by MCNtalk on MCN Talk mcntalk.com/2012/08/29/earphones-as-damaging-as-jet-engine-noise/

…  of Leicester found that listening to high volume on your headphones can damage the coating of nerve cells in your ears, causing temporary deafness. …

Topics: Injury and trauma, brain</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7144-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7144_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:53:42">http://thechart.blogs.cnn.com/2011/11/14/hearing-loss-affects-1-in-5-americans-study-finds/</link><title>Hearing loss affects 1 in 5 Americans, study finds</title><description>Hearing loss affects 1 in 5 Americans, study finds

14 Nov 2011 by ddellorto on The Chart thechart.blogs.cnn.com/2011/11/14/hearing-loss-affects-1-in-5-americans-study-finds/

…  exposures -- like listening to music too loudly -- can contribute to long term hearing damage over time,” says Dr. Frank R. …  concern.” Here’s how hearing loss happens with headphones: You have your headphones on and are jamming to your favorite tune …

Topics: Danielle Dellorto - CNN Medical Senior Producer, Environment, brain, Health and tech</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7144-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7144_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:54:25">http://earsrule.wordpress.com/causes-of-hearing-loss/</link><title>Causes of Hearing Loss</title><description>Causes of Hearing Loss

24 Feb 2013 by yelakantiv on Ears earsrule.wordpress.com/causes-of-hearing-loss/

…  things that causes hearing loss. First of all you can get it at birth, with an infection or injury, age, prolonged exposure to …  them.           Headphones: Everybody loves headphones. It's what we use to hear …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7144-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7144_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:55:07">http://hiddenhearingblog.com/2012/12/01/exercising-with-ipods-and-earbud-headphones-not-good-for-your-hearing-health/</link><title>Exercising with iPods and earbud headphones not good for your hearing health</title><description>Exercising with iPods and earbud headphones not good for your hearing health

1 Dec 2012 by Róisín FitzGerald on Hidden Hearing's (Ireland) Blog hiddenhearingblog.com/2012/12/01/exercising-with-ipods-and-earbud-headphones-not-good-for-your-hearing-health/

…  to indicate that people who exercise with iPods and earbud headphones in their ears may be damaging their hearing health.  Researchers in …  aging adults. Earbuds are placed directly in the ear and can boost the sound signal by as much as six to nine decibels. It's enough …

Topics: hearing news, Hearing Loss, hidden hearing, exercise and ipods</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7144-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7144_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:55:32">http://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2010/12/28/study-hearing-loss-on-the-rise-with-girls/</link><title>Study: Hearing Loss On The Rise With Girls</title><description>Study: Hearing Loss On The Rise With Girls

29 Dec 2010 by caseyshea9 on CBS Pittsburgh pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2010/12/28/study-hearing-loss-on-the-rise-with-girls/

…  days on i-Pods or MP3 players, but blasting tunes on their headphones may not be causing hearing damage after all. It's not who …  height=240 type=video] High volumes and long exposure can cause hearing loss by damaging the specialized sensory cells inside the ear …

Topics: News, health, Local, Dr. Maria Simbra, Hearing Loss, study, PEDIATRICS, Dr. Todd Hillman</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7144-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7144_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:56:18">http://hiddenhearingblog.com/2012/02/08/earphones-hearing-loss-and-more/</link><title>Earphones — hearing loss and more</title><description>Earphones — hearing loss and more

8 Feb 2012 by John Murphy on Hidden Hearing's (Ireland) Blog hiddenhearingblog.com/2012/02/08/earphones-hearing-loss-and-more/

…  is said that the maximum limit of sound that a human ear can sustain is around 85db. Beyond this there is a possibility of damage to the …  to sleep. The good one? According to Dr Vinaya, headphones are better than earphones as they cut out external sound hence you …

Topics: hearing loss, earphones</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>