<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7165">vice president residence</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:29:59" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7165-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7165_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:30:00">http://kendalnite.wordpress.com/2008/08/30/number-one-observatory-circle-vice-presidents-house/</link><title>Number One Observatory Circle, Vice President's House</title><description>Number One Observatory Circle, Vice President's House

30 Aug 2008 by Kendal on America's Castles kendalnite.wordpress.com/2008/08/30/number-one-observatory-circle-vice-presidents-house/

…  on only historic places that has to do with Presidents or Vice Presidents. Number One Observatory is home to the Vice President during the time they serve in office.  The house is a Victorian …

Topics: Historical Sites, Number One Observatory Circle, Vice President's House, Vice President's Residence, Naval Observatory in Washington</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7165-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7165_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:30:20">http://robinsonsresidence.wordpress.com/news/construction-updates/the-magnolia-residences-tower-b-topping-off-ceremony/</link><title>THE MAGNOLIA RESIDENCES TOWER B TOPPING-OFF CEREMONY</title><description>THE MAGNOLIA RESIDENCES TOWER B TOPPING-OFF CEREMONY

1 Sep 2013 by Robinsons Residences on Robinsons Land Residences robinsonsresidence.wordpress.com/news/construction-updates/the-magnolia-residences-tower-b-topping-off-ceremony/

…  Construction Development Corporation, Robinsons Land Vice President for Project Management Engr. Emmanuel Arce, Robinsons Land General …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7165-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7165_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:31:04">http://greatriversofhope.wordpress.com/2013/12/29/namadi-sambos-furniture-house-upgrade-gulp-n2-1-billion-in-four-years-premium-times/</link><title>Namadi Sambo’s Furniture, House Upgrade Gulp N2.1 Billion In Four Years-PREMIUM TIMES.</title><description>Namadi Sambo’s Furniture, House Upgrade Gulp N2.1 Billion In Four Years-PREMIUM TIMES.

29 Dec 2013 by greatriversofhope on Rivers of Hope greatriversofhope.wordpress.com/2013/12/29/namadi-sambos-furniture-house-upgrade-gulp-n2-1-billion-in-four-years-premium-times/

Vice President Namadi Sambo By Ini Ekott Vice President Namadi …  is spending a fortune to furnish and upgrade his official residence and guest house, two projects costing N2.1 billion and lingering …

Topics: Nigeria, Abuja, goodluck jonathan, Jonathan, National Assembly, Yakubu Gowon, Federal Capital Territory Administration, Corruption news, guest house, Namadi Sambo, Vice President of the United States, Sambo</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7165-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7165_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:31:23">http://evilofindifference.wordpress.com/2012/10/12/raddatz-visited-biden-at-his-residence-in-march/</link><title>Raddatz Visited Biden at His Residence in March</title><description>Raddatz Visited Biden at His Residence in March

12 Oct 2012 by evilofindifference on Evil of indifference evilofindifference.wordpress.com/2012/10/12/raddatz-visited-biden-at-his-residence-in-march/

…  records reveal that the moderator of last night's vice presidential debate, Martha Raddatz, visited Vice President Joe Biden at his official residence on March 26, 2012. Raddatz is an …

Topics: Mainstream media, corruption, liberal media, State-run media, Presstitution</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7165-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7165_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:31:48">http://babaolofofo.wordpress.com/2012/12/05/vice-president-namadi-sambo-to-get-a-n2billion-home/</link><title>Vice President Namadi Sambo To Get A N2billion Home</title><description>Vice President Namadi Sambo To Get A N2billion Home

5 Dec 2012 by abeyjunior on Baba Olofofo babaolofofo.wordpress.com/2012/12/05/vice-president-namadi-sambo-to-get-a-n2billion-home/

…  Vice President is getting a home worth N2 billion from the government of Nigeria. …  Mohammed, is going into the construction of the official residence of Vice President Namadi Sambo, while N300 million is for the …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7165-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7165_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:32:12">http://rahulgandhiindia.wordpress.com/2014/01/13/rahul-gandhi-meets-jat-leaders/</link><title>Rahul Gandhi meets Jat leaders</title><description>Rahul Gandhi meets Jat leaders

13 Jan 2014 by rahulgandhiindia on RahulGandhiindia's Blog rahulgandhiindia.wordpress.com/2014/01/13/rahul-gandhi-meets-jat-leaders/

…  Gandhi meets Jat leaders, a set on Flickr.Congress Vice President Rahul Gandhi meets the representatives of the Jat Community . …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7165-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7165_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:32:35">http://theupsizers.wordpress.com/2012/10/21/entry-171-your-vice-president-whoever-he-ends-up-being-needs-your-help/</link><title>Entry 171: Your Vice President (Whoever He Ends Up Being) Needs Your Help</title><description>Entry 171: Your Vice President (Whoever He Ends Up Being) Needs Your Help

21 Oct 2012 by markhal on The Upsizers theupsizers.wordpress.com/2012/10/21/entry-171-your-vice-president-whoever-he-ends-up-being-needs-your-help/

…  been a great embarrassment. Until very recently, our vice president, the second most powerful person in the country (third during the J. …

Topics: Number One Observatory Circle, Chief of Naval Operations, vice president’s official residence, GuideStar, Joe Biden, dick cheney, Lynne Cheney, Joan Mondale, Walter Mondale, Dan Quayle, Al Gore, Archie Bunker's Chair, Hirshhorn Museum</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7165-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7165_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:33:02">http://homar.wordpress.com/2010/07/08/perks-and-privileges/</link><title>Perks and Privileges</title><description>Perks and Privileges

8 Jul 2010 by Homar Murillo on Mga muni-muni at kuro-kuro homar.wordpress.com/2010/07/08/perks-and-privileges/

…  6, Article VII of the 1987 Philippine Constitution, the President shall have an official residence. Although Malacañang Palace has …  head of state, no similar perks were accorded to the Vice-President. However, all of these may change. While President Noy would …

Topics: Coconut Palace, Jejomar Binay, Vice President BINAY, Binay official residence</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7165-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7165_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:33:21">http://whitehouse.blogs.cnn.com/2012/07/27/white-house-day-for-friday-july-27/</link><title>White House day for Friday July 27</title><description>White House day for Friday July 27

27 Jul 2012 by lesajansen on The 1600 Report whitehouse.blogs.cnn.com/2012/07/27/white-house-day-for-friday-july-27/

…  Press Briefing by Press Secretary Jay Carney PRESIDENT OBAMA'S SCHEDULE: 9:00AM Pool Call Time 9:40AM THE PRESIDENT and THE VICE PRESIDENT receive the Presidential Daily Briefing/Oval Office/ Closed …  THE PRESIDENT attends a campaign event/ Private Residence, McLean, Virginia / Closed Press 7:35PM THE PRESIDENT delivers …

Topics: Daily Schedule, CNN White House Producer Lesa Jansen</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7165-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7165_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:33:57">http://whitehouse.blogs.cnn.com/2012/09/14/potus-schedule-for-friday-september-14-olympians-and-paralympians-at-the-white-house/</link><title>POTUS' Schedule for Friday, September 14: Olympians and Paralympians at the White House</title><description>POTUS' Schedule for Friday, September 14: Olympians and Paralympians at the White House

14 Sep 2012 by adamatcnn on The 1600 Report whitehouse.blogs.cnn.com/2012/09/14/potus-schedule-for-friday-september-14-olympians-and-paralympians-at-the-white-house/

President Obama has just one public event on his schedule Friday, an event with the …  at 9:30 AM. The president will also have lunch with the Vice President in the private dining room, where foreign policy will no likely …  the evening, Obama will attend a fundraiser at a private residence in Washington DC. Press Secretary Jay Carney will brief the press …

Topics: Daily Schedule</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>