<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7166">pita recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:34:33" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7166-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7166_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:34:34">http://globalgrind.com/2009/09/23/world-of-pitas-pita-recipes/</link><title>World of pitas - pita recipes</title><description>World of pitas - pita recipes

23 Sep 2009 by User Contribution on Global Grind globalgrind.com/2009/09/23/world-of-pitas-pita-recipes/

&lt;p&gt;Marinated Feta with Greek Olives and Roasted Peppers with Toasted Pita&lt;/p&gt;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7166-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7166_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:35:27">http://cestlaviecuisine.com/2012/10/18/pita-pizza-heaven/</link><title>Pita Pizza Heaven</title><description>Pita Pizza Heaven

19 Oct 2012 by Cestlaviecuisine on C'est la Vie Cuisine cestlaviecuisine.com/2012/10/18/pita-pizza-heaven/

…  week’s recipe is a perfect week night dinner. Quick to fix up, delicious and will …  day at work. The idea is pretty simple: make a pizza using pita bread. I started making this recipe a year ago. It was one of those …  Anyway, I just added a bunch of ingredients on top of pita bread, stick it in the oven for 15 minutes, and voila! The fun part about …

Topics: Menu, Main Dish, french food, goat cheese, recipe, cheese, Food, pita bread, Pizza, Foodies</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7166-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7166_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:35:56">http://hermitess75.wordpress.com/2011/02/02/nummy/</link><title>Nummy!</title><description>Nummy!

2 Feb 2011 by hermitess75 on hermitess75 hermitess75.wordpress.com/2011/02/02/nummy/

…  snack. :D I made it myself. :chef: I got the idea from a recipe in my Vegetarian Cookbook, but modified it (naturally) to my tastes. PITA PIZZA1 whole wheat pita, toastedsliced fresh tomatofresh Mozzarella …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7166-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7166_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:36:27">http://gobuckwheat.wordpress.com/2013/04/08/recipe-chicken-shawarma-with-impromptu-gluten-free-pita/</link><title>Recipe: Chicken Shawarma with Impromptu Gluten-Free Pita</title><description>Recipe: Chicken Shawarma with Impromptu Gluten-Free Pita

8 Apr 2013 by idiotsyncracy on BUCKWHEAT gobuckwheat.wordpress.com/2013/04/08/recipe-chicken-shawarma-with-impromptu-gluten-free-pita/

…  where I had Chicken Shawarma (a garlic-based chicken recipe served with Tzatziki sauce) for dinner and was not even close to feeling …  my delight when I found (or thought I found) gluten-free pita bread on sale at Whole Foods! Nesteled between Udi's frozen Blueberry …

Topics: Recipes, Dinner, Chicken, Gluten-free, Middle Eastern, pita bread</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7166-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7166_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:37:11">http://lefoodsnob.wordpress.com/2011/05/17/pita-bread/</link><title>Pita Bread</title><description>Pita Bread

18 May 2011 by lefoodsnob on Le Food Snob lefoodsnob.wordpress.com/2011/05/17/pita-bread/

…  of recipes I wanted to try, I obviously copied down the recipe for Pita Bread wrong. My recipe for Pita Bread looked suspiciously (and exactly) …

Topics: Bread, Healthy Eating, Recipe rating: , vegetarian</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7166-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7166_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:38:13">http://cookingnurse.wordpress.com/2012/04/04/soft-wrap-bread-turned-pita/</link><title>Soft wrap bread turned pita</title><description>Soft wrap bread turned pita

4 Apr 2012 by emily676 on The Cooking Nurse cookingnurse.wordpress.com/2012/04/04/soft-wrap-bread-turned-pita/

…  love love love the soft wrap bread recipe from King Arthur Flour. It is not a tortilla and not a pita, but somewhere in the middle. I always struggle with getting a good pita puff when I make a pita recipe, but I accidentally made pitas with my …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7166-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7166_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:38:33">http://hanssusser.wordpress.com/2013/09/24/soup-sandwich-small-budget-big-taste/</link><title>Soup &amp; Sandwich - Small Budget / Big Taste</title><description>Soup &amp; Sandwich - Small Budget / Big Taste

24 Sep 2013 by Hans Susser on hanssusser hanssusser.wordpress.com/2013/09/24/soup-sandwich-small-budget-big-taste/

beautiful food, Big Taste, boursin cheese, dinner, easy recipes, ethnic recipes, great taste, hans sussers food, jamon serrano, Olive oil, Pita, pita bread, recipes, serrano ham, Small Budget, Soup via Soup &amp; Sandwich - Small Budget / Big Taste.

Topics: Recipes, Beautiful Food, Dinner, Easy Recipes, ethnic recipes, Great Taste, hans sussers food, olive oil, tomato bisque, PITA, Boursin cheese, big taste..., jamon serrano, pita bread, Serrano Ham, small budget, soup &amp; sandwich</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7166-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7166_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:39:11">http://simplynutricising.com/nutritionpage/recipes/snacks/pita-chips/</link><title>Pita Chips</title><description>Pita Chips

27 Jan 2013 by simplynutricising on Simply Nutricising simplynutricising.com/nutritionpage/recipes/snacks/pita-chips/

…  inch pita bread 2 Tablespoons of olive oil Salt, pepper, rosemary, and thyme to taste Directions Slice two  6 inch pita bread into 8 pieces each. Brush olive oil on top of every …  piece. Bake at 350 degrees for 20 minutes. *Same recipe to make Tortilla Chips! Use whole wheat tortillas instead of pita chips …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7166-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7166_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:39:53">http://fortheloveofcooking1.wordpress.com/2011/09/30/tuna-hummus-pita-oh-my/</link><title>Tuna, Hummus, Pita...OH MY!</title><description>Tuna, Hummus, Pita...OH MY!

30 Sep 2011 by aleenaiman fortheloveofcooking1.wordpress.com/2011/09/30/tuna-hummus-pita-oh-my/

…  This time I decided to put a twist on my fried tuna ball recipe.  For the balls, follow the same recipe expect this time, use a …  measuring spoon for your balls so they fit into the pita. For the the rest, keep reading! Tuna Pita Ingredients: Pita bread Baby spinach leaves Hummus EVOO Red crushed …

Topics: Fried Food, Tuna, tuna balls, Pita...OH MY!, PITA, hummus, lunch</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7166-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7166_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:40:27">http://recipesbymissy.wordpress.com/2009/04/07/pita-chips/</link><title>Pita Chips</title><description>Pita Chips

8 Apr 2009 by bylinemjf on Missy's Recipes recipesbymissy.wordpress.com/2009/04/07/pita-chips/

…  cooking lately. Risotto, red pepper hummus, jerk chicken (recipe to follow), iced tea, pita chips. Here's the recipe for the last one, which is so easy it hardly …

Topics: easy/quick</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>