<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7167">aluminium extrusion</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:41:05" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7167-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7167_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:41:05">http://sme2010.wordpress.com/2014/04/18/group-comprises-aluminium-and-plastic-expertise/</link><title>Group comprises aluminium and plastic expertise</title><description>Group comprises aluminium and plastic expertise

18 Apr 2014 by smeditor on Southern Manufacturing &amp; Electronics 2014 sme2010.wordpress.com/2014/04/18/group-comprises-aluminium-and-plastic-expertise/

…  of BWC Aluminium and BWC Plastics, the BWC Group offer fabrication expertise in the two materials. BWC Aluminium is one of the UK’s largest, independent stockholders of bespoke aluminium extrusion. The collective knowledge of staff members represents over 120 …

Topics: manufacturing, News, South14</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7167-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7167_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:41:35">http://petercombe.wordpress.com/2009/10/07/thomas-heatherwick/</link><title>Thomas Heatherwick</title><description>Thomas Heatherwick

7 Oct 2009 by petercombe on a tale of a few cities petercombe.wordpress.com/2009/10/07/thomas-heatherwick/

…  Extrusions, includes six extruded, mirror polished, aluminium benches made without fixtures or fittings, which have been produced by the world’s largest extrusion machine. Heatherwick Studio commissioned a specially designed die …

Topics: Design, Art, London, Extrusions, Thomas Heatherwick, Haunch of Venison Gallery</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7167-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7167_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:41:57">http://aluminiumwiremanufacturers.wordpress.com/2013/06/26/reasons-behind-the-growth-of-aluminium-extrusions-manufacturers/</link><title>Reasons Behind The Growth of Aluminium Extrusions Manufacturers</title><description>Reasons Behind The Growth of Aluminium Extrusions Manufacturers

26 Jun 2013 by bradsmith531 on Banco Aluminium Limited aluminiumwiremanufacturers.wordpress.com/2013/06/26/reasons-behind-the-growth-of-aluminium-extrusions-manufacturers/

…  and steel, which have been in use for thousands of years, aluminium is relatively young, having been identified as an elemental metal in …  metal is that one can make numerous products while doing extrusion; and with inbuilt features of the metal. This process is quite cost …

Topics: Aluminium Extrusion Manufacturers India</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7167-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7167_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:42:23">http://strategicanalysis.wordpress.com/2006/10/13/greek-aluminium-production/</link><title>Greek Aluminium production</title><description>Greek Aluminium production

12 Oct 2006 by strategicanalysis on Strategic Analysis &amp; OSINT Management strategicanalysis.wordpress.com/2006/10/13/greek-aluminium-production/

…  aluminium sector, from the mining of bauxite to the production of the final …  and employed 40,000 people directly or indirectly, while aluminium exports accounted for approximately 5.5% of overall exports of the …  aluminium products can be divided into lamination and extrusion products, cables and foundry products depending on how they are …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7167-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7167_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:42:56">http://aluminiumwiremanufacturers.wordpress.com/2014/02/19/with-passing-time-aluminium-extrusion-manufacturers-are-developing-innovative-products/</link><title>With Passing Time Aluminium Extrusion Manufacturers Are Developing Innovative Products</title><description>With Passing Time Aluminium Extrusion Manufacturers Are Developing Innovative Products

19 Feb 2014 by bradsmith531 on Banco Aluminium Limited aluminiumwiremanufacturers.wordpress.com/2014/02/19/with-passing-time-aluminium-extrusion-manufacturers-are-developing-innovative-products/

…  present times, aluminium metal is by far most versatile metal. We can extrude, cast form, …  modern art; in short is used in almost all walks of life. Aluminium metal is relatively cheap, at least after we learned to process it. …  ore, and that made it more valuable Than Gold Aluminium Extrusion is defined as a course of shaping substance, such as aluminium, by …

Topics: Aluminium extrusions india, Business</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7167-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7167_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:43:30">http://aluminiumwiremanufacturers.wordpress.com/2014/01/21/aluminium-extrusions-manufacturers-india-has-conquered-the-market/</link><title>Aluminium Extrusions Manufacturers India Has Conquered The Market</title><description>Aluminium Extrusions Manufacturers India Has Conquered The Market

21 Jan 2014 by bradsmith531 on Banco Aluminium Limited aluminiumwiremanufacturers.wordpress.com/2014/01/21/aluminium-extrusions-manufacturers-india-has-conquered-the-market/

Aluminium is a very ductile and malleable element that can be shaped in any form, …  engineering corporations across the globe make the use of aluminium as it helps them to manufacture light weight air planes and machines. …  of using it, then you must continue to read this post Extrusion is defined as a process of shaping material, such as aluminium, by …

Topics: Aluminium Extrusions Manufacturers India, Business</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7167-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7167_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:43:46">http://aluminiumwiremanufacturers.wordpress.com/2014/04/02/own-a-stylish-aluminium-window-frames-designed-by-banco-aluminium/</link><title>Own A Stylish Aluminium Window Frames Designed by Banco Aluminium</title><description>Own A Stylish Aluminium Window Frames Designed by Banco Aluminium

2 Apr 2014 by bradsmith531 on Banco Aluminium Limited aluminiumwiremanufacturers.wordpress.com/2014/04/02/own-a-stylish-aluminium-window-frames-designed-by-banco-aluminium/

…  versatile metal Aluminium is found in abundance in the environment, is the most sought metal …  The flexibility strength and light weight qualities of Aluminium metal are some of the traits that make it most desired in various …  presently manufacturers are opting for Aluminium extrusion process to design and shape end products with ease. A Versatile …

Topics: aluminium window frames, Business</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7167-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7167_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:44:10">http://blog.gjames.com/2012/02/24/aluminium-conveyor-rollers/</link><title>Aluminium conveyor rollers</title><description>Aluminium conveyor rollers

24 Feb 2012 by gjamesau on Built On Experience blog.gjames.com/2012/02/24/aluminium-conveyor-rollers/

…  our extensive range of aluminium extrusions, G.James produce a range of high-tensile strength aluminium extrusions for use as roller shells. Whilst not a new product for …  our range of aluminium extrusions please peruse our online extrusion catalogue or contact Extrusion Sales on (07) 3877 …

Topics: Mining, Aluminium, High Tensile, Rollers, Conveyor, Noise Reduction, Power saving</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7167-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7167_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:44:33">http://aluminiumwiremanufacturers.wordpress.com/2013/06/27/banco-aluminium-manufactures-aluminium-sections-to-fit-the-requirement-of-all-industries/</link><title>Banco aluminium Manufactures aluminium Sections To Fit the Requirement Of All Industries</title><description>Banco aluminium Manufactures aluminium Sections To Fit the Requirement Of All Industries

27 Jun 2013 by bradsmith531 on Banco Aluminium Limited aluminiumwiremanufacturers.wordpress.com/2013/06/27/banco-aluminium-manufactures-aluminium-sections-to-fit-the-requirement-of-all-industries/

aluminium extrusion a common name of aluminium Profiles is a technique used to transform aluminium alloy into …

Topics: Aluminium profiles, Real Estate, Business</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7167-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7167_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:44:56">http://my3dprinterbuild.wordpress.com/2012/08/09/1st-parts-arrive/</link><title>1st Parts Arrive...</title><description>1st Parts Arrive...

9 Aug 2012 by Bradders on Building a 3D Printer my3dprinterbuild.wordpress.com/2012/08/09/1st-parts-arrive/

…  align="alignright" width="300"] Aluminium Extrusion[/caption] Order parts and they arrive (some time …  to be done. The first parts to order / receive are the aluminium extrusion which bolts together with the aid of printed parts to make …

Topics: 3D Printer, Mendel, MendelMax, parts, parts</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>