<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7168">fabric glue</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:45:13" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7168-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7168_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:45:14">http://stickyassglue.wordpress.com/2011/05/19/how-well-does-your-glue-work-on-fabric/</link><title>How Well Does Your Glue Work On Fabric?</title><description>How Well Does Your Glue Work On Fabric?

19 May 2011 by stickyassglue on Sticky Ass Glue stickyassglue.wordpress.com/2011/05/19/how-well-does-your-glue-work-on-fabric/

Glue Crew, I do a lot of arts and crafts, and have used your glue on lots of projects.  I haven’t tried using it on fabric yet though.  Do you recommend this?  It seems like the glue may show through the fabric?  What’s the deal? You are correct.  We don’t recommend using …

Topics: Stubbornly Strong Glue, How To Use SAG for Various Projects, Sticky Ass Glue, Sticky Jack Glue, DIY, Glue, Polyurethane Glue, www.stickyassglue.com, Arts &amp; Crafts, gluing fabric</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7168-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7168_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:45:49">http://agirlscreativedoings.wordpress.com/2013/11/26/diy-fabric-bow-tutorial/</link><title>DIY Fabric Bow Tutorial</title><description>DIY Fabric Bow Tutorial

26 Nov 2013 by huyones agirlscreativedoings.wordpress.com/2013/11/26/diy-fabric-bow-tutorial/

…  tutorials, I put together a "how to" for the fabric bows that I make. These bows are super easy to make. Materials: Fabric Hot glue or fabric glue Headband or alligator clip Let's get started! 1. …

Topics: fabric glue, fabric bow, alligator clip, hot glue, bow</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7168-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7168_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:46:20">http://destashification.com/2014/01/27/fabric-christmas-decorations-no-sew/</link><title>Fabric Christmas Decorations - No Sew</title><description>Fabric Christmas Decorations - No Sew

27 Jan 2014 by destashification on The Destashification Project destashification.com/2014/01/27/fabric-christmas-decorations-no-sew/

…  is a family tradition.  These use left over Christmas fabric (see note on fabric at end of post.) Materials: Styrofoam balls …  5") Stash Christmas Fabric Iron Washable white glue Bowl (not your best china - this will be messy) Glasses (not your best …

Topics: Tutorial, Home Decor, No Sewing Fabric Projects, Scrap Couture, seasonal home décor, Christmas, no-sew Christmas ornaments</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7168-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7168_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:46:51">http://firsttimemumblog.wordpress.com/2012/12/13/potpourri-heart/</link><title>Homemade Potpourri Heart</title><description>Homemade Potpourri Heart

13 Dec 2012 by firsttimemumblog on firsttimemumblog's Blog firsttimemumblog.wordpress.com/2012/12/13/potpourri-heart/

…  you need Unwanted or leftover fabric Mesh fabric Hard paper/ Old Christmas Cards Potpourri Lace (to go around the heart shape) Ribbon Adhesive spray Glue Scissors and some patience Instructions 1) Draw two heart shape on a …

Topics: Home Decor, Art, Homemade potpourri heart, Christmas Craft</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7168-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7168_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:47:27">http://qualitycornices.wordpress.com/2008/01/19/no-sew-welt-cord/</link><title>No sew welt cord</title><description>No sew welt cord

19 Jan 2008 by brevell on Quality Cornices News qualitycornices.wordpress.com/2008/01/19/no-sew-welt-cord/

…  sewing there are several ways  of making welt cord using glue and tape.  The glue I use comes from R.W. Rowley and is called fringe adhesive.  It can best be used on an upholstery weight fabric that has a rubberized type of backing to prevent the glue from bleeding …

Topics: Cornice Boards, Welt Cord, Miscellaneous</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7168-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7168_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:48:07">http://clutch-me.com/2012/02/04/helpful-hints-how-to-put-glue-into-u-channel-purse-frames/</link><title>Helpful Hints: How to put glue into U-channel purse frames</title><description>Helpful Hints: How to put glue into U-channel purse frames

4 Feb 2012 by Winn on Clutch-Me.Com clutch-me.com/2012/02/04/helpful-hints-how-to-put-glue-into-u-channel-purse-frames/

…  really hard to capture the clear liquid glue of Gutermann's glue on camera, so I've taken pics of the inner …  off with ease!  :) *If you are a novice, pre-tape your fabric to protect it from excess glue.  Tape the areas where you don't …  shown in purple."][/caption] *After inserting the fabric on that side, let it set for 5 minutes before starting the other side.  …

Topics: Helpful Tips, Gutermann glue, Glue, Adhesive, fabric glue, clutch glue</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7168-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7168_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:48:47">http://gotli.wordpress.com/2009/05/12/the-making-of-gothic-lolita-mini-hat-part-2/</link><title>The making of; Gothic Lolita mini hat (part2)</title><description>The making of; Gothic Lolita mini hat (part2)

12 May 2009 by bama44 on BAMA gotli.wordpress.com/2009/05/12/the-making-of-gothic-lolita-mini-hat-part-2/

…  5; 5\. Then you will get this sudden information about a fabric that is used to make other fabrics hard. It has a side with glue on,. The fabric you have cut in part 4, have to be marked again on this …

Topics: Posts, 1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7168-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7168_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:49:14">http://mariebrowning.wordpress.com/2012/09/28/no-sew-fabric-embellishments/</link><title>"No-Sew" Fabric Embellishments</title><description>"No-Sew" Fabric Embellishments

28 Sep 2012 by mariebrowning on Marie Browning mariebrowning.wordpress.com/2012/09/28/no-sew-fabric-embellishments/

…  are some easy no-sew fabric embellishments that can be made with Tombow’s MONO Multi and MONO …  chipboard tag from Bazzill, and use MONO Aqua Liquid Glue to glue on the fabric. Cut the fabric around the edge leaving a ¼” overhang of fabric. Let …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7168-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7168_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:49:47">http://craftycrafts.wordpress.com/2010/09/07/cute-rugs/</link><title>Cute Rugs!</title><description>Cute Rugs!

7 Sep 2010 by kamikinard on crafty crafts craftycrafts.wordpress.com/2010/09/07/cute-rugs/

…  Girl Dolls, or for any other dolls too! Materials: Fuzzy Fabric Funky Fringe Fabric Glue Scissors   Directions: 1\. Cut fabric to the size and shape you …

Topics: Crafts for Your Dolls, crafts for dolls, crafts for girls and boys, 18" doll crafts, doll crafts</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7168-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7168_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:50:28">http://blog.austinkids.org/2010/04/14/batik-for-kids/</link><title>Batik for kids!</title><description>Batik for kids!

14 Apr 2010 by austinkids blog.austinkids.org/2010/04/14/batik-for-kids/

…  craft paint Washable clear (or blue) school glue Paint brushes Fabric you want to paint 1\. Draw your pattern with glue onto your fabric.  I used an old pair of shoes that are made of cloth. Let your glue dry …

Topics: Craft, 5 years &amp; up, Batik, Fabric Arts</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>