<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7173"> severed spinal cord</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:08:44" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7173-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7173_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:08:45">http://beyondthedish.wordpress.com/2013/12/13/stem-cell-mediated-scarring-of-the-spinal-cord-aids-in-recovery/</link><title>Stem Cell-Mediated Scarring of the Spinal Cord Aids in Recovery</title><description>Stem Cell-Mediated Scarring of the Spinal Cord Aids in Recovery

14 Dec 2013 by mburatov on Beyond the Dish beyondthedish.wordpress.com/2013/12/13/stem-cell-mediated-scarring-of-the-spinal-cord-aids-in-recovery/

…  injury to the spinal cord, glial cells and neural stem cells in the spinal cord contribute to the …  of paralysis. Such paralysis is often permanent, since the severed nerves do not grow back. The absence of neural regeneration required …

Topics: Alternatives to Embryonic Stem Cells, Neurological treatments, stem cell biology, model systems, neural stem cells, spinal cord injury, spinal cord injury, axon sprouting, chondroitin sulfate proteoglycans, NoGo, myelin-associated glycoprotein, oligodendrocyte myelin glycoprotein, axonal growth cones, axon repulsion, glial scar, Olfactory ensheathing cells, spinal cord regeneration</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7173-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7173_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:09:07">http://news.optuszoo.com.au/2014/03/25/mckinnon-has-vertebrae-fracture/</link><title>McKinnon has vertebrae fracture</title><description>McKinnon has vertebrae fracture

24 Mar 2014 by Optus Zoo on Optus Zoo News news.optuszoo.com.au/2014/03/25/mckinnon-has-vertebrae-fracture/

…  McKinnon has a C4 and C5 vertebrae fracture but that his spinal cord is not severed. McKinnon was injured and carried off on a stretcher during Monday …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7173-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7173_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:09:32">http://northeastchapter.wordpress.com/2008/10/08/blair-morgan-paralyzed/</link><title>Blair Morgan Paralyzed</title><description>Blair Morgan Paralyzed

9 Oct 2008 by sledmass on Northeast Chapter News northeastchapter.wordpress.com/2008/10/08/blair-morgan-paralyzed/

…  superstar, crushed his T5 and T6 vertebrae causing major spinal cord damage. He underwent surgery in Montreal where doctors confirmed his spinal cord was severed, resulting in paralysis from just above the …

Topics: News, Announcements, General Interest</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7173-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7173_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:09:56">http://sarahpflanagan.wordpress.com/2012/06/04/robotic-rehabilitation-helps-rats-recover-from-spinal-cord-injuries/</link><title>Robotic Rehabilitation helps Rats Recover from Spinal Cord Injuries</title><description>Robotic Rehabilitation helps Rats Recover from Spinal Cord Injuries

4 Jun 2012 by sarahpflanagan sarahpflanagan.wordpress.com/2012/06/04/robotic-rehabilitation-helps-rats-recover-from-spinal-cord-injuries/

…  found that rats with partially-severed spinal cords could recover the ability to walk with a combination of drug …  alternative neural pathways, rather than the spinal cord, to bypass the injury. It's a pretty neat finding and provides a new …

Topics: Science, Science, technology</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7173-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7173_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:10:21">http://mbtimetraveler.com/2013/07/07/human-head-transplants-soon-possible/</link><title>Human head transplants soon possible</title><description>Human head transplants soon possible

7 Jul 2013 by Michael Bradley on Michael Bradley - Time Traveler mbtimetraveler.com/2013/07/07/human-head-transplants-soon-possible/

…  head transplants has been being unable to connect the spinal cord of the head to the donor’s body.  This leaves the animal paralyzed from …  advancements regarding the reconnection of surgically severed spinal cords has lead Canevero to believe the procedure can be …

Topics: Humor and Observations, Science, transplants, human head transplant, frankenstein, Surgical Neurology International, Dr. Sergio Canevero, Turin Advanced Neuromodulation Group</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7173-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7173_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:10:46">http://qz.com/99413/first-ever-human-head-transplant-is-now-possible-says-neuroscientist/</link><title>First-ever human head transplant is now possible, says neuroscientist</title><description>First-ever human head transplant is now possible, says neuroscientist

1 Jul 2013 by Christopher Mims on Quartz qz.com/99413/first-ever-human-head-transplant-is-now-possible-says-neuroscientist/

…  that scientists were unable to connect the animals' spinal cords to their donor bodies, leaving them paralyzed below the point of …  advances in re-connecting spinal cords that are surgically severed mean that it should be technically feasible to do it in humans. (This …

Topics: technology, Science, Medicine, Research, Neuroscience, Medical Science, Bioethics, transplant, Head Transplant, Sergio Canavero, Turin Advanced Neuromodulation Group</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7173-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7173_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:11:13">http://neurophilosophy.wordpress.com/2006/08/18/a-bridge-over-severed-axons/</link><title>A bridge over severed axons</title><description>A bridge over severed axons

18 Aug 2006 by Mo Costandi on Mo Costandi neurophilosophy.wordpress.com/2006/08/18/a-bridge-over-severed-axons/

…  with an enzyme was used to regenerate axons in the severed spinal cord of rats, leading to a partial restoration of mobility. First, short …

Topics: Neuroscience</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7173-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7173_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:11:28">http://globalgrind.com/2010/10/15/teen-shoots-a-12-yr-old-and-severed-his-spinal-cord-police-also-found-a-mean-arsenal-of-weapons-a/</link><title>Teen Shoots A 12 yr Old And Severed His Spinal Cord, Police Also found A Mean Arsenal Of Weapons At Shooter's Crib.</title><description>Teen Shoots A 12 yr Old And Severed His Spinal Cord, Police Also found A Mean Arsenal Of Weapons At Shooter's Crib.

15 Oct 2010 by James Fuller on Global Grind globalgrind.com/2010/10/15/teen-shoots-a-12-yr-old-and-severed-his-spinal-cord-police-also-found-a-mean-arsenal-of-weapons-a/

Teen Shoots A 12 yr Old And Severed His Spinal Cord, Police Also found A Mean Arsenal Of Weapons At Shooter's Crib.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7173-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7173_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:12:04">http://beyondthedish.wordpress.com/2011/12/06/repairing-spinal-cord-injury-with-dental-pulp-stem-cells/</link><title>Repairing Spinal Cord Injury With Dental Pulp Stem Cells</title><description>Repairing Spinal Cord Injury With Dental Pulp Stem Cells

6 Dec 2011 by mburatov on Beyond the Dish beyondthedish.wordpress.com/2011/12/06/repairing-spinal-cord-injury-with-dental-pulp-stem-cells/

…  human dental pulp stem cells to treat rats with severe spinal cord injury. When these spinal cord-injured rats were transplanted with …  and their support cells; they promoted the regeneration of severed nerves; and they replaced lost support cells by generating new ones. …

Topics: Alternatives to Embryonic Stem Cells, Neurological treatments</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7173-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7173_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:12:20">http://amoraloutrage.wordpress.com/2013/11/07/spinal-cord-injury-prosthetic-bladder-controls-urine/</link><title>Spinal cord injury: Prosthetic bladder 'controls urine'</title><description>Spinal cord injury: Prosthetic bladder 'controls urine'

8 Nov 2013 by Heidi on A Moral Outrage amoraloutrage.wordpress.com/2013/11/07/spinal-cord-injury-prosthetic-bladder-controls-urine/

…  could one day restore bladder function to patients with a severed spinal cord has been devised by UK researchers and tested in animals. Nerve …

Topics: health, Medical Discoveries</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>