<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7185">constitution of italy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:07:29" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7185-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7185_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:07:30">http://giustiziaitaliana.wordpress.com/2013/01/16/homes-in-italy-never-buying-a-house-or-apartment-in-italy/</link><title>Homes in Italy: Never Buying a House or Apartment in Italy</title><description>Homes in Italy: Never Buying a House or Apartment in Italy

16 Jan 2013 by ricky300668 on Giustizia Italiana giustiziaitaliana.wordpress.com/2013/01/16/homes-in-italy-never-buying-a-house-or-apartment-in-italy/

…  case, a paradox, a trap. You should know that in Italy the Constitution is shredded paper also the machinery of justice and twisted and perverse. Never buy a house in Italy, if you do, …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7185-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7185_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:08:01">http://antoniocapillo82.wordpress.com/2011/07/16/viva-litalia/</link><title>Viva l'Italia!</title><description>Viva l'Italia!

16 Jul 2011 by Antonio Capillo on DEVELOPMENT IN PROGRESS antoniocapillo82.wordpress.com/2011/07/16/viva-litalia/

…  Italy, from now on, if you feel you are victim of mobbing or unjust firing from your employer and you want to take him/her/it …  Eventually, we will get rid of useless judges, courts, and Constitution. Reaching the first realised utopia of a country without crime. …

Topics: Italy, Mother Country, Italia, roman law, labour law, Mafia, taxes, rigts, constitution, italian constitution</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7185-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7185_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:08:18">http://jsandersavvocatoamericano.wordpress.com/2014/01/31/constitutional-differences-differenze-costituzionale/</link><title>Constitutional Differences (Differenze Costituzionale)</title><description>Constitutional Differences (Differenze Costituzionale)

31 Jan 2014 by John Sanders on J Sanders: Avvocato Americano jsandersavvocatoamericano.wordpress.com/2014/01/31/constitutional-differences-differenze-costituzionale/

…  of the three topics of this blog are law and Italy.  Yet, I haven't addressed the differences between the U.S. Constitution and the Italian Constitution.  I'd like to take note of some …

Topics: Law, Italy, John Sanders, constitution, Supreme Court, SCOTUS</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7185-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7185_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:08:41">http://mcinitaly.wordpress.com/2013/10/01/mara-love/</link><title>Mara Love</title><description>Mara Love

1 Oct 2013 by studyabroadmeredith on Meredith College in Italy mcinitaly.wordpress.com/2013/10/01/mara-love/

…  to travel has helped us to expand our horizons in terms of not only cultural differences between Italy and America but also in …  changed over time.  We discussed what is included in the Constitution and why it is there.  The Assembly to write the Constitution was …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7185-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7185_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:09:04">http://appablog.wordpress.com/2012/11/06/italy-libya-terzi-in-tripoli-support-for-strengthening-of-libyan-institutions-and-society/</link><title>Italy-Libya: Terzi in Tripoli - Support for strengthening of Libyan institutions and society</title><description>Italy-Libya: Terzi in Tripoli - Support for strengthening of Libyan institutions and society

6 Nov 2012 by africanpressorganization on Database of Press Releases related to Africa - APO-Source appablog.wordpress.com/2012/11/06/italy-libya-terzi-in-tripoli-support-for-strengthening-of-libyan-institutions-and-society/

…   Italy-Libya: Terzi in Tripoli - Support for strengthening of Libyan institutions and society  ROME, Italy, November 6, 2012/African …  Mario Monti, who conveyed his congratulations for the constitution of the new government in a letter to Prime Minister …

Topics: Libya, FOR Foreign Policy, Italy</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7185-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7185_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:09:35">http://laroucheirishbrigade.com/2012/07/03/defense-of-constitutional-values-by-germany-lets-join-them/</link><title>DEFENSE OF CONSTITUTIONAL VALUES BY GERMANY: LET'S JOIN THEM</title><description>DEFENSE OF CONSTITUTIONAL VALUES BY GERMANY: LET'S JOIN THEM

3 Jul 2012 by LaRouche Irish Brigade on LaRouche Irish Brigade laroucheirishbrigade.com/2012/07/03/defense-of-constitutional-values-by-germany-lets-join-them/

…  of Lidia Undiemi of Sicily for {Wall Street Journal Italia}: Merkel …  is the prelude to a historic battle in the defense of the Constitution which will inevitably cross national borders, since a negative …  from going into force in the 16 other nations, including Italy. Thousands of citizens, but also parliamentarians and high-level …

Topics: Economy, Euro, Europe, Eurozone, ECB, British imperial strategy, republicanism, Mario Monti, Italy, national sovereignty, Constitutional law, Austerity Treaty, British Financial Empire, Angela Merkel, German Constitutional Court, esm treaty, Lidia Undiemi, Sicily</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7185-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7185_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:10:08">http://tamermowafy.wordpress.com/2011/11/16/my-bookmarx-11162011/</link><title>My Bookmarx 11/16/2011</title><description>My Bookmarx 11/16/2011

16 Nov 2011 by Tamer Mowafy on بهدوء tamermowafy.wordpress.com/2011/11/16/my-bookmarx-11162011/

Italy: The fall of the empire | libcom.org Last night a huge crowd gathered outside …  A German Referendum on Europe? Merkel Eyes Constitution Revamp to Boost EU Powers - SPIEGEL ONLINE - News - International …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7185-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7185_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:10:30">http://appablog.wordpress.com/2012/06/14/nigeria-new-arab-constitutions-should-envisage-protection-for-religious-minorities-says-terzi/</link><title>Nigeria: New Arab constitutions should envisage protection for religious minorities, says Terzi</title><description>Nigeria: New Arab constitutions should envisage protection for religious minorities, says Terzi

14 Jun 2012 by africanpressorganization on Database of Press Releases related to Africa - APO-Source appablog.wordpress.com/2012/06/14/nigeria-new-arab-constitutions-should-envisage-protection-for-religious-minorities-says-terzi/

…  protection for religious minorities, says Terzi  ROME, Italy, June 14, 2012/African Press Organization (APO)/ -- Italy is working to …  world" that are inspired by "the consolidation of constitutions, values and principles that bring more protection for …

Topics: Nigeria, FOR Foreign Policy, REL Religion, Italy</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7185-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7185_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:10:54">http://purbeckhumanities.co.uk/2010/09/24/timeline-of-1848-9-revolutions-in-italy/</link><title>Timeline of 1848-9 Revolutions in Italy</title><description>Timeline of 1848-9 Revolutions in Italy

24 Sep 2010 by MRY on The Purbeck School Humanities Blog - History, Geography, PRE purbeckhumanities.co.uk/2010/09/24/timeline-of-1848-9-revolutions-in-italy/

…  of 1848 in Europe and Italy Note especially the sequence of events. In some areas the …  Revolution   Jan. 12. Revolution in Palermo demands Constitution of 1812       Feb. 10. Ferdinando II grants a …

Topics: History, A Level (GCE), Italy</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7185-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7185_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:11:16">http://wanderinggourmet.wordpress.com/2007/03/31/italian-becomes-official-language-of-italy/</link><title>Italian becomes official language ... of Italy?</title><description>Italian becomes official language ... of Italy?

31 Mar 2007 by angie on The Wandering Gourmet wanderinggourmet.wordpress.com/2007/03/31/italian-becomes-official-language-of-italy/

…  is confused that Italian was not the official language of Italy? Or is it just me? This is bizarre - I always thought the official …  language has only been put through as part of the Italian Constitution. And 75 Politicians opposed Italian being the official language of …

Topics: Culture, language, News</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>