<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7235">silicone roof coatings</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:49:03" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7235-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7235_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:49:04">http://davem5771.wordpress.com/2013/12/09/best-flat-roof-replacement-for-tpo-santa-fe-silicone-coating/</link><title>Best Flat Roof Replacement For TPO Santa Fe (Silicone Coating)</title><description>Best Flat Roof Replacement For TPO Santa Fe (Silicone Coating)

9 Dec 2013 by dave on Dave the AD/HD Guy davem5771.wordpress.com/2013/12/09/best-flat-roof-replacement-for-tpo-santa-fe-silicone-coating/

…  Flat Roof Replacement for TPO Santa Fe (Silicone Coating) Is your TPO Roof …  material but the seams. The Solution ?   A seamless 100% Silicone Coating  ( 50 Year Product Warranty).  No need for tearing off that …

Topics: Best Flat Roof Replacement for TPO Santa Fe, Flat roof Replacement Santa Fe, flat roof estimate, Roofing Contractor Santa Fe, Roof Replacement Albuquerque NM, TPO Roof Repair Santa Fe, Roof Repair Albuquerque, NM, Flat Roof Repair Albuquerque, NM, Roof Repair Rio Rancho, NM, Roof Repair Santa Fe, NM, Flat Roof repair Rio Rancho, NM, 5 Star Roof Repair Reviews Albuquerque Rio Rancho Santa, Roof Repair Roof Albuquerque NM, Roof Repair Reviews Rio Rancho, Commercial Roof Replacement &amp; Repair Albuquerque, R, Commercial Roof Repair &amp; Replacement Albuquerque, commercial roof coating, Flat Roof Replacement for TPO Santa Fe, TPO Roof Coating Santa Fe</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7235-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7235_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:49:27">http://buyliquidroof.wordpress.com/2014/03/13/elastomeric-coatings-for-new-roofs-and-retrofits/</link><title>Elastomeric Coatings for New Roofs and Retrofits</title><description>Elastomeric Coatings for New Roofs and Retrofits

13 Mar 2014 by buyliquidroof on Buy Liquid Roof buyliquidroof.wordpress.com/2014/03/13/elastomeric-coatings-for-new-roofs-and-retrofits/

…  Guaranteed to “last 20-25 years, longer than other roof coating materials. Help home or business owners to save money when heating …  Neoprene • Hypalon • Latex/acrylic • Silicone • Urethane With most roof membranes Elastomeric roof coatings …

Topics: Buyliquidroof.com, elastomeric roof coatings</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7235-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7235_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:49:48">http://buyliquidroof.wordpress.com/2014/03/20/choose-elastomeric-coatings-to-protect-your-roof/</link><title>Choose Elastomeric Coatings to Protect Your Roof</title><description>Choose Elastomeric Coatings to Protect Your Roof

20 Mar 2014 by buyliquidroof on Buy Liquid Roof buyliquidroof.wordpress.com/2014/03/20/choose-elastomeric-coatings-to-protect-your-roof/

…  rain, and heat all combine inevitably take a beating over roof and causing damage and leaking. To protect your roof, it is important to …  elastomeric coatings are butyl, acrylic, polyurethane, and silicone. The best option for flat roof repair or for low-sloping roof is …

Topics: Buyliquidroof.com, elastomeric roof coatings</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7235-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7235_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:50:10">http://bornofgaia.wordpress.com/2010/06/01/rv-roof-repair-cobra-is-shedding-an-old-skin/</link><title>RV roof repair: Cobra is shedding an old skin</title><description>RV roof repair: Cobra is shedding an old skin

1 Jun 2010 by bornofgaia on Bornofgaia's Blog bornofgaia.wordpress.com/2010/06/01/rv-roof-repair-cobra-is-shedding-an-old-skin/

…  a morning and an afternoon scraping away layers of  old roof patch, waterproofing tape, silicone, and road dirt.  Once I had all the seams exposed and relatively …

Topics: Green Living, motor home, d-i-y</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7235-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7235_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:50:53">http://epdmcoatings.wordpress.com/2014/03/26/elastomeric-roof-coating-beneficial-for-roofing-epdmcoatings-com/</link><title>Elastomeric Roof Coating beneficial for roofing – Epdmcoatings.com</title><description>Elastomeric Roof Coating beneficial for roofing – Epdmcoatings.com

26 Mar 2014 by Brian McCalister on EPDM Coatings LLC epdmcoatings.wordpress.com/2014/03/26/elastomeric-roof-coating-beneficial-for-roofing-epdmcoatings-com/

…  kinds of roofs can be saved with an elastomeric roof coating .One that greatly resembles rubber once it’s applied. Benefit …  to freshly sprayed polyurethane foam. Unlike some other coatings, elastomeric coatings can handle those and ones with just about any …  bitumen or a single-ply application of PVC or TPO. Silicone Elastomeric Coatings Silicone elastomeric coating displays …

Topics: elastomeric roof coatings, elastomeric roof coatings</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7235-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7235_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:51:08">http://neogard.wordpress.com/2012/02/03/guide-specs/</link><title>Guide Spec’s</title><description>Guide Spec’s

3 Feb 2012 by neogard on NEOGARD High Performance Coating Systems neogard.wordpress.com/2012/02/03/guide-specs/

…  new Fluid-Applied Roof Coating and Coated Foamed Roofing specifications are now available on …  M Permathane FR Permathane II FR Elastacryl FR Silicone …

Topics: Daily news</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7235-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7235_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:51:31">http://supplies.twobuffalo.com/neogard-biodegradable-cleaner/</link><title>NEOGARD BioDegradable Cleaner</title><description>NEOGARD BioDegradable Cleaner

7 Nov 2010 by Alex V on Two Buffalo Construction Supplies supplies.twobuffalo.com/neogard-biodegradable-cleaner/

…  can be used to clean existing acrylic, polyurethane, and silicone roof and wall surfaces. It can also be used to clean uncoated surfaces like …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7235-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7235_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:51:49">http://conformalcoating.wordpress.com/2013/06/11/designing-for-selective-robotic-conformal-coating-processing-rule-13-sticking-coatings-to-non-stick-silicones-is-a-pain/</link><title>Designing for Selective Robotic Conformal Coating Processing: Rule 13 "Sticking coatings to non stick silicones is a pain"</title><description>Designing for Selective Robotic Conformal Coating Processing: Rule 13 "Sticking coatings to non stick silicones is a pain"

11 Jun 2013 by Lee Hitchens on Conformal Coating conformalcoating.wordpress.com/2013/06/11/designing-for-selective-robotic-conformal-coating-processing-rule-13-sticking-coatings-to-non-stick-silicones-is-a-pain/

…  silicone RTVs to circuit boards to provide support to components for long term …  to the surface unless the conformal coating itself is a silicone. Acrylic and urethane coatings do not stick to silicone. So, don't try unless you want defects …

Topics: conformal coating, conformal coatings, Spray, Robot, selective, Conformal Coating Processing, Equipment, Robotic, design rules</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7235-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7235_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:52:07">http://conformalcoating.wordpress.com/2010/06/23/silicone-conformal-coating-dip-application-systems/</link><title>Silicone Conformal Coating Dip Application Systems</title><description>Silicone Conformal Coating Dip Application Systems

23 Jun 2010 by Lee Hitchens on Conformal Coating conformalcoating.wordpress.com/2010/06/23/silicone-conformal-coating-dip-application-systems/

…  offer Dip Conformal Coating Equipment for processing silicone conformal coatings in batch, inline and customised processes in electronic production. …  up to handle silicones correctly incuding moisture cure silicone conformal coatings.  All of the dip conformal coating systems can …

Topics: Humiseal conformal coating</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7235-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7235_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:52:29">http://conformalcoating.wordpress.com/2009/03/05/dip-conformal-coating-using-silicone-conformal-coatings/</link><title>Dip Conformal Coating using Silicone Conformal Coatings</title><description>Dip Conformal Coating using Silicone Conformal Coatings

5 Mar 2009 by Lee Hitchens on Conformal Coating conformalcoating.wordpress.com/2009/03/05/dip-conformal-coating-using-silicone-conformal-coatings/

…  understand the special requirements of dipping silicone conformal coatings. Using their DS101 Conformal Coating Dip system, the issues of dipping …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>