<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7239">roundabout safety</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:04:45" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7239-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7239_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:04:46">http://local4traffic.wordpress.com/2009/08/19/a-hawk-watching-over-you/</link><title>A "HAWK" watching over you!</title><description>A "HAWK" watching over you!

19 Aug 2009 by wdivblog on Local 4 Traffic local4traffic.wordpress.com/2009/08/19/a-hawk-watching-over-you/

…  beacons at the pedestrian crossings at the Maple/Drake roundabout in West Bloomfield Township. The HAWK is a new form of pedestrian …  pedestrians cross the approaches to a roundabout. “Safety is the top priority of the Road Commission for Oakland County, and we …

Topics: Traffic, Oakland County, Lauren Podell, hawk</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7239-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7239_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:05:12">http://ciprianicharlesdesigns.wordpress.com/2014/04/12/roundabouts-engineers-making-the-world-a-little-more-beautiful-and-safe/</link><title>Roundabouts: Engineers making the world a little more beautiful and safe.</title><description>Roundabouts: Engineers making the world a little more beautiful and safe.

12 Apr 2014 by CCD Engineering on Cipriani Charles Designs ciprianicharlesdesigns.wordpress.com/2014/04/12/roundabouts-engineers-making-the-world-a-little-more-beautiful-and-safe/

…  for many years.   Definition. A roundabout is a physical layout where a number of approach roads join a …  serve a multitude of functions such as: 1\. Traffic Safety According to the Insurance Institute of Highway Safety (IIHS) …  by allowing all vehicles to merge into streams around the roundabout and then to diverge out to the desired radiating …

Topics: roundabouts, Roundabouts: Engineers making the world a little more b, Traffic Safety, Smoother transitions., Aesthetics, Operations and maintenance, environmentally friendly</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7239-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7239_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:05:55">http://roundlakeroadproject.com/2013/12/04/pedestrian-safety-information-and-roundabouts-near-schools/</link><title>Pedestrian Safety Information and Roundabouts near Schools</title><description>Pedestrian Safety Information and Roundabouts near Schools

4 Dec 2013 by Creighton Manning on Round Lake Road Improvement Project roundlakeroadproject.com/2013/12/04/pedestrian-safety-information-and-roundabouts-near-schools/

…  is independent information regarding pedestrian safety at roundabouts and collected information regarding roundabouts located near schools. 1 - Insurance Institute of Highway Safety Q&amp;A (Question #8) - "Studies in Europe indicate that, on …  – Federal Highway Administration (FHWA) Roundabout Guide, Chapter 5 - Safety. -Section 5.1 discusses the overall …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7239-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7239_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:06:11">http://mywheelsareturning.com/map-roundies-in-michigan/</link><title>Michigan Roundabouts &amp; Resources</title><description>Michigan Roundabouts &amp; Resources

19 May 2010 by GLHowe on MyWHaT mywheelsareturning.com/map-roundies-in-michigan/

…  for Division St.  Elsewhere... Slides: Pedestrian Safety and Accessibility Considerations at Modern Roundabouts (PDF) WI-DOT Roundabout Guidelines  Latest NCHRP report: Roundabouts and Pedestrians with …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7239-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7239_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:06:56">http://essentialsforlife.com.au/2013/10/20/how-to-drive-safely-around-a-roundabout-road-safety-series/</link><title>How to drive safely around a roundabout \- Road Safety Series</title><description>How to drive safely around a roundabout \- Road Safety Series

20 Oct 2013 by ezinternet on Essentials For Life essentialsforlife.com.au/2013/10/20/how-to-drive-safely-around-a-roundabout-road-safety-series/

Road Safety Series \- Roundabouts Learn how to safely enter and exit a roundabout. CLICK ON THE IMAGE to be taken to the video that shows you the correct procedures for roundabouts...

Topics: road safety, roundabouts, how a driving school would teach roundabouts, learners test, how to drive around a roundabout, Learning to Drive, Life’s Important Things, Road Safety Series</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7239-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7239_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:07:16">http://stilwellpartnership.wordpress.com/road-safety/</link><title>Road Safety</title><description>Road Safety

9 Dec 2009 by stilwellpartnership on The Stilwell Partnership Blog stilwellpartnership.wordpress.com/road-safety/

…  continue to pioneer measures to improve road safety for all, by good design and by improved training for road users. Our …  In 1990, we developed and introduced the first tracked roundabout in the UK. This made use of spiral white road markings to take vehicles through a roundabout safely, minimising the number of conflicting traffic movements.  …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7239-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7239_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:07:32">http://trialbyjeory.wordpress.com/2011/11/18/boris-agrees-urgent-safety-review-of-deadly-bow-roundabout/</link><title>Boris agrees urgent safety review of deadly Bow roundabout</title><description>Boris agrees urgent safety review of deadly Bow roundabout

18 Nov 2011 by trialbyjeory on Trial by Jeory trialbyjeory.wordpress.com/2011/11/18/boris-agrees-urgent-safety-review-of-deadly-bow-roundabout/

…  of two cyclists on the so-called cycle superhighway at Bow Roundabout, London Assembly member John Biggs has now secured a commitment from Boris Johnson for an urgent safety review. Here is John's press release: Boris and TfL agree …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7239-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7239_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:07:59">http://us41momentum.com/modern-roundabouts-are-safer-and-dont-waste-time-and-fuel/</link><title>?Roundabouts?</title><description>?Roundabouts?

25 Mar 2012 by US41Momentum on Multimodal Momentum us41momentum.com/modern-roundabouts-are-safer-and-dont-waste-time-and-fuel/

…  courtesy of Washington State DOThttp://www.wsdot.wa.gov/safety/roundabouts/benefits.htm[/caption] Florida Roundabout Inventory - (click) Florida-Roundabouts-Inventory There are …  must slow down and yield to traffic before entering a roundabout. Speeds in the roundabout are typically between 15 and 20 miles per …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7239-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7239_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:08:27">http://roadsafety.wordpress.com/2009/07/15/roundabout-driving-explained/</link><title>Roundabout driving explained!</title><description>Roundabout driving explained!

15 Jul 2009 by roadsafety on Road Safety &amp; Arrive Alive Blog roadsafety.wordpress.com/2009/07/15/roundabout-driving-explained/

…  drive at roundabouts! We have approached the road safety experts of the Arrive Alive road safety website, and gained valuable advice on how to drive safely at …  would like to advise visitors to view the Road Safety Blog and this Blog post: Teach drivers which lane to drive at a …

Topics: Arrive Alive Website, Road Safety Advice, ArriveAlive.mobi</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7239-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7239_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:08:48">http://journolisaventura.wordpress.com/2012/09/20/whittington-roundabout-issue-result/</link><title>Whittington Roundabout Issue - Result</title><description>Whittington Roundabout Issue - Result

20 Sep 2012 by Lisa S Ventura on Lisa Ventura: Hold The Front Page! journolisaventura.wordpress.com/2012/09/20/whittington-roundabout-issue-result/

…  due to the amount of press coverage that the Whittington Roundabout issue has received, and due to the amount of comments about how …  is since the roadworks took place, there will be an urgent safety review of the roundabout in the next few weeks. Obviously I would …

Topics: PR, News</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>