<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7259">radish root</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:28:18" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7259-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7259_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:28:19">http://throughatoonerdarkly.wordpress.com/2014/01/03/radish-roots/</link><title>Radish Roots</title><description>Radish Roots

3 Jan 2014 by nilochahtims on through a tooner, darkly throughatoonerdarkly.wordpress.com/2014/01/03/radish-roots/

Topics: rotoscope, Food, light, Lebanon, Close-Up, reflection 2, Shadow, Purple, Pink, COLOR, Plant, Illumination, round</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7259-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7259_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:28:46">http://whyraw.wordpress.com/2010/02/24/root/</link><title>Day 23 - roots</title><description>Day 23 - roots

24 Feb 2010 by Gabriel Azoulay on WHY - Wellness, Health, Yoga whyraw.wordpress.com/2010/02/24/root/

…  the organs that contain the seeds of life. The burdock root, a long, string like root, with its snake like quality it's phallic symbol might escape us. However, take the radish, a small, pink hue dot of a pod, shielded with a large array of green …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7259-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7259_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:29:13">http://fzheng01.wordpress.com/2011/03/30/the-art-of-gardening-root-crop/</link><title>The art of gardening-----root crop</title><description>The art of gardening-----root crop

30 Mar 2011 by fzheng01 on Decorative Art fzheng01.wordpress.com/2011/03/30/the-art-of-gardening-root-crop/

Root crop is a major producer in the garden from carrots to daikon to parsley. They …  into the late season. Especially a purple kind of leaves radish is the queen of the vegetables. We all see the difference between mature big radish and small under-development radish. We all knew that we like root crops …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7259-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7259_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:29:39">http://easyrecipes2.wordpress.com/2012/10/13/radish-leaf-and-root-tart/</link><title>Radish Leaf and Root Tart</title><description>Radish Leaf and Root Tart

13 Oct 2012 by easyrecipes2 on easy food recipes easyrecipes2.wordpress.com/2012/10/13/radish-leaf-and-root-tart/

…  so to inject a little colour into our lives I made these Radish Tarts.  Not only is it pretty, it is also frugal as I've used both the radish greens (tops) and the root.In the past I've made the most of my turnip greens: making …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7259-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7259_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:30:04">http://sourplum.wordpress.com/2009/03/10/winter-vegetable-review/</link><title>WINTER VEGETABLE REVIEW</title><description>WINTER VEGETABLE REVIEW

10 Mar 2009 by Monica on the sour plum sourplum.wordpress.com/2009/03/10/winter-vegetable-review/

…  Radish   Right: A season ends and a season begins with radish, turnip, and tomato salad Winter is wearing out its last weeks and …  too late.  What a rich winter it was with the variety of root vegetables that grow in the cold dirt of the north: black radish, turnip …

Topics: Dinner, Appetizer, winter, autumn, Vegetables, Tarts, amuse bouche, Turnip, salad, winter vegetables, radish, Beets, celery root, romanesco, parsnip, pumpkin, Carrot, Seasons, Savory</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7259-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7259_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:30:21">http://carolyncaresblog.com/2013/10/08/tillage-radish-cover-crop-update/</link><title>Tillage Radish Cover Crop Update</title><description>Tillage Radish Cover Crop Update

8 Oct 2013 by carolyncares on Carolyn CAREs carolyncaresblog.com/2013/10/08/tillage-radish-cover-crop-update/

…  have been asking, so here is an update on our Tillage Radish and Oat cover crop. We have received more rain this fall than we have …  from other crops grown in our area. The leaves and the root will almost disappear completely over the winter, leaving the nutrients …

Topics: farm, Agriculture, organic, Organic, Cover Crop, cover crop, Tillage radish</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7259-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7259_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:30:49">http://passionsandmusings.wordpress.com/2009/10/19/perfect-drink-for-halloween/</link><title>Perfect drink for Halloween...</title><description>Perfect drink for Halloween...

19 Oct 2009 by consuelobernardi on passionsandmusings passionsandmusings.wordpress.com/2009/10/19/perfect-drink-for-halloween/

…  of Canadian Living.EyeballtiniVeins and all, this carved radish eyeball is a fantastic accent for a classic gin martini. Up the creep factor by leaving the 'optic nerve' (or hairy root end) attached.2 oz gin or vodka (50 ml)1/4 oz dry vermouth (7 ml)eyeball:1 …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7259-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7259_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:31:08">http://vmccallblog.com/2013/03/06/radish-bunch-solo/</link><title>Radish Bunch Solo</title><description>Radish Bunch Solo

6 Mar 2013 by vmccall on VICTORIA MCCALL vmccallblog.com/2013/03/06/radish-bunch-solo/

Radish Bunch     ©2010 Victoria McCall  This painting, titled Radish Bunch, was inspired by a scene which caught my eye while shopping. The …  small painting celebrates the exuberance of that little radish bunch in its own unfurled solo …

Topics: Painting, Still Life, radish, Art</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7259-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7259_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:31:36">http://foodspark.wordpress.com/2013/03/10/root-salad-fennel-celery-root-radish/</link><title>root salad - fennel, celery root, radish</title><description>root salad - fennel, celery root, radish

10 Mar 2013 by LC on food spark foodspark.wordpress.com/2013/03/10/root-salad-fennel-celery-root-radish/

root salad - fennel, celery root, radish, a photo by pipsyq on Flickr.

Topics: Food</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7259-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7259_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:31:55">http://agsciencewriter.wordpress.com/2014/04/17/radishes-a-new-cover-crop-option/</link><title>Radishes: A new cover crop option</title><description>Radishes: A new cover crop option

17 Apr 2014 by jhgiese on Ag Science Writer agsciencewriter.wordpress.com/2014/04/17/radishes-a-new-cover-crop-option/

…  forage or oilseed radishes began to take root several years ago, and their use as cover crops is growing. Both are …  of being used for cover crops and animal forages. Forage radish (Raphanus sativus L. var. niger J. Kern.), also known as the daikon radish or Japanese radish, has a very large taproot. Originally developed for …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>