<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7261">elvish language</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:36:24" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7261-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7261_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:36:26">http://russellzazueta.wordpress.com/2014/03/17/constructed-lenguage-assignment/</link><title>Constructed Lenguage Assignment</title><description>Constructed Lenguage Assignment

17 Mar 2014 by russellzr on Russell Zazueta russellzazueta.wordpress.com/2014/03/17/constructed-lenguage-assignment/

…  Today I will tell you about what is a constructed language and I will show you one language that you may like: "The Elvish".First, a planned or constructed language (short: conlang) is …

Topics: Q</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7261-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7261_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:36:44">http://takeahappymoment.wordpress.com/2013/09/27/geek-happiness-are-elvish-klingon-dothraki-and-navi-real-languages-john-mcwhorter/</link><title>Geek Happiness - Are Elvish, Klingon, Dothraki and Na'vi real languages? - John McWhorter</title><description>Geek Happiness - Are Elvish, Klingon, Dothraki and Na'vi real languages? - John McWhorter

27 Sep 2013 by TakeAHappyMoment on Take A Happy Moment takeahappymoment.wordpress.com/2013/09/27/geek-happiness-are-elvish-klingon-dothraki-and-navi-real-languages-john-mcwhorter/

…  Elvish, Klingon, Dothraki and Na'vi real languages? - John …  full lesson: http://ed.ted.com/lessons/are-elvish-... What do Game of Thrones' Dothraki, Avatar's Na'vi, Star Trek's Klingon and LOTR's Elvish have in common? They are all fantasy constructed languages, or conlangs. …

Topics: videos, Inspirational, Documentaries, STORIES/NEWS, ExtraORDINARY People, John McWhorter, klingon, game of thrones, Avatar, Constructed Language, Star Trek, Pandoran biosphere, Elvish languages, Are Elvish, Dothraki and Na’vi real languages</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7261-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7261_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:37:13">http://kateshrewsday.com/2013/05/20/how-to-get-by-in-elvish/</link><title>How To Get By In Elvish</title><description>How To Get By In Elvish

20 May 2013 by kateshrewsday on Kate Shrewsday kateshrewsday.com/2013/05/20/how-to-get-by-in-elvish/

…  mass to begin when my daughter turned and spoke to me in Elvish. I have little idea what she said, beyond the vague knowledge that it …  readily available, needless to say I would have learnt the language too. But the original language Tolkien created before the outbreak …

Topics: J.R.R. Tolkien, Fiction, lord of the rings, Shrewsday Mansions, Elvish, Quena, rivendell</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7261-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7261_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:37:51">http://ricardoqs.wordpress.com/2014/03/11/constructed-language/</link><title>Constructed Language</title><description>Constructed Language

12 Mar 2014 by ricisa9 on Art and Literature ricardoqs.wordpress.com/2014/03/11/constructed-language/

…  Language   Hi guys! This time I’m bringing to you an interesting …  heard at the famous movie “The lord of the rings”, Elvish languages. J.R.R. Tolkien was the author of the “The lord of the …  new language for this singular people and that’s when Elvish was born. The language had an initial influence by Latin, Greek  and …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7261-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7261_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:38:19">http://proswrite.com/2012/12/27/2667/</link><title>If you're entertained by invented languages, …</title><description>If you're entertained by invented languages, …

27 Dec 2012 by ProsWrite on Pros Write proswrite.com/2012/12/27/2667/

…  It lists both old and new novels which include an invented language. Plus a weather report in Elvish for Tolkien fans. Enjoy! Related articles New Zealand Weatherman …

Topics: Other Stuff</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7261-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7261_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:38:43">http://catholicdiscussion.wordpress.com/2008/02/04/elvish-translation/</link><title>Elvish Translation</title><description>Elvish Translation

4 Feb 2008 by Xavier on Master+Xavier's+Lair catholicdiscussion.wordpress.com/2008/02/04/elvish-translation/

…  out a site which has an entire area devoted to the Elvish Language. There is a sidebar on the right which contains translations of the …

Topics: My Life, Writers, Authors, Personal Commentary, Epic Films, lord of the rings, Movies, Tolkien, Middle Earth, Elves, Life, England, English, Literature, chivalry, death, Elvish, language, languages, dictionaries, dictionary, Dead Languages, ELF, Magic</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7261-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7261_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:39:10">http://www.thehumanimprint.com/2014/01/14/conlangs-what-in-the/</link><title>CONLANGS: What in the...</title><description>CONLANGS: What in the...

14 Jan 2014 by Human Imprint on The Human Imprint thehumanimprint.com/2014/01/14/conlangs-what-in-the/

…  Na'vi, Star Trek's Klingon and LOTR's Elvish are all fictitiously constructed languages used for the purpose of …  The conundrum being…what then constitutes as a real language? The TED talk may help straighten things out a …  flip this lesson by using: http://ed.ted.com/lessons/are-elvish-klingon-dothraki-and-na-vi-real-languages-john-mcwhorte …

Topics: Cultural Identity: Language, Religion, Ethnicity, Gende, TeD, Lesson Plans: Cultural Identity: Language, Religion, Et, HuGe: By Theme, language, Culture, Conlangs, Constructed Language, Elvish, TED Talks, TED education, Tolken, Avatar</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7261-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7261_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:39:35">http://hudsonmtansey.wordpress.com/2008/06/02/my-name-in-elvish/</link><title>My Name in Elvish</title><description>My Name in Elvish

2 Jun 2008 by Hudson on Rants, Raves, and Whatnots hudsonmtansey.wordpress.com/2008/06/02/my-name-in-elvish/

That is "hudson tansey" in elvish language. the site to go to, to write your name in elvish</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7261-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7261_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:39:55">http://fantasywanderlust.wordpress.com/2013/10/28/language-spotlight-elvish/</link><title>LANGUAGE SPOTLIGHT: Elvish</title><description>LANGUAGE SPOTLIGHT: Elvish

28 Oct 2013 by wanderlustcam on Wanderlust fantasywanderlust.wordpress.com/2013/10/28/language-spotlight-elvish/

…  and the way I tend to portray them. I'll start with Elvish, as that is by far the most developed language I have created (I would have liked to do Lupari, as it is a more …

Topics: People, Wanderlust, Lupari, Abril, theia, Elvish, language, Dialect, Linguistics, Fantasy</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7261-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7261_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:40:24">http://raymerick.wordpress.com/2012/09/06/how-to-write-in-elvish/</link><title>How to write in Elvish</title><description>How to write in Elvish

6 Sep 2012 by raymerick on Ray Merick raymerick.wordpress.com/2012/09/06/how-to-write-in-elvish/

…  J.R.R. Tolkien invented for Elves. He also invented the language, but it will be hard to learn and useless. But I think a lot of people will be interested in Elvish alphabet, which I just loved. It's beautiful, it looks great and …

Topics: Everything Else, Elves, lord of the rings, secret writing, elvish language, elvish alphabet</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>