<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7265">grassland plants</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:53:07" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7265-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7265_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:53:09">http://environmentalgeography.wordpress.com/2012/03/27/step-aside-rainforests/</link><title>Step Aside Rainforests</title><description>Step Aside Rainforests

27 Mar 2012 by amacvay on Environmental Geography environmentalgeography.wordpress.com/2012/03/27/step-aside-rainforests/

…  Romania, Grassland A recent article in the National Geographic Daily News reveals that …  More Diverse Than Rain Forests - In Small Areas." The grassland pictured here has the highest number of plants in a square foot - though rainforests still have the largest number of …

Topics: Current Enviro Events</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7265-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7265_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:53:36">http://danielromeroaraya.wordpress.com/2014/02/16/life-history-field-survey-average-plant-height-in-grasslands-and-disturbed-sites/</link><title>Life History Field Survey Average Plant Height in Grasslands and Disturbed Sites</title><description>Life History Field Survey Average Plant Height in Grasslands and Disturbed Sites

16 Feb 2014 by danielromeroaraya on danielromeroaraya danielromeroaraya.wordpress.com/2014/02/16/life-history-field-survey-average-plant-height-in-grasslands-and-disturbed-sites/

…  surveying three different species, ten replicates, from grassland, disturbed and forest habitats. The traits recorded included height, …  site species. Our alternative hypothesis stated that plants in the grassland would be taller than in the disturbed site using a …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7265-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7265_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:53:51">http://volcanicplainsspotlight.wordpress.com/2013/03/22/putting-science-into-grassland-management/</link><title>Putting Science into Grassland Management</title><description>Putting Science into Grassland Management

22 Mar 2013 by vvpreporter1 on Victorian Volcanic Plains Spotlight volcanicplainsspotlight.wordpress.com/2013/03/22/putting-science-into-grassland-management/

…  grasslands ecology. Checkout his article on how to burn a grassland Other recent articles are Grasslands of the Darling Downs - a …  field and Why does a C4 grass fail to recolonise a C3 grassland when it is the better …

Topics: Victorian Volcanic plain, Grasslands, ecological burning, Grassland Ecology, Management, kangaroo grass</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7265-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7265_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:54:10">http://sierrraaamann.wordpress.com/2013/11/05/5-temperate-grassland-fun-facts/</link><title>5 Temperate Grassland Fun Facts!</title><description>5 Temperate Grassland Fun Facts!

5 Nov 2013 by sierrraaamann on Biomes, Biomes, Biomes. sierrraaamann.wordpress.com/2013/11/05/5-temperate-grassland-fun-facts/

…  A temperate grassland is characterized by a rich mix of grasses &amp; under laid by some of …  &amp; cold winters with infrequent fires. \- Dominant plants include; lush, perennial grasses &amp; herbs; most are resistant to …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7265-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7265_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:54:32">http://wildtracks.wordpress.com/world-ecosystems/grassland-ecosystems/</link><title>Grassland Ecosystems</title><description>Grassland Ecosystems

6 Jan 2012 by wildtracks on Wild Tracks wildtracks.wordpress.com/world-ecosystems/grassland-ecosystems/

…  would encourage the growth of trees and other rainforest plants, thus destroying the balance of life in the tropical grasslands of the …  not be able to adapt to the new types of vegetation. Grassland Ecosystem References: Woodward, Susan L., Biomes of Earth, …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7265-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7265_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:54:48">http://earthfriendlygardening.wordpress.com/2007/06/17/an-ode-to-meadows-grasslands/</link><title>An ode to meadows &amp; grasslands</title><description>An ode to meadows &amp; grasslands

17 Jun 2007 by Caroline Brown on Earth Friendly Gardening earthfriendlygardening.wordpress.com/2007/06/17/an-ode-to-meadows-grasslands/

…  agricultural and development pressures have driven grassland birds to some of the worst declines, followed closely by shrub, …  with many varieties of annual, biennial, and perennial plants. These habitats can contain native wildflowers such as black-eyed susan, …

Topics: Environment, Nature / Ecology</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7265-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7265_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:55:08">http://prairieecologist.com/2011/01/10/why-grassland-birds-are-poor-indicators-of-prairie-quality/</link><title>Why Grassland Birds are Poor Indicators of Prairie Quality</title><description>Why Grassland Birds are Poor Indicators of Prairie Quality

10 Jan 2011 by Chris Helzer on The Prairie Ecologist prairieecologist.com/2011/01/10/why-grassland-birds-are-poor-indicators-of-prairie-quality/

…  presented this argument to a Nebraska symposium on grassland birds in 2008 and managed to escape relatively unscathed.  Now I’m …  enjoyed working on my graduate research, which focused on grassland birds and their vulnerability to prairie fragmentation.  I also …  in prairies (most of which are invertebrates, followed by plants). [caption id="attachment_680" …

Topics: General, Prairie Management, Prairie Natural History, Prairie Insects, Insects, Conservation, prairie plants, Grassland birds, Prairie Birds, Henslow's sparrow, Indicator Species, Species diversity, Resilience, prairie quality, Biological diversity, Biodiversity, Measures of Success</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7265-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7265_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:55:41">http://upperlachlan.wordpress.com/2012/10/10/plant-id-and-nutrition-information-days/</link><title>Plant Id and Nutrition Information Days</title><description>Plant Id and Nutrition Information Days

10 Oct 2012 by Upper Lachlan Landcare on Upper Lachlan Landcare Network upperlachlan.wordpress.com/2012/10/10/plant-id-and-nutrition-information-days/

…  you unsure what those plants in your back paddock are? Not sure if it’s a nutritious pasture …  weeds and forbs. Increase your understanding of native grassland management. Fri, 16th November, 10am - 2pm 'Gunning Junction …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7265-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7265_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:56:04">http://ligerforestecology.wordpress.com/2013/11/14/spf-ecosystems/</link><title>SPF ecosystems</title><description>SPF ecosystems

14 Nov 2013 by ligerforestecology on Liger Forest Ecology ligerforestecology.wordpress.com/2013/11/14/spf-ecosystems/

…  lot of landscapes in the forest like: evergreen forest, grassland, cassava farm, rice farm,  bamboo forest and …  width="299"] strangler fig[/caption] Grassland: When we walked through grassland around us we saw evergreen forest because the grassland it grow in …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7265-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7265_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:56:35">http://ianluntecology.com/2012/03/02/super-seeds/</link><title>Super Seeds</title><description>Super Seeds

1 Mar 2012 by Ian Lunt on Ian Lunt's Ecological Research Site ianluntecology.com/2012/03/02/super-seeds/

…  if I could make a wish for our endangered grassland plants, I’d wish that they too could form persistent seed banks. If they did, …  few native species have long-term, persistent seed banks. Grassland game-changers It’s interesting to reflect back on the big ideas …

Topics: Grassland, Ecology, Biodiversity, Plants, Australia, Regeneration, Restoration, Nature, Environment, Seed Banks, Seeds, Themeda</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>