<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7326">volcanoe eruption</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:50:24" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7326-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7326_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:50:25">http://jonthm9.wordpress.com/2013/09/21/stopping-earth-events/</link><title>Stopping earth events</title><description>Stopping earth events

21 Sep 2013 by jonthm9 on HIUS is health jonthm9.wordpress.com/2013/09/21/stopping-earth-events/

…  We use ground sonar around the active or dormant volcanoe.  We drill down, and vent the steam gradually!  We pass it through a …  Saving the world four billion dollars a year in volcanoe damages.                And he also produce basically …

Topics: climate change, free power, Energy, Environment, Physics, carbon dioxide, mining, Free Power, carbon, environment, Geology, Volcanoe, Tsunami</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7326-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7326_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:50:41">http://museumofsouthtaranaki.wordpress.com/2012/06/16/looking-at-volcanoes/</link><title>Looking at volcanoes</title><description>Looking at volcanoes

16 Jun 2012 by museumofsouthtaranaki on Aotea Utanganui - Museum of South Taranaki museumofsouthtaranaki.wordpress.com/2012/06/16/looking-at-volcanoes/

…  Mt Taranaki, why eruptions occur and the likelihood of an eruption in our region. The younger ones then built a volcanoe and, with the help of some basic household chemicals, the mountain …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7326-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7326_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:51:01">http://hoboduke.wordpress.com/2010/08/29/believe-your-eyes-and-ears/</link><title>Believe your eyes and ears!</title><description>Believe your eyes and ears!

29 Aug 2010 by hoboduke on Hoboduke Nonsense hoboduke.wordpress.com/2010/08/29/believe-your-eyes-and-ears/

…  to feed survivors by flood."][/caption]    Volcanoe near Sumatra adds to earth's suicide.    Volcanoe alert from Jakarta Indonesia informs us on another impending natural …

Topics: the end is near, Global Warming, Culture, Save the earth, Halloween, tragedy, Voodoo, how to fail without trying, Volcanoe, Christian, atheist, Catholic Church, Hurricane Earl</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7326-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7326_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:51:23">http://gath.wordpress.com/2010/04/18/the-volcanic-eruption-at-eyjafjallajokull-and-levantine-archaeology/</link><title>The volcanic eruption at Eyjafjallajökull and Levantine archaeology</title><description>The volcanic eruption at Eyjafjallajökull and Levantine archaeology

18 Apr 2010 by arenmaeir on The Tell es-Safi/Gath Excavations Official (and Unofficial) Weblog gath.wordpress.com/2010/04/18/the-volcanic-eruption-at-eyjafjallajokull-and-levantine-archaeology/

…  that the whole world is discussing the eruption of Eyjafjallajökull, the Icelandic volcanoe, this can be useful for archaeologists in the Levant as well. In the past, when I would discuss the effects of the Thera eruption on the ancient Aegean, and the possibility of volcanic ash being …

Topics: Miscellaneous</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7326-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7326_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:51:44">http://mountaincatgeology.wordpress.com/2009/03/19/undersea-volcano/</link><title>Undersea Volcano</title><description>Undersea Volcano

19 Mar 2009 by clownshue on Mountain Cat Geology mountaincatgeology.wordpress.com/2009/03/19/undersea-volcano/

…  undersea volcanoe erupted near Nuku'Alofa, Tonga on monday March 16, 2009, it has …  moment. There have been no security warnings yet as the eruption is not considered to be threatening. Tonga is located about 1300 miles …

Topics: Volcanoes, Tonga</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7326-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7326_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:51:59">http://soilsci.wordpress.com/2010/10/02/914/</link><title>I was doing some research on volcanoes and came ac …</title><description>I was doing some research on volcanoes and came ac …

3 Oct 2010 by aander93 on Geosmin.... soilsci.wordpress.com/2010/10/02/914/

…  in. I'm just curious as to whether you can predict an eruption that will result in a large or small ash fall. I would assume that …  considering they are able to give a time range of when a volcanoe will erupt, although that range could be from a few days to a few …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7326-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7326_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:52:18">http://soilsci.wordpress.com/2009/11/01/11-1-09/</link><title>11-1-09</title><description>11-1-09

2 Nov 2009 by mattgwilt on Geosmin.... soilsci.wordpress.com/2009/11/01/11-1-09/

…  at the international space station.  This is what the eruption of the Sarychev Volcano looks like from above.  This volcanoe is located just northwest of Japan.  This is said to be one of the …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7326-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7326_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:52:33">http://durangodevo.wordpress.com/2008/05/08/from-sarah-in-argentina/</link><title>From Coach Sarah Tescher in Argentina</title><description>From Coach Sarah Tescher in Argentina

8 May 2008 by durangodevo on Durango DEVO durangodevo.wordpress.com/2008/05/08/from-sarah-in-argentina/

…  of my head lamp that it was snowing...snowing ash.  The volcanoe that erupted close by has hit home (or home away from home).  It is …  the volcanoe has erupted or just burped before its big eruption.  The winds have been to the east but have now switched toward …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7326-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7326_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:52:55">http://marimouth.wordpress.com/2012/02/28/hands-on-science-experiments-for-the-youngest-and-oldest-kids/</link><title>Hands On Science Experiments For The Youngest And Oldest Kids</title><description>Hands On Science Experiments For The Youngest And Oldest Kids

28 Feb 2012 by marimouth on marimouth marimouth.wordpress.com/2012/02/28/hands-on-science-experiments-for-the-youngest-and-oldest-kids/

…  apply in this activity. Encourage the children to create a volcanoe out of the modeling clay to provide a container for their eruption. I am sure we all remember creating a volcanic eruption in a homade …

Topics: Special Needs, School, Mari Nosal, Education Parenting Early Childhood School Age Learning, Education, Education Parenting Early Childhood Special Needs Autis, After School Programs, multi age preschool, Parents, Parenting, Autism, Multiage, Early Childhood, positive classroom climate, Science</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7326-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7326_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:53:13">http://dearkitty1.wordpress.com/2006/11/18/tony-blair-admits-iraq-war-is-disaster/</link><title>Tony Blair admits Iraq war is 'disaster'</title><description>Tony Blair admits Iraq war is 'disaster'

18 Nov 2006 by petrel41 on Dear Kitty. Some blog dearkitty1.wordpress.com/2006/11/18/tony-blair-admits-iraq-war-is-disaster/

…  it. However, this is definitely not a disaster like the eruption of a volcanoe. It is man made. By ... exactly, Bush, Blair and their gang. It is …

Topics: Peace and War, Religion, Crime</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>