<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7328">reduce acne redness</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:57:18" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7328-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7328_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:57:19">http://skinshop.wordpress.com/2012/02/01/mirror-recommends-kalme-undercoat-for-acne-rosacea/</link><title>Mirror recommends KALME Undercoat for Acne Rosacea</title><description>Mirror recommends KALME Undercoat for Acne Rosacea

1 Feb 2012 by amy2anderson on Skinshop's Blog skinshop.wordpress.com/2012/02/01/mirror-recommends-kalme-undercoat-for-acne-rosacea/

Acne Rosacea is notoriously hard to treat. One of the most uncomfortable things about the condition is not just the redness but the extreme skin sensitivity. Many people with acne rosacea …  for acne rosacea for exactly this problem as it can reduce skin sensitivity by up to …

Topics: Rosacea news, Rosacea Cures, Kalme, Acne Rosacea</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7328-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7328_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:57:36">http://bestskinproductsforacne.wordpress.com/2010/07/31/sudden-change-scar-zone-a-acne-treatment-acne-scar/</link><title>Sudden Change Scar Zone A, Acne Treatment + Acne Scar</title><description>Sudden Change Scar Zone A, Acne Treatment + Acne Scar

31 Jul 2010 by Tony on Best Skin Products for Acne bestskinproductsforacne.wordpress.com/2010/07/31/sudden-change-scar-zone-a-acne-treatment-acne-scar/

…  acne &amp; reduce scarsAll-in-one medicated cream eliminates pimples and …  Sensitive SkinBegin to quickly diminish acne pimples &amp; redness scarring &amp; brown spots with the help of Scar ZoneA Acne Cream. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7328-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7328_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:57:56">http://skinshop.wordpress.com/2009/07/08/lisa-faulkner-endorses-kalme/</link><title>Lisa Faulkner Endorses KALME</title><description>Lisa Faulkner Endorses KALME

8 Jul 2009 by Journo on Skinshop's Blog skinshop.wordpress.com/2009/07/08/lisa-faulkner-endorses-kalme/

…  the product. She told the paper that it has really helped reduce the redness. In the article she says, Like most who suffer from rosacea and other uncomfortable skin conditions such as acne, eczema and psoriasis, Lisa has, over the years, spent a fortune testing …

Topics: Rosacea news, skincare, Skincare products, skin shop, Rosacea, rosacea cure, Skin Treatments, rosacea products, skinshop, skincare news, skincare problems</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7328-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7328_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:58:12">http://katharo.wordpress.com/2009/01/21/azelex-azelaic-acid-cream-acne-treatment/</link><title>Azelex - Azelaic Acid Cream Acne Treatment</title><description>Azelex - Azelaic Acid Cream Acne Treatment

21 Jan 2009 by katharo on Acne Free Clear Skin katharo.wordpress.com/2009/01/21/azelex-azelaic-acid-cream-acne-treatment/

…  name) which is an azelaic acid cream for my moderate acne and rosacea (redness). The medication is supposed to:  reduce the growth of bacteria in hair folicles kill free radicals subdue …

Topics: Azelex, azelaic acid cream, Azelaic Acid, azelex cream, azelaic acid acne, azelaic acid gel, azelaic acid skin, Topical Acne Cream Treatments, azelaic acid 20, azelaic acid rosacea</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7328-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7328_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:58:27">http://skinshop.wordpress.com/2012/09/18/tips-on-how-to-use-silver-serum-with-kalme-products-for-acne-rosacea/</link><title>Tips on how to use Silver Serum with KALME products for Acne Rosacea</title><description>Tips on how to use Silver Serum with KALME products for Acne Rosacea

18 Sep 2012 by amy2anderson on Skinshop's Blog skinshop.wordpress.com/2012/09/18/tips-on-how-to-use-silver-serum-with-kalme-products-for-acne-rosacea/

…  or in conjunction with KALME producst for the treatment of acne rosacea. Silver Serum helps reduce the infection and worsening of the small pussy spots associated with …

Topics: Tips, Rosacea news, Acne Tips, silver serum, acne rosacea tips</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7328-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7328_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:58:47">http://alwaysblend.wordpress.com/2012/07/07/sponsored-review-acnes-medicated-skincare/</link><title>Sponsored Review: Acnes Medicated Skincare</title><description>Sponsored Review: Acnes Medicated Skincare

7 Jul 2012 by flyingtazos55 on Blending our lives with different colours alwaysblend.wordpress.com/2012/07/07/sponsored-review-acnes-medicated-skincare/

…  Helps sooth redness and skin irritation caused by acne. Prevent aggravation of pimples. Deep Cleansing: Helps unclogs pores and reduce blemishes by deep cleansing to remove dirt, oil, impurities and excess …

Topics: Singapore, Beauty, Review, Advertisement, Acnés</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7328-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7328_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:59:20">http://zabrockizho.wordpress.com/2013/07/30/alcohol-cause-acne-scars-natural-treatment-hormonal/</link><title>Alcohol Cause Acne Cures Home Treatment Cystic</title><description>Alcohol Cause Acne Cures Home Treatment Cystic

30 Jul 2013 by zabrockizho on zabrockizho zabrockizho.wordpress.com/2013/07/30/alcohol-cause-acne-scars-natural-treatment-hormonal/

…  To Cure Acne with natural remedies alcohol cause acne For Good Achieve lasting acne freedom Simple proven science of clear …  more red as I grew older. Makes my skin clearer reduces redness. I've in the end found a product that works though Eucerin Redness …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7328-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7328_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:59:34">http://acnerosaceacure.wordpress.com/acne-rosacea-cure/</link><title>Acne Rosacea Cure</title><description>Acne Rosacea Cure

4 May 2008 by acnerosaceacure on Acne Rosacea Cure acnerosaceacure.wordpress.com/acne-rosacea-cure/

Acne rosacea cure involves making use of different therapies, medications, skin care …  is not cent percent curable, acne rosacea cures can reduce the effects of this embarrassing skin condition so that you regain your …  of the face. As the rosacea afflicts you, a distinctive redness which looks like permanent blush or flush will take up a major portion …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7328-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7328_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 15:59:54">http://acnerosaceacure.wordpress.com/2008/05/04/ance-rosacea-cure/</link><title>Ance Rosacea Cure</title><description>Ance Rosacea Cure

4 May 2008 by acnerosaceacure on Acne Rosacea Cure acnerosaceacure.wordpress.com/2008/05/04/ance-rosacea-cure/

Acne rosacea cure involves making use of different therapies, medications, skin care …  is not cent percent curable, acne rosacea cures can reduce the effects of this embarrassing skin condition so that you regain your …  of the face. As the rosacea afflicts you, a distinctive redness which looks like permanent blush or flush will take up a major portion …

Topics: Acne Rosacea Cure</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7328-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7328_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 16:00:08">http://zabrockizho.wordpress.com/2013/07/30/can-alcohol-cause-acne-get-rid-natural-treatment-cystic/</link><title>Can Alcohol Cause Acne Get Rid Best Treatment Cystic</title><description>Can Alcohol Cause Acne Get Rid Best Treatment Cystic

30 Jul 2013 by zabrockizho on zabrockizho zabrockizho.wordpress.com/2013/07/30/can-alcohol-cause-acne-get-rid-natural-treatment-cystic/

…  To Cure Acne with natural remedies can alcohol cause acne For Good Achieve lasting acne freedom Simple proven science of clear …  alcohol cause acne There are places on my face where the redness has totally disappeared and in that location consume been moments over …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>