<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7406">does my child have adhd</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:11:56" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7406-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7406_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:11:57">http://learningdisabilitiesadhd.wordpress.com/2012/07/08/about-adhd-how-do-i-know-if-my-child-does-not-have-adhd/</link><title>About ADHD: How Do I Know if My Child Does NOT have ADHD?</title><description>About ADHD: How Do I Know if My Child Does NOT have ADHD?

8 Jul 2012 by Dr. Collins on Learning Disabilities and ADHD Blog learningdisabilitiesadhd.wordpress.com/2012/07/08/about-adhd-how-do-i-know-if-my-child-does-not-have-adhd/

…  ADHD: How do I know if my child does NOT have ADHD? What signs should a parent look for to know that …

Topics: Learning Disabilities, post-format-video, ADHD, QEEG, neurofeedback, adhd in children, treatment for adhd, About ADHD, Attention Deficit Disorder, ADHD symptoms, ADHD diagnosis, ADD/ ADHD, children ADHD, ADHD disorder, ADHD Testing, adhd tests, Adult ADD, adhd signs, adhd treatment, ADHD in Kids, adhd schools</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7406-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7406_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:12:13">http://voxxi.com/2012/03/16/adhd-myths-and-facts-from-a-parent-of-adhd-kid-vhealth/</link><title>ADHD myths and facts from a parent's perspective</title><description>ADHD myths and facts from a parent's perspective

16 Mar 2012 by lavoxepuckett on Voxxi voxxi.com/2012/03/16/adhd-myths-and-facts-from-a-parent-of-adhd-kid-vhealth/

…  after my son Kennedy was diagnosed by his pediatrician as having ADHD, my husband and …  align="aligncenter" width="410"] ADHD does not make for 'bad kids'. They're just more distracted than …  That is why I think that being an advocate for your child is extremely important. Kids with ADHD will grow out of it [caption …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7406-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7406_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:12:42">http://daysofwonderandgrace.wordpress.com/2011/07/15/the-fasd-adhd-tangle/</link><title>The FASD ADHD Tangle</title><description>The FASD ADHD Tangle

15 Jul 2011 by Carrie Zeman on daysofwonderandgrace daysofwonderandgrace.wordpress.com/2011/07/15/the-fasd-adhd-tangle/

…  exposure (PAE) is common in children adopted from Korea, my antennae go up when I meet parents of adopted Korean kids diagnosed with …  ADHD. He was a nice guy and conceded that yes, ADHD alone does not cause all those things. But, he pointed out, they often occur …

Topics: prenatal exposure, ADHD, FASD, prenatal alcohol exposure</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7406-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7406_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:12:57">http://bravolifecoaching.com/faq/</link><title>FAQ</title><description>FAQ

19 Nov 2012 by Nery on Bravo Life Coaching for People with ADHD bravolifecoaching.com/faq/

…  do I know if coaching is right for me or my child? Most people come to coaching because there is a goal they want to …  the meeting to include both parent and child. How long does coaching last? Because change takes place over time I work with my …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7406-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7406_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:13:13">http://elephanttreefeatures.com/2013/07/20/creating-an-adhd-friendly-home-for-your-child/</link><title>Creating an ADHD-Friendly Home for Your Child</title><description>Creating an ADHD-Friendly Home for Your Child

20 Jul 2013 by Elephant Tree Features on Conversations in Boulder County elephanttreefeatures.com/2013/07/20/creating-an-adhd-friendly-home-for-your-child/

…  the most loving things you do. Being supportive, however, does not mean that there are no boundaries. On the contrary, clear boundaries …  and point out any deviations from normal routines.  My own daughter likes to write our routines down and decorate them before we …

Topics: All Things ADHD, ADHD, organize, attention deficit hyperactivity disorder, Executive Functions, ADHD children at home, help children with ADHD</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7406-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7406_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:13:33">http://rafboundcomgest.wordpress.com/2010/10/06/how-does-adderall-work-on-adhd/</link><title>How does adderall work on adhd</title><description>How does adderall work on adhd

6 Oct 2010 by rafboundcomgest on Dietz rafboundcomgest.wordpress.com/2010/10/06/how-does-adderall-work-on-adhd/

…  for recreational purposes, for school, work, or for ADHD .Does it work better for ADD or ADHD?.ADHDI have taken adderall for my ADHD and i just started taken vyvanse. If your dog shampoo does not work go …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7406-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7406_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:13:48">http://spedsupport4parents.wordpress.com/2011/06/10/to-medicate-or-not-to-medicate-your-adhder/</link><title>To Medicate or Not to Medicate Your ADHDer?</title><description>To Medicate or Not to Medicate Your ADHDer?

10 Jun 2011 by spedsupport4parents on spedsupport4parents spedsupport4parents.wordpress.com/2011/06/10/to-medicate-or-not-to-medicate-your-adhder/

…   As a parent, I've had to decide if I wanted to give my child medication for ADHD.  I know what a tough decision this is for a …  a child at school.  Because there are 3 types of ADHD, it does look different in different children (especially in girls).  However, the …

Topics: Special Education, Sped, Education, Help for Different Disabilities, Parenting Issues, Special Needs, Support for Parents, Special Needs Children, struggling students, ADHD, ADHD Medication, adhd meds</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7406-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7406_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:14:03">http://distractedstudents.wordpress.com/2013/02/24/what-is-adhd-a-distracted-exploration-of-the-disorder/</link><title>What is ADHD? - A distracted exploration of the disorder!!</title><description>What is ADHD? - A distracted exploration of the disorder!!

24 Feb 2013 by Aditi Anand on Distracted Students distractedstudents.wordpress.com/2013/02/24/what-is-adhd-a-distracted-exploration-of-the-disorder/

…  everyone! This is the first article from my series of “An intriguing Sunday morning with Aditi Anand” There …  and I was like “What is ADHD?”. Now, one, the name does sound cool even for a disorder and second I am a diehard Biology fan, the …  having the disorder. (reassuring words) So, every normal child has to be ‘normally’ hyperactive and inattentive; being a little …

Topics: Randoms, ADHD</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7406-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7406_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:14:28">http://holeinherstocking.wordpress.com/2012/05/31/should-you-tell-people-you-have-adhd/</link><title>Should you tell people you have ADHD?</title><description>Should you tell people you have ADHD?

31 May 2012 by gigs26 on Dancing with a hole in her stocking holeinherstocking.wordpress.com/2012/05/31/should-you-tell-people-you-have-adhd/

…  told the people I'm closest to who are affected by my ADHD and who can help me deal with it and can deal with me more effectively …  courage from another that I do not demand of myself. Does this mean I must be open about my own ADHD before I even know whether I …

Topics: health, ADHD, ADHD Heroines, Mental Health, News &amp; Events, Ari Tuckman, ADHD / ADD, Andrés Torres, gigante, adult adhd, ADD and work, ADHD and work</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7406-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7406_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:14:48">http://learningdisabilitiesadhd.wordpress.com/2012/06/03/about-adhd-the-three-main-symptoms-of-adhd-in-children/</link><title>About ADHD: The Three Main Symptoms of ADHD in Children</title><description>About ADHD: The Three Main Symptoms of ADHD in Children

4 Jun 2012 by Dr. Collins on Learning Disabilities and ADHD Blog learningdisabilitiesadhd.wordpress.com/2012/06/03/about-adhd-the-three-main-symptoms-of-adhd-in-children/

…  What are some of the signs of ADHD that I will notice in my child? When will these ADHD symptoms appear? Some of the more common …  clinical environments. Inattention is when the child does not have any long term focus or organization of thought. Hyperactivity is …

Topics: Learning Disabilities, ADHD, QEEG, neurofeedback, adhd in children, treatment for adhd, About ADHD, What is ADHD?, Attention Deficit Disorder, adult adhd, ADHD symptoms, ADHD diagnosis, ADD/ ADHD, children ADHD, ADHD disorder, ADHD Testing, adhd tests, Adult ADD, adhd signs, adhd treatment, St. Louis, Missouri, ADHD in Kids, adhd schools</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>