<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7412">when queen elisabeth</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:33:20" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7412-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7412_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:33:21">http://austrianwineusa.com/2012/08/09/all-hail-elisabeth-hirschbuchler-wine-queen-of-austria/</link><title>All Hail Elisabeth Hirschbüchler, Wine Queen of Austria</title><description>All Hail Elisabeth Hirschbüchler, Wine Queen of Austria

9 Aug 2012 by AustrianWineUSA on Austrian Wine austrianwineusa.com/2012/08/09/all-hail-elisabeth-hirschbuchler-wine-queen-of-austria/

…  just a few days, Austrian Wine Queen, Elisabeth Hirschbüchler, will land on US soil for the first time! During her …  Elisabeth's reign of royalty began in May of 2011 when she was elected Wine Queen of Niederösterreich (aka Lower Austria), a …

Topics: Austrian Wine, summer of riesling, Summer of Riesling, ode to austria, Austrian wine queen, wine queen elisabeth, Elisabeth Hirschbüchler</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7412-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7412_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:33:38">http://cassons.wordpress.com/2013/02/13/english-money/</link><title>English money</title><description>English money

13 Feb 2013 by cassons on Cassons Abroad cassons.wordpress.com/2013/02/13/english-money/

…  called pounds. One pound is like one dollar and 60 cents. Queen Elisabeth II is on the front. Instead of a paper dollar, the English …  a two pound coin! I used two pounds to get a fighter pod when we went shopping at Boswell's, a big store with toys.  - Max Here …

Topics: Oxford</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7412-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7412_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:34:01">http://todayindeadroyalty.com/2012/10/03/october-3rd/</link><title>October 3rd!</title><description>October 3rd!

3 Oct 2012 by samanthaimperiatrix on Today in Dead Royalty todayindeadroyalty.com/2012/10/03/october-3rd/

…  mention today. The first belongs to Elisabeth of Valois, Queen consort of Spain and daughter to Henry II and Catherine d'Medici, …  was quite close to her sister-in-law, Mary, Queen of Scots when they were growing up together. Elisabeth was married to Phillip II of …

Topics: Daily Posts, Plantagenets, French royalty</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7412-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7412_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:34:18">http://ellamr2.wordpress.com/2011/01/15/watching-you-watching-me/</link><title>Watching you watching me</title><description>Watching you watching me

15 Jan 2011 by Ella Rychlewski on From Uganda... a picture a day ellamr2.wordpress.com/2011/01/15/watching-you-watching-me/

This picture reminds me of my mother for some reason... but don't tell her that. We were very lucky and got to see lots of wildlife when we were in Queen Elisabeth, including this hippopotamus.

Topics: Uganda, Travel, Animal, National, Queen, elisabeth, park, Hippo, hippopotamus, wildlife</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7412-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7412_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:34:51">http://pearlswindow.wordpress.com/2008/09/22/elisabeth-hasselbeck-leaving-the-view-lawd-i-hope-so/</link><title>Elisabeth Hasselbeck Leaving "The View"? Lawd, I hope so!</title><description>Elisabeth Hasselbeck Leaving "The View"? Lawd, I hope so!

22 Sep 2008 by pearlswindow on Pearl's Window pearlswindow.wordpress.com/2008/09/22/elisabeth-hasselbeck-leaving-the-view-lawd-i-hope-so/

…  sure they looooooove her over there! She would be their queen bee! The National Enquirer reports, "Elisabeth feels she can't …  feels she constantly has to defend herself. Besides that, when she gets passionate about her opinions, the others make her look like …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7412-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7412_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:35:07">http://eevamakinen.com/2014/01/31/not-all-those-who-wonder-are-lost/</link><title>"Not all those who wonder are lost."</title><description>"Not all those who wonder are lost."

31 Jan 2014 by eevamakinen on Travel with me eevamakinen.com/2014/01/31/not-all-those-who-wonder-are-lost/

…  is couple of my favourite shots from Queen Elisabeth National Park in Uganda. [caption id="attachment_654" …  width="1000"] The sight in the morning when waking up at 6am. I think this is the most magical moment of nature …

Topics: travel photography, Uganda, gorilla, Africa, wildlife, Africa 2, national park, Traveling, Blog, matkablogi, Matkailu, Matkakuvat, Afrikka, gorilla trekking, Travel photos, Traveller, Queen Elisabeth National Park, Safari, animals, Elephants, Morning Mist, Birds, TRAVEL BLOG, Blogger, reppureissaus, elefantti, luontokuva, Vuoden luontokuva, Nikon, Photography</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7412-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7412_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:35:44">http://musicblvd.com/track/counting-crows-goodnight-elisabeth/</link><title>Counting Crows Goodnight Elisabeth</title><description>Counting Crows Goodnight Elisabeth

16 Aug 2012 by Action Factory on Music Blvd musicblvd.com/2012/08/16/counting-crows-goodnight-elisabeth/

…  she slips in something comfortable And I'll miss you when I'm slipping in between If you wrap yourself in daffodils I will wrap myself in pain And if you're the queen of California Baby I am the king of the rain And I say Goodnight …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7412-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7412_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:36:00">http://theroyalpost.com/2012/02/16/future-queens-of-europe-princess-elisabeth-of-belgium/</link><title>Future Queens of Europe: Princess Elisabeth of Belgium</title><description>Future Queens of Europe: Princess Elisabeth of Belgium

17 Feb 2012 by theroyalpost on The Royal Post theroyalpost.com/2012/02/16/future-queens-of-europe-princess-elisabeth-of-belgium/

…  of our readers requested that we do a post on Princess Elisabeth of Belgium as part of our series on Future Queens of Europe and so …  of the heir apparent be titled Count Hainaut. Consequently when Princess Elisabeth was born it was expected that she would be styled …

Topics: Royal Family of Belgium, post-format-gallery, Princess Elisabeth of Belgium</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7412-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7412_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:36:23">http://aucapeuro.wordpress.com/2013/10/01/dbq-queen-elisabeth/</link><title>DBQ: Queen Elisabeth</title><description>DBQ: Queen Elisabeth

1 Oct 2013 by Kris Merino on Ms. Merino's Advanced Placement European History aucapeuro.wordpress.com/2013/10/01/dbq-queen-elisabeth/

…  essay I want you to: Highlight the thesis. Underline when you use each document (cite the document in parenthesis). Label your …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7412-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7412_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:36:41">http://fabriziofaraco.wordpress.com/2012/01/29/top-10-seth-godins-quotes-made-in-antwerp-belgium-april-1-2010/</link><title>TOP 10 Seth Godin’s Quotes Made in Antwerp, Belgium. April 1, 2010</title><description>TOP 10 Seth Godin’s Quotes Made in Antwerp, Belgium. April 1, 2010

29 Jan 2012 by Fabrizio Faraco on fabriziofaraco fabriziofaraco.wordpress.com/2012/01/29/top-10-seth-godins-quotes-made-in-antwerp-belgium-april-1-2010/

Via Scoop.it - H2H Marketing Yesterday, when I entered the Queen Elisabeth Hall in Antwerp to see a presentation by Seth Godin, I was shocked by the number of people there, maybe 600? more? I am not good at numbers so if you k...Via zestnzen.wordpress.com</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>