<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7415">most anticipated games of 2013</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:42:58" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7415-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7415_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:42:59">http://chapwithacap.wordpress.com/2013/01/24/big-list-of-2013-games/</link><title>Most Anticipated Games of 2013!</title><description>Most Anticipated Games of 2013!

24 Jan 2013 by chapwithacap on Chap With A Cap chapwithacap.wordpress.com/2013/01/24/big-list-of-2013-games/

…  and let me know what you think or if I missed any of your anticipated games. Anyway, it's a pretty long list, so please stay with …  Blacklist The new Splinter Cell release has one of the most drastic and controversial changes seen in the whole series. A new voice …

Topics: Trailers, Games, Xbox, xbox 360, Playstation 3, Microsoft, Video Games, Console Platforms, video game console</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7415-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7415_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:44:06">http://mobiwebsoftdev.wordpress.com/2013/04/18/most-anticipated-games-of-2013/</link><title>Most Anticipated Games of 2013</title><description>Most Anticipated Games of 2013

18 Apr 2013 by Alex Williams on MobiWebSoftDev mobiwebsoftdev.wordpress.com/2013/04/18/most-anticipated-games-of-2013/

…  you love playing games all day long? Most of us like it, whenever we are free. It is the age of …  from. Here we will take a brief look at some of the most anticipated games of this year. Grand Theft Auto V GTA has always been …

Topics: Games, anticipated games, anticipated games 2013, games 2013</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7415-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7415_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:44:26">http://skillsnest.wordpress.com/2013/01/07/most-anticipated-games-for-2013/</link><title>Most Anticipated Games for 2013</title><description>Most Anticipated Games for 2013

7 Jan 2013 by skillsnest on Skillsnest's Blog skillsnest.wordpress.com/2013/01/07/most-anticipated-games-for-2013/

…  a cool, content rich career. Ni No Kuni:  A Japanese Most anticipated game also called “Another World”  Game rich in content and …

Topics: Software, Code, Games, Gaming, METRO, Pikmin3, Star Trek, nino kuni, luigis mansion, The Last of Us, Army of Two, Game and Wario, StarCraft2, Sim City, metal gear, Rayman Legends, Devil May Cry, in justice gods among us</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7415-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7415_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:44:43">http://findthebluekey.com/2012/12/17/most-anticipated-games-of-2013/</link><title>Most Anticipated Games of 2013</title><description>Most Anticipated Games of 2013

17 Dec 2012 by robstaalduinen on Find The Blue Key findthebluekey.com/2012/12/17/most-anticipated-games-of-2013/

…  excuses locked in, lets have a look at my three of my most anticipated games of the coming year. In no particular order... 1\. Crysis …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7415-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7415_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:44:59">http://ryanlee20.wordpress.com/2013/06/16/the-most-anticipated-games-of-2013/</link><title>The most anticipated games of 2013</title><description>The most anticipated games of 2013

16 Jun 2013 by ryanlee20 on ryanlee20 ryanlee20.wordpress.com/2013/06/16/the-most-anticipated-games-of-2013/

…  video games is a hobby for many of us. Whether it be for fun, competing against friends or strangers online or …  X &amp; Y Pokemon has been around for a long time, and most people of my generation grew up playing the original games. And although …

Topics: Video Games, Pokemon, Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell, blacklist, Sam Fisher, Assassin's Creed, Television Program, Splinter Cell, gta, tmnt, the walking dead</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7415-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7415_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:45:18">http://mindthegames.com/2013/08/29/the-most-anticipated-games-of-2013/</link><title>The Most Anticipated Games of 2013</title><description>The Most Anticipated Games of 2013

29 Aug 2013 by Roger Pokorny on MindtheGames mindthegames.com/2013/08/29/the-most-anticipated-games-of-2013/

…  of AAA releases by the end of 2013. There is so many games coming out this year that you could easily forget that certain games are on the horizon. So here is a list of some of the most anticipated games. The list is in no particular order. Knack Platform(s): …

Topics: Playstation 3, PlayStation, Xbox, Gaming Thoughts, wii u, Assassin's Creed, Black Flag, ubisoft, Knack, PS4, video game industry, anticipated games, Next-Gen Consoles, Crash Bandicoot, Sly Cooper, Mark Cerny</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7415-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7415_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:45:46">http://eddysshow.wordpress.com/2012/12/27/most-anticipated-games-of-2013/</link><title>Most anticipated games of 2013</title><description>Most anticipated games of 2013

27 Dec 2012 by EddysShow! on EddysShow! eddysshow.wordpress.com/2012/12/27/most-anticipated-games-of-2013/

…  you keep an eye on in 2013? Join us as we look at the #Most anticipated games of 2013. IGN, Machinima and others already have their list, …

Topics: new, 2013, Games, Video Games, Game Industry, upcoming, New Releases</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7415-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7415_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:46:02">http://thedavidryan.wordpress.com/2012/12/11/the-most-anticipated-games-of-2013/</link><title>The most anticipated games of 2013</title><description>The most anticipated games of 2013

11 Dec 2012 by thedavidryan on The Ryanblog! thedavidryan.wordpress.com/2012/12/11/the-most-anticipated-games-of-2013/

…  to the bright lights of 2013 and the games that I’m most looking forward to over the next year, that’s if we even get there …  question Naughty Dog’s The Last of Us is the most hotly anticipated game of 2013 for Playstation owners. This PS3 exclusive looks to be …

Topics: Games, gta V, Video Games, Computer games, The Last of Us, BEYOND two souls, gta, Grand theft Auto, Watch Dogs, deadpool, Marvel, star wars</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7415-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7415_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:46:25">http://aspiegamingblog.wordpress.com/2013/01/03/most-anticipated-game-of-2013/</link><title>Most Anticipated Game of 2013</title><description>Most Anticipated Game of 2013

4 Jan 2013 by Sam Hale on Aspie Gaming aspiegamingblog.wordpress.com/2013/01/03/most-anticipated-game-of-2013/

…  going to discuss the game that I am looking forward to the most in 2013. I'll admit that this is a crowded category for me. There are many games to look forward to: Bioshock: Infinite, Beyond: Two Souls and the Last of …

Topics: Video Games, Games, Videogames, Gaming, xbox 360, PS3, PC, Video Game History, video game character, Video Games Industry, video game characters, Tomb Raider, Crystal Dynamics, attempted rape, Controversy, Rhianna Pratchett, Reboot, Lara Croft, iconic female character, Sex Symbol</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7415-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7415_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:46:46">http://ryuz4ki57inenglish.wordpress.com/2013/01/06/most-anticipated-games-in-2013/</link><title>Most anticipated games in 2013</title><description>Most anticipated games in 2013

6 Jan 2013 by ryuz4ki57 on Nibelheim - Ryuzaki57's mirror site ryuz4ki57inenglish.wordpress.com/2013/01/06/most-anticipated-games-in-2013/

…  been soooooo excited since the reveal trailer of the last adventures of Lightning, whom I revere. Yet the trailer is lame …  Ark (PSP)[/caption] Shining Blade was one of those games that look disappointing when you play, but that let you precious …  and eagerly awaits March. Never management in video games will have been so meticulous, and online possibilities should introduce …

Topics: Bandai, Namco, Japan, Final Fantasy, Square=Enix, SEGA, Senran Kagura, Atelier, Sim City, EA, maxis, Capcom, Ace Attorney, God Eater, Opinion, legend of heroes</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>