<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7424">best italian food Rome</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:12:57" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7424-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7424_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:12:58">http://verzolaandrea.wordpress.com/2013/09/12/coming-soon-the-crew-italian-chefs-and-food-hunters/</link><title>Coming soon : "The Crew " Italian Chefs and Food Hunters</title><description>Coming soon : "The Crew " Italian Chefs and Food Hunters

12 Sep 2013 by verzolaandrea on Food Marketing verzolaandrea.wordpress.com/2013/09/12/coming-soon-the-crew-italian-chefs-and-food-hunters/

…  a relational method .. Support our customers to discover Italian traditions using food as a means to learn the language she sings. We …  the earth through the products that generate and teach the best way to prepare and serve From farms in Salento craft shops, local markets …

Topics: Formazione, Corsi, coaching, Food, corsi di cucina, corsi di cucina professionale, Corsi motivazionali, Chef Training, bloggers, Eventi</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7424-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7424_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:13:20">http://allinrome.wordpress.com/2013/10/24/great-food-in-testaccio/</link><title>Great food in Testaccio</title><description>Great food in Testaccio

24 Oct 2013 by allinrome on AllinRome by M&amp;J Place Hostel allinrome.wordpress.com/2013/10/24/great-food-in-testaccio/

…  trap,where meals are overpriced and not even close to Italian cuisine, with real cuoco in it! Via Veneto has become ONLY tourist …  and traditional Italian ones. And not only, is the best place to get some fresh meat, veg, or pasticcini, dolci and anything that …

Topics: Events, Curiosity, Places, hostels 2, Museums</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7424-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7424_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:13:40">http://takeatripwithus.wordpress.com/2012/11/20/i-will-be-there-rome/</link><title>I will be there Rome!</title><description>I will be there Rome!

20 Nov 2012 by Lauri P on Take a trip with us! takeatripwithus.wordpress.com/2012/11/20/i-will-be-there-rome/

…  and all the times I keep hearing the same. They say that Italian food is the best food what you can ever taste or eat.                       …

Topics: Italy</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7424-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7424_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:13:59">http://missbabysunshine.wordpress.com/2010/06/13/when-in-rome/</link><title>When in Rome...</title><description>When in Rome...

13 Jun 2010 by missbabysunshine on Miss Baby Sunshine's Kitchen missbabysunshine.wordpress.com/2010/06/13/when-in-rome/

…  realized that I never finished my Italian travel story. So here it is~~ Rome was our last stop. Did you know that …  and breath taking Sistine Chapel I think the food in Rome is underrated. This place had fantastic roman specialty dishes. Ostaria da Nerone is a MUST go in Rome. Also, we had the best gelato in Rome at a place called, San Crispino. Our fantastic …

Topics: Travel, My Life, Romantic dinner, Food, Italy, Rome</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7424-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7424_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:14:14">http://rometraveller.org/home/</link><title>Useful Information on Rome</title><description>Useful Information on Rome

28 Jun 2012 by europeantraveller on Rome Italy Travel Expert rometraveller.org/home/

…  and favourite reasons for loving Rome, Learn about the best ice cream in the Pantheon area, the best restaurants in Piazza Navona and the best attractions for family groups visiting the Italian capital. Staying in Rome There are many options for stayin in the …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7424-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7424_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:14:32">http://allinrome.wordpress.com/2013/05/08/fresh-food-markets-in-rome/</link><title>Fresh food markets in Rome</title><description>Fresh food markets in Rome

8 May 2013 by allinrome on AllinRome by M&amp;J Place Hostel allinrome.wordpress.com/2013/05/08/fresh-food-markets-in-rome/

…  and have learned a huge part of their culture. The best way to see Rome is by walk, you will be surprise, and to soak up the real …  as kitchen utensils, tablecloths and toys. Roma's food markets are famous all around the world, offering all colours and variety …

Topics: Events, Curiosity, Places, hostels 2, Museums</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7424-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7424_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:14:51">http://thesophomoreslump2.com/2013/01/02/5343/</link><title>Revisiting Rome</title><description>Revisiting Rome

3 Jan 2013 by rommel on The Sophomore Slump thesophomoreslump2.com/2013/01/02/5343/

…  and the Vatican. It is the city I still deem to be the best in the world. During my 2 years assignment in Italy, I usually take the …  That girl whit and the lover of the rad and fab took an Italian exploration in Rome, Sorrento and Florence. Her clear and crispy, …

Topics: Travel, Italy, Flashback Friday</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7424-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7424_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:15:33">http://colinroweconference.wordpress.com/lodging/</link><title>Lodging</title><description>Lodging

26 Mar 2014 by laurenhoffman129 on Colin Rowe Conference colinroweconference.wordpress.com/lodging/

…  tim@godata.info And while you are here,enjoy some of the best restaurants in Rome: Food and Drink 1. http://travel.cnn.com/10-best-italian-restaurants-rome-920961 2.http://www.foodandwine.com/articles/rome-restaurants 3. …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7424-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7424_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:15:46">http://travellingsommelier.wordpress.com/2011/05/10/enoteche-wine-bars-in-rome/</link><title>Enoteche, wine bars, in Rome</title><description>Enoteche, wine bars, in Rome

10 May 2011 by Katie on Toast to your Taste travellingsommelier.wordpress.com/2011/05/10/enoteche-wine-bars-in-rome/

…  booking flights to Rome and who is interested in tasting Italian wines they can't find anywhere else. Rome has a long-standing …  theses bars it's all about the wine. Where the best place to visit wine bars? The historic city centre. That's where …

Topics: wine tasting, Italy, Rome, Sightseeing, Rome, Italy, Flights</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7424-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7424_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:16:00">http://heartrome.com/2012/03/04/regional-delights-in-the-heart-of-rome-part-1/</link><title>Regional delights in the heart of Rome: Part 1</title><description>Regional delights in the heart of Rome: Part 1

4 Mar 2012 by HeartRome on HeartRome heartrome.com/2012/03/04/regional-delights-in-the-heart-of-rome-part-1/

…  some recommendations for those of you who want to take an Italian regional culinary journey through Rome. Italian cuisine is so varied …  These restaurants located across the city are the next best thing! Buzz in Rome are a fantastic source of information for all things …

Topics: Rome, Food, MiLan, Veneto, Eternal City, Regional Cuisine, Genoa, Venice, emiglia romagna, Friuli Venezia Giulia, Lombardy, post-format-standard, Rome Offsite, Food &amp; Wine</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>