<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7430">conflict mali</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:32:43" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7430-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7430_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:32:44">http://oneparagraphanswers.wordpress.com/2013/04/15/why-is-there-a-conflict-in-northern-mali/</link><title>Why is there a Conflict in Northern Mali?</title><description>Why is there a Conflict in Northern Mali?

15 Apr 2013 by jrtrust on One Paragraph Answers oneparagraphanswers.wordpress.com/2013/04/15/why-is-there-a-conflict-in-northern-mali/

…  is there a conflict in Northern Mali? A group in the region of Northern Mali known as “Azawad” wants …  from the rest of Mali. The root cause of this 2012-13 conflict is racial. Northern Mali is home to Tuaregs and Arabs, relatively …

Topics: Conflicts in Africa, civil wars</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7430-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7430_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:33:01">http://fortelespeciale.wordpress.com/2013/01/18/mali-conflict/</link><title>Mali Conflict</title><description>Mali Conflict

18 Jan 2013 by xtream88 on Who Dares Wins fortelespeciale.wordpress.com/2013/01/18/mali-conflict/

…  has increased its troop strength in Mali to 1,400 to help fight militant Islamists in the north, the French …  by West African nations have also started arriving in Mali. Some 100 Togolese soldiers landed in Bamako on Thursday, with 80 …  total, 3,300 regional troops will be deployed in the conflict under a UN Security Council resolution. France has been pushing …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7430-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7430_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:33:20">http://kelseysuggitt.wordpress.com/2013/01/15/conflict-in-mali/</link><title>Conflict in Mali</title><description>Conflict in Mali

15 Jan 2013 by kelseysuggitt on Research into Africa kelseysuggitt.wordpress.com/2013/01/15/conflict-in-mali/

…  situation in Mali has escalated over the last few days to the extent that France has decided …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7430-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7430_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:33:35">http://hts2041.wordpress.com/2013/02/01/conflict-in-mali/</link><title>Conflict in Mali</title><description>Conflict in Mali

1 Feb 2013 by bentowns3nd on HTS 2041: The Modern Middle East hts2041.wordpress.com/2013/02/01/conflict-in-mali/

…  of the Middle East, the current political disturbance in Mali engages several of the major themes discussed in recent readings, notably …  in the Sahel.The polity now known as the Republic of Mali achieved independence from France in 1960; events in 2012 saw its …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7430-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7430_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:33:55">http://thaiphong.wordpress.com/2013/01/28/the-conflict-in-mali/</link><title>The Conflict in Mali</title><description>The Conflict in Mali

28 Jan 2013 by thaiphong on THAIPHONG - NEWS - CULTURE - ENTERTAINMENT - ARTWORK - MOVIE thaiphong.wordpress.com/2013/01/28/the-conflict-in-mali/

…  Operation Serval, intervening in a complicated, months-old conflict in northern Mali. A year earlier, Tuareg rebels had attacked government positions throughout northern Mali, temporarily seizing control of a large area and declaring it a new state …

Topics: News - Tin tức tổng hợp, Politics, Libya, Transportation, Aviation, middle east, Jean Yves le Drian</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7430-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7430_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:34:15">http://themoretheychange.wordpress.com/2013/02/03/mali-analysis-round-up-part-2/</link><title>Mali analysis round-up (Part 2)</title><description>Mali analysis round-up (Part 2)

3 Feb 2013 by Juliette on The More Things Change themoretheychange.wordpress.com/2013/02/03/mali-analysis-round-up-part-2/

…  pieces (some related to France's intervention in Mali, some not) I've found on Mali. Part 1 is available …  European Journal of International Law On the Roots of the Conflict "Jihad in Africa: The danger in the desert" - article in …  assessment of the human rights situation after three week conflict" - Amnesty International briefing note "Mali: Human …

Topics: Africa, Mali, France, serval, Resources, Resources</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7430-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7430_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:34:29">http://bleedingheartsmecca.wordpress.com/2014/04/18/a-humanitarian-song-for-mali-by-kathleen-white/</link><title>A Humanitarian Song for Mali by Kathleen White</title><description>A Humanitarian Song for Mali by Kathleen White

18 Apr 2014 by bleedingheartsmecca on Bleeding Hearts Mecca bleedingheartsmecca.wordpress.com/2014/04/18/a-humanitarian-song-for-mali-by-kathleen-white/

…  happening in Mali? People are in conflict, betraying each other, the fighting doesn't …  continues, though many of those displaced by the northern conflict have begun to return home. The trouble of which Fatoumata Diawara …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7430-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7430_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:34:44">http://rememberwhereweparked.com/2014/03/31/assignment-8-6/</link><title>Assignment 8</title><description>Assignment 8

31 Mar 2014 by ablinkin25 on Remember where we parked rememberwhereweparked.com/2014/03/31/assignment-8-6/

…  Payne What is the impact Islamic rebels in Mali are having on the country’s cultural heritage? I chose the book Mali's Conflict, the Sahel's Crisis by Richard Gowan. I had a lot of trouble …  of detail about my research question.  There is a serious conflict or problem that is going on in Mali right now with the destruction of …

Topics: Finding Information: Books, Articles &amp; Web Sources</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7430-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7430_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:35:00">http://iisablog.org/2012/01/15/mali-humanitarian-crises-preparing-for-a-larger-conflict/</link><title>Mali Humanitarian Crises: Preparing for a larger conflict</title><description>Mali Humanitarian Crises: Preparing for a larger conflict

15 Jan 2012 by Institute of Islamic Strategic and Socio-Political Affairs on Institute of Islamic Strategic and Socio-Political Affairs iisablog.org/2012/01/15/mali-humanitarian-crises-preparing-for-a-larger-conflict/

…  intervention may not be the beginning of the end of the conflict in Mali and the Sahel. The ongoing conflict has perspective to widen further and …

Topics: Security, Arab Spring, Mali, Sahel, United Nations, Algeria, Morocco, Ban Ki-moon, Papers</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7430-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7430_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:35:19">http://bockshorn.wordpress.com/2013/02/26/the-war-in-mali-the-road-to-nowhere/</link><title>The War in Mali: the Road to Nowhere</title><description>The War in Mali: the Road to Nowhere

26 Feb 2013 by pidgeonjimi on BOCKSHORN.wordpress.com bockshorn.wordpress.com/2013/02/26/the-war-in-mali-the-road-to-nowhere/

…  situation in Mali changed radically after France intervened in the conflict between the Tuareg people, Islamic fundamentalists and rebels who …  army is demoralized, and the country has been plunged into conflict and anarchy. What kind of future lies ahead for Mali? viaThe War in …</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>