<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7435">trendy bar Berlin</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:48:52" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7435-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7435_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:48:52">http://curlyjproductions.wordpress.com/2010/05/18/berlins-bar-scene/</link><title>Berlin's Bar Scene</title><description>Berlin's Bar Scene

18 May 2010 by ellisjo on Curly J Productions curlyjproductions.wordpress.com/2010/05/18/berlins-bar-scene/

…  kind of people who want to live on the edge. It’s a trendy city for trendy people. And not in the main stream ‘listen to dance …  want to experience a more upmarket style of fashionable bar head west. And if you’re a bit edgier and more urban you’re definitely …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7435-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7435_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:49:07">http://light-absorption.com/2013/05/22/berlin-short-report/</link><title>BERLIN SHORT REPORT</title><description>BERLIN SHORT REPORT

22 May 2013 by Anne Drew on LIGHT ABSORPTION light-absorption.com/2013/05/22/berlin-short-report/

…  back to Paris. To resume my quick trip to Berlin, if you wanna see a minimum of it, take at least one week. Leave the …  bit of their history. There is so much districts to see, trendy events to attend, bars and clubs to run and a buch of amazing shops. If …

Topics: Style, all black, black look, Berlin, Black Berlin, Germany, Prenzlauer Berg, Underground, Mauer Park, East Side Gallery, Berlin Wall, mitte, trendy berlin, Sandro, Urban Outffiters, monki, Berlin fashion, all black berlin, Chaos In Form, trinity ring, Great Stay, Berliners, i love berlin</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7435-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7435_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:49:28">http://theshychef.wordpress.com/location/</link><title>Location</title><description>Location

2 Mar 2009 by denialwaits on The Shy Chef theshychef.wordpress.com/location/

…  Shy Chef lives and cooks in the heart of Berlin,  in the famous, bohemian district of Kreuzberg - a colourful, …  well-preserved local area is filled with cozy cafes and trendy bars, for those who would like to continue their evening after finishing …  a residential building erected in 1888, a prime example of Berlin's beautiful 'Grunderzeit' architecture - a very typical …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7435-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7435_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:49:43">http://urbanruinsblog.com/2014/01/19/the-build-up-to-berlin/</link><title>THE BUILD UP TO BERLIN</title><description>THE BUILD UP TO BERLIN

19 Jan 2014 by urbanruinsblogger on Urban Ruins urbanruinsblog.com/2014/01/19/the-build-up-to-berlin/

…  Berlin is host to most of the City's nightlife with trendy areas such as Kreuzberg offering lively bars, good music, quirky …  February: 1\. Klubnacht at Berghain/ Panorama Bar \- A solid reputation for being one of the best clubs in the world, home to …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7435-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7435_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:50:01">http://www.jointhestylehighclub.com/2008/07/14/when-in-rome/</link><title>When in Rome...</title><description>When in Rome...

14 Jul 2008 by stylehighclub on Style High Club jointhestylehighclub.com/2008/07/14/when-in-rome/

…  as I have unfortunately never been there. But when in Berlin do head to Kreuzberg (take the S-Bahn to Ostkreuz or the U-Bahn to …  the river Spree. Complete with hammocks and its own beach bar.   pictures: Badeschiff website 3) Freischwimmer, a great …  the canal. Also, don't miss Klub der Visionaere, a trendy bar, just opposite. pictures: Freischwimmer …

Topics: Berlin, City Guide, Clubbing, Bars</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7435-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7435_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:50:16">http://lovefoodpinny.wordpress.com/2011/08/22/a-review-berlin-continued-part-3/</link><title>A Review - Sophie'n eck, Große Hamburger Straße 37, 10115 Berlin</title><description>A Review - Sophie'n eck, Große Hamburger Straße 37, 10115 Berlin

22 Aug 2011 by lovefoodpinny on lovefoodpinny lovefoodpinny.wordpress.com/2011/08/22/a-review-berlin-continued-part-3/

…  (part 3 of the Berlin Posts) This lovely restaurant/bar is located on a quiet corner street and has an impressive outside facade …  It is in what was the Jewish quarter. This is a bohemian, trendy area with lots of individual one-off shops. Although it has no beer …

Topics: Berlin, Food, Eating, Travel, Reviews - Dining out, Meat, Restaurants, cookery, Sophie'n eck, love food pinny, pinny</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7435-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7435_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:50:34">http://thomasdebackere.wordpress.com/2012/01/18/hugo-hot-locations-on-foursquare/</link><title>HUGO HOT LOCATIONS ON FOURSQUARE</title><description>HUGO HOT LOCATIONS ON FOURSQUARE

18 Jan 2012 by thomasdebackere on Fashionated thomasdebackere.wordpress.com/2012/01/18/hugo-hot-locations-on-foursquare/

…  was the beginning of Berlin Fashion Week and HUGO BOSS is kicking it off by sponsoring foursquare specials at the hottest locations in town, including trendy bars, restaurants and stores. If you are spending time in Berlin this week or the next, follow HUGO BOSS on foursquare and unlock …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7435-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7435_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:50:54">http://jonnywhitlam.wordpress.com/2011/10/02/the-chair/</link><title>The Chair</title><description>The Chair

2 Oct 2011 by jonnywhitlam on Jonny Whitlam Photography jonnywhitlam.wordpress.com/2011/10/02/the-chair/

…  caption="The Chair"][/caption] Berlin is full of 'vintage' furniture, from flea markets to trendy bars to 'junk shops' all over the city. This kind of furniture …

Topics: Europe, Photography, Photography (2), Germany, Berlin, Deutschland, furniture, vintage</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7435-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7435_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:51:09">http://thetrendmix.com/2012/10/30/ludost/</link><title>Ludost</title><description>Ludost

30 Oct 2012 by trendmixer on The Trend Mix thetrendmix.com/2012/10/30/ludost/

…  Berlin, London or New York. The new trendy capital is Belgrade! The proof is this new bar. "Ludost" (Madness) has a  deco very Brooklynn  designed by …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7435-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7435_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:51:28">http://iamatters.wordpress.com/2013/12/12/how-to-be-a-hipster-in-berlin-emma-lippens-maarten-taurin/</link><title>HOW TO BE A HIPSTER IN BERLIN? EMMA LIPPENS &amp; MAARTEN TAURIN</title><description>HOW TO BE A HIPSTER IN BERLIN? EMMA LIPPENS &amp; MAARTEN TAURIN

12 Dec 2013 by iamatters2013 on ia matters iamatters.wordpress.com/2013/12/12/how-to-be-a-hipster-in-berlin-emma-lippens-maarten-taurin/

…  more. BARS &amp; CLUBS \- Mein Haus am See: A popular, trendy bar with a relaxed atmosphere andunexpected interior. Always filled with …

Topics: trips, After School, MASTER PROEF</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>