<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7461">navalni trial latest news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:08:40" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7461-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7461_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:08:41">http://fox43.com/2013/09/17/latest-on-sanduskys-bid-for-a-new-trail/</link><title>Latest on Sandusky's bid for a new trial</title><description>Latest on Sandusky's bid for a new trial

17 Sep 2013 by tkauffmanfox43 on WPMT FOX43 fox43.com/2013/09/17/latest-on-sanduskys-bid-for-a-new-trail/

…  that heard Jerry Sandusky's bid for a new trial Tuesday on charges he sexually assaulted 10 boys, spanning two …  That he didn't have enough time to prepare for trial, that those who accused him waited too long to report the abuse to police, and that the prosecutor at trial improperly referenced a television interview Sandusky did with Bob Costas …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7461-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7461_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:09:18">http://aworldgossip.wordpress.com/2011/07/06/casey-anthony-trial-latest-news/</link><title>Casey Anthony Trial Latest News</title><description>Casey Anthony Trial Latest News

6 Jul 2011 by vidyabalansexy on A World Gossip aworldgossip.wordpress.com/2011/07/06/casey-anthony-trial-latest-news/

…  Anthony Trial Latest News Casey Anthony horrendous story was over. Casey found not obligated on …

Topics: World News, casey anthony, Casey Anthony trial, casey anthony trial live, Casey Anthony Verdict, CNN</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7461-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7461_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:09:36">http://chicagodefender.com/2012/06/10/latest-in-edwards-corruption-trial-a-news-guide/</link><title>Latest in Edwards corruption trial: A news guide</title><description>Latest in Edwards corruption trial: A news guide

10 Jun 2012 by rtmadmincd on The Chicago Defender chicagodefender.com/2012/06/10/latest-in-edwards-corruption-trial-a-news-guide/

…  he ran for president. Q: WHAT WAS REVEALED IN THE TRIAL? A: The trial exposed a sordid sex scandal that unfolded while Edwards' wife was …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7461-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7461_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:09:57">http://emmock.com/2013/10/17/bible-blog-1172/</link><title>Bible Blog 1172</title><description>Bible Blog 1172

17 Oct 2013 by emmock on Emmock's Blog emmock.com/2013/10/17/bible-blog-1172/

…  Lectionary daily readings along with a headline from world news: Alexei Navalni ALEXEI NAVALNI, OPPONENT OF PUTIN, STILL BARRED FROM POLITICS IN …

Topics: taking up the Cross, Jesus' family values, Alexei Navalni</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7461-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7461_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:10:10">http://beritawowkeren.wordpress.com/2012/05/13/latest-in-edwards-corruption-trial-a-news-guide/</link><title>Latest in Edwards corruption trial: A news guide</title><description>Latest in Edwards corruption trial: A news guide

13 May 2012 by beritawowkeren on Your Online Information beritawowkeren.wordpress.com/2012/05/13/latest-in-edwards-corruption-trial-a-news-guide/

(AP)–1 day ago RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — A federal judge refused to throw out campaign corruption charges ... http://p.ost.im/p/estu9u</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7461-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7461_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:10:29">http://beritawowkeren.wordpress.com/2012/05/15/latest-in-edwards-corruption-trial-a-news-guide-2/</link><title>Latest in Edwards corruption trial: A news guide</title><description>Latest in Edwards corruption trial: A news guide

15 May 2012 by beritawowkeren on Your Online Information beritawowkeren.wordpress.com/2012/05/15/latest-in-edwards-corruption-trial-a-news-guide-2/

RALEIGH, N.C. — Former presidential hopeful John Edwards' attorneys are presenting his defense against charge ... http://p.ost.im/p/eGkQ4d</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7461-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7461_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:10:43">http://kilkennycyclingclub.com/2013/05/01/latest-news-for-2013-state-time-trial/</link><title>Latest news for 2013 State Time Trial</title><description>Latest news for 2013 State Time Trial

1 May 2013 by Graham McArthur on Kilkenny Cycling Club kilkennycyclingclub.com/2013/05/01/latest-news-for-2013-state-time-trial/

…  30 April 2013 Great numbers for the 2013 State Time Trial, we have 175 competitors. Some things of note amongst these are 74 …  we have seen in quite a while. We have had some great news with the new owners of the Bridge Hotel at Langhorne Creek letting us use …

Topics: Racing, News, Juniors, Masters, Seniors, road</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7461-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7461_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:10:58">http://federalcrimesblog.com/2012/05/12/latest-in-edwards-corruption-trial-a-news-guide/</link><title>Latest in Edwards corruption trial: A news guide</title><description>Latest in Edwards corruption trial: A news guide

12 May 2012 by McNabb Associates, P.C. on Federal Criminal Defense Lawyers federalcrimesblog.com/2012/05/12/latest-in-edwards-corruption-trial-a-news-guide/

…  not guilty. Here is a look at the first weeks of the trial, and some highlights of witness testimony: Q: WHAT EVIDENCE HAS THE …  finance laws. It's unknown whether Edwards, a former trial lawyer, will take the stand in his own defense. Q: IF CONVICTED, WHAT …  find additional federal criminal news, please read Federal Criminal Defense Daily. Douglas McNabb and other …

Topics: federal criminal attorneys, Federal Criminal Defense Attorneys - McNabb Associates, federal criminal lawyer, federal criminal attorney, Douglas McNabb, federal criminal defense attorneys, federal criminal defense attorney, federal criminal defense lawyer, McNabb Associates, federal criminal defense lawyers, federal attorney, federal attorneys, federal lawyers, Federal Lawyer, federal criminal lawyers, federal judge, John Edwards, John Edwards Trial, Rielle Hunter, Campaign Finance Laws, Federal Crime, Federal Crimes, Federal Lawyer, Federal Attorney, Federal Criminal Defense, Federal Criminal Lawyer, Federal Criminal Attorney, Douglas C. McNabb, transnational criminal defense</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7461-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7461_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:11:11">http://livingontilt.com/2013/01/23/the-latest-news-for-saeed-abedini-on-trial-in-iran/</link><title>The Latest News for Saeed Abedini on Trial in Iran</title><description>The Latest News for Saeed Abedini on Trial in Iran

23 Jan 2013 by Katherine Harms on Living On Tilt livingontilt.com/2013/01/23/the-latest-news-for-saeed-abedini-on-trial-in-iran/

…  the trial continued, but Saeed Abedini, the accused, was not permitted to attend. See the Update in this article from yesterday. This trial is not conducted the way we expect trials in the US to proceed. Please …

Topics: Christianity, Iran, christian persecution, Saeed Abedini, Evin Prison, American Center for Law &amp; Justice</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7461-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7461_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:11:33">http://growngreen.wordpress.com/2013/08/21/carrot-trials-latest/</link><title>Carrot Trials Latest</title><description>Carrot Trials Latest

21 Aug 2013 by Grown Green @ Hartley Farm on Grown Green @ Hartley Farm growngreen.wordpress.com/2013/08/21/carrot-trials-latest/

…  results from the carrot trial after another wheel-hoeing: and basically you can see that St Valery looks very good when compared to the other trial and control varieties. Three lines of St Valery are in the middle of the …  too, especially compared to the three Amsterdam Maxi 2 trial to the left of St Valery, and Amsterdam Forcing, furthest three left …

Topics: Carrot, Hartley Farm, Growing, Trials, trial, wheel hoe, St Valery, amsterdam forcing, Maxi, Napoli, Yellowstone, Purple Haze, white satin, Rainbow Bunching, summer fayre, Bank Holiday</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>