<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7472">python re tutorial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:43:25" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7472-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7472_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:43:27">http://kalaharix.wordpress.com/2013/03/11/python-and-qt-designer-tutorial/</link><title>Python and Qt Designer tutorial</title><description>Python and Qt Designer tutorial

11 Mar 2013 by charlesg628 on Gambas, Basic4Android and Linux kalaharix.wordpress.com/2013/03/11/python-and-qt-designer-tutorial/

…  often complained about the lack of integration between Python and UI designers so I was interested by a tutorial written by Kunal Deo …  who would struggle. To modify an immortal phrase: so I re-wrote the tutorial (Python, QT Designer) Media File Converter Tutorial (in …

Topics: Linux in general</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7472-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7472_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:43:43">http://moshez.wordpress.com/2008/04/24/teach-yourself-python-over-a-long-period/</link><title>Teach Yourself Python Over a Long Period</title><description>Teach Yourself Python Over a Long Period

24 Apr 2008 by moshez on Moshe'z moshez.wordpress.com/2008/04/24/teach-yourself-python-over-a-long-period/

…  down. This is easy. Thinking Like a Computer Scientist in Python is a useful book for non-programmers, while the online tutorial is a …  This will be useful later, because it will stop you from re-inventing the wheel. Next, choose some open-source programming project in …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7472-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7472_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:43:59">http://ferretfarmer.net/2013/09/05/tutorial-real-time-chat-with-django-twisted-and-websockets-prerequisites/</link><title>TUTORIAL: Real-time chat with Django, Twisted and WebSockets - Prerequisites</title><description>TUTORIAL: Real-time chat with Django, Twisted and WebSockets - Prerequisites

5 Sep 2013 by ferretfarmer on ferretfarmer ferretfarmer.net/2013/09/05/tutorial-real-time-chat-with-django-twisted-and-websockets-prerequisites/

…  to Part 1. I'm assuming a basic competency writing Python code, as well as access to a development environment, editor, and …  it's worth your rereading the tutorial, and re-completing the first 4 stages before continuing) Twisted is a bit harder …

Topics: Python, Django, twisted, websockets, Tutorial, Programming, Tutorials</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7472-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7472_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:44:09">http://pythongamebook.wordpress.com/2013/07/07/finally-i-write-again/</link><title>Goblins tutorial</title><description>Goblins tutorial

7 Jul 2013 by Horst JENS on The Python Game Book Blog pythongamebook.wordpress.com/2013/07/07/finally-i-write-again/

…  migrating from python2 to python3. Also i heard a lot of python related talks. Summary: python3 is really there, Kivy, Blender, Ubuntu, …  to do something on my ThePythonGameBook... and decided to re-do the goblins tutorial with python3. [caption id="attachment_611" …

Topics: Python, python3</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7472-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7472_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:44:24">http://benxshen.wordpress.com/2009/10/14/diigo-diary-10142009/</link><title>Diigo Diary 10/14/2009</title><description>Diigo Diary 10/14/2009

14 Oct 2009 by benxshen on Benx Blog benxshen.wordpress.com/2009/10/14/diigo-diary-10142009/

…  re-introduction to JavaScript - MDCtags: javascript, tutorial, intro, *經典*, *i_learning*Importing Python Modulestags: python, tips, what-is, faq, sogaJSDB: JavaScript for …

Topics: Diigo Diary</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7472-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7472_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:44:38">http://nirmaangju.wordpress.com/workshops/</link><title>Workshops</title><description>Workshops

29 Oct 2012 by PrayaS - A Step Forward on NIRMAAN - Potential | Innovative | Engineers nirmaangju.wordpress.com/workshops/

…  Workshop on technology which even google uses i.e. Python \- Programming Language, also to include workshop on Animation i.e. …  attend these workshop you need not to master them, if you re new for then again you can attend the same and learn the new tech by IIT …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7472-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7472_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:44:48">http://pauleveritt.wordpress.com/2013/04/08/video-and-source-for-my-pycon-pyramid-tutorial-with-a-twist-of-python-3/</link><title>Video and source for my PyCon Pyramid tutorial with a twist of Python 3</title><description>Video and source for my PyCon Pyramid tutorial with a twist of Python 3

8 Apr 2013 by Paul Everitt on Chatterbox, Reloaded pauleveritt.wordpress.com/2013/04/08/video-and-source-for-my-pycon-pyramid-tutorial-with-a-twist-of-python-3/

…  Pyramid tutorial at PyCon. The fun twist: I based it on Python 3, which Pyramid has supported for about a year and a half. I have a …  with a source Python, they simply closed the ticket but re-opened in another ticket.) My only other issue was process-related. I …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7472-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7472_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:45:06">http://severnclaystudio.wordpress.com/2008/03/01/pantograph-04-is-out/</link><title>Pantograph 0.4 is out</title><description>Pantograph 0.4 is out

2 Mar 2008 by severnclay on Severn Clay Studio severnclaystudio.wordpress.com/2008/03/01/pantograph-04-is-out/

…  highlights: Export an animation to SWF - requires ming-python package Export to PDF option to re-load last settings curve rendering Enjoy it …

Topics: Pantograph</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7472-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7472_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:45:22">http://tombrander.wordpress.com/2008/12/28/getting-started-with-google-app-engine-hello-world/</link><title>Getting Started With Google App Engine-Hello World</title><description>Getting Started With Google App Engine-Hello World

28 Dec 2008 by Tom Brander on Life and Musings tombrander.wordpress.com/2008/12/28/getting-started-with-google-app-engine-hello-world/

…  versions and not 64 bit versions. I installed the latest Python, 2.61 which according to the Python site is the continuing line from the …  than a window that opened and closed too fast to see. Re-reading the getting started info it came clearer to me that I had to follow …

Topics: Free Hosting, Free Hosting, Freeware, Freeware, Google App Engine, Google App Engine, Vista, Vista, vista 64, vista 64, Python, Python</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7472-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7472_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 23:45:41">http://alphacentauri32.wordpress.com/2011/03/29/goal-setting/</link><title>Goal setting - Django</title><description>Goal setting - Django

29 Mar 2011 by Greg Christian on Greg Christian's weblog alphacentauri32.wordpress.com/2011/03/29/goal-setting/

…  of reaching it. Today I decided to learn Django, the Python framework. I made a commitment to spend 1/2 to 1 hour each day, six days …  Having done that much, I think I would be ready to start re-designing one of my websites using Django. Setting up Django and Python on …

Topics: for fun, Python, Goal, Goal Setting, Django</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>