<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7483">facebook paying?</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:16:26" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7483-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7483_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:16:27">http://ddeashion.com/2013/01/02/paying-for-facebook/</link><title>Paying for Facebook???</title><description>Paying for Facebook???

2 Jan 2013 by http://www.ddeashion.com Indie Review on Indie Review ddeashion.com/2013/01/02/paying-for-facebook/

Facebook Tests Payments to Send Messages Facebook Inc. said Thursday it has begun testing a system for users to send …  of messages that are relevant and useful." Facebook says the new test is designed to route messages sent from outside of a …

Topics: Recent news, Deondrae Porter, facebook, Payment, Online Advertising, Tatiana Gonchoroff</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7483-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7483_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:16:44">http://engerlaw.wordpress.com/2014/02/10/if-you-are-paying-for-facebook-advertisi/</link><title>If you are paying for Facebook Advertisi</title><description>If you are paying for Facebook Advertisi

10 Feb 2014 by Mathew Enger Esq. on Tech-Real Estate-Law engerlaw.wordpress.com/2014/02/10/if-you-are-paying-for-facebook-advertisi/

If you are paying for Facebook Advertising, STOP. Your likes are fake, and are costing you real ones. http://ow.ly/tuawG</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7483-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7483_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:17:03">http://straightoutdigital.wordpress.com/2014/04/15/stop-paying-for-facebook-likes/</link><title>Stop paying for Facebook Likes</title><description>Stop paying for Facebook Likes

15 Apr 2014 by Simon Blangiardo on Straight Out Digital straightoutdigital.wordpress.com/2014/04/15/stop-paying-for-facebook-likes/

…  with your current brand KPI's, but my advice is paying for likes is becoming redundant as promoted posts and custom audiences is where Facebook is pushing brands to spend money, and I agree with them that it's …

Topics: reach, facebook likes, Likes are dead, engagement, generated-stories, facebook</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7483-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7483_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:17:17">http://nickbradbury.com/2011/11/17/are-you-paying-attention-to-facebook/</link><title>Are You Paying Attention to Facebook?</title><description>Are You Paying Attention to Facebook?

17 Nov 2011 by Nick Bradbury on Nick Bradbury nickbradbury.com/2011/11/17/are-you-paying-attention-to-facebook/

…  how Google hoped to benefit from knowing what you're paying attention to. These days Google is turning into the stodgy company and Facebook is the scrappy upstart. And now Facebook is the one hoping to benefit …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7483-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7483_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:17:28">http://akcora.wordpress.com/2011/05/26/advertising-on-facebook-without-paying-facebook/</link><title>Advertising on Facebook without paying Facebook!</title><description>Advertising on Facebook without paying Facebook!

26 May 2011 by akcora on Cuneyt's Blog akcora.wordpress.com/2011/05/26/advertising-on-facebook-without-paying-facebook/

…  that Turkish companies have found a way to advertise on Facebook -for free. The basic idea is this; why would you pay for your ad to appear on Facebook pages while you can have Facebook users post your ad to their walls …

Topics: facebook, English</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7483-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7483_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:17:44">http://zitsocialmediagh.com/2013/12/11/are-you-paying-the-right-price-for-a-facebook-post-boost/</link><title>Are You Paying The Right Price For A Facebook Post Boost?</title><description>Are You Paying The Right Price For A Facebook Post Boost?

11 Dec 2013 by Zakiyu Iddris Tandunayir on ZIT SOCIAL MEDIA zitsocialmediagh.com/2013/12/11/are-you-paying-the-right-price-for-a-facebook-post-boost/

Facebook is growing in numbers every day, businesses are spending on Facebook than ever. Are you one of the businesses spending on Facebook and are you doing it the right way? Many are taking the advantage …

Topics: facebook, Social Media, social network, postboost, facebook advertising, facebook page</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7483-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7483_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:17:59">http://wzakcleveland.com/3503511/facebook-paying-10-in-settlement/</link><title>Facebook Paying $10 in Settlement?!?</title><description>Facebook Paying $10 in Settlement?!?

9 Oct 2012 by lilD on 93.1 WZAK wzakcleveland.com/3503511/facebook-paying-10-in-settlement/

Facebook’s trying again to resolve a lingering privacy lawsuit filed by unhappy …  a judge threw out the last proposed settlement, Facebook has revised its offer to resolve the so-called “Fraley” suit, …  Those are ads in which companies pay to inform a Facebook user’s friends when that user has “liked” a particular brand or …

Topics: Entertainment News, facebook lawsuit, facebook settlement, facebook ten dollar settlement</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7483-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7483_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:18:31">http://zhiphopcleveland.com/2906201/facebook-is-paying-people/</link><title>Is Facebook Is Paying People?</title><description>Is Facebook Is Paying People?

7 May 2011 by Terence J. on Z 107.9 zhiphopcleveland.com/2906201/facebook-is-paying-people/

Facebook will now reward users who watch certain ads on the site with Facebook Credits, which can be redeemed to purchase goods on Facebook Deals, the company's new Groupon-like daily deals service. The  …

Topics: Entertainment News, 10, cents, check, facebook, Finance, Financial, Internet, Money, Network, News, paid, People, program, Social, social networking, twitter, z1079</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7483-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7483_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:19:02">http://techtonicc.wordpress.com/2011/08/31/facebook-paying-hackers/</link><title>Facebook Paying Hackers</title><description>Facebook Paying Hackers

31 Aug 2011 by Techtonicc on Techtonicc techtonicc.wordpress.com/2011/08/31/facebook-paying-hackers/

…  you haven't heard yet, Facebook actually WANTS you to hack their site.  Facebook stated that they have paid over $40,000 already to its new "bug …  aka hackers) to send details of any vulnerabilities in Facebook's security.  If any bugs are found, Facebook will pay the finder …

Topics: technology, facebook, Facebook Hacking, hack facebook, get paid for hacking, money for hacking facebook</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7483-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7483_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:19:14">http://coreystewart.wordpress.com/2013/12/10/if-youre-not-paying-anymore-then-facebook-isnt-playing-anymore-digital-music-newsdigital-music-news/</link><title>If Youre Not Paying Anymore, Then Facebook Isnt Playing Anymore... | Digital Music NewsDigital Music News</title><description>If Youre Not Paying Anymore, Then Facebook Isnt Playing Anymore... | Digital Music NewsDigital Music News

9 Dec 2013 by Corey Stewart on Corey Stewart coreystewart.wordpress.com/2013/12/10/if-youre-not-paying-anymore-then-facebook-isnt-playing-anymore-digital-music-newsdigital-music-news/

…  to the future of Facebook, where ‘organic’ and ‘viral’ will soon come with a price tag. …  by AdAge, non-advertising contributors simply aren’t paying the bills, which means that Facebook will be heavily prioritizing paid placements over organic ones. via …

Topics: facebook</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>