<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7486">board games teenagers</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:25:24" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7486-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7486_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:25:25">http://littlegametweaks.wordpress.com/2014/02/19/2012-saw-board/</link><title>Board Games 2012</title><description>Board Games 2012

19 Feb 2014 by Greg on Little Game Tweaks littlegametweaks.wordpress.com/2014/02/19/2012-saw-board/

…  saw board gaming continuing to grow from a greasy teenager into an intimidatingly gorgeous adult, with great games popping onto shelves every month like bones slotting audibly into their …  want in on the action. In the last couple of months tie-in board games have been announced for "Bioshock: Infinite," …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7486-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7486_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:25:40">http://eastcliffrichard.wordpress.com/2006/03/19/board-teenagers/</link><title>Board Teenagers</title><description>Board Teenagers

19 Mar 2006 by eastcliffrichard on Eastcliff Richard eastcliffrichard.wordpress.com/2006/03/19/board-teenagers/

…  don't expect to encounter a fully erected ironing board in the middle of the road at that time of night, do …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7486-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7486_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:25:55">http://belscustomcakes.wordpress.com/2012/12/22/chessboard-cake/</link><title>Chessboard cake</title><description>Chessboard cake

22 Dec 2012 by Bels custom cakes on Bel's custom cakes belscustomcakes.wordpress.com/2012/12/22/chessboard-cake/

This was ordered for an 18th birthday. The chess pieces were a bit big for the board. My teenager plays chess so he played the game to remove some of the pieces off the board. The customer was very happy with it when they collected

Topics: gumpaste figures, Misc, Novelty Cakes, Boy cakes, bels custom cakes, cake maker sunshine coast, chess cake, chess board, Chess Pieces</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7486-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7486_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:26:11">http://youngadultmaterials265.wordpress.com/2012/08/04/chess/</link><title>44.) Chess</title><description>44.) Chess

4 Aug 2012 by ceora_b on Materials for Teens (15-18) youngadultmaterials265.wordpress.com/2012/08/04/chess/

…  has been played since ancient times. Chess is a two-player board game that is played on a chessboard, that is square and checkered. It is …  be very challenging. Selection: I selected Chess board games, because it is a good idea to have family game nights at the library. I …

Topics: Games</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7486-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7486_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:26:33">http://gavinsbrain.wordpress.com/2011/01/10/2-fun-board-games/</link><title>2 Fun Board Games</title><description>2 Fun Board Games

11 Jan 2011 by gavinsbrain on Gavin's brain's Blog gavinsbrain.wordpress.com/2011/01/10/2-fun-board-games/

…  lot of us know about board games. Today, I am going to tell you about two really fun board games. Both …  to use your armies to take over the world. If you have teenagers, then this would be a very fun game to play with them. Those are …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7486-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7486_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:26:49">http://brooksfreelibraryharwich.wordpress.com/2013/04/09/april-vacation-programs/</link><title>April Vacation Programs by Ann Carpenter</title><description>April Vacation Programs by Ann Carpenter

9 Apr 2013 by Suzanne Martell on Brooks Free Library brooksfreelibraryharwich.wordpress.com/2013/04/09/april-vacation-programs/

…  the Brooks Free Library also circulates many different board games. From simple games intended for preschoolers or even toddlers to complex …

Topics: Newspaper column</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7486-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7486_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:27:04">http://emeraldtablet.wordpress.com/2013/02/18/pinterest/</link><title>Pinterest</title><description>Pinterest

18 Feb 2013 by Emerald Tablet on Emerald Tablet emeraldtablet.wordpress.com/2013/02/18/pinterest/

…  have also started a board to honor Osprey Publishing: …  as this board is filled with all my published books, games, mods, and podcasts. And finally I have a board dedicated to all the …  70s, 80, 90 and 2000+ role-playing games that we played as teenagers and perhaps still play today: …

Topics: Troy Christensen, Games, Pinterest, publshing, Books</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7486-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7486_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:27:20">http://stuntiesrule.wordpress.com/about/</link><title>About</title><description>About

20 Mar 2014 by hagbard1970 on Stunties Rule stuntiesrule.wordpress.com/about/

…  is a gaming junkie. I love board games, rpg's, table top, and all sorts of computer and console games. I …  time to indulge my addiction, but being a parent of five teenagers limits that. I am lucky enough to play Warhammer Fanatsy on a …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7486-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7486_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:27:36">http://flatbrokeblog.wordpress.com/2009/11/20/seventh-day-of-flat-broke-christmas-cheap-and-fun-board-games/</link><title>Seventh Day of Flat Broke Christmas: Cheap (and fun) board games</title><description>Seventh Day of Flat Broke Christmas: Cheap (and fun) board games

20 Nov 2009 by Flat Broke Diva on The Flat Broke Blog flatbrokeblog.wordpress.com/2009/11/20/seventh-day-of-flat-broke-christmas-cheap-and-fun-board-games/

…  of Christmas, Flat Broke Blog gave to me: Cheap and fun board games! When people cut their budgets, one of the first items to be scrapped …

Topics: Holidays, gift shopping, 12 Days of Flat Broke Christmas</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7486-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7486_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:27:54">http://giantchess.wordpress.com/2010/03/19/wooden-chess-pieces-for-children-and-house-decoration/</link><title>Wooden Chess Pieces For Children And House Decoration</title><description>Wooden Chess Pieces For Children And House Decoration

19 Mar 2010 by giantchess on Interior Home Decoration Furniture and Outdoor Furniture Decoration giantchess.wordpress.com/2010/03/19/wooden-chess-pieces-for-children-and-house-decoration/

…  to join this game. You just need chess pieces and chess board to play. Just find an interesting area for having chess and you will more …

Topics: Garden Chess Sets</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>