<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7488">DIY shops london open sunday</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:31:14" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7488-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7488_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:31:15">http://56abikespace.wordpress.com/2012/03/05/london-bike-kitchen-woo-yeaaah/</link><title>London Bike Kitchen WOO YEAAAH</title><description>London Bike Kitchen WOO YEAAAH

5 Mar 2012 by 56abikespace on 56abikespace's Blog 56abikespace.wordpress.com/2012/03/05/london-bike-kitchen-woo-yeaaah/

…  London Bike Kitchen, an  "open DIY workshop" in Hoxton, has just opened shop! Bike kitchens started …

Topics: Bike Culture</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7488-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7488_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:31:37">http://hiddenart.co.uk/events-2/past-hidden-art-events/hidden-art-open-studios/hidden-art-open-studios-and-fair-2009/</link><title>Open Studios 2009</title><description>Open Studios 2009

28 Feb 2012 by hiddenartdesign on Hidden Art hiddenart.co.uk/events-2/past-hidden-art-events/hidden-art-open-studios/hidden-art-open-studios-and-fair-2009/

…  Fair took place in Old Truman Brewery, 85 Brick Lane, London E1. Bringing together around 60 UK designer-makers and designers, the …  Clay throwing demonstration and tile making, • DIY Christmas gift workshops, • Bag designing for children, • Recycling …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7488-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7488_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:31:53">http://peckhamresidents.wordpress.com/2008/06/14/sun-15th-june-open-day-the-spike-copeland-rd-railway-bridge/</link><title>Sun 15th June open day The Spike, Copeland Rd railway bridge</title><description>Sun 15th June open day The Spike, Copeland Rd railway bridge

14 Jun 2008 by peckhamresidents on Peckham Residents' Network peckhamresidents.wordpress.com/2008/06/14/sun-15th-june-open-day-the-spike-copeland-rd-railway-bridge/

…  of the place and makes dreams come true.Emerging from DIY culture, the Spike Surplus Scheme landed in 1998 in an abandoned, …  burnt-out building. This building was formerly The South London Children’s Scrap Scheme, and before that, the administrative block for …

Topics: Events, Green Living</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7488-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7488_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:32:11">http://piliontrust.com/2013/04/25/low-cost-quaility-recycled-paint-available-at-low-cost/</link><title>Low cost quaility recycled paint available at low cost.</title><description>Low cost quaility recycled paint available at low cost.

25 Apr 2013 by cockneyreject on Pilion Trust's Blog piliontrust.com/2013/04/25/low-cost-quaility-recycled-paint-available-at-low-cost/

…  8 Clarendon Buildings 25 Horsell Road Islington London N5 1XL 020 7700 2498 Open: Monday to Friday 10am to 5pm – contact …  cheaper when compared to buying new paint from commercial DIY stores. A membership scheme is available for not-for-profit …

Topics: Splash Pilion, recycled paint, Community Groups, the paint place, forest recycling project, Repaint</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7488-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7488_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:32:29">http://londonscn.wordpress.com/spaces/</link><title>Spaces</title><description>Spaces

2 Feb 2010 by bowlcourt on Autonomous London londonscn.wordpress.com/spaces/

…  56a Infoshop is a volunteer-run, 100% unfunded, DIY-run social centre in Walworth, South London. Hosting an amazing collection of radical literature they share the …  co-op &amp; a free D.I.Y Bicycle repair space and are open Wednesdays – Saturdays. If you would like to run a reading group, …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7488-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7488_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:32:42">http://lotusevents.wordpress.com/2013/12/12/got-craft-things-to-do-2/</link><title>got craft? :: things to do!</title><description>got craft? :: things to do!

12 Dec 2013 by lotus events on lotus events lotusevents.wordpress.com/2013/12/12/got-craft-things-to-do-2/

…  and here are our top 5 things to do at the show! DIY WORKSHOPS - There will be plenty of free workshops hosted by Spool of …  Serious Sausage. POP-UP - Our new pop-up shop, London Fields Shoppe, will be open from December 12-23 at 845 East Hastings between Hawks and Campbell Avenue …

Topics: got craft, Etsy, Vancouver, craft fair, Poppytalk, spool of thread, pop-up, uppercase, Food Cart, Christmas, Maritime Labour Centre, Craft, handmade, london fields shoppe, Blog Roll, les amis du fromage</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7488-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7488_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:33:01">http://togsblog.wordpress.com/2006/04/15/jesus-wept/</link><title>Jesus Wept....</title><description>Jesus Wept....

15 Apr 2006 by togsblog on Togsblog, the ramblings of a bitter &amp; twisted press photographer togsblog.wordpress.com/2006/04/15/jesus-wept/

…  in the face of all the evidence said, “Nobody wants the shops to open on Easter Sunday” Well, you genius! So retailers are nobody? So …  husbands and fathers it means tidying up the garden, doing DIY jobs around the house, all sorts of boring shite. The Church should do …

Topics: Mostly Bollox, Rant</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7488-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7488_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:33:16">http://realmomtime.com/2013/05/24/hamleys-and-harrods-london-shopping/</link><title>London's Shopping Shrines: Hamleys and Harrods</title><description>London's Shopping Shrines: Hamleys and Harrods

24 May 2013 by Real Mom Time (RMT) on Real Mom Time (RMT) realmomtime.com/2013/05/24/hamleys-and-harrods-london-shopping/

…  who goes to a city like London and doesn't shop at least a little bit? OK, perhaps C would, but not I, RMT'ers! While London is chock full of shops, stores, and stalls to get your shop on, I'm going to highlight two …  At this station, a Hamleys worker showed us how this DIY sticker kit worked. T got to keep the sticker they made …

Topics: Restaurants, Food, Toys, Games, Restaurants, Travel (2), kids, Shopping, Clothes, Women, gifts, Markets, Deals, Shops, Stores, star wars, London, Covent Garden, Build A Bear, pub, Underground, Transport for London, West End, piccadilly circus, Knightsbridge, harrods, Hamleys, Sales, half yearly</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7488-09"><link>http://diyhappinesskits.wordpress.com/tips-archive/</link><title>Tips Archive</title><description>Tips Archive

26 Feb 2011 by nhsslam on DIY Happiness diyhappinesskits.wordpress.com/tips-archive/

…  your local park - perhaps with your camera! Tip by Caro at DIY …  along the Thames for the amazing panorama views you get of London. Tip by Ingrid Weimers in …  never wasting food, getting stuff from second hand shops. Tip by …  21st May 2011. Mind: keep learning. Open the dictionary on any page, read the definition of a word you’ve never …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7488-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7488_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:35:15">http://misexperienciaspersonales.wordpress.com/2012/10/18/shopping-round-london-town/</link><title>Shopping Round London Town</title><description>Shopping Round London Town

18 Oct 2012 by Ma. Novie Godmalin on Mis Experiencias Personales misexperienciaspersonales.wordpress.com/2012/10/18/shopping-round-london-town/

…  stuffs, stress and etc not just for the preparation of our DIY wedding but also for all the things that were going round the house at the …  travel to start our day of shopping. Little that we know, shops in Oxford Street open late on Sundays so we spend the whole morning …

Topics: Travel, London, True Story, Fashion, Oxford Street, Shopping, shopping, Westfield, Stratford, Olympic Park, Kenton Station, London Underground, Forever 21, Victoria Secret, selfridges, lv, BHS, l'occitane, charity soap, Pret A Manger</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>