<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7492">oldest jokes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:44:44" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7492-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7492_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:44:45">http://averystrangeplace.com/2013/12/11/the-oldest-joke/</link><title>The Oldest Joke</title><description>The Oldest Joke

12 Dec 2013 by averystrangeplace on A VERY STRANGE PLACE averystrangeplace.com/2013/12/11/the-oldest-joke/

Q: Why did the chicken cross the road? A: The Silent Formless One possessed the totality of the chicken's being and compelled him to absorb the sheer inanity of reality's being in to it's beautiful devastation in the infinite purge, start …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7492-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7492_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:44:57">http://hemlockscholar.wordpress.com/2014/04/03/oldest-joke-in-the-book/</link><title>Oldest Joke in the Book</title><description>Oldest Joke in the Book

4 Apr 2014 by thuckydides on Hemlock.scholar hemlockscholar.wordpress.com/2014/04/03/oldest-joke-in-the-book/

…  imagine; but it would surprise most to learn that raunchy jokes have been around since society began. The oldest joke on record was a Sumerian pondering from 1900 BCE.  It goes as …

Topics: Other</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7492-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7492_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:45:10">http://claudemariottini.com/2008/08/03/the-world%e2%80%99s-second-oldest-joke/</link><title>&gt;The World’s Second Oldest Joke</title><description>&gt;The World’s Second Oldest Joke

3 Aug 2008 by Claude Mariottini on Dr. Claude Mariottini - Professor of Old Testament claudemariottini.com/2008/08/03/the-world’s-second-oldest-joke/

…  world’s second oldest joke is an Egyptian joke about King Snofru. Here is the joke:“How do …  and urge the pharaoh to go catch a fish.”The world’s oldest recorded joke has been traced back to 1900 BC. It is a Sumerian joke.To …  of Old TestamentNorthern Baptist SeminaryTag: Jokes var addthis_pub = 'claude …

Topics: Jokes</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7492-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7492_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:45:23">http://dreamranch.wordpress.com/2014/04/19/oldest-santa-fe-joke/</link><title>Oldest Santa Fe joke</title><description>Oldest Santa Fe joke

19 Apr 2014 by John Robertson on dreamranch dreamranch.wordpress.com/2014/04/19/oldest-santa-fe-joke/

Question: How many Santa Feans does it take to change a light bulb? Answer: Three. One to change the bulb and two to step back and say how good it used to look.

Topics: passing by, Santa Fé, oldest joke</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7492-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7492_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:45:45">http://oldstersview.wordpress.com/2008/11/14/ananova-ancient-greeks-wrote-parrot-sketch/</link><title>The oldest joke?</title><description>The oldest joke?

14 Nov 2008 by oldstersview on Oldster's View oldstersview.wordpress.com/2008/11/14/ananova-ancient-greeks-wrote-parrot-sketch/

…  have revealed it is in the world's oldest joke book - entitled Philogelos, or The Lover of Laughter, reports The …

Topics: fun stuff</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7492-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7492_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:46:02">http://chopstix.wordpress.com/2008/07/31/oldest-joke/</link><title>Oldest Joke</title><description>Oldest Joke

31 Jul 2008 by Moye on CHOPSTIX chopstix.wordpress.com/2008/07/31/oldest-joke/

…  thought the oldest joke in the world asked why the chicken crossed the road, but apparently …  good humor was always classic--as in, the root of all good jokes will always be funny. Apparently, it's not. Apparently, the oldest joke in the world is, ...A saying of the Sumerians, who lived in what …

Topics: Thoughts, oldest joke, Humor, Comedy, Sumarians, Ancient civilization, History</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7492-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7492_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:46:18">http://latestvcnews.wordpress.com/2014/04/02/perhaps-the-oldest-joke-on-the-internet/</link><title>Perhaps the oldest joke on the internet</title><description>Perhaps the oldest joke on the internet

2 Apr 2014 by latestvcnews on Startup News Fresh latestvcnews.wordpress.com/2014/04/02/perhaps-the-oldest-joke-on-the-internet/

http://ift.tt/1jYJ2im more… The limk Perhaps the oldest joke on the internet appeared first on Limk. Vía Limk http://ift.tt/1ihwPzH

Topics: startup news, VC, Start-up, News</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7492-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7492_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:46:36">http://newbloggycat.com/2013/06/27/joke-of-the-day-the-oldest-profession/</link><title>Joke of the day - The oldest profession</title><description>Joke of the day - The oldest profession

26 Jun 2013 by newbloggycat on newbloggycat newbloggycat.com/2013/06/27/joke-of-the-day-the-oldest-profession/

…  and a computer scientist were arguing about what was the oldest profession in the world. The doctor remarked, "Well, in the Bible …  required surgery, so I can rightly claim that mine is the oldest profession in the world." The civil engineer interrupted …

Topics: good clean jokes, good clean jokes, Clean Jokes, good jokes, Funny Jokes, Humor, Jokes, free-jokes, Doctor, Civil Engineer, computer scientist</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7492-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7492_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:46:52">http://bigshotmovieclub.com/2013/07/03/clubhouses-the-oldest-joke-in-the-book/</link><title>Clubhouses: The Oldest Joke in the Book</title><description>Clubhouses: The Oldest Joke in the Book

3 Jul 2013 by swinshall on Big Shot Movie Club bigshotmovieclub.com/2013/07/03/clubhouses-the-oldest-joke-in-the-book/

…  Groucho is happy to take the credit for it, similar jokes predating the resignation letter pop up throughout history. In John …

Topics: What's my Line, Woody Allen, Jokes, Clubhouses, clubhouses, Groucho Marx, Annie Hall, Friars Club, Quotations, the forsyte saga, john galsworthy</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7492-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7492_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:47:07">http://jewishhumor.wordpress.com/2012/07/03/the-oldest-jewish-joke-probably-2/</link><title>THE OLDEST JEWISH JOKE--PROBABLY</title><description>THE OLDEST JEWISH JOKE--PROBABLY

3 Jul 2012 by davidmallow on Jewish Humor jewishhumor.wordpress.com/2012/07/03/the-oldest-jewish-joke-probably-2/

…  would be impossible to say what the oldest Jewish joke is. But the oldest Jewish joke theme is probably the Ten Commandments. After smashing the …

Topics: Moses, Sinai, commandments, Really Old Jokes</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>