<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7494">cartoons festival</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:50:05" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7494-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7494_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:50:06">http://lescurieusesblog.wordpress.com/2013/08/19/a-tribute-to-love-is/</link><title>A tribute to 'Love is...'</title><description>A tribute to 'Love is...'

19 Aug 2013 by lescurieusesblog on Les Curieuses lescurieusesblog.wordpress.com/2013/08/19/a-tribute-to-love-is/

…  I was little, I always loved the 'Love is...' cartoons. So when I read that the International Cartoon Festival Knokke-Heist has chosen to pay a tribute to this cartoon couple during …

Topics: Culture, Kim Grave, Roberto Casali, Love is, International Cartoon Festival Knokke-Heist, 52nd edition, casino knokke, Eva Mouton, lectrr, pieter de poortere, Sacha Eckes</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7494-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7494_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:50:21">http://camimbo758.wordpress.com/2013/12/11/green-music-man-cartoon-silicone-usb-flash-disk-special-for-all-kinds-of-festival-day-gifts-16gb/</link><title>Green Music Man Cartoon Silicone Usb Flash Disk, Special For All Kinds Of Festival Day Gifts (16gb)</title><description>Green Music Man Cartoon Silicone Usb Flash Disk, Special For All Kinds Of Festival Day Gifts (16gb)

11 Dec 2013 by ecutup on Camimbo camimbo758.wordpress.com/2013/12/11/green-music-man-cartoon-silicone-usb-flash-disk-special-for-all-kinds-of-festival-day-gifts-16gb/

…  Cartoon Silicone Usb Flash Disk, Special For All Kinds Of Festival Day Gifts (16gb)- Get Lowest Price- Compare Prices- Go to …  Cartoon Silicone USB Flash disk, Special for All Kinds of Festival Day Gifts …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7494-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7494_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:50:35">http://jellebrunt.wordpress.com/2013/11/26/slim-pickings-fat-chances/</link><title>Slim Pickings Fat Chances</title><description>Slim Pickings Fat Chances

26 Nov 2013 by jellebrunt on Jelle Brunt jellebrunt.wordpress.com/2013/11/26/slim-pickings-fat-chances/

…  Jelle Brunt. Slim Pickings won at: Zwolle animation festival 2010 - Best student film Nocicortinfestival 2010 - Short of(f) …  festivals: Cartoon Brew tv's student animation festival 2010 Zlin internation film festival 2010 Anima mundi 2010 18th …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7494-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7494_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:50:48">http://themoonwassweet.wordpress.com/2013/05/08/sicaf/</link><title>SICAF</title><description>SICAF

8 May 2013 by MewLab on High Above the Sky themoonwassweet.wordpress.com/2013/05/08/sicaf/

…  23- 28th 2013 Seoul International Cartoon and Animation Festival (SICAF), which marks its 17th anniversary this year is establishing …  leading global festivals featuring the world's best cartoons and animation contents, extending well beyond the Republic of Korea …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7494-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7494_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:51:05">http://outdoorsy.gardenxl.com/2014/04/26/gardening-told-by-cartoons/</link><title>Gardening told by cartoons...</title><description>Gardening told by cartoons...

26 Apr 2014 by GardenXL on Outdoorsy outdoorsy.gardenxl.com/2014/04/26/gardening-told-by-cartoons/

…  in the UK we have collected some of the cleverest cartoons about gardening and the outdoors. Each year Shrewsbury's International cartoon festival draws together some of the best artists from around the world to …  and have been used solely on this blog to acknowledge the festival and our interests in …

Topics: media, Articles, gardening, shrewbury cartoon festival, Chris Madden Cartoons, patrick hardin cartoons, mark anderson cartoons, Gardening cartoons, funny gardening cartoons</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7494-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7494_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:51:24">http://ashbyartsfestival.wordpress.com/2011/05/31/ashby-cartoons-%e2%80%93-go-on-show-for-festival/</link><title>Ashby Cartoons – Go on Show for Festival</title><description>Ashby Cartoons – Go on Show for Festival

31 May 2011 by Jennifer Cotterill on Ashbyartsfestival's Blog ashbyartsfestival.wordpress.com/2011/05/31/ashby-cartoons-–-go-on-show-for-festival/

…  cartoons depicting important local events will go on display for the first time at this year’s Ashby Arts Festival. This important exhibition will be one of the highlights of the …  for local people. In 2010, Ashby Museum commissioned 28 cartoons, based on important events in the town and surrounding area’s …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7494-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7494_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:51:41">http://europeancartooncenterkruishoutem.wordpress.com/2013/07/17/cartoonfestival-knokke-heist/</link><title>Cartoonfestival Knokke-Heist</title><description>Cartoonfestival Knokke-Heist

17 Jul 2013 by Admin on The amazing world of cartoons and cartoonists europeancartooncenterkruishoutem.wordpress.com/2013/07/17/cartoonfestival-knokke-heist/

…  opening ceremony. In the cartoon competition world the festival still has a ‘ big name’ – although the competition itself gets …  part of the exhibition – this year the ‘Love is …’ cartoons of Kim Caseli, but at the same time those tourists see the selected …

Topics: cartoonfestivals, cartoons, Knokke, Humor, Cartoonfestival</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7494-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7494_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:52:09">http://justiceforcomfortwomen.org/2014/01/30/angouleme-comic-festival-comfortwomen-issue-press-conference-suddenly-cancelled-by-festival-committees-request/</link><title>Angouleme Comic Festival, 'ComfortWomen' issue press conference suddenly Cancelled by Festival Committee's request.</title><description>Angouleme Comic Festival, 'ComfortWomen' issue press conference suddenly Cancelled by Festival Committee's request.

30 Jan 2014 by justiceforcomfortwomen on justiceforcomfortwomen justiceforcomfortwomen.org/2014/01/30/angouleme-comic-festival-comfortwomen-issue-press-conference-suddenly-cancelled-by-festival-committees-request/

…  2014 Angouleme Comic Festival,Cartoons about former Korean sex slaves to the Japanese military during World War II will be exhibited. Some 20 cartoons and four videos including animations by local artists telling tragic …

Topics: Comfort Women, Angouleme Festival, world war2, Japanese Government, War Victims, Articles</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7494-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7494_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:52:23">http://europeancartooncenterkruishoutem.wordpress.com/2012/07/15/cartoon-festival-knokke-heist/</link><title>Cartoon festival Knokke-Heist</title><description>Cartoon festival Knokke-Heist

14 Jul 2012 by Admin on The amazing world of cartoons and cartoonists europeancartooncenterkruishoutem.wordpress.com/2012/07/15/cartoon-festival-knokke-heist/

…  was the opening ceremony of the 51st cartoon festival of Knokke-Heist. The guest of honor of this years' festival was the Belgian comedian and comic writer Urbanus. So at the festival …  countries and 1714 entries. The jury selected at about 120 cartoons for the exhibition (on the beach). The winners were: Krzysztof …

Topics: cartoonfestivals, Cartoon, press cartoon, humour, Festival, Knokke</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7494-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7494_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:52:50">http://planetpledis.wordpress.com/2013/07/13/news-hello-venus-become-the-new-ambassadors-of-sicaf/</link><title>News: Hello Venus become the new ambassadors of 'SICAF'</title><description>News: Hello Venus become the new ambassadors of 'SICAF'

13 Jul 2013 by Aron's orange on Planet Pledis ★ planetpledis.wordpress.com/2013/07/13/news-hello-venus-become-the-new-ambassadors-of-sicaf/

…  'The 17th Seoul International Cartoon and Animation Festival'!   The girls attended the ceremony on the 10th at the …  happy to become the SICAF ambassadors. As people who love cartoons, it's like a dream. We're going to work hard to promote …

Topics: Hello Venus, News</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>