<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7496">why IEEE member</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:55:54" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7496-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7496_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:55:55">http://mahdinmahboob.wordpress.com/2008/07/13/inauguration-of-the-ieee-student-branch-brac-university/</link><title>Inauguration of the IEEE Student Branch @ BRAC University</title><description>Inauguration of the IEEE Student Branch @ BRAC University

12 Jul 2008 by mahdin on Mahdin Mahboob's Articles mahdinmahboob.wordpress.com/2008/07/13/inauguration-of-the-ieee-student-branch-brac-university/

…  thanks to Sahar for the report Inauguration of the IEEE Student Branch @ BRAC University Sahar Noor Abdal THE Inaugural …  everyone's attention with his beautiful examples of why students should become members of IEEE and how they will be benefited from …

Topics: Star Campus, Others, IEEE</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7496-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7496_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:56:10">http://energyautonomoussystem.wordpress.com/2013/01/16/ieee-institute-of-electrical-and-electronics-engineers/</link><title>IEEE \- Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers</title><description>IEEE \- Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers

16 Jan 2013 by plaip on Energy solution energyautonomoussystem.wordpress.com/2013/01/16/ieee-institute-of-electrical-and-electronics-engineers/

…  has already view some standards like IEEE 802 - LAN. It's the standard dealing with local area networks and metropolitan area networks. Member grades : I would to present you some member grades Student Members …  This magazine is free when you are Student member. Why to join …

Topics: Have fun ! Off Topic ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7496-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7496_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:56:27">http://imctvr9.com/quienes-somos/</link><title>About</title><description>About

6 Aug 2012 by ieeetvr9 on IMCtvR9 imctvr9.com/quienes-somos/

…  6LncQ9oa] What is IMC TV R9 ? We are an IEEE volunteer group from Region 9 (Latinoamerica and Caribe countries). Our …  However our topics are not limited to IEEE issues, that is why that some pages are used to complement information that students and …  in reality means a way to destroy this initiative. That is why that IMC R9 decides to create this project with its own founds in order to …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7496-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7496_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:56:41">http://wsnblog.com/2013/10/08/exploring-the-impact-of-the-internet-of-things/</link><title>Exploring the Impact of the Internet of Things</title><description>Exploring the Impact of the Internet of Things

8 Oct 2013 by marcozennaro on Wireless Sensor Networks Blog wsnblog.com/2013/10/08/exploring-the-impact-of-the-internet-of-things/

…  IEEE's The Institute: The “next big thing” is the Internet of …  uses it and for what purpose. These and other issues are why the IEEE Future Directions Committee, the organization’s R&amp;D arm, …  skills to create value and impact industry,” says IEEE Member Roberto Minerva, chair of the initiative’s working group. …

Topics: wsn-general, IEEE, Iot</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7496-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7496_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:56:57">http://blog.postmaster.gr/2012/09/25/re-ieee-annual-election-important-message-for-region-8-members/</link><title>re: IEEE Annual Election – Important Message for Region 8 Members</title><description>re: IEEE Annual Election – Important Message for Region 8 Members

25 Sep 2012 by adamo on Managing organized complexity blog.postmaster.gr/2012/09/25/re-ieee-annual-election-important-message-for-region-8-members/

…  the IEEE Region 8 Director's mail to members:Less than 15% of the IEEE …  important!Dear Director, do not ask me to vote. Find out why I am not voting, even though I am a member and eliminate the problem. Dear candidate, this is your challenge too: …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7496-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7496_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:57:13">http://echorand.me/research/</link><title>Research</title><description>Research

24 Jul 2011 by Amit on Bits from /home/gene echorand.me/research/

…  Algorithms Blog posts Services Reviewer for IEEE Congress on Evolutionary Computation, 2012 Reviewer for IEEE …  for Journal of Mechanical Design, ASME Program Committee Member for  Simulated Evolution and Learning (SEAL), 2010 Reviewer for …  for IEEE Congress on Evolutionary Computation, 2010 Why not switch to/adopt/try Open Source tools for your research? Open …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7496-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7496_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:57:30">http://tryingtoreason.wordpress.com/2012/09/02/why-im-voting-for-durrani-for-ieee-president-elect/</link><title>Why I'm voting for Durrani for IEEE President-Elect</title><description>Why I'm voting for Durrani for IEEE President-Elect

2 Sep 2012 by Chuan-Zheng on Trying to Reason tryingtoreason.wordpress.com/2012/09/02/why-im-voting-for-durrani-for-ieee-president-elect/

…  plans have some detail; Roberto de Marca's have none. IEEE members should consider that when voting. I’m normally underwhelmed …  to me. That’s fine, and I’d be intrigued to hear why. But statements with some particularity about plans evoke more confidence …

Topics: Engineering institutions, IEEE, IEEE president-elect 2013</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7496-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7496_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:57:46">http://tryingtoreason.wordpress.com/2011/07/01/promotion-is-not-the-answer/</link><title>Promotion is not the answer</title><description>Promotion is not the answer

1 Jul 2011 by Chuan-Zheng on Trying to Reason tryingtoreason.wordpress.com/2011/07/01/promotion-is-not-the-answer/

IEEE volunteers assume that people don’t understand the benefits of membership. …  figures out that too many people don’t appreciate why they should be a member. They’ll then set out to “introduce” people to the benefits of …

Topics: Engineering institutions, Engineering, Institution, IEEE, IET</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7496-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7496_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:58:03">http://dilsonlira.wordpress.com/2007/11/09/ieee-communications-digest-mashup/</link><title>IEEE Communications Digest Mashup</title><description>IEEE Communications Digest Mashup

9 Nov 2007 by dilsonlira on A few words about bits, equations and thoughts dilsonlira.wordpress.com/2007/11/09/ieee-communications-digest-mashup/

…  intuitive way, connecting blocks and pipes - that's why the name. Certainly this short description of Pipes can be useful, but …  this post: one of the first pipes I've created is a IEEE Communications Digest (for those who are not familiarized with, IEEE means …

Topics: technical, Mashup, Web 2.0, IEEE, wireless, communications, signal processing, Pipes, Mobile</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7496-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7496_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 00:58:19">http://eco-sustain.org/2013/03/13/smieee/</link><title>Senior Member \- IEEE</title><description>Senior Member \- IEEE

13 Mar 2013 by Stephen Makonin on Eco-Sustainability and the Smart Home eco-sustain.org/2013/03/13/smieee/

…  week I was honoured to receive recognition by the IEEE. I was elevated to the Senior Member (smIEEE) grade. Quote from the letter: "Only 8% of the IEEE's approximately 419,900 members hold this grade, which requires …

Topics: General, IEEE, technology, Environment, Science</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>