<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7504">leiden schools</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-27 01:20:37" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7504-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7504_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 01:20:38">http://notesofanidealist.wordpress.com/2013/03/16/leiden-summer-school-2013/</link><title>Leiden Summer School 2013</title><description>Leiden Summer School 2013

16 Mar 2013 by notesofanidealist on Notes of an idealist notesofanidealist.wordpress.com/2013/03/16/leiden-summer-school-2013/

…  align="aligncenter" width="300"] Leiden[/caption] I have received the following letter about the Leiden Summer School (which I went to in 2009): Dear Sir/Madam, We are happy to announce the eighth edition of the Leiden Summer School in Languages and Linguistics which will be held from 15 …

Topics: Russian, Summer Schools, Indo-European, historical linguistics, languages</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7504-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7504_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 01:20:52">http://notesofanidealist.wordpress.com/2011/03/03/leiden-summer-school-2011/</link><title>Leiden Summer School 2011</title><description>Leiden Summer School 2011

3 Mar 2011 by notesofanidealist on Notes of an idealist notesofanidealist.wordpress.com/2011/03/03/leiden-summer-school-2011/

…  have received the email below about this year's Leiden Summer School in Languages and Linguistics.  It looks rather …  We are happy to announce the sixth edition of the Leiden Summer School in Languages and Linguistics which will be held from 18 July – 29 July 2011 at the Faculty of Humanities of Leiden University. The Summer School offers a number of courses on a wide …

Topics: Russian, Leiden, Summer School, Indo-European, languages</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7504-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7504_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 01:21:07">http://erroladamsjdmls.wordpress.com/2012/08/07/leiden-law-blog-articles-new-a-ph-d-in-law-us-developments-and-the-demands-of-legal-research/</link><title>Leiden Law Blog - Articles - New: A Ph.D. in Law. US Developments and the Demands of Legal Research</title><description>Leiden Law Blog - Articles - New: A Ph.D. in Law. US Developments and the Demands of Legal Research

8 Aug 2012 by Errol A. Adams, J.D., M.L.S. on Errol A. Adams, J.D. M.L.S' Blog erroladamsjdmls.wordpress.com/2012/08/07/leiden-law-blog-articles-new-a-ph-d-in-law-us-developments-and-the-demands-of-legal-research/

…  on Scoop.it - The Information Specialist's Scoop The Leiden Law Blog is part of the Leiden Law School, Leiden University. The blog stands out by reacting to the …

Topics: Articles of Interest to Law Librarians</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7504-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7504_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 01:21:30">http://notesofanidealist.wordpress.com/2010/03/23/leiden-summer-school-2010/</link><title>Leiden Summer School 2010</title><description>Leiden Summer School 2010

23 Mar 2010 by notesofanidealist on Notes of an idealist notesofanidealist.wordpress.com/2010/03/23/leiden-summer-school-2010/

…  have received an email as follows: Leiden Summer School in Languages and Linguistics: 19 July - 30 July …  We are happy to announce the fifth edition of the Leiden Summer School in Languages and Linguistics which will be held from 19 July – 30 July 2010 at the Faculty of Humanities of Leiden University. The Summer School offers a number of courses on a wide …

Topics: Russian, Summer Schools, Leiden, Indo-European, languages</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7504-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7504_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 01:21:44">http://aikidoschoolleiden.wordpress.com/media/</link><title>Media</title><description>Media

10 Jul 2013 by Aikido School Leiden on Aikido School Leiden aikidoschoolleiden.wordpress.com/media/

…  school Leiden geeft een demonstratie op de jaarlijkse Japanmarkt in Leiden (Mei 2011) [youtube=http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wiENcbGW3nQ] 50 …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7504-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7504_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 01:22:07">http://metro.co.uk/2013/04/22/netherlands-school-massacre-threat-arrest-made-as-leiden-pupils-stay-home-3661656/</link><title>Netherlands school massacre threat: Arrest made as Leiden pupils stay home</title><description>Netherlands school massacre threat: Arrest made as Leiden pupils stay home

22 Apr 2013 by Carl Morris on Metro metro.co.uk/2013/04/22/netherlands-school-massacre-threat-arrest-made-as-leiden-pupils-stay-home-3661656/

…  Police stand in front of the Da Vinci College, in Leiden, following the online threat that someone would shoot pupils and a …  an arrest following the anonymous threat as more than 20 schools were told to shut their doors. The suspect is a former pupil of the …

Topics: World</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7504-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7504_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 01:22:32">http://crn2.wordpress.com/2013/12/06/leiden-law-blog/</link><title>Leiden Law Blog</title><description>Leiden Law Blog

6 Dec 2013 by jelmerbrouwer on CRN on Citizenship &amp; Immigration crn2.wordpress.com/2013/12/06/leiden-law-blog/

…  from Leiden University regularly post on issues of citizenship and migration on Leiden Law Blog. Leiden Law Blog is part of the Leiden Law School, Leiden University. The …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7504-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7504_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 01:22:50">http://dames1hds.wordpress.com/about-2/de-teams/leiden-dames-1/</link><title>Leiden</title><description>Leiden

13 Oct 2013 by dames1hds on HDS Dames 1 dames1hds.wordpress.com/about-2/de-teams/leiden-dames-1/

Team Facebook Club Site datum Heb nog niks! Heb ik een teampagina gemist? Twitter, Facebook, Pinterest, Fotopagina, wat dan ook? Of heeft je club pagina's die nog ontbreken? Geef het door en ik zal ze er zo snel mogelijk b …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7504-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7504_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 01:23:01">http://inalux.wordpress.com/2012/02/04/cold-under-our-feet/</link><title>Cold Under Our Feet...</title><description>Cold Under Our Feet...

4 Feb 2012 by Jos Runarka on A Push for a Moment inalux.wordpress.com/2012/02/04/cold-under-our-feet/

…  falls until minus 18 under zero Celcius. In Leiden temperature was 16 degree below zero Celcius. Again the Netherlands as …  gets fog. Our feets gets colder and colder... Leiden 2012 Old man testing the ice? Leiden 2012 Survival kit Leiden 2012 There are a lot of bridges in The …

Topics: streetphotography, Living in Holland, BW, Photography, Leica M, Netherlands</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7504-10"><link>http://goatysnews.wordpress.com/2013/04/22/ex-student-of-the-british-school-in-voorschoten-arrested-after-website-threat-of-mass-shooting-22-schools-closed-in-lieden-220413-1045z/</link><title>Netherlands: Ex student of The British School in Voorschoten arrested after website threat of mass shooting; 22 schools closed in Lieden - 220413 1045z</title><description>Netherlands: Ex student of The British School in Voorschoten arrested after website threat of mass shooting; 22 schools closed in Lieden - 220413 1045z

22 Apr 2013 by Goaty's News on Goaty's News (UK) goatysnews.wordpress.com/2013/04/22/ex-student-of-the-british-school-in-voorschoten-arrested-after-website-threat-of-mass-shooting-22-schools-closed-in-lieden-220413-1045z/

Topics: News, Netherlands, Terrorism, schools, Lieden, the british school, Voorschoten, mass shooting</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>