<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7505">ethnic myanmar</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-27 01:24:47" name="WordPress" id="FW14-e026"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e026-7505-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7505_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 01:24:48">http://nyiwin.wordpress.com/2010/11/21/my-writings-blogs-are-on-google-search-results/</link><title>My writings / blogs are on google search results!</title><description>My writings / blogs are on google search results!

21 Nov 2010 by nyiwin on Nyiwin's Blog nyiwin.wordpress.com/2010/11/21/my-writings-blogs-are-on-google-search-results/

…  my blog! Later, as I was searching for “Myanmar ethnic groups” while searching for “Tarongs”, I got the following result: ·  List of ethnic groups in Burma - Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia Burma (or Myanmar) …

Topics: infotainment, Life, infotainment</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7505-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7505_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 01:25:02">http://asyrafrasid.wordpress.com/2012/08/03/save-rohingya-activists-march-to-the-myanmar-embassy-in-kuala-lumpur/</link><title>'Save Rohingya' activists march to the Myanmar Embassy in Kuala Lumpur</title><description>'Save Rohingya' activists march to the Myanmar Embassy in Kuala Lumpur

3 Aug 2012 by asyrafrasid on asyrafrasid asyrafrasid.wordpress.com/2012/08/03/save-rohingya-activists-march-to-the-myanmar-embassy-in-kuala-lumpur/

…  scream to demand the government of Myanmar, countries that are members of ASEAN and the United Nations to care about the massacre of ethnic Rohingya Muslims. Protesters scream to demand the government of …  ASEAN and the United Nations to care about the massacre of ethnic Rohingya Muslims. Protesters scream to demand the government of …

Topics: Protest, Rohinyga, Kuala Lumpur, Myanmar, Malaysia, Ramadan</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7505-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7505_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 01:25:18">http://kabamakyei.wordpress.com/2014/02/07/the-people/</link><title>The People</title><description>The People

7 Feb 2014 by jypanthro on Republic of the Union of Myanmar kabamakyei.wordpress.com/2014/02/07/the-people/

…  135 ethnic groups comprise the Myanmar people. About 70 percent of the population arrived from Central Asia …  century. Apart from the Chinese and Indians, most minority ethnic groups live mainly in the hills. The hills peoples' lifestyles and …

Topics: History, Culture</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7505-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7505_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 01:25:35">http://alfredmeier.me/2014/02/13/myanmar-census-from-march-30-to-april-10-2014/</link><title>Myanmar Census from March 30 to April 10, 2014.</title><description>Myanmar Census from March 30 to April 10, 2014.

13 Feb 2014 by Alfred Wilhelm Meier on Living in SouthEast Asia. alfredmeier.me/2014/02/13/myanmar-census-from-march-30-to-april-10-2014/

…  Myanmar census  from March 30 to April 10, 2014, will include the …  that does not mean that they will be recognized as an ethnic group or as citizens of Myanmar, the Union Minister for Immigration and …  there is no recognized term for Rohingya as one of the 135 ethnic groups in Myanmar and no code number for Rohingya will be given during …

Topics: Myanmar (Burma), Bangladesh, Rohingya, Myanmar Census 2014, Myanmar population, Myanmar, Myanmar government, ethnic groups in Myanmar, national census</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7505-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7505_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 01:26:11">http://fazrulhasnor.wordpress.com/2013/01/10/karen-tribe-new-year-celebration-in-kuala-lumpur/</link><title>Karen Tribe New Year Celebration in Kuala Lumpur</title><description>Karen Tribe New Year Celebration in Kuala Lumpur

10 Jan 2013 by fazrulhasnor on FAZRUL HASNOR fazrulhasnor.wordpress.com/2013/01/10/karen-tribe-new-year-celebration-in-kuala-lumpur/

…  10.2013. Perhaps 5 million Karen tribal members live in Myanmar. Another 300,000 Karen-ethnic peoples have roots in Thailand, and thousands of others live there as …

Topics: Malaysia, Culture, Feature, News, Culture 2, Society, Festival, Malaysia, Festival 2, Karen tribe, new year</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7505-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7505_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 01:26:37">http://fazrulhasnor.wordpress.com/2011/10/11/myanmar-activists-protest-treatment-of-minority-groups/</link><title>Myanmar activists protest treatment of Minority Groups</title><description>Myanmar activists protest treatment of Minority Groups

11 Oct 2011 by fazrulhasnor on FAZRUL HASNOR fazrulhasnor.wordpress.com/2011/10/11/myanmar-activists-protest-treatment-of-minority-groups/

…  display placards against Myanmar's President Thein Sein outside the Myanmar embassy in Kuala …  and torture committed by Myanmar's army against ethnic minority fighters, armed groups and civilians. Photo by Fazrul …  and torture committed by Myanmar's army against ethnic minority fighters, armed groups and civilians. Photo by Fazrul …

Topics: Politic, Religion, Malaysia, Culture, Heritage, Crime, Law, News, Protest, Politic, news 2, Society, society, protest 2, Law 2, Malaysia, World, Street, Myanmar</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7505-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7505_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 01:26:59">http://fazrulhasnor.wordpress.com/2012/10/27/protest-rohingya-at-kuala-lumpur/</link><title>Protest Rohingya at Kuala Lumpur</title><description>Protest Rohingya at Kuala Lumpur

27 Oct 2012 by fazrulhasnor on FAZRUL HASNOR fazrulhasnor.wordpress.com/2012/10/27/protest-rohingya-at-kuala-lumpur/

Protesters gathered in front of Tabung Haji building in Kuala Lumpur to protest the Government of Myanmar to stop the atrocities and ethnic disputes between ethnic Rohingya &amp; Rakhine in Myanmar. October 25,2012. Photo by Fazrul Hasnor

Topics: Politic, Religion, Crime, Protest, Politic, Society, protest 2, Malaysia, Rally, Street, Myanmar, rally 2, 2012, Rohingya, Rakhine</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7505-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7505_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 01:27:19">http://zulfadhlizaki.wordpress.com/2012/06/17/muslim-rohingyas-protest-in-kuala-lumpur/</link><title>Muslim Rohingyas protest in Kuala Lumpur</title><description>Muslim Rohingyas protest in Kuala Lumpur

17 Jun 2012 by zulfadhlizaki on My guise of view zulfadhlizaki.wordpress.com/2012/06/17/muslim-rohingyas-protest-in-kuala-lumpur/

…  ethnic Rohingya from Myanmar and living in Malaysia calling for a stop to the killings and violence …  Kuala Lumpur. Thousands of displaced Muslim Rohingyas and ethnic Rakhine Buddhists were in need of food, water and shelter in …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7505-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7505_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 01:27:48">http://allisonstuby.wordpress.com/portfolio-3/sexual-violence-still-terrorizes-the-ethnic-minorities-of-burmamyanmar/</link><title>Sexual violence still terrorizes the ethnic minorities of Burma/Myanmar</title><description>Sexual violence still terrorizes the ethnic minorities of Burma/Myanmar

11 Apr 2014 by astuby on Allison Stuby allisonstuby.wordpress.com/portfolio-3/sexual-violence-still-terrorizes-the-ethnic-minorities-of-burmamyanmar/

…  vicious gang rape occurred in the Kachin state of Myanmar/Burma. It is one of over 100 rapes since 2010 documented in a report …  that is home to one of the world’s longest running ethnic conflicts. In the 1960s, the democratically elected government was …  until recently by imprisoning opposition and minority ethnic leaders. In 2008, a new constitution was implemented that allowed for …</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e026-7505-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e026/7505_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-27 01:27:59">http://voaburmese.wordpress.com/2010/08/02/whats-in-a-name-burma-or-myanmar/</link><title>What's in a Name? Burma or Myanmar</title><description>What's in a Name? Burma or Myanmar

2 Aug 2010 by voaburmese on VOA Burmese Blog voaburmese.wordpress.com/2010/08/02/whats-in-a-name-burma-or-myanmar/

…  today have trouble referring to the country, Burma - Myanmar? " Burma" or "Myanmar", would the country still …  it had the opposite effect. Human rights groups and ethnic tribes in Burma, ( of which many do not speak the official language …

Topics: Burma (Myanmar), Feature Story, News, Burma, Myanmar, Shakespeare, what's in a name? a rose by any other name smells as sw</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>