<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7014">Asian culture</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:43:02" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7014-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7014_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:43:02">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2012-08-15/bin-hammam-payments-came-out-of-personal-accounts</link><title>Bin Hammam: Payments came out of personal accounts</title><description>Wednesday August 15, 2012 6:05 pm

... president of Asian soccer are politically motivated and that he plans to fight "this clear abuse of power and... to 20 Asian associations, bin Hammam confirmed he made payments to soccer officials and others but said... by the Asian Football Confederation and FIFA, but have been described by Bin Hammam as "a repeat of what</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7014-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7014_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:45:32">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2012-08-30/mls-portland-timbers-add-food-carts-to-stadium-culinary-concessions</link><title>MLS: Portland Timbers add food carts to stadium culinary concessions</title><description>Thursday August 30, 2012 7:24 pm

Portland's culture as well as embracing it, are featuring food cart cuisine at several home matches this season.... bring in Asian cuisine from Stumptown Dumplings. Of course, it would be all the more of a feel-good partnership</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7014-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7014_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:47:05">http://www.sportingnews.com/sport/story/2012-08-22/canadian-womens-open-brittany-lincicome-opens-title-defense</link><title>Canadian Women's Open: Brittany Lincicome opens title defense</title><description>Wednesday August 22, 2012 8:29 pm

... bid to experience the city's culture. "I'm loving it here," she said. "It's like Asian-food Heaven."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7014-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7014_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:48:18">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2012-05-10/new-stadium-the-pinnacle-of-houston-dynamos-quest-to-build-the-perfect-franchise</link><title>New stadium pinnacle of Dynamo's quest to build perfect franchise</title><description>Thursday May 10, 2012 5:46 pm

... going to Asian Chamber of Commerce events in Houston with Brian Ching," who is from Hawaii. Canetti came... creates a culture, an environment. You can build history around it." In that comment lies the heart of "MLS</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7014-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7014_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:51:57">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2012-03-31/american-football-sets-foot-in-cricket-crazy-india</link><title>American football sets foot in cricket-crazy India</title><description>Saturday March 31, 2012 9:12 pm

... landscape of Asian TV," EFLI founder and chief executive Sunday Zellar told The Associated Press. "In addition,... and the culture of the American football game will have planted itself on the ground and in the hearts</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7014-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7014_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:55:37">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2012-02-15/crass-comments-on-jeremy-lin-put-the-twit-in-twitter</link><title>Crass comments on Jeremy Lin put the twit in Twitter</title><description>Wednesday February 15, 2012 11:42 am

... white, Asian or anyone else. Everything about race is awash in complexities. One group's positives can... sport, its culture and the race that makes up its majority, inside what seemed to be a salute to Lin. It was</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7014-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7014_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:59:29">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2012-02-14/as-the-legend-of-lin-grows-anthony-says-hell-fit-in</link><title>As the legend of Lin grows, Anthony says he'll fit in</title><description>Tuesday February 14, 2012 11:39 pm

... a pop culture sensation, the Knicks were mostly Anthony's team. And for two beyond-dreary halves of two... converged with Asian Heritage Night--planned weeks ago to coincide with Chinese New Year--but nobody could have... about 25 Asian media outlets had to wait outside.) FROM SI Nash joins in on Linsanity bandwagon Don't</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7014-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7014_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:03:26">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2011-08-10/british-prime-minister-pledges-to-fight-back-vs-rioters-tension-spreads</link><title>British prime minister pledges to fight back vs. rioters; tension spreads</title><description>Wednesday August 10, 2011 6:07 pm

... let a "culture of fear" take hold, tensions flared in Birmingham, where a murder probe was opened after... South Asian communities who had been patrolling their neighborhood to keep it safe from looters. "They... South Asian community not to seek revenge against the car's occupants, reported to be black. "Today</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7014-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7014_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:05:58">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2011-07-18/world-cup-gives-japan-joyful-respite-from-disaster</link><title>World Cup gives Japan joyful respite from disaster</title><description>Monday July 18, 2011 12:42 pm

... first Asian nation to win the Women's World Cup, beating the United States 3-1 in a penalty shootout... youth pop culture. Japan's national newspapers printed special editions that were handed out to pedestrians... Japanese culture. The victory came against a backdrop of concern about the crippled nuclear power plant</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7014-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7014_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:08:59">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2011-07-18/fans-give-nadeshiko-japan-a-heros-welcome</link><title>Thousands hail 'Nadeshiko' as World Cup champs return home</title><description>Monday July 18, 2011 10:36 pm

... champion. No Asian team had ever won the cup. But Japan, which went in at No. 4 in the rankings, just would... youth pop culture. Japan's biggest newspapers printed special editions. Scenes from the game have replayed</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>