<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7015">the raven</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:11:00" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7015-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7015_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:11:03">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-02-03/phelps-the-raven</link><title>PHELPS THE RAVEN</title><description>Sunday February 3, 2013 4:59 pm

Phelps told the AP. "Ravens by seven." When the Ravens won the 2001 Super Bowl, Phelps was a teenager just... routed the New York Giants 34-7. "I slept through the alarm to wake up and watch the game," Phelps said.... shows you the Super Bowl and the events surrounding the game through the eyes of Associated Press journalists</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7015-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7015_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:11:46">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2014-02-17/olb-suggs-signs-4-year-extension-with-ravens</link><title>OLB Suggs signs 4-year extension with Ravens</title><description>Monday February 17, 2014 3:18 pm

... saves the Ravens salary cap room and puts the linebacker in position to finish his career in Baltimore. The 31-year-old Suggs signed a six-year deal in 2009 that expired after the 2014 season. Now he's... announce the extension, Suggs said, "Sizzle will be a Raven for life." Suggs was expected to count $12.4</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7015-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7015_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:14:44">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2014-02-17/nfl-ravens-terrell-suggs-contract-extension-salary-cap-eugene-monroe-dennis-pitta</link><title>Suggs' extension making Ravens' offseason better already</title><description>Monday February 17, 2014 11:18 am

Suggs, the pass rusher who was the NFL's Defensive Player of the Year in 2011, signed a four-year deal,... rumors The Ravens are currently some $12 million under the cap, according to the Baltimore Sun , before... eliminated from the playoffs on the final Sunday of the season. Newsome reiterated his goal of extending contracts,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7015-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7015_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:16:10">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2014-02-18/monday-s-sports-in-brief</link><title>Monday's Sports In Brief</title><description>Tuesday February 18, 2014 4:36 am

... end of the season. James made the comments in a wide-ranging interview with NBA TV. The Heat star can... knee - the third procedure in nine months. The three-time NBA All-Star tore the lateral meniscus in his... team. Now the Pro Bowl linebacker embraces the idea of going the distance as a Baltimore Raven. Suggs signed</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7015-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7015_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:19:41">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2014-02-09/super-bowl-rings-auctioned-spygate-matt-estrella-ravens-jamie-sharper-damien-berry-leonard-lyles</link><title>Spygate videographer sells Super Bowl ring for $15,810</title><description>Sunday February 9, 2014 6:21 pm

Estrella, the New England Patriots videographer involved in Spygate, even parted with his. He gave up the... According to the Baltimore Sun , ex-Ravens running back Damien Berry auctioned his Super Bowl XLVII ring for... agreement and the check made out to Berry, the Sun reports. Another former Raven, Jamie Sharper, auctioned his</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7015-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7015_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:20:48">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2013-07-01/texas-am-players-arrested-deshazor-everett-floyd-raven-assault-fight-warrant</link><title>Texas A&amp;M arrests: Deshazor Everett, Floyd Raven charged with assault</title><description>Monday July 1, 2013 2:25 pm

Floyd Raven, have been charged with two counts each of assault causing bodily injury, the Bryan-College... According to the paper, Raven turned himself in to authorities Monday morning. He is expected to post a $4,000... pounding the truck at the scene of the fight. The assault charge and a charge of criminal mischief, are</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7015-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7015_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:24:33">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-01-30/super-bowl-2013-ravens-49ers-ed-reed-new-orleans-game-time</link><title>Ed Reed wants to be a Raven for life</title><description>Wednesday January 30, 2013 10:39 pm

... after the season, but he talked about his desire to finish his career with the Ravens. "I always said... came into the league and got drafted that I didnÂ't want to be one of those guys jumping from team to team,ÂÂ"... football on the moon."ÂÂ Playing this Super Bowl in his hometown of New Orleans has created a different</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7015-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7015_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:25:46">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2013-07-01/2-texas-a-m-football-players-arrested-after-fight</link><title>2 Texas A&amp;M football players arrested after fight</title><description>Monday July 1, 2013 4:51 pm

Floyd Raven were charged after the April 7 fight. Both surrendered at the Brazos County Jail on Monday.... attacked at the apartment complex by a group that included Everett and Raven. Police say they both had visible injuries from the attack, and a car was damaged. Bond was set at $5,000 for Everett, and Raven was free on $4,000</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7015-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7015_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:27:21">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-09-22/texans-vs-ravens-score-result-injury-andre-johnson-ed-reed-ray-rice</link><title>Andre Johnson leaves Texans game with injury, Ravens prevail</title><description>Sunday September 22, 2013 5:19 pm

... entered the game a week after sustaining a concussion. He left the game against the Baltimore Ravens on... limping off the field. His exact injury was immediately disclosed. At that juncture in the game, Johnson had... play for the first time with the Texans. On the same day, retired Raven Ray Lewis was inducted into the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7015-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7015_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:29:32">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2012-06-10/wr-derrick-mason-set-to-retire-as-a-raven</link><title>WR Derrick Mason set to retire as a Raven</title><description>Sunday June 10, 2012 11:02 pm

... member of the Baltimore Ravens. Mason will be joined by Ravens general manager Ozzie Newsome and head coach... afternoon. The 38-year-old Mason played 15 years in the NFL, six of them with Baltimore. Mason is the Ravens'... released by the Ravens before the 2012 season. He latched on with the New York Jets, was released and finished</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>