<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7044">song of ice and fire</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:30:15" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7044-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7044_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:30:16">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2014-02-01/ground-zero-a-quiet-spot-amid-super-bowl-revelry</link><title>Ground Zero: A quiet spot amid Super Bowl revelry</title><description>Saturday February 1, 2014 7:59 pm

... temperatures of the week, a long line of mostly Denver and Seattle fans toured the National September 11 Memorial... construction and scheduled to open this spring. The hushed voices and muffled sounds of the surrounding city... rendition of the national anthem right in the middle of the plaza. A crowd gathered around, and cheered loudly</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7044-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7044_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:35:11">http://www.sportingnews.com/nhl/story/2013-06-21/stanley-cup-finals-nhl-playoffs-2013-bruins-blackhawks-game-5</link><title>Playoff journal: On the passage of time and Fall Out Boy</title><description>Friday June 21, 2013 3:58 pm

... pictures of the beard I was growing for charity, and there were 63 of those. I've been shaving this year,... away, and now everything in hockey is lit up and on fire. Is the North American sporting public incapable of processing more than one song at a time? If there's no Game 7, forgetting that song ever existed</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7044-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7044_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:38:55">http://www.sportingnews.com/nhl/story/2009-04-19/flyers-pull-series-2-1-against-pens</link><title>Flyers pull series to 2-1 against Pens</title><description>Sunday April 19, 2009 10:05 pm

... flashes of the old Broad Street Bullies spirit and revved up the crowd. The bond with the past and the... delight of the sold-out crowd and the Flyers showed they still had plenty of fight left in this series.... center ice, and the refs couldn't stop Flyers center Darroll Powe and Letang from throwing punches along</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7044-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7044_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:43:29">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2009-08-04/long-shot-receiver-redskins-twitter-king</link><title>Long-shot receiver is Redskins' 'Twitter king'</title><description>Tuesday August 4, 2009 10:40 pm

... about it, and educate and talk about the perils. Talk about the cautions that need to be taken." Shelton's... football and religion. The son of a Fort Worth pastor often recites Bible verses or discusses religion in... to mind and people laugh about it. " Like asking the difference between "goons" and goblins. Saying Santa</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7044-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7044_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:46:24">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2007-07-13/pure-camp-afc</link><title>Pure camp: AFC</title><description>Friday July 13, 2007 2:55 pm

... grabbed me and wrapped me up with tape and put me outside with Mike. I tried to be a team player and help... They put fire extinguisher powder, honey and toilet tissue all over the interior of his brand-new Lexus.... the end of camp we have a softball game. Most of the older guys play in it, and most of the others sit</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7044-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7044_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:48:15">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2007-07-13/pure-camp-nfc</link><title>Pure camp: NFC</title><description>Friday July 13, 2007 2:35 pm

... got up and sang the Folgers crystal coffee song. Towards the end of it, everybody starting singing, "The... drills and roll and bounce back up and chase the ball. It was kind of senseless because very seldom do... come down and go to Disney World and Epcot and enjoy themselves while I sweat and work. OT Jon Jansen, Washington</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>