<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7062">marquette university news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:27:13" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7062-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7062_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:27:15">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2014-02-09/memphis-gonzaga-result-joe-jackson-przemek-karnowski</link><title>Memphis' Joe Jackson produces moment for the ages vs. Gonzaga</title><description>Sunday February 9, 2014 10:54 am

... against Marquette, with Andre Turners buzzer-beater against Boston College and with any number of Derrick... has a University of Memphis degree, three NCAA Tournament appearances on the way to four and 1,531 career... Sporting News last year it would have been easier to go elsewhere, somewhere people didnt expect him to</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7062-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7062_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:29:45">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2013-06-21/quinn-cook-cj-fair-out-team-usa-world-university-games-tryout-roster-mckillop</link><title>C.J. Fair, Quinn Cook decline World University Games tryout</title><description>Friday June 21, 2013 10:02 am

World University Games squad. Fair cited a personal reason for keeping him from attending the upcoming... (Raleigh) News &amp; Observer reports . The 27-man World University Games tryout roster still will include... World University Games run July 7-16 in Kazan, Russia. Davidson's Bob McKillop will coach the team,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7062-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7062_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:30:57">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2013-10-31/big-east-expansion-candidates-tom-crean-indiana-basketball-marshall-henderson</link><title>Starting 5: Ranking the Big East's expansion candidates; Tom Crean's five-year plan</title><description>Thursday October 31, 2013 9:46 am

Sporting News' Hall of Fame college basketball writer dives deeply into one topic in his sport, then answers... Sporting News coach of the year Jim Crews following the passing of Rick Majerus. SLU might have done a little... Creighton, Marquette, Butler and DePaul. "¨ SLU is a no-brainer for the Big East, and its too far out on</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7062-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7062_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:33:44">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2013-06-03/team-usa-world-university-games-training-camp-roster-doug-mcdermott-williams</link><title>Team USA's World University Games roster loaded with top-flight talent</title><description>Monday June 3, 2013 2:02 pm

World University Games training camp attendees includes 29 players vying for the 12 roster spots for... World University Games training camp rosters USA Basketball has ever had," said Syracuse coach Jim Boeheim,... Sporting News' Top 25 rankings reset A look at the entire tryout roster: Eric Atkins, Notre Dame senior</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7062-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7062_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:35:53">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2013-06-14/sporting-news-college-basketball-player-rankings-top-50-2013-1</link><title>Sporting News' college basketball player rankings: Who has the most ranked players?</title><description>Friday June 14, 2013 4:30 pm

WORLD UNIVERSITY GAMES FINALISTS: 16 players named Now that you've gobbled that deliciousness, you... World University Games finalist &amp;: denotes Team USA U19 roster player FIVE Louisville: Chane Behanan... TWO Marquette: Davante Gardner *, Jamil Wilson Michigan: Mitch McGary , Glenn Robinson Michigan</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7062-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7062_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:37:55">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2013-06-28/rodney-hood-achilles-injury-out-duke-basketball-world-university-games-mckillop</link><title>Rodney Hood's Achilles injury knocks him out of Team USA tryouts</title><description>Friday June 28, 2013 11:17 am

World University Games roster after injuring his right Achilles' tendon Wednesday. But the good news... Gardner, Marquette senior forward Treveon Graham, VCU junior guard Jerian Grant, Notre Dame senior guard</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7062-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7062_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:38:49">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2013-07-01/xavier-big-east-conference-realignment-catholic-7-musketeers</link><title>Conference realignment: Xavier ready for Big East challenge</title><description>Monday July 1, 2013 6:51 pm

Sporting News. "It's a tribute to the players and coaches that built the program to what it is." Xavier... because the university's complete investment in the success of the basketball program--which included the vision... Sporting News. The impact of competing in the Big East will be felt when the Musketeers begin their double</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7062-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7062_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:42:51">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2013-07-03/brad-stevens-replacement-butler-boston-celtics-barry-collier</link><title>Brad Stevens' departure to Celtics heightens Butler's challenge</title><description>Wednesday July 3, 2013 7:53 pm

... which no university can compete." CELTICS STUNNER: News | Deveney: High-risk move by Ainge This territory... John's and Marquette. Most of the confidence that Butler would be able to manage this transition was invested</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7062-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7062_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:46:04">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2013-07-03/nba-draft-2014-top-5-picks-andrew-wiggins-team-usa-u19-team-creighton-grant-gibb</link><title>Talking 2014 NBA Draft, FIBA's stupidity and Creighton's Big East title chances</title><description>Wednesday July 3, 2013 1:55 pm

Sporting News' college basketball writer answers five questions burning in his sport--while openly questioning... World University Games later this month. But the ratings wouldn't justify paying for it. So FIBA worries... day the news broke that the NCAA ruled in Creighton's favor on Gibbs' petition for a sixth year of eligibility.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7062-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7062_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:47:47">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2013-03-31/bracketracket-shockers-coach-k-and-sportsmanship</link><title>BracketRacket: Shockers, Coach K and sportsmanship</title><description>Sunday March 31, 2013 5:35 am

Municipal University of Wichita in 1926 on the way to becoming a state university in 1964. It has an enrollment... which beat Marquette in a Big East matchup for the East Regional title Saturday - along with Pittsburgh and... AWAY News flash: people like to watch NCAA tournament games on television, especially when upstarts</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>