<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7063">Spanish unemployment</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:50:07" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7063-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7063_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:50:10">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2012-09-26/power-to-the-people-seattle-sounders-give-fans-right-to-retain-or-fire-gm-adrian</link><title>Power to the people: Sounders give fans right to retain or fire GM Adrian Hanauer</title><description>Wednesday September 26, 2012 8:17 pm

... members at Spanish powers Barcelona and Real Madrid. There, club presidents can be elected and ousted similar... on the unemployment line if voted out. He'll just need a new business card, and as a part owner he'd likely</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7063-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7063_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:53:19">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2012-01-29/third-tier-mirandes-inspires-in-spains-copa-del-rey</link><title>Third-tier Mirandes inspires in Spain's Copa del Rey</title><description>Sunday January 29, 2012 10:50 am

... troubled Spanish town during tough financial times. Mirandes is only the second third-tier club to have... in high unemployment like the rest of Spain during the current recession, has a team on the verge of an... tremendous unemployment crisis, so it's an honor to play on a team that can provide some kind of pleasure.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7063-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7063_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:54:39">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2012-02-09/chad-ochocinco-new-england-patriots-evelyn-lozada-basketball-wives</link><title>Ochocinco returning to original surname with marriage to reality TV personality</title><description>Thursday February 9, 2012 11:59 am

... to the Spanish equivalent of 85 was temporary. Lozada is the former fiancĂŠe of former NBA player Antoine</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7063-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7063_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:57:51">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2011-07-11/spain-celebrates-anniversary-of-world-cup-win</link><title>Spain celebrates anniversary of World Cup win</title><description>Monday July 11, 2011 10:14 am

... as the Spanish capital dedicated a park to the national team. Del Bosque said the victory was important... recession. Unemployment has more than doubled since 2007 and now stands at 35 percent for people aged 16 to</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>