<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7067">used kindle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:35:43" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7067-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7067_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:35:45">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2011-06-13/ravens-kindle-says-he-has-been-cleared-to-play</link><title>Ravens' Kindle says he has been cleared to play</title><description>Monday June 13, 2011 8:03 pm

Sergio Kindle said this weekend he was cleared to play in March after missing his rookie season with a... fracture. Kindle suffered the injury after he fell down two flights of stairs. In an interview with the... terrible," Kindle said. "Especially when you're not used to it and football's what you want to do in life."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7067-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7067_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:40:33">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2012-08-18/baltimore-ravens-sloppy-play-raises-concerns</link><title>Baltimore Ravens' sloppy play raises concerns</title><description>Saturday August 18, 2012 4:59 pm

... getting used to things, but we're getting better every day," Oher insisted. Fortunately for the Ravens,... Sergio Kindle sustained a shoulder burner. "That's good news," Harbaugh said. The bad news: Just about</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7067-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7067_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:43:56">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2009-01-06/texas-could-have-used-time-killing-drive-lubbock</link><title>Texas could have used time-killing drive in Lubbock</title><description>Tuesday January 6, 2009 8:37 pm

Sergio Kindle said. Kindle himself is a question mark. The junior linebacker-defensive end was one of... family," Kindle said. There will be some speculation about Brown's future as well. In November, Brown and</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7067-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7067_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:45:13">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2010-04-07/draft-picks-grown-here-texas</link><title>Draft picks grown here: Texas</title><description>Wednesday April 7, 2010 2:02 pm

... like it used to, who has stepped into its place? Five universities can make a case for being the next great... Sergio Kindle As coaches sized up Sergio Kindle at the Combine, Kindle tried to evaluate them, too, because... styles, Kindle says. Theyre aggressive, and they dont really dwell on the good things. They harp on</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7067-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7067_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:46:33">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2011-12-16/bowl-gifts-a-bowl-by-bowl-breakdown-of-the-booty</link><title>Bowl-by-bowl breakdown of the booty</title><description>Friday December 16, 2011 6:17 pm

Amazon Kindle Fire, Apple iPod nano, Deuce watch, LunaTik wristband (to hold iPod), beanie, Nike backpack... Balance not used that day will be forfeited. Product details are provided as they were available. Most watches,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7067-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7067_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:51:28">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2011-04-24/afc-team-reports-2011-draft</link><title>AFC Team Reports: 2011 draft</title><description>Sunday April 24, 2011 7:26 pm

Sergio Kindle, last year. "Ś Expect the Ravens to use one of their nine total picks on a wide receiver.... first-rounder used on a corner after taking Kareem Jackson last year. If they take an outside linebacker in the... should be used on offensive players. "Ś Wide receiver is the biggest need but no one of value at that position</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7067-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7067_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:55:18">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/feed/2010-08/2010-preview/story/big-12-predictions-for-the-2010-season</link><title>Big 12 predictions for the 2010 season</title><description>Thursday August 26, 2010 4:36 pm

... sophomore used the word dominant three times. The fourth time summed up OU's goals this season: "We were... Sergio Kindle, Brian Robinson, Tim Crowder," Acho says. "Those are the guys who set the standard for playing... Orakpo and Kindle earn All-American status the past two years, Acho will get his chance in 2010. He led UT</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7067-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7067_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:58:31">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2010-04-24/ravens-trade-their-way-productive-nfl-draft</link><title>Ravens trade their way to 'productive' NFL draft</title><description>Saturday April 24, 2010 9:45 pm

Sergio Kindle in the second round. Then he fortified the defensive line with 350-pound Terrence Cody of... Baltimore used two fifth-round picks to take wide receiver David Reed of Utah and defensive tackle Arthur... netted Kindle, Dickson and Pitta. Although it made for a skittish first day of the draft, Newsome had</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7067-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7067_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:00:39">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2010-05-11/these-nfl-rookies-could-make-quick-impact</link><title>These NFL rookies could make quick impact</title><description>Tuesday May 11, 2010 8:07 pm

Sergio Kindle, OLB, Ravens (second round) . With Jarret Johnson sidelined (shoulder surgery), Kindle... being used as a pass-rush specialist, like Terrell Suggs was as a rookie in 03. C.J. Spiller, RB, Bills</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7067-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7067_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:04:47">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2010-05-07/maximizing-minicamp-teams-use-workouts-attack-key-concerns</link><title>Maximizing minicamp: Teams use workouts to attack key concerns</title><description>Friday May 7, 2010 11:36 pm

... agent and used his first two picks on defensive players: linebacker Sean Weatherspoon and defensive tackle... Sergio Kindle, defensive tackle Terrence Cody and tight ends Ed Dickson and Dennis Pitta. The Ravens have</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>