<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7078">count in korean</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:25:56" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7078-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7078_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:25:56">http://www.sportingnews.com/olympics/story/2014-02-20/2014-sochi-olympics-us-canada-womens-hockey-gold-medal-schedule-figure-skating</link><title>2014 Sochi Olympics: Gold up for grabs on ice, slopes Thursday</title><description>Thursday February 20, 2014 5:11 am

... will meet in the women's hockey gold medal game for the fourth time in five Olympics. Reigning gold medalist... ninth in her first world championships in March. For one night, at least, Kostner embraced the pressure.... Lipnitskaia in both programs in the team competition. "I was concentrating and focused on performing well</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7078-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7078_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:29:31">http://www.sportingnews.com/olympics/story/2012-07-30/olympics-2012-fencing-protest-south-korea-cash-appeal</link><title>Olympics 2012: South Korean fencer stages protest after clock error</title><description>Monday July 30, 2012 3:13 pm

Medal count: U.S., China tied after Day 3 She had already been ruled the loser in a semifinal epee... "I was in a very good shape coming here," she said through an interpreter. "In fact, I expected the gold... tied 5-5 in sudden death when Heidemann appeared to score in the final second. Had the match ended tied,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7078-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7078_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:30:34">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2013-07-28/nl-capsules</link><title>NL Capsules</title><description>Monday July 29, 2013 12:00 am

(7-8) in the second inning and Harper followed with a two-run drive in the third. Harper returned to... a ball in the opener. BRAVES 2, CARDINALS 0 ATLANTA (AP) - Andrelton Simmons hit a two-run double in... Louis in a matchup of NL division leaders. Teheran allowed two hits in seven innings, striking out six</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7078-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7078_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:33:16">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2013-05-29/hyun-jin-ryu-shutout-dodgers-angels-freeway-series-score-result</link><title>Hyun-Jin Ryu tosses 2-hit shutout as Dodgers beat Angels in Freeway Series</title><description>Wednesday May 29, 2013 12:40 am

... dazzled in earning his first complete game in the major leagues, pitching a two-hitter in which the left-hander... from the Korean league to the major leagues. "Mostly it's to preserve the arm but the habit started in... Kendrick in the second and a double by Chris Iannetta in the eighth. "He worked in some good change-ups</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7078-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7078_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:35:44">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2013-06-14/rookie-pitchers-shelby-miller-jose-fernandez-hyun-jin-ryu-numbers-stats</link><title>Numbers that matter: Keys to rookie success of Miller, Fernandez, Ryu</title><description>Friday June 14, 2013 11:37 am

1.32 ERA in 13 2/3 innings (including one start), and cemented his spot in the rotation this spring. Even... either. In 2011, he had a 9.1 BB% at high-Class A Palm Beach and a 9.3 BB% at Class AA Springfield. In... enough in spring training (3.29 ERA in 27 1/3 innings) to earn a spot in the Dodgers' rotation from the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7078-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7078_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:43:25">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2013-02-16/clayton-kershaw-to-start-third-straight-season-opener-for-dodgers</link><title>Clayton Kershaw to start third straight season opener for Dodgers</title><description>Saturday February 16, 2013 9:07 pm

... consistent in his outings. You don't get big fluctuations. "You kind of know what to count on, what to expect."... innings in a 1-0 victory over the Giants at Dodger Stadium. In 2012, Kershaw threw three scoreless innings... South Korean reporters. "He's got a little Sid Fernandez in him," Mattingly said. "He kind of catches</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7078-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7078_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:49:00">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-01-31/super-bowl-watch-beyonce-avocados-practice</link><title>SUPER BOWL WATCH: Beyonce, avocados, practice</title><description>Thursday January 31, 2013 6:35 pm

Timberlake, in his first major musical performance in four years (hosting Saturday Night Live doesn't count... married in New Orleans. Then in 2008, they decided to move here from Washington, D.C. Now living in a stately... Casinos in the Biggest Little City in the World are expecting a bump in Super Bowl betting this year thanks</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7078-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7078_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:49:52">http://www.sportingnews.com/olympics/story/2012-08-04/olympics-2012-united-states-china-neck-and-neck-in-olympic-medals-race</link><title>Olympics 2012: United States, China neck-and-neck in Olympic medals race</title><description>Saturday August 4, 2012 6:42 pm

... locked in a tight battle with China in the ultimate Olympic competition -- the race for No. 1 in the medals.... medal in each list -- 26-25 in golds and 54-53 overall. Behind the two powerhouses, the battle for the... Zealand in gold medals was in 1984\. "In terms of our top-5 finish, it's still a mathematical possibility,"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7078-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7078_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:54:03">http://www.sportingnews.com/olympics/story/2012-07-28/olympics-2012-results-united-states-saturday-medals-count-athletes-event</link><title>Olympics 2012 results: United States Saturday medals, athletes, events and scores</title><description>Saturday July 28, 2012 5:36 pm

... seventh in 10m air rifle. Jason Turner finished 34th and did not survive qualifying in the 10m air pistol.... racing in final of 4x100m free relay. She raced in the preliminary stage earlier in the day. Elizabeth... silver in the 400m IM. Peter Vanderkaay wins bronze in 400m free. Dana Vollmer finished first in 100m</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7078-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7078_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:58:10">http://www.sportingnews.com/olympics/story/2012-07-30/olympics-2012-racism-tweet-michel-morganella-soccer-results-swiss</link><title>Olympics 2012: Swiss soccer player booted for offensive tweet</title><description>Monday July 30, 2012 11:13 am

... playing in the 2-1 loss against South Korea on Sunday. He said in the tweet that South Koreans "can go... South Korean team in London to offer a personal explanation. "We would like to apologize, especially... entire game in both of Switzerland's matches. He received a yellow card against South Korea in Coventry. The</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>