<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7083">I'm on the road again</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:51:26" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7083-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7083_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:51:28">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2014-02-22/suns-roll-past-road-weary-spurs-106-85</link><title>Suns roll past road-weary Spurs 106-85</title><description>Saturday February 22, 2014 1:30 am

... home. The Spurs went 6-3 on the swing. The Suns, 3-0 since the All-Star break, snapped San Antonio's... great." The Suns outscored San Antonio 28-12 in the second quarter to lead 47-35 at the break, the Spurs'... quarter of the season. The Suns outscored the Spurs 17-7 to open the second half, taking a 64-42 lead on</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7083-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7083_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:52:19">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2014-02-19/ruth-aside-nats-harper-hopes-to-avoid-the-wall</link><title>Ruth aside, Nats' Harper hopes to avoid the wall</title><description>Wednesday February 19, 2014 4:25 pm

... during the offseason, but he came up with one on Wednesday that invoked the great Bambino. "Babe Ruth... factor in the Nationals' letdown season of 2013. His left knee bothered him the rest of the way, and he... close eye on the repaired joint over the next few weeks. "With the surgery of the knee, he's got to be mindful</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7083-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7083_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:56:11">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2014-02-24/character-questions-on-center-stage-at-nfl-combine</link><title>Character questions on center stage at NFL combine</title><description>Monday February 24, 2014 7:30 pm

... came to the NFL scouting combine with more to prove than just about anyone else. Not on the field, off... may be the most important part of the draft process for Lyerla, and history shows the wrong answers could... after the fact. How players and agents handle the weekend's questions depends on the strategy - and</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7083-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7083_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:58:26">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2014-02-24/warriors-clamp-down-on-pistons-in-104-96-win</link><title>Warriors clamp down on Pistons in 104-96 win</title><description>Tuesday February 25, 2014 12:18 am

... anyway. The Warriors figure that's a good sign at the start of a lengthy road trip. "It's not necessarily... build the character and the image of the team." Curry had 19 points, nine assists and eight rebounds, and the Warriors clamped down on the Detroit Pistons in the second half of a 104-96 victory Monday</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7083-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7083_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:00:05">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2014-02-17/spring-training-2014-yankees-alex-rodriguez-arod-launch-into-space</link><title>The Screwball: 2014 Spring Training Mad Libs</title><description>Monday February 17, 2014 4:03 pm

... brings to the table on the field that will be important for (TEAM) as it tries to (RETURN TO THE PLAYOFFS,... will like the most. At the end of the day, its all about performing, (PLAYER) said. Im not here to relive (THE BIG GAME, THE CONTROVERSIAL COMMENTS, OR THE MASCOT TWEET). This is a new chapter, and Im</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7083-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7083_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:02:52">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2014-02-25/burks-favors-lead-jazz-to-110-98-win-over-celtics</link><title>Burks, Favors lead Jazz to 110-98 win over Celtics</title><description>Tuesday February 25, 2014 1:48 am

... and set the tone early on his way to 20 points to help the Utah Jazz beat the Boston Celtics 110-98 on... step slow on the defensive end. Usually I'm the only guy who helps out when guys make mistakes. I'm the guy... member of the Jazz roster was on the team was on the team when Utah last defeated Boston, 110-97 on March</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7083-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7083_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:07:45">http://www.sportingnews.com/nascar/story/2014-02-18/goodyear-blimp-daytona-500-2014-tv-coverage-nascar-college-football</link><title>NASCAR from 1,500 feet in the Goodyear Blimp</title><description>Tuesday February 18, 2014 10:58 am

... beneath the cars as the drivers light up the brakes on pit road. PHOTOS: Inside the Goodyear Blimp |... 3 back on top From 1,500 feet above the track, behind the controls of the Goodyear Blimp, Dougherty can... racecars. To the right is the familiar site of the Atlantic Ocean. It is spring break and the beaches and A1A</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7083-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7083_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:11:40">http://www.sportingnews.com/nascar/story/2014-02-23/daytona-500-2014-live-blog-race-updates-lineup-start-time-prerace-danica-patrick-dale-earnhardt-jr</link><title>LIVE BLOG: It's race day at Daytona, and we've got everything covered</title><description>Sunday February 23, 2014 9:42 am

Daytona 500. The crowd erupts as as huge crash occurs on the final lap. 11:10 Dillon, who started on the pole,... about half the field pits before the green flag. 8:46 The jet dryers are putting the finishing touches on... takes the lead ... :) 1:53 Danica also spun on pit road. Who knew the first spins would be on pit road?</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7083-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7083_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:13:08">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2014-02-23/jermaine-o-neal-carries-warriors-past-nets-93-86</link><title>Jermaine O'Neal carries Warriors past Nets, 93-86</title><description>Sunday February 23, 2014 3:22 am

... following the All-Star break, Jermaine O'Neal promised his teammates to play the rest of the regular season... since the break. "Whatever I have, I'm going to leave it on the able. I've said that quite a few times,... leading the way in the locker room and on the court. "He's getting an opportunity to put a stamp on what</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7083-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7083_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:16:20">http://www.sportingnews.com/nascar/story/2014-02-24/dale-earnhardt-jr-celebrating-daytona-500-hendrick-motorsports-rick-hendrick-steve-letarte-ring-the-bell</link><title>Dale Earnhardt Jr. looking forward to celebrating Daytona 500 win</title><description>Monday February 24, 2014 11:57 am

... put up on the wall. Thats something to remind everyone about the win. But the fun part of the celebration is the ring the bell, where all the employees get to ring a bell with the race winner. PHOTOS:... do that again. When we got to that corner at the gate, I couldn't hold on inside. The roll bar was slick</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>