<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7091">don't listen to a word i say</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:27:42" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7091-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7091_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:27:45">http://www.sportingnews.com/nascar/story/2014-02-19/nascar-lets-fans-enjoy-open-communication</link><title>NASCAR lets fans enjoy open communication</title><description>Wednesday February 19, 2014 5:13 pm

... favorite word. No one could figure it out - as much a mystery to fans as what a baseball manager says to... said. "I'm passionate about what I do. When I get into the race, I don't even know what's going on. We're... Montoya to calm down and focus on salvaging a solid points day. "Don't tell me to relax, dude!" Montoya</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7091-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7091_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:29:14">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2013-10-28/basketballs-bounce-in-his-dreams-evansvilles-bryce-weiler-sees-a-different-game</link><title>Basketballs bounce in his dreams: Evansville's Bryce Weiler sees a different game</title><description>Monday October 28, 2013 9:00 am

... schedule. Ill get to lunch maybe a minute late, and hell say, I was going to give you until 6 minutes... me as a broadcaster to actually be able to follow the action. I know I have to be on my A-game describing... sports  I want to find a job that can make me happy seven days a week. I dont think Im going to need</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7091-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7091_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:34:08">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2013-07-08/move-over-wilt-kastles-can-pass-lakers-win-streak</link><title>Move over Wilt: Kastles can pass Lakers win streak</title><description>Monday July 8, 2013 11:39 pm

Kastles to go for the Olympics and give it a chance to break the streak, I walked off the court in tears... Still, it's a tough sell - Jerry West and Wilt Chamberlain taking a back seat to a team that plays its entire... asked to defend the streak. "I see what they have done to make this happen and what it means to them,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7091-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7091_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:34:49">http://www.sportingnews.com/sport/story/2013-05-08/pga-tour-the-players-tiger-woods-phil-mickelson-sawgrass-tpc</link><title>PGA Tour, The Players: Tiger Woods leads field to Sawgrass</title><description>Wednesday May 8, 2013 10:39 am

"fiddly." A universal word might be "unpredictable." The objective a few years ago was for players to define... that, it's a guessing game. Some say a great short game is critical. Others would say the penalty of missing... never a bad idea to listen to Couples talk about Sawgrass. Remember, it was Couples who once was asked</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7091-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7091_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:38:26">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2011-09-20/jim-boeheim-is-making-sense-on-conference-expansion-but-will-anybody-listen</link><title>Boeheim makes sense on realignment, but will anybody listen?</title><description>Tuesday September 20, 2011 11:54 am

... going to end up with mega conferences and 10 years from now either I'm going to be dead wrong--and I'll... Texas A&amp;M this week and going to Texas Tech next weekend? And why is Syracuse going to Miami in basketball... better, you don't have to wait 10 years to ask. TOP SPORTS STORIES Brawl video: Watch high school football</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7091-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7091_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:41:54">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2007-12-11/dont-give-vick-0151-give-him-second-chance</link><title>Don't give up on Vick &amp;#0151; give him a second chance</title><description>Tuesday December 11, 2007 3:20 pm

... first I had nothing to add to the Mike Vick story. What else could be said? Then I heard everyone talking... mess. I don't want to talk about Vick's punishment at all -- we've heard about it ad nauseum. I want... age, with a few bucks and some athletic ability, Vick has a tremendous opportunity to change his ways, to</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7091-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7091_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:46:48">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2012-08-16/nfl-concussions-report-brain-damage-effects-former-retired-part-iii</link><title>SN concussion report: NFL career worth it? Two Hall of Famers say no</title><description>Thursday August 16, 2012 2:44 pm

... said no. A tenth player said, "I don't think so," and a third Hall of Famer said "don't know." Three of... self. I'm monitoring how I speak. I'm monitoring how I make decisions," he says. "It's not a good way... exercise. I tried not exercise. I tried to walk around. I tried to lay down. I tried with the TV on," he</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7091-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7091_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:50:40">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2013-03-24/kansas-vs-north-carolina-jeff-withey-leader-nba-draft-defense-jayhawks</link><title>Kansas vs. North Carolina: Jeff Withey "Ëcapable of dominating this tournament'</title><description>Sunday March 24, 2013 12:15 am

... right? A lot of people still seem to regard the 7-footer as an oaf, a plodder--a typical, Ostertagian... he is? A heck of an athlete. Watch him get off the floor for a defensive rebound and dare to say he lacks... willing to say it: "If we can win and I can showcase the things I can do, it's a win-win." But he still</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7091-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7091_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:52:00">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2012-12-28/maybe-andy-reid-isn-t-going-anywhere</link><title>Andy Reid future: Eagles owner's silence a sign that coach might not be on way out?</title><description>Friday December 28, 2012 11:26 pm

... qualifies as a successful season? "I don't have a level or anything like that," Lurie said. "I just want to... "Again, I am not going to make blanket statements," Lurie said. "I really wanted to try to explain to you... is due to make $6 million in 2013. That's a lot of money to pay a guy to go away. Sure, the Eagles have</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7091-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7091_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:55:24">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2013-02-25/lakers-trade-rumor-mark-cuban-fine-amnesty-kobe-bryant-mavericks-rockets</link><title>Mark Cuban's original point lost in mini-feud with Lakers, Bryant</title><description>Monday February 25, 2013 12:19 pm

... reason I wouldn't get rid of Dirk. I'll take a hit for a season rather than get rid of Dirk. That's just... is. So I'm just saying that hypothetically. When I say amnesty Kobe, I don't think they'd do it, but they've... Mavs, that listen to everything I say "Ś But I do have to give props to @kobebryant for a great tweet. #Welldone.''</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>