<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7098">tour moscow</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:07:34" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7098-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7098_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:07:35">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2008-07-30/cska-moscow-part-euroleague-exhibition-tour</link><title>CSKA Moscow part of Euroleague exhibition tour</title><description>Thursday July 31, 2008 3:31 am

... champion CSKA Moscow will join two other Euroleague teams in playing exhibition games against NBA opponents this... American tour, which features five games from Oct. 10-21. CSKA Moscow, which won its sixth Euroleague title</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7098-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7098_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:10:53">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2013-08-17/friday-s-sports-in-brief</link><title>Friday's Sports In Brief</title><description>Saturday August 17, 2013 6:13 am

... caddie, PGA Tour rookie Patrick Reed shot a 6-under 64 to take a one-stroke lead in the Wyndham Championship... a PGA Tour rookie, and Huh is in his second year. Charlie Wi (65), Bob Estes (66), Rory Sabbatini (66),... FIELD MOSCOW (AP) - Allyson Felix flew out of the blocks, same as usual. She tried to settle into her</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7098-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7098_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:14:14">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-08-14/tuesday-s-sports-in-brief</link><title>Tuesday's Sports In Brief</title><description>Wednesday August 14, 2013 4:32 am

FIELD MOSCOW (AP) - The Eatons finished their working honeymoon in Russia ever so close to making it... - PGA Tour Commissioner Tim Finchem says two British newspaper reports of a bid to take over the European Tour are inaccurate. The Telegraph and The Daily Mail reported that the PGA Tour made an "audacious"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7098-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7098_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:17:58">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2013-07-03/bc-ap-sports-preview-digest</link><title>BC-AP Sports Preview Digest</title><description>Thursday July 4, 2013 12:00 am

... of the Tour de France and Simon Gerrans of Australia retained the overall leader's yellow jersey. - MOSCOW \- A leading Chechen rebel is calling on Islamist militants in Russia's North Caucasus to</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7098-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7098_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:21:20">http://www.sportingnews.com/nascar/story/2013-07-05/thursday-s-sports-in-brief</link><title>Thursday's Sports In Brief</title><description>Friday July 5, 2013 4:41 am

... of the Tour de France in a sprint finish and Daryl Impey became the first South African to wear the race... career Tour stage. He was caught in a crash close to the end of the stage and spent a lot of energy catching... championships in Moscow. --- SOCCER ROME (AP) - Lionel Messi's Argentina will face Mario Balotelli's Italy next</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7098-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7098_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:25:10">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-07-04/wednesday-s-sports-in-brief</link><title>Wednesday's Sports In Brief</title><description>Thursday July 4, 2013 5:14 am

... of the Tour de France in a sprint finish and Australian veteran Simon Gerrans kept the yellow jersey.... Armstrong's Tour wins were stripped for doping. --- PRO HOCKEY NEW YORK (AP) - Alex Ovechkin is an NHL first-team... OLYMPICS MOSCOW (AP) - A leading Chechen rebel on Wednesday called on Islamist militants in Russia's North</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7098-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7098_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:27:41">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-03-14/wednesday-s-sports-in-brief</link><title>Wednesday's Sports In Brief</title><description>Thursday March 14, 2013 5:41 am

... during the tour's Asian swing. The LPGA Tour and the International Management Group said that Gulbis is being... OLYMPICS MOSCOW (AP) - Jean-Claude Killy and IOC inspectors gave their approval of the progress in Sochi</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7098-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7098_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:30:16">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-01-12/friday-s-sports-in-brief</link><title>Friday's Sports In Brief</title><description>Saturday January 12, 2013 5:07 am

... the 2002 Tour de France. Saugy suggested that Tygart had "deficiencies" in his recollection of their discussion in Moscow in 2010 soon after U.S. federal investigators opened a probe into Armstrong and doping in... Asian Tour money title last year. He also holds the Asian Tour record for most career victories, winning</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7098-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7098_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:32:46">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2012-10-23/monday-s-sports-in-brief</link><title>Monday's Sports in Brief</title><description>Tuesday October 23, 2012 8:32 am

... seven Tour de France titles and banned for life by cycling's governing body Monday following a report... Paris, Tour director Christian Prudhomme said at a news conference he no longer considers Armstrong the... of the Tour de France from 1999-2005." BASEBALL SAN FRANCISCO (AP) - Hunter Pence hit a bizarre, two-run</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7098-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7098_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:34:29">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2012-10-18/wednesday-s-sports-in-brief</link><title>Wednesday's Sports in Brief</title><description>Thursday October 18, 2012 8:54 am

... seven-time Tour de France winner. Armstrong stepped down as chairman of Livestrong in an attempt to minimize... that his Tour titles be stripped, which could come before the end of the month. BASEBALL DETROIT (AP)... (4). MOSCOW (AP) - Caroline Wozniacki advanced to the quarterfinals of the Kremlin Cup by beating Urszula</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>