<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7104">How to go from New York to Montreal</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:40:21" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7104-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7104_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:40:24">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2014-02-17/askspector-tweetbag-mlb-captains-derek-jeter-yankees-usa-olympic-hockey-curling-1994-expos-twins-orioles</link><title>#AskSpector: So, what does a baseball team's captain do, anyway?</title><description>Monday February 17, 2014 1:15 pm

... history from Groupon . So, theres some space to fill today. What to do? What to do? Oh, wait, Ive got... conclusion to reach from a few minutes of talking to someone, but I also seem to have lost my train of thought.... told the New York Daily News hes still 275 pounds . From the looks of pictures, its hard to believe</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7104-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7104_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:43:45">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2014-02-06/mls-schedule-winter-major-league-soccer-don-garber</link><title>Should MLS switch to a winter schedule?</title><description>Thursday February 6, 2014 11:21 am

... damage to the field is likely to linger into the spring. "If you play back-to-back games and in between... Mainz from 2010 to 2013\. "You're looking forward to just kind of getting through the first half, focusing... enough to address certain issues. With the NCAA soccer season running from August to December, it's unclear</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7104-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7104_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:44:47">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2014-01-27/mls-major-league-soccer-toronto-fc-philadelphia-union-dc-united</link><title>The MLS Wrap: Busy offseasons have East trio looking like contenders</title><description>Monday January 27, 2014 10:47 am

Philadelphia had to trade veteran Jeff Parke to pave the way for Edu, and will likely now turn to young central... White to go from intriguing prospect to solid starter in order to ensure a successful run to the playoffs.... they try to work with all the new pieces, and try to turn losing teams into winners. The investment made</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7104-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7104_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:48:51">http://www.sportingnews.com/nhl/story/2013-06-25/boston-bruins-loss-tuukka-rask-maple-leafs-worst-hockey-losses-stanley-cup-final</link><title>Stanley Cup finals: How historic was Bruins' loss? Think 1951</title><description>Tuesday June 25, 2013 2:18 am

Canadiens got to go to overtime. The Bruins gave up the tying goal to Bryan Bickell with 1:16 left, and then... tough way to lose, tough way to lose a game, tough way to lose a series," said Boston captain Zdeno Chara... tougher to sort out, going from a victory story to be retold for ages to a defeat that is nearly incomprehensible</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7104-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7104_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:50:50">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-04-29/tebow-time-in-new-york-over-after-jets-cut-qb</link><title>Tebow Time in New York over after Jets cut QB</title><description>Monday April 29, 2013 10:57 am

"excited" to be in New York. It turned out to be one of the few high points in Tebow's stay with the Jets.... year. From the day the Jets made the move to bring Tebow in to compete with Sanchez, many fans and media... everyone from Johnson to Ryan to former general manager Mike Tannenbaum to former offensive coordinator</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7104-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7104_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:53:57">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-11-01/thursday-s-sports-in-brief</link><title>Thursday's Sports In Brief</title><description>Friday November 1, 2013 5:21 am

... that led to a 211-game suspension that the New York Yankees third baseman is trying to overturn. In addition... Friday to introduce Williams as the team's fifth manager since it moved to Washington from Montreal in... Abdullah took to Twitter to blast the NFL and Commissioner Roger Goodell for not doing enough to ensure players'</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7104-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7104_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:58:16">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2013-09-30/mls-wrap-sizing-up-the-supporters-shield-playoff-races</link><title>MLS Wrap: Sizing up the Supporters Shield, playoff races</title><description>Monday September 30, 2013 2:25 pm

And the New York Red Bulls? They weren't given much of a chance to take anything from a visit to Seattle... a row to secure a playoff spot, and avoid having to go to New York in the regular season finale needing... destined to keep stumbling to the finish line. Dallas is five points back, with no sign of being able to</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7104-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7104_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:00:45">http://www.sportingnews.com/nhl/story/2013-04-30/nhl-playoffs-2013-schedule-first-round-odds-penguins-canucks-blackhawks</link><title>NHL playoffs: How each team can win, and when they'll lose</title><description>Tuesday April 30, 2013 9:51 am

... prepare to open the first round, and what it will take for them to hoist hockey's Holy Grail. As a statistical... only seem to make him stronger. Will go home when: Math turns out to be a thing that exists. 6. NEW YORK... if: Due to a rift in the space-time continuum, this year's playoffs are transported to 2016\. Will go home</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7104-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7104_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:01:57">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2013-09-23/major-league-soccer-mls-united-states-columbus-crew-san-jose-earthquakes-vancouv</link><title>The MLS Wrap: Upsets shake up playoff race even more</title><description>Monday September 23, 2013 12:24 pm

... berth to 16 of 19. That's right, with a month to go before the playoffs, only Toronto FC, D.C. United... climb to within two points of fifth-place New England with four matches left to play, including a pair... opportunity to close the gap on the playoff pack in the West, dropping a decision to New York that saw the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7104-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7104_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:04:56">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2013-09-23/the-mls-wrap-upsets-shake-up-playoff-race-even-more</link><title>The MLS Wrap: Upsets shake up playoff race even more</title><description>Monday September 23, 2013 10:12 am

... berth to 16 of 19. That's right, with a month to go before the playoffs, only Toronto FC, D.C. United... climb to within two points of fifth-place New England with four matches left to play, including a pair... opportunity to close the gap on the playoff pack in the West, dropping a decision to New York that saw the</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>