<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7118">part time jobs texas city</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:28:46" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7118-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7118_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:28:48">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-07-23/49ers-determined-to-return-to-super-bowl-and-win</link><title>49ers determined to return to Super Bowl and win</title><description>Tuesday July 23, 2013 2:05 pm

... the most part, added some other pieces," All-Pro defensive lineman Justin Smith said. "The goal is still... the full-time starter over now-departed Alex Smith in November, Kaepernick dazzled under center as a second-year... Kansas City, where he will be the Chiefs' starter under new coach Andy Reid. Kaepernick went 7-3 as a</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7118-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7118_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:32:35">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-05-03/former-cornerback-al-harris-retires-as-a-packer</link><title>Former cornerback Al Harris retires as a Packer</title><description>Friday May 3, 2013 10:08 am

... the two-time Pro Bowl cornerback was that he was somehow able to say he retired as a member of the Green... awesome time, but the better part of my years were in Green Bay, (so) it was just important to me to retire... Kansas City Chiefs, said he came up with the idea the day he announced his retirement in December 2011</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7118-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7118_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:35:23">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-02-01/thursday-s-sports-in-brief</link><title>Thursday's Sports in Brief</title><description>Friday February 1, 2013 7:35 am

... coaching jobs and seven general manager positions - were all filled by white candidates since the regular... A four-time Pro Bowler, he was Green Bay's MVP in 2002 and was part of the team that won the Super Bowl... first time in an interview with Dr. Phil McGraw for the "Dr. Phil Show," the first part of which aired</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7118-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7118_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:36:08">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2012-12-15/friday-s-sports-in-brief</link><title>Friday's Sports In Brief</title><description>Saturday December 15, 2012 8:45 am

Oklahoma City star Kevin Durant wrote "Newtown CT" on both shoes for the Thunder's 113-103 victory over... recover in time for him to practice this week. COLLEGE FOOTBALL LUBBOCK, Texas (AP) - Kliff Kingsbury was... recently, Texas A&amp;M, said those jobs were purely business. Kingsbury, a mentor to Heisman Trophy winner</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7118-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7118_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:37:01">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2012-08-14/todd-graham-asu-arizona-state-culture-change-sun-devils-dennis-erickson-pitt</link><title>Todd Graham may love 'em and leave 'em, but nothing phony about Arizona State coach</title><description>Tuesday August 14, 2012 12:00 pm

... two head jobs\--at Rice and Pittsburgh--after one season. Who, infamously, informed Pitt's players by text... rules are part of our daily lives now." It's a transformation from undisciplined to airtight. Asked for... Mesquite, Texas, he was something of a hero. If there was a league in most any sport, Graham was in it--and</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7118-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7118_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:41:12">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2007-11-10/long-snappers-have-underrated-tenuous-jobs</link><title>Long snappers have underrated, tenuous jobs</title><description>Sunday November 11, 2007 1:10 am

... underrated jobs in sports. It's also one of the most tenuous, where one bad snap could cost them everything.... Muhlbach (Texas A&amp;M, four, UFA) -- Green Bay: Rob Davis (Shippensburg, 12, UFA) -- Houston: Bryan Pittman... switch jobs with you any time." Copyright 2007 Associated Press. All rights reserved. This material may</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7118-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7118_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:44:15">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2011-05-11/new-coach-turgeon-calls-maryland-a-special-place</link><title>New coach Turgeon calls Maryland 'a special place'</title><description>Wednesday May 11, 2011 5:55 pm

... years at Texas A&amp;M. After speaking at length with Williams on Sunday night, Turgeon knew it was time to... 97-40 at Texas A&amp;M and took the team to the NCAA Tournament in each of his four seasons at the school. He... Kansas City Chiefs shirt over his Texas A&amp;M shirt, the two talked about the future of the basketball program.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7118-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7118_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:46:30">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2011-03-16/move-to-gainesville-was-the-right-thing-for-weis</link><title>Move to Gainesville was "˜the right thing' for Weis</title><description>Wednesday March 16, 2011 6:03 pm

Kansas City, somewhere that quickly became anywhere in the panicked mind of a parent, Hannah Weis was... Kansas City Chiefs. Nothing to do with using this job as a springboard to something bigger. It had everything... Kansas City, perspective raps you in the head like an 18-pound sledgehammer. "It was time," Weis says,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7118-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7118_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:47:07">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2010-11-30/oklahoma-sts-gundy-wins-big-12-coach-of-the-year</link><title>Okla. State's Gundy wins Big 12 Coach of the Year</title><description>Tuesday November 30, 2010 7:28 pm

OKLAHOMA CITY \-- For Mike Gundy, part of becoming a better coach was learning to let go. Once he yielded... Oklahoma and Texas A&amp;M. Gundy received 12 of 20 first-place votes from the AP panel. Texas A&amp;M's Mike Sherman... language and time management," Gundy said. "I allowed Dana and Bill, of course, to do their jobs and my presence</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7118-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7118_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:50:30">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2009-03-18/boylen-wasted-no-time-getting-utah-back-ncaas</link><title>Boylen wasted no time getting Utah back to NCAAs</title><description>Wednesday March 18, 2009 11:09 pm

Salt Lake City probably envisioned happening so soon. "He did his work, believed in us, thought we could... being part of two NBA championships there. Eventually he returned to Michigan State to be on Izzo's staff,... out for jobs, most notably at Texas A&amp;M and with the Orlando Magic -- Utah picked him to be a head coach.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>