<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7133">museum of natural history</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:17:53" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7133-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7133_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:17:54">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-02-03/celebs-babies-beer-its-super-bowl-ad-time</link><title>Celebs, babies, beer: its Super Bowl ad time</title><description>Sunday February 3, 2013 9:11 pm

... tools of their trade. The stakes are high, with 30-second spots going for as much as $4 million this... havoc at a natural history museum, getting chased by bikers, going to a petting zoo and playing in a park.... instead of making fun of him they join in the fun. "Is that my wedding dress?" says his wife when she</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7133-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7133_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:19:50">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2012-11-09/lee-macphail-dies-obituary-new-york-yankees-gm-al-president-baltimore-orioles-gm</link><title>Former AL president, Hall of Fame GM Lee MacPhail, 95, dead</title><description>Friday November 9, 2012 1:20 pm

Fla., of natural causes, the Hall of Fame announced. MacPhail, inducted in 1998 after a five-decade... decades," Hall of Fame chairman of the board Jane Forbes Clark said. "As a Hall of Fame executive, Lee developed... president of MLB's Player Relations Committee. Lee MacPhail was elected to the Hall of Fame's board of directors</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7133-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7133_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:22:07">http://www.sportingnews.com/olympics/story/2012-06-25/london-olympics-2012-england-ready-but-subway-a-worry</link><title>London Olympics 2012: England ready, but subway a worry</title><description>Monday June 25, 2012 11:43 am

... hopes of averting a security nightmare like last August's wave of rioting, or even worse: a terror strike.... is one of the best ways to enjoy London at any time. The stretch of tree-lined riverbank south of the... British Museum and Natural History Museum are best for the family, the National Gallery and the Tate Modern</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7133-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7133_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:24:48">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2012-05-23/astrodome-fades-crumbles-as-houston-decides-fate</link><title>Astrodome fades, crumbles as Houston decides fate</title><description>Wednesday May 23, 2012 2:47 pm

... piles of cardboard boxes littered the stadium floor alongside a crumpled mat of synthetic football field.... million as of 2010, including the cost of transforming the site into a plaza with green space and a water... cloud of smoke. "It will be another chapter in the Astrodome's long history," Bluthardt added. ---</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7133-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7133_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:26:19">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2011-02-27/hall-of-fame-center-fielder-duke-snider-dies-at-84</link><title>Hall of Fame center fielder Duke Snider dies at 84</title><description>Sunday February 27, 2011 3:31 pm

Baseball Hall of Fame and Museum, which announced the death on behalf of the family. Snider had been ill for... "integral part of Dodger history" and part of an "unparalleled triumvirate of center fielders" in New York. "Then... streets of Brooklyn," Hall of Fame President Jeff Idelson said. Snider was elected to the Hall of Fame</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7133-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7133_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:28:45">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2010-06-15/no-18-for-celtics-would-be-no-2-for-new-big-3</link><title>No. 18 for Celtics would be No. 2 for new Big 3</title><description>Tuesday June 15, 2010 8:10 pm

11 out of 13 from 1957-69. In the '70s, a nucleus of John Havlicek, Dave Cowens and JoJo White won two.... in NBA history, the Celtics had gone an unprecedented 21 years without adding to their record cache of... it's the natural conclusion for one of Russell's teammates. "You want to keep on winning? He was the guy,"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7133-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7133_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:33:18">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2008-07-09/tiger-stadiums-outfield-walls-coming-down</link><title>Tiger Stadium's outfield walls coming down</title><description>Wednesday July 9, 2008 2:30 pm

... walls of Tiger Stadium on Wednesday, punching through to the interior of the ballpark that stood for... "It's a natural museum of a hundred years that they're destroying," he said. Robert Neil, 42, also stopped... demolishing some of the stadium's massive concrete walls. The Detroit contractor and MCM Management Corp. of suburban</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7133-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7133_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:36:29">http://www.sportingnews.com/nhl/story/2007-09-28/nhl-2007-08-preview-taking-flight</link><title>NHL 2007-08 preview: Taking flight</title><description>Friday September 28, 2007 1:42 pm

Yankees of the NHL just a few years ago, spending way more money than most teams and sending picks and... a wing of a natural history museum sometimes, but look closer: The dinosaurs get the spotlight, but behind... still one of the best. He returned for a base salary of $2 million when he could've made more elsewhere because</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>