<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7134">history of yoga</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:37:12" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7134-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7134_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:37:17">http://www.sportingnews.com/olympics/story/2014-02-09/2014-sochi-olympics-jamie-anderson-lands-second-us-gold-medal</link><title>2014 Sochi Olympics: Jamie Anderson lands second U.S. gold medal</title><description>Sunday February 9, 2014 10:10 am

... piece of history for Jones, the 33-year-old, one-time ski resort housekeeper from Bristol, who was unapologetic... the top of the mountain, watching rider after rider take a fall. Of the 24 runs in finals, no fewer than... Worst of all, Sarka Pancochova of the Czech Republic lost it on the first jump of her second run, the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7134-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7134_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:40:39">http://www.sportingnews.com/nhl/story/2014-01-26/ducks-beat-la-kings-3-0-on-dodger-stadium-ice</link><title>Ducks beat LA Kings 3-0 on Dodger Stadium ice</title><description>Sunday January 26, 2014 2:09 am

... game west of the Rocky Mountains in recognition of the NHL's near half-century in Los Angeles and their rivalry... celebrations of the cold-weather sport's rich California roots, Anaheim showed who's currently in charge of... longest skid of an otherwise solid season. After getting a goal in the opening minutes of Thursday's loss, Los</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7134-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7134_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:42:29">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2009-10-08/after-summer-new-hobbies-shaq-tries-yoga</link><title>After a summer of new hobbies, Shaq tries yoga</title><description>Thursday October 8, 2009 11:30 pm

... career out of twisting around opposing centers. Now he is doing it to himself. After a summer of boxing,... worst yoga student in the history of yoga," O'Neal said Thursday. His massive 7-foot-1, 325-pound frame... owner of Cleveland Yoga in Beachwood. She was O'Neal's instructor for the class and is special ordering</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7134-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7134_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:46:02">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2012-11-15/stanford-vs-oregon-stepfan-taylor-running-into-cardinal-record-books</link><title>Stanford vs. Oregon: Stepfan Taylor running into Cardinal record books</title><description>Thursday November 15, 2012 8:13 pm

... the rest of Stanford's offensive linemen gathered in a meeting room this week to watch video of a moment... in one of the biggest games of his career. Taylor is 202 yards shy of Darrin Nelson's school record of... as one of the best running backs of all time in Stanford history." Those around him believe Taylor's</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7134-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7134_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:49:48">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2012-03-31/for-40-ish-baseball-stars-these-are-good-ol-days</link><title>For 40-ish baseball stars, these are good ol' days</title><description>Saturday March 31, 2012 1:56 am

... big part of the Yankees' plan for 2012. These days, baseball's oldest stars are some of its greatest. ... what's left of it, has started to go gray. In some cases, the chiseled torsos of youth have added a few pounds.... league history, according to STATS LLC. Bobby Wallace of the St. Louis Cardinals was 44 years, 8 months,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7134-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7134_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:53:51">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2012-03-30/40-somethings-still-enjoying-the-goold-ole-days</link><title>40-somethings still enjoying the good ole days</title><description>Friday March 30, 2012 10:17 pm

... big part of the Yankees' plan for 2012. These days, baseball's oldest stars are some of its greatest. ... what's left of it, has started to go gray. In some cases, the chiseled torsos of youth have added a few pounds.... league history, according to STATS LLC. Bobby Wallace of the St. Louis Cardinals was 44 years, 8 months,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7134-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7134_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:57:11">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2012-03-16/pat-summitt-alzheimers-tennessee-volunteers-ncaa-tournament-baylor-stands-in-way</link><title>Fitting end for Summitt would be to reach it one last time</title><description>Friday March 16, 2012 1:46 pm

... behalf of millions of people. "I want to cut down more nets," Summitt said. The quest begins Saturday... how much of a distraction Summitt's situation has been. Even if they could, nobody would say it out of reverence... do her yoga and load up her iPad with all sorts of puzzles and memory games to exercise her brain. She</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7134-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7134_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:01:23">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2011-08-09/ricky-williams-nfl-story-could-have-a-surprisingly-good-end</link><title>Ricky Williams' NFL story could have a surprisingly good end</title><description>Tuesday August 9, 2011 12:23 pm

"A lot of those things are way, way, way in the past. My relationship and my experience with him, there... Williams of years past " of the battles with anxiety disorder that left him doing interviews with his helmet on, of the magazine covers in a wedding dress, and certainly not of the pre-emptive retirement and</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7134-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7134_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:02:41">http://www.sportingnews.com/nhl/feed/2011-06/nhl-free-agency/story/ray-emery-hip-injury-chicago-blackhawks-flyers-anaheim-ducks-avascular-necrosis</link><title>Ray Emery turns career-threatening injury into career-defining opportunity with Chicago Blackhawks</title><description>Thursday August 4, 2011 10:07 am

... the head of his femur, which fits into to the hip, was dead because of a lack of bloodflow and the more... section of Emery's fibula. Surgery meant the removal of dead bone from Emery's hip and the extraction of... clean bill of health until June. "He kind of fell of the radar screen a little bit," Ruch said. "I was really</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7134-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7134_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:04:24">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2011-05-19/kareem-abdul-jabbar-discusses-the-lakers-his-future-his-faith-and-more</link><title>Kareem Abdul-Jabbar discusses the Lakers, his future, his faith and more</title><description>Thursday May 19, 2011 11:58 am

... a lot of sense. No, probably a lot of them didn't and still don't. I was kind of a mystery man as far... old idea of "what (players) do is their own business" kind of dominated. (Shortly after) I got out of the... terms of flexibility and the use of my (feet). Lots of yoga. I used to run a lot, but I've slowed down.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>