<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7137">Cat movies</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:45:31" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7137-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7137_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:45:33">http://www.sportingnews.com/nascar/story/2012-12-24/nascar-crew-chief-scott-zipadelli-stepdaughter-cancer-torie-costa</link><title>Crew chief Scott Zipadelli no longer lives for racing as stepdaughter battles cancer</title><description>Monday December 24, 2012 12:55 pm

... watch movies and make her feel better or wherever she wants to go--whatever we want to do, we're doing."... of my cat when I was in New York. "Ś The way he looks so forward to seeing me, it makes me happy that</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7137-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7137_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:46:33">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2012-05-17/pet-memories-help-rams-rookies-vets-break-ice</link><title>Pet memories help Rams rookies, vets break ice</title><description>Thursday May 17, 2012 6:37 am

... favorite movies, etc., during introductions, the new players were asked to recall the name of their first... dog or cat getting squashed by trains or buses. "We had one whose parents just put him down that morning,"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7137-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7137_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:49:15">http://www.sportingnews.com/nhl/story/2010-01-21/review-rock-tries-hockey-tooth-fairy</link><title>Review: 'The Rock' tries hockey in 'Tooth Fairy'</title><description>Thursday January 21, 2010 7:24 am

... spray, a cat repeller.   Johnson is perhaps ill suited to believably play a cynic. His enormous grin,... Claus" movies) shows little imagination in what could have been a quirkier, more interesting kids tale.... But movies that implore whether or not you can handle the tooth aren't to be picked apart like a dentist.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7137-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7137_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:53:57">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2009-10-29/jim-brown-shares-lessons-college-athletes</link><title>Jim Brown shares lessons with college athletes</title><description>Friday October 30, 2009 12:00 am

... had in movies and afterward. "That love scene was something," Brown said with his wife, Monique, in the... "best cat in the league." He could have accomplished more, he said, "only if football's all you're talking</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7137-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7137_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:54:45">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2009-09-25/strahan-brings-gap-toothed-grin-prime-time-tv</link><title>Strahan brings gap-toothed grin to prime-time TV</title><description>Friday September 25, 2009 7:20 am

... joking, cat-and-dog type thing." The two met at a Knicks game six years ago, and hit it off. When Strahan... greatest movies ever made, man." Strahan never planned to get into acting. It just seemed a natural move</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7137-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7137_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:58:00">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2009-02-10/draft-profile-mitch-king-defensive-lineman-iowa</link><title>Draft Profile: Mitch King, defensive lineman, Iowa</title><description>Tuesday February 10, 2009 3:35 pm

... time. Cat or a dog? I'd rather be a ... Dog because they are loyal and trustworthy. Cats are selfish... in the movies. The last concert I attended was ... Kenny Chesney. I went and saw him perform on my birthday.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7137-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7137_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:59:58">http://www.sportingnews.com/nascar/story/2008-09-27/paul-newman-succumbs-cancer-age-83</link><title>Paul Newman succumbs to cancer at age 83</title><description>Saturday September 27, 2008 2:44 pm

... sports movies: Greatest hockey movie ever: Slap Shot Making pool cool: The Hustler With his strong,... film Cat on a Hot Tin Roof. Elizabeth Taylor played his unhappy wife and Burl Ives his wealthy, domineering... to make movies and continued to pile up Oscar nominations, his looks remarkably intact, his acting becoming</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>