<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7146">why do leaves fall</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:26:52" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7146-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7146_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:26:54">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2013-01-31/super-bowl-world-series-2013-ravens-49ers-giants-tigers-prediction-schedule</link><title>Super Bowl vs. World Series: Why the Fall Classic is superior</title><description>Thursday January 31, 2013 1:41 pm

... about the Fall Classic and Super Sunday as events, and everything that goes into making Sunday a forgettable... excuses to do so. 4. Halftime The NFL and whatever network is showing the Super Bowl force-feeds sports... It's about the game, and that is the biggest reason why the Fall Classic always will trump Super Sunday.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7146-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7146_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:29:44">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2013-09-26/screwball-giants-total-baseball-ask-spector</link><title>The Screwball: Giants at a loss how to explain disappointing season</title><description>Thursday September 26, 2013 3:21 pm

" is why that is the case. "I can't really answer your question," Giants outfielder Hunter Pence told... not the why. "It took a lot last year for us," Bumgarner said. "Everybody had to be perfect. In a lot... thing to do, a hard thing to repeat anytime. It doesn't happen very often." It has not happened since the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7146-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7146_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:30:45">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2013-08-08/penn-state-ncaa-bill-obrien-christian-hackenberg-joe-paterno-jerry-sandusky</link><title>Bill O'Brien: 'All that matters is what happens here'</title><description>Thursday August 8, 2013 10:00 am

... day of fall camp, about refusing to allow others to dictate what you can and can't do. "You're going... can't do what any other coach in the same situation would do when a player leaves: reward another player.... what I do. You are bright guys; that's why you're here." O'Brien then rolled right into an anecdote about</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7146-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7146_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:35:09">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2013-01-28/free-agency-2013-michael-bourn-kyle-lohse-jim-thome-joe-saunders</link><title>Free agency 2013: Why haven't Michael Bourn, Kyle Lohse, others landed deals?</title><description>Monday January 28, 2013 2:05 pm

Seattle, leaves the Mariners with plenty to make a long-term commitment. After Chone Figgins, the Mariners... before next fall. Jim Thome The 42-year-old slugger says he wants to play. Can he still slug is the question.... need to do something to show their fans they're serious about following up on their success of 2012? Saunders</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7146-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7146_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:38:37">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2013-07-25/meyer-talks-discipline-pac-12-rivals-talk-tempo</link><title>Meyer talks discipline; Pac-12 rivals talk tempo</title><description>Thursday July 25, 2013 4:15 am

... we all do, and I'm pretty optimistic that we do that," Delany added. "But I want us also to keep in mind why we're doing it and I think it's to make better connections between our athletes, the educational... thing to do," said Delany, who played college basketball for North Carolina. "Whether that's 2,000, 3,000,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7146-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7146_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:42:24">http://www.sportingnews.com/nhl/story/2013-07-03/nhl-free-agents-conference-names-danny-briere-joey-chestnut-hot-dog-contest</link><title>#AskSpector: Free agents, conference names, hot dog contests</title><description>Wednesday July 3, 2013 5:35 pm

Islanders do sign Danny Briere , which I think is the best place for him to go, it would make more sense... would do well to check in on Damien Brunner and Michael Ryder . @RunsWithHawks asks: "when is the... asks: "do u think that sens will offer Alfie w/e the #SensArmy wishes for?!" Doesn't the #SensArmy pretty</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7146-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7146_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:46:02">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2013-07-03/nba-draft-2014-top-5-picks-andrew-wiggins-team-usa-u19-team-creighton-grant-gibb</link><title>Talking 2014 NBA Draft, FIBA's stupidity and Creighton's Big East title chances</title><description>Wednesday July 3, 2013 1:55 pm

... to see why league GMs are so eager to get to that day. Next year's draft should be the best in more than... No. 3, a do-everything forward who has an astonishing understanding of how to play the game properly. At... happens to fall into that spot. But it'll be a point guard, either Kentucky's Andrew Harrison or Oklahoma</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7146-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7146_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:47:22">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2013-06-27/big-ten-schedule-ranking-nonconference-ohio-state-michigan-wisconsin</link><title>Big Ten boasts toughest non-conference schedule of all</title><description>Thursday June 27, 2013 3:01 pm

... way to do that is more interesting games," Delany said. MORE: Big Ten's top returning players | Rankings:... experiences. And why not start three years early: No conference plays more games against BCS teams this season,... That leaves us with solid games and just enough intrigue: Nebraska playing host to UCLA, Wisconsin at</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7146-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7146_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:49:15">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2013-05-07/sec-network-espn-bias-ownership-derrick-thomas-manziel-stoops</link><title>SEC Network, ESPN partnership doesn't sit well</title><description>Tuesday May 7, 2013 5:35 pm

It just leaves the lingering, annoying thought that--to wrap this up with a nice southern bow--the SEC... candidate this fall, has 21 career sacks. Thomas, who died in an auto accident in 2000, had 52 career sacks,... that's why Thomas has been ignored again, what do we make of Tedy Bruschi being elected to the Hall? Bruschi</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7146-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7146_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:52:05">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2012-08-25/dodgers-red-sox-trade-josh-beckett-adrian-gonzalez-carl-crawford</link><title>Dodgers' trade still leaves them as NL's fourth-best team</title><description>Saturday August 25, 2012 2:06 pm

Morse leaves a game after getting hit by a pitch on his right hand (X-rays were negative). Extending... card. So why does the Cardinals' season lean toward disappointing? Easy. A 13-21 record in one-run games.... won't do much for his fastball. Attitude issues aside, the main reason for Beckett's disappointing season</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>