<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7154">stones satisfaction</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:11:14" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7154-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7154_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:11:15">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2014-01-30/practice-squaders-ignored-but-vital-at-super-bowl</link><title>Practice-squaders ignored but vital at Super Bowl</title><description>Thursday January 30, 2014 7:56 pm

... their satisfaction comes from how well they impersonate others. "If (the Seattle defenders) go out and... Rolling Stones, Prince, Tom Petty and Bruce Springsteen, finally culminating with a much-ridiculed performance</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7154-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7154_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:14:28">http://www.sportingnews.com/olympics/story/2012-07-28/olympics-2012-opening-ceremony-queen-elizabeth-london-paul-mccartney</link><title>Olympics 2012 opening ceremony: Queen plays big part in spectacle</title><description>Saturday July 28, 2012 2:26 am

Beatles, the Stones and The Who to send the planet a message: Britain, loud and royal proud, is ready to roll.... Rolling Stones' "(I Can't Get No) Satisfaction" and "Bohemian Rhapsody," by still another Queen, and other</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7154-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7154_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:15:14">http://www.sportingnews.com/olympics/story/2012-06-19/london-2012-summer-olympics-opening-ceremony-song-playlist-bands</link><title>London 2012 Summer Olympics: Opening Ceremony playlist leaked; Bands competing in qualifiers</title><description>Tuesday June 19, 2012 10:29 am

Rolling Stones \- Satisfaction Millie Small - My Boy Lollipop The Kinks - All Day and All of the Night</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7154-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7154_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:19:50">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2005-09-09/lets-spend-three-nights-together</link><title>Let's spend three nights together</title><description>Friday September 9, 2005 2:36 pm

Ramirez, the Stones belt out hits nightly. Like Manny, the Stones sometimes act as though they've lost a few... For the Stones: A party song that the Stones sold (out) to various commercial endeavors. It also has become... For the Stones: A late-'70s hit about relationships. Like many Stones songs, this one has been interpreted</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7154-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7154_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:24:04">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2006-02-05/black-and-golden-steelers-win-super-bowl-40</link><title>Black and golden: Steelers win Super Bowl 40</title><description>Monday February 6, 2006 12:38 am

Super Bowl satisfaction. Related articles Iyer's Super Bowl blog How the game was won One for the thumb... Rolling Stones rocked a Ford Field filled with Terrible Towels, Willie Parker broke a record 75-yard touchdown... night, satisfaction was more than Mick Jagger's signature song that closed the halftime show. It was</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>