<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7165">vice president residence</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:49:49" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7165-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7165_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:49:50">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2013-05-06/jonathan-holton-commits-west-virginia-facebook-video-voyeurism-rhode-island</link><title>West Virginia extends Jonathan Holton a scholarship if he's cleared of felony charges</title><description>Monday May 6, 2013 2:02 pm

... school's vice president for student affairs, said in a statement in March 2012. "Respect for the rights... from a residence hall, the Daily Mail reported. It would seem unlikely that the Mountaineers would attach</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7165-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7165_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:54:04">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2012-12-19/roger-springfield-investigation-syracuse-media-relations-police-probe</link><title>Roger Springfield investigation: Syracuse media relations aide under police scrutiny</title><description>Wednesday December 19, 2012 10:39 pm

... senior vice president for public affairs at the university, said Wednesday night. Quinn did not provide... Springfield's residence Wednesday night. Attorney James McGraw has been hired to represent Springfield. He did</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7165-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7165_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:57:39">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2012-11-30/hofstra-players-arrested-for-breaking-dorm-rooms-second-degree-burglary</link><title>Four Hofstra players arrested in dorm-room burglaries</title><description>Friday November 30, 2012 1:05 pm

... classes, residence halls and facilities, pending the outcome of the case. Melissa Connolly, Hofstra's vice president of university relations, said the public safety department has worked with Nassau</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7165-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7165_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:00:06">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2012-10-08/key-dates-in-the-penn-state-child-sex-abuse-case</link><title>Key dates in the Penn State child sex abuse case</title><description>Tuesday October 9, 2012 12:00 am

... senior vice president for finance and business. The grad assistant says he reported what he saw, and Curley... State President Graham Spanier to say he talked over the situation with "Joe" and had second thoughts... executive vice president Rodney Erickson is appointed to replace Spanier. Irate students take to the streets.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7165-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7165_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:02:59">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2012-10-06/key-dates-in-the-penn-state-child-sex-abuse-case</link><title>Key dates in the Penn State child sex abuse case</title><description>Saturday October 6, 2012 1:31 pm

... senior vice president for finance and business. The grad assistant says he reported what he saw, and Curley... State President Graham Spanier to say he talked over the situation with "Joe" and had second thoughts... executive vice president Rodney Erickson is appointed to replace Spanier. Irate students take to the streets.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7165-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7165_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:06:27">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2012-01-22/key-dates-in-the-penn-state-child-sex-abuse-case</link><title>Key dates in the Penn State child sex abuse case</title><description>Sunday January 22, 2012 3:43 pm

Senior Vice President for Finance and Business Gary Schultz. The grad assistant says he reported what... at his residence in College Township, Pa. Spring 2008 - Termination of contact with Victim 1 occurs when... executive vice president Rodney Erickson is appointed to replace Spanier. Irate students take to the streets.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7165-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7165_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:09:48">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/feed/2011-11/penn-state-scandal/story/email-tv-talk-add-new-twists-to-penn-state-case</link><title>Email, TV talk add new twists to Penn State case</title><description>Tuesday November 15, 2011 9:04 pm

... ousting of president Graham Spanier and charges of perjury against the athletic director and a senior vice president. MORE PENN STATE SCANDAL COVERAGE SANDUSKY INTERVIEW: Says he's innocent, but admits... senior vice president Gary Schultz, who oversaw campus police. Paterno has not been charged with any crime,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7165-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7165_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:12:35">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2011-10-26/chuck-blazer-group-emerges-to-rival-cosmos-bid-for-mls-team-in-new-york-city</link><title>Rival emerges in Cosmos' bid to land MLS expansion team</title><description>Wednesday October 26, 2011 12:15 pm

Cosmos vice chairman Terry Byrne told Sporting News over the summer that he expected "lots of progress"... maintains a residence at the Trump Tower in Manhattan and was a key whistle blower in the scandal that brought... CONCACAF president Jack Warner and FIFA presidential challenger Mohamed Bin Hammam. Last month, MLS president</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7165-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7165_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:16:15">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/feed/2011-11/penn-state-scandal/story/key-dates-in-the-penn-state-sex-abuse-case</link><title>Key dates in the Penn State sex abuse case</title><description>Monday November 7, 2011 7:31 pm

Senior Vice President for Finance and Business Gary Schultz. The grad assistant reports what he has seen... at his residence in College Township, Pa. Spring 2008--Termination of contact with Victim 1 occurs when... university President Graham Spanier. Curley and Schultz, who have stepped down from their positions, surrender</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7165-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7165_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:19:37">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2010-10-27/sbj-michael-jordan-all-in-as-bobcats-owner</link><title>SBJ: Michael Jordan 'all in' as Bobcats owner</title><description>Wednesday October 27, 2010 11:52 am

... senior vice president of the league's team marketing and business operations department. "I had to dig... title is vice president of Jump D.C., consider her Jordan's chief access officer. All requests and most... executive vice president of sports marketing at GMR. "It wasn't something [Jordan] wanted to do. Now, as</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>