<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7176"> weather in nyc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:29:16" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7176-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7176_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:29:18">http://www.sportingnews.com/nhl/story/2014-02-05/sochi-olympics-2014-hockey-schedule-nhl-player-in-olympics</link><title>Sochi Olympics: New York snowstorm could delay NHL's arrival</title><description>Wednesday February 5, 2014 3:06 pm

Nor'easter in NYC Sat nite-Sun morning.  Bob McKenzie (@TSNBobMcKenzie) February 5, 2014 Three charters... limitations in Sochi could cause huge problems if weather is an issue  Bob McKenzie (@TSNBobMcKenzie) February 5, 2014 In addition to 3 flights leaving Newark Sunday, there's one leaving Atlanta at 7 pm Sunday nite.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7176-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7176_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:31:01">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2014-01-29/after-25-years-madden-video-game-an-undeniable-part-of-nfl-culture</link><title>After 25 years, Madden video game an undeniable part of NFL culture</title><description>Wednesday January 29, 2014 10:49 pm

To be in a museum? That will always be there." SUPER BOWL: Weather letdown?  | Media Day images ... has been in Madden since before he was in Madden, because the game allows users to create their own players,... you grow in the game, you raise the level and hope and anticipate that you're successful in beating whoever</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7176-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7176_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:32:10">http://www.sportingnews.com/nhl/story/2011-11-06/messier-finch-ohno-among-runners-at-nyc-marathon</link><title>Messier, Finch, Ohno among runners at NYC Marathon</title><description>Sunday November 6, 2011 5:30 pm

... followed in the footsteps of 1994 Stanley Cup champion teammates Mike Richter and Adam Graves by completing... Olympic team in a country so deep in the sport. Firehiwot Dado wasn't a favorite coming into the women's race... earlier. In April, Mutai ran the fastest 26.2 miles in history: 2:03:02 in Boston. It didn't count as a</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7176-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7176_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:34:31">http://www.sportingnews.com/sport/story/2011-08-09/two-nyc-triathletes-die-organizers-ponder-changes</link><title>Two NYC triathletes die, organizers ponder changes</title><description>Tuesday August 9, 2011 8:28 am

... degrees in Central Park on Sunday with high levels of humidity, according to the National Weather Service.... participated in another triathlon -- things he would like to see enacted in the future. "It's something we're... said, in 2003, the swim portion was canceled due to high bacteria levels in the water. In Central Park</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7176-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7176_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:37:29">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2009-10-27/chance-showers-for-game-1</link><title>Chance of showers for Game 1</title><description>Tuesday October 27, 2009 6:50 pm

... soggy weather in the Bronx for Game 1 of the World Series. John Murray, a meteorologist with the National... night in Philadelphia. --- On the Net: National Weather Service Forecast Office for New York: http://www.weather.gov/nyc Copyright 2009 Associated Press. All rights reserved. This material may not be</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7176-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7176_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:40:50">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2010-05-25/hushed-seconds-and-then-super-explosion</link><title>For Jets, Giants supporters, hushed seconds give way to Super Bowl explosion</title><description>Tuesday May 25, 2010 9:55 pm

Super Bowl in the new $1.6 billion Meadowlands Stadium in what might well be the first cold weather championship... Colts in Super Bowl III. "I was in a rice paddy in Vietnam," Helwig said. "I listened on the radio at... Super Bowl in 2014." Some of the greatest games in NFL history have been played in the cold, including the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7176-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7176_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:41:51">http://www.sportingnews.com/nhl/story/2009-06-07/my-profile-brian-leetch-former-nhl-defenseman-and-hockey-hall-fame-candidate</link><title>My profile: Brian Leetch, former NHL defenseman and Hockey Hall of Fame candidate</title><description>Sunday June 7, 2009 6:59 am

1968, in Corpus Christi, Texas Status: Married Alma mater: Boston College What I'm up to these days:... watch in other sports: Tiger and LeBron Favorite city to visit: NYC \-- I lived there for 18 years... a week in Ireland with friends This story appears in Sporting News Today. If you are not receiving Sporting</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7176-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7176_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:42:59">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2007-12-12/dont-miss-out-these-college-basketball-trips</link><title>Don't miss out on these college basketball trips</title><description>Wednesday December 12, 2007 5:45 pm

Anyone in a cold-weather city has to appreciate the scene outside Pauley for a Saturday afternoon game... New York in November or December can tell you there is nothing like Christmastime in the city. New York... basketball in a magical venue: the 2K Sports College Hoops Classic in early November; the NIT Season Tip-Off</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>