<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7212">mud pumps</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:00:57" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7212-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7212_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:00:58">http://www.sportingnews.com/sport/story/2012-11-04/hurricane-sandy-fallout-cold-arrives-adds-to-post-storm-misery</link><title>Hurricane Sandy fallout: Cold arrives, adds to post-storm misery</title><description>Sunday November 4, 2012 3:11 pm

... foul-smelling mud. Firefighters and police officers sat in the front rows and drew applause. Roman Catholic... their pumps, drivers waited in line for hours for a chance at a fill-up, snapping at each other and honking... when the pumps might be running again. "We are expecting a delivery. But yesterday we weren't expecting</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7212-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7212_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:05:44">http://www.sportingnews.com/sport/story/2012-11-02/hurricane-sandy-fallout-as-storm-victims-tempers-boil-mayor-defends-marathon-pla</link><title>Hurricane Sandy fallout: As storm victims' tempers boil, mayor defends marathon plan</title><description>Friday November 2, 2012 3:23 pm

... their pumps, gasoline became a precious commodity, especially for those who depend on their cars for... see the pumps run dry when it was almost their turn. Others ran out of gas before they reached the front... air and mud-caked mattresses and couches lined the borough's streets. Residents picked through their belongings,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7212-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7212_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:09:59">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2010-12-22/poinsettia-bowl-to-go-on-despite-flooding</link><title>Poinsettia Bowl to go on despite flooding</title><description>Wednesday December 22, 2010 7:07 pm

... bilge pumps. The two teams are scheduled to play in the Poinsettia Bowl on Thursday night at Qualcomm... through the mud, if that's what it takes. "Sometimes college football has become big business but these are</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7212-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7212_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:11:17">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2008-07-17/big-papi-homers-class-aaa-rehab-start</link><title>Big Papi homers in Class AAA rehab start</title><description>Friday July 18, 2008 2:02 am

Toledo Mud Hens bullpen to give Pawtucket a 1-0 lead. "That's exactly what happens at Fenway," Ortiz... name, it pumps you up and puts you in the mood." Two batters later, Red Sox catching prospect George Kottaras</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>