<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7218">edward kennedy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:17:06" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7218-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7218_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:17:06">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2009-08-26/patriots-coach-praises-sen-kennedy</link><title>Belichick praises late Senator Edward Kennedy</title><description>Wednesday August 26, 2009 8:10 pm

... late Sen. Edward Kennedy, who sent him personal notes and congratulations on the team's successes. Belichick... Wednesday that Kennedy's "leadership and his courage were certainly something I personally always looked up to"... added that Kennedy attended the team's Super Bowl victory visits to the White House. Kennedy played football</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7218-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7218_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:19:04">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2009-04-07/mass-sen-edward-kennedy-throws-first-pitch</link><title>Mass. Sen. Edward Kennedy throws first pitch</title><description>Tuesday April 7, 2009 9:49 pm

Massachusetts Sen. Edward Kennedy threw out the ceremonial first pitch at the Boston Red Sox season opener on Tuesday.... around Kennedy's shoulders and they walked toward the mound. After his pitches, Kennedy returned to the... drove Kennedy off the field with Kennedy's wife, Vicki, seated on a back cushion. Earlier, Keith Lockhart</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7218-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7218_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:21:49">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2009-09-02/curt-schilling-expresses-interest-running-for-kennedys-senate-seat</link><title>Curt Schilling expresses interest in running for Edward M. Kennedy's Senate seat</title><description>Thursday September 3, 2009 1:24 am

... the late Edward M. Kennedy. Schilling, a registered independent and longtime Republican supporter, wrote... well as Kennedy's nephew former U.S. Rep. Joseph P. Kennedy II. So far, only state Attorney General Martha... comment. Kennedy died last week at age 77 from a brain tumor. The Massachusetts Legislature is considering</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7218-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7218_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:23:56">http://www.sportingnews.com/sport/story/2013-04-15/boston-marathon-bombing-two-killed-scores-injured-as-explosions-rock-race-route</link><title>Boston Marathon bombings: Three killed, scores injured, maimed by blasts near finish line</title><description>Monday April 15, 2013 6:29 pm

Commissioner Edward Davis asked people to stay indoors or go back to their hotel rooms and avoid crowds as bomb... John F. Kennedy Library. The police commissioner said that it may have been caused by an incendiary device</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7218-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7218_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:26:52">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2013-01-14/salary-arbitration-eligibles-list</link><title>Salary Arbitration Eligibles List</title><description>Monday January 14, 2013 9:25 pm

3b; Ian Kennedy, rhp; Gerardo Parra, lhp; Cliff Pennington, ss; Tony Sipp, lhp; Brad Ziegler, rhp. ATLANTA... Motte, rhp; Edward Mujica, rhp; Marc Rzepczynski, lhp. SAN DIEGO (8) - John Baker, c; Everth Cabrera, ss;</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7218-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7218_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:30:10">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-02-02/pro-football-hall-of-fame-2013-class-bill-parcells-warren-sapp-cris-carter-ogden</link><title>Pro Football Hall of Fame 2013 class: Bill Parcells, Warren Sapp among electees</title><description>Saturday February 2, 2013 6:14 pm

Modell and Edward DeBartolo Jr. Players and coaches from the Baltimore Ravens, who will face the San Francisco... Cortez Kennedy, Curtis Martin, Willie Roaf. 2011 -- Richard Dent, Marshall Faulk, x-Chris Hanburger,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7218-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7218_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:34:43">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2009-08-26/red-sox-pay-tribute-kennedy</link><title>Red Sox pay tribute to Kennedy</title><description>Wednesday August 26, 2009 11:35 pm

U.S. Sen. Edward Kennedy before their game on Wednesday night, paying tribute to a lifelong fan whose family... where Kennedy threw out the ceremonial first pitch on opening day, 97 years after his grandfather, Boston... recognition of Kennedy's connection to Cape Cod. Copyright 2009 Associated Press. All rights reserved. This material</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7218-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7218_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:36:34">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2009-09-22/schilling-wont-run-for-kennedys-seat-senate</link><title>Schilling won't run for Kennedy's seat in Senate</title><description>Wednesday September 23, 2009 2:55 am

... running for Edward M. Kennedy's seat in the U.S. Senate. Earlier this month, Schilling expressed interest... said. Kennedy, who was first elected to the Senate in 1962, died Aug. 25 of brain cancer at age 77. Primaries... pursue Kennedy's seat. "I think the country is sick and tired of elected officials beholden to special</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7218-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7218_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:38:56">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2012-06-24/baseball-capsules</link><title>Baseball Capsules</title><description>Monday June 25, 2012 12:00 am

... slam off Edward Mujica. Darren Oliver (2-2) pitched a scoreless eighth for the Blue Jays, who have won... off Ian Kennedy, but fell to 0-4 in his last eight stars. Craig Breslow (2-0) pitched 1 2-3 innings of</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7218-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7218_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:42:05">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2009-09-17/celtics-co-owner-pagliuca-will-run-for-kennedys-senate-seat</link><title>Celtics co-owner Pagliuca will run for Kennedy's Senate seat</title><description>Friday September 18, 2009 12:03 am

... late Sen. Edward M. Kennedy's passion. In announcing his bid for the Democratic nomination to succeed the... against Kennedy for job losses attributed to Bain acquisitions, but Pagliuca vigorously defended the industry.... against Kennedy, Pagliuca said he is a lifelong Democrat. "You have to treat your friends (well) and be</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>