<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7260">iowa girls high school basketball</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:50:29" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7260-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7260_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:50:31">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2012-03-16/badgers-senior-steps-up-just-in-time</link><title>Badgers senior steps up just in time</title><description>Friday March 16, 2012 7:28 pm

Boys &amp; Girls Club where he's serving an internship this semester. Now, Vanderbilt star Jeffery Taylor... points at Iowa on Feb. 23, beginning a startling seven-game stretch in which he's averaged 11.1 points and... career high of 13 - and tied a school record with seven 3-pointers. He chipped in 10 points in 28 minutes</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7260-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7260_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:52:16">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2011-08-31/what-theyre-saying-texas-ams-big-move</link><title>What they're saying: Texas A&amp;M's big move</title><description>Wednesday August 31, 2011 3:40 pm

... their girls basketball team won the national championship last year. They will be a huge addition to... Kansas basketball coach Bill Self, via ESPN "I would rather it not happen, but I still believe that even... state for high school football, and the high school coaches are outstanding in the state of Texas. But, again,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7260-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7260_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:54:33">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2010-03-18/leading-tiny-terriers-tourney-fits-dahlman-s-hard-working-back</link><title>Leading tiny Terriers into tourney fits Dahlman's hard-working background</title><description>Thursday March 18, 2010 9:32 pm

... in the girls state tournament. Theyre playing basketball because thats what you do in the Dahlman household:... homework, play basketball. The plan leads to success because thats the way Nate Dahlmans father did it, and... year in high school, Minneapolis natives Rundles and Wofford teammate Jamar Diggs went to Braham to play</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7260-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7260_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:55:26">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2010-03-25/names-and-numbers-from-regional-semifinals</link><title>Names and numbers from the regional semifinals</title><description>Friday March 26, 2010 2:35 am

... get one school within a win of the Final Four. Last year and 2006, when Connecticut and Villanova reached,... little girls and Syracuse students in there told the guys that Syracuse had lost," he said, referring... Northern Iowa in the second round. Two No. 1 seeds reached the Final Four last year - Connecticut and North</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7260-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7260_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:57:32">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2005-02-28/qa-korver-wants-ball-game-line</link><title>Q&amp;A: Korver wants the ball with game on the line</title><description>Monday February 28, 2005 10:59 pm

... teenage girls. TSN: You grew up near Los Angeles, but you wound up playing high school ball in Pella, Iowa. How does that happen? KORVER: My father and mother went to Central College, which is in... you play basketball, because you want to have the ball in your hands when the clock is running down, and</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>