<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7274">detroit riot</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:01:26" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7274-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7274_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:01:27">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-07-01/weekend-sports-in-brief</link><title>Weekend Sports In Brief</title><description>Monday July 1, 2013 4:26 am

... clashed with riot police outside Maracana Stadium. Brazil, a five-time world champion, beat the reigning world... behind Detroit's Miguel Cabrera. Davis is the first player in major league history to have at least 30</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7274-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7274_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:02:41">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2012-12-18/monday-s-sports-in-brief</link><title>Monday's Sports in Brief</title><description>Tuesday December 18, 2012 8:29 am

... victory over Detroit in the Gotham Classic made Boeheim just the third Division I men's coach to reach 900 wins.... called a "riot" on the fans who were arrested, saying a security official was punched and knocked to the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7274-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7274_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:05:06">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2012-10-29/fans-fill-sf-streets-to-celebrate-giants-win</link><title>Fans fill SF streets to celebrate Giants' win</title><description>Monday October 29, 2012 7:44 am

... defeated the Detroit Tigers Sunday night, greeting diners, bar patrons and other merry makers. At Polk and... clad in riot gear looked on as revelers danced around Civic Center plaza where they watched the game on... in by riot police to fight some of the fires. Mayor Edwin Lee announced the ticker-tape parade would</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7274-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7274_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:07:49">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2012-10-29/world-series-2012-thousands-gather-at-city-hall-to-celebrate-giants</link><title>World Series 2012: City celebrates; parade set for Wednesday</title><description>Monday October 29, 2012 1:47 am

... clad in riot gear looked on as revelers danced around Civic Center plaza where they watched the game on... rain in Detroit couldn't dampen the drive, talent and determination of the San Francisco Giants team tonight.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7274-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7274_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:11:06">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2012-05-16/lawrie-joins-list-of-baseball-s-wildest-rants</link><title>Lawrie joins list of baseball's wildest rants</title><description>Wednesday May 16, 2012 7:39 pm

... a near-riot at Comiskey Park in 1979. The idea was for fans to break despised disco records to the ballpark,... games of a Detroit-Chicago doubleheader. An overflow crowd turned rowdy and overran the field, setting fires</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7274-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7274_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:13:23">http://www.sportingnews.com/nhl/feed/2011-09/khl-crash/story/russian-jet-carrying-hockey-team-crashes-36-dead</link><title>Jet carrying hockey team crashes; at least 43 dead</title><description>Wednesday September 7, 2011 9:12 am

... was in Detroit and spoke with members of the Red Wings shortly after news of the crash arrived. "Our... respects. Riot police were also present as fans chanted sport songs in memory of the athletes. Yaroslavl</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7274-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7274_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:15:03">http://www.sportingnews.com/nhl/story/2011-06-22/corey-perry-caps-nhl-awards-night-by-receiving-hart-trophy</link><title>Corey Perry caps NHL Awards night by receiving Hart Trophy</title><description>Wednesday June 22, 2011 9:03 pm

... points. Detroit's Nicklas Lidstrom returned to the awards platform by winning his seventh Norris Trophy... topped Detroit's Datsyuk in 2010, ending the Red Wings forward's four-year run as the award winner. St.... "You're a riot," movie director Kevin Smith told "How I Met Your Mother" actress and Vancouver-native Cobie</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7274-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7274_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:16:00">http://www.sportingnews.com/nhl/story/2009-06-12/pittsburgh-penguins-fans-celebrate-championship</link><title>Pittsburgh Penguins fans celebrate championship</title><description>Saturday June 13, 2009 3:28 am

... beat the Detroit Red Wings 2-1 to win the Cup for the third time, following titles in 1991 and 1992. The... deal with Detroit last summer, turning down a better-paying offer with a longer term from Pittsburgh. "I... victory over Detroit because the Red Wings beat the Penguins in Pittsburgh last year. "This is amazing. It</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7274-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7274_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:18:47">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2009-04-03/police-near-michigan-state-ready-final-four</link><title>Police near Michigan State ready for Final Four</title><description>Friday April 3, 2009 4:24 pm

... be at Detroit's Ford Field, about a 90-mile drive from campus. East Lansing dealt with a riot after... in the Detroit area but also has options for those remaining near campus. The Breslin Center will show</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7274-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7274_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:19:48">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2009-03-26/williams-finds-herding-ducks-easier-players</link><title>Williams finds herding ducks easier than players</title><description>Thursday March 26, 2009 11:43 pm

... incited a riot when he got into it with (former Memphis player) Shawne Williams. Few called Memphis fans... good. "Detroit seems to be a little more spread out," said Cole Aldrich, who played in last year's regionals at Detroit. "In Indy, it feels a little more cozy." ------ TICKETS AVAILABLE: Indy organizers hoped</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>