<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7294">assumption of mary</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:11:45" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7294-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7294_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:11:47">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2012-09-25/detroit-lions-week-4-fantasy-football-lineups-projections-defense-sacks</link><title>Lions report: Outside pass rush nearly non-existent</title><description>Tuesday September 25, 2012 3:26 pm

... under the assumption that their deep pass rush would be enough to prop up the defense. Three games into the... a Hail Mary attempt by Rams quarterback Sam Bradford on the final play of a Week 1 win, and Vanden Bosch's... largely out of fear their substandard defensive backfield will be exposed, they need the front four to play</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7294-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7294_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:12:59">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2009-08-20/guilty-plea-will-serve-plaxico-burress-well-long-run</link><title>Guilty plea will serve Plaxico Burress well in the long run</title><description>Thursday August 20, 2009 6:57 pm

... chances of an acquittal to the outcome of the O.J. Simpson case. But the difference in Simpson's situation... composed of citizens of sound mind could have found a way to let him walk. Despite Burress' past (and,... the pool of 10 guilty men that our government would rather set free in lieu of sending one innocent man</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7294-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7294_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:13:39">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2008-10-12/matt-ryan-has-falcons-looking-professional-again</link><title>Matt Ryan has Falcons looking professional again</title><description>Sunday October 12, 2008 10:12 pm

... promise of a bright future. The biggest challenge was quickly finding Vick's replacement as the face of the franchise. The role required an exciting young skill player who would be dynamic and successful,... make that assumption based on his performance. Ryan looks as if he has been around the league for a long</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7294-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7294_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:15:37">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2008-08-16/camp-caravan-expectations-cleveland-have-no-ceiling</link><title>Camp caravan: Expectations in Cleveland have no ceiling</title><description>Saturday August 16, 2008 3:40 pm

... cradle of professional football is buzzing with the kind of excitement not seen in these parts since local... do. The assumption is that G.M. Phil Savage's gutting and restocking of the organization necessitated... capable of leading an NFL offense right now. What could go wrong? Injuries happen, of course, and if there's</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>