<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7348">map of the united states</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:50:03" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7348-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7348_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:50:06">http://www.sportingnews.com/sport/story/2014-02-12/sports-little-affected-by-latest-winter-storm-southern-fans-get-nailed</link><title>Sports affected by latest winter storm; Southern fans get nailed</title><description>Wednesday February 12, 2014 3:33 pm

... where the daytime high was a balmy 64 and overnight lows along the Black Sea coast were in the mid-40s.... eastern half of the United States was hit or under the threat of a winter storm that dropping snow and ice up... Service map of the storm showed possible effects hitting 22 states from Texas to Maine. A more serious</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7348-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7348_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:51:12">http://www.sportingnews.com/sport/story/2014-01-30/2014-sochi-olympics-pairs-skater-simon-shnapir-returns-to-russia</link><title>2014 Sochi Olympics: Pairs skater Simon Shnapir returns to Russia</title><description>Thursday January 30, 2014 12:56 pm

... year is a map of Simon Shnapir's life. The Winter Games are in Russia, where he was born. To earn a spot... moved to the suburb of Sudbury, 20 miles west of Boston. Simon grew up a huge fan of New England sports... place in the United States. His images of his family's time in Russia come from photographs and retold stories.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7348-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7348_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:53:24">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2013-05-10/the-full-volley-ferguson-manchester-united-juventus-cropper</link><title>The Full Volley: Ferguson wrote the manual of how to run a club</title><description>Friday May 10, 2013 7:20 pm

... and a map to keep track of all 49. He won 13 league trophies since the beginning of the Premier League,... represent the good ole days " the era of pure British grit, of bloody headbands and pints after the match... helped the United States to the final of the CONCACAF U-20 Championship, which doubled as qualifying for</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7348-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7348_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:54:10">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2013-06-21/the-full-volley-benji-joya-dani-cuevas-usa-u20-world-cup</link><title>The Full Volley: Joya and Cuevas take unconventional route to the top</title><description>Friday June 21, 2013 4:15 pm

Laguna. The pair make unlikely protagonists for the United States, which is currently in Turkey for the... March the duo left to join the United States in the CONCACAF U-20 Championship in Puebla. Both consider... them on the map, the World Cup could raise their stocks considerably. The United States is in arguably</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7348-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7348_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:56:02">http://www.sportingnews.com/sport/story/2013-08-14/track-and-field-gay-rights-controversy-on-sideline-at-worlds</link><title>Track and field: Gay rights controversy on sideline at worlds</title><description>Wednesday August 14, 2013 6:21 pm

Olympics that the United States boycotted. Although the athletes at the worlds won't be competing in Sochi,... accused of breaking the law. Russia has given contradictory signals on how the law will apply to the Olympics.... who qualified for the final of the men's 5,000. "But here I want to focus on the things I need to do."</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7348-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7348_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:56:39">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2013-08-12/mexico-olympics-one-year-el-tri-world-cup</link><title>One year from Olympic glory, where did it go wrong for Mexico?</title><description>Monday August 12, 2013 9:05 am

... represent the dawn of a new era for the country's No. 1 sport. The talented youngsters - who outplayed Brazil's... against each of Jamaica, Costa Rica and the United States. The U.S. national team has even moved above Mexico... has made the issue of Carlos Vela all the more desperate, as well as raise the topic of naturalized players</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7348-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7348_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 03:59:13">http://www.sportingnews.com/sport/story/2013-07-03/wimbledon-facebook-insights-2013</link><title>Wimbledon 2013 through Facebook insights</title><description>Wednesday July 3, 2013 12:13 pm

... throughout the first week of play. Over 11.6 million total global interactions so far (includes mentions,... Britain 2. United States 3\. India 4. Italy 5. Australia Top social moments 1. Rafael Nadal (5) stunned... advance to the third round to keep British hopes alive " 6/28 Map guide: Top five countries where tennis</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7348-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7348_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:01:56">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-03-15/thursday-s-sports-in-brief</link><title>Thursday's Sports In Brief</title><description>Friday March 15, 2013 5:33 am

... against the Clippers. Anthony left in the third quarter of the Knicks' 117-94 loss to Denver on Wednesday... beating the United States 3-1 to earn a berth in the final round of the World Baseball Classic. Pinch-hitter... 6-2 in the quarterfinals of the BNP Paribas Open in the earliest meeting between the two rivals since</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7348-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7348_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:03:32">http://www.sportingnews.com/sport/story/2012-10-28/hurricane-sandy-watch-frankenstorm-new-york-transit-shutdown</link><title>Hurricane Sandy watch: New York City shutting down mass transit ahead of storm</title><description>Sunday October 28, 2012 11:20 am

... make up the nation's largest transit system, are shutting down Sunday night in advance of the massive storm... to hit the eastern third of the United States. "A situation like this, you don't want to be overly panicked... miles. -- Map: New York area evacuation zones "As the storm has not changed course, the storm is still</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7348-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7348_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 04:06:13">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2012-09-14/russians-prepare-to-invade-timberwolves</link><title>Russian national team stars prepare to invade Timberwolves</title><description>Friday September 14, 2012 7:56 pm

... back on the map after leading the national team to a bronze medal at the London Olympics. Now they're... Russia. All of the kids look at basketball a different way." The Timberwolves are in the middle of a reclamation... helping the United States to the Olympic title, emerging as coach Mike Krzyzewski's favored big man. He's</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>