<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7403">usc trojans</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:30:48" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7403-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7403_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:30:49">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/feed/2011-07/preseason-rankings/story/no-25-usc-trojans-at-a-glance</link><title>No. 25 USC Trojans at a glance</title><description>Saturday August 6, 2011 11:59 am

... way the Trojans\--compromised by the seeping disease of bowl ineligibility--should be looked at one of the... that the Trojans take one of the biggest leaps of any offense in the country. Of course, that still leaves... and the Trojans are especially talented in the middle of the secondary. And don't discount the heavy hand</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7403-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7403_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:31:27">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2012-08-20/pac-12-all-conference-matt-barkley-marqise-lee-usc-trojans-stanford-cardinal</link><title>All Pac-12: USC Trojans loaded on both sides of ball</title><description>Monday August 20, 2012 5:21 pm

Holmes, Sr., USC OL David Yankey, Soph., Stanford OL Carson York, Sr., Oregon WR Marqise Lee, Soph., USC... Robey, Jr., USC S John Boyett, Sr., Oregon S T.J. McDonald, Sr., USC Specialists K Andre Heidari, Soph.,... Barkley, USC Coach of the year: Lane Kiffin, USC MORE PAC-12: Rich Rodriguez has plenty to prove |</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7403-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7403_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:33:30">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2012-09-03/usc-trojans-ncaa-joe-mcknight-lane-kiffin-no-distraction</link><title>USC Trojans won't be distracted, Lane Kiffin says</title><description>Monday September 3, 2012 11:26 am

USC didn't look distracted in its 49-10 win against Hawaii, and Trojans coach Lane Kiffin said he expects... former USC football standout Joe McKnight and former Trojans basketball player Davon Jefferson in 2008... 2009. The Trojans are bowl-eligible this season--the first time in three seasons as the school remains on</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7403-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7403_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:35:12">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2012-07-24/usc-trojans-picked-to-return-to-top-of-pac-12</link><title>USC Trojans picked to return to top of Pac-12</title><description>Tuesday July 24, 2012 8:13 pm

... expects the Trojans to reclaim their spot atop the league. USC has been picked to win the Pac-12 in the annual... Tuesday. The Trojans were picked to win the South Division on 117 of the 123 ballots, while Oregon was picked... margin. USC was picked to win the league championship game by 102 of the voters. USC has enjoyed an outstanding</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7403-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7403_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:37:01">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2012-04-17/usc-trojans-football-radio-deal-with-espn-takes-team-national</link><title>ESPN radio deal to take USC Trojans football national</title><description>Tuesday April 17, 2012 2:05 pm

... have done USC games locally in Los Angeles and are expected to stay. The deal is an important part of USC's... manager of USC Sports Properties. "The story is about USC's brand. This deal is one small sign of the brand... manage USC's multimedia rights. USC previously had a deal with Touchdown Radio Network, but the deal was</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7403-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7403_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:39:13">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2012-07-29/usc-trojans-kahlil-dukes-commitment-point-guard</link><title>USC Trojans land rising point guard Kahlil Dukes</title><description>Sunday July 29, 2012 5:08 pm

... committing to USC on Sunday. The 5-foot-10 point guard from Capital Prep in Connecticut texted multiple media... join the USC recruiting class of 2013, ESPN.com reported . Dukes had a monster junior season and cemented</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7403-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7403_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:40:24">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2013-01-14/kevin-oneill-fired-usc-trojans-coach-pat-haden-pac-12</link><title>Kevin O'Neill fired as USC Trojans coach in fourth season</title><description>Monday January 14, 2013 12:00 pm

... fired as USC men's basketball coach Monday, the school announced. O'Neill compiled a 48-65 record with the Trojans in three-plus seasons. His 2011 team finished 19-15 and lost in the first round of the... commitment to USC and help build the Trojan program in the right direction." USC athletic director Pat Haden</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7403-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7403_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:41:33">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/feed/2011-07/preseason-rankings/story/top-50-countdown-no-25-usc-trojans</link><title>Top 50 countdown: No. 25 USC Trojans</title><description>Saturday August 6, 2011 3:58 pm

... assess than USC, and the on-field questions are only one source of the confusion. NCAA scholarship sanctions... troubles, the Trojans still possess one of the most talented rosters in the conference. If they are focused... chance the Trojans could drift toward mediocrity. "We're not thinking about the negative aspects of the season,"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7403-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7403_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:42:23">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2012-06-04/usc-trojans-jesse-scroggins-quarterback-transfer-matt-barkley</link><title>USC Trojans backup QB Jesse Scroggins transferring</title><description>Monday June 4, 2012 5:11 pm

USC sophomore quarterback Jesse Scroggins is transferring, USC coach Lane Kiffin announced Monday. "After... transfer from USC," Kiffin said. "Jesse had a very strong spring semester in the classroom, therefore he is academically... leaves the Trojans with three quarterbacks on scholarship, including starter and Heisman Trophy candidate</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7403-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7403_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:43:56">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2012-07-01/college-football-recruiting-2013-michael-hutchings-usc-trojans</link><title>Michael Hutchings, SN's No. 5 overall player, commits to USC Trojans</title><description>Sunday July 1, 2012 3:01 pm

... committed to USC on Sunday, according to 247Sports.com . The 6-foot-2, 215-pound linebacker from De La Salle... unbeatable at USC," Hutchings told 247Sports.com . "My parents felt the same way and they were involved a little... education at USC and the coaching staff at SC is great. Mr. (Pat) Haden is also a great guy and everything just</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>