<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7404">kobe bryant</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:46:10" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7404-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7404_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:46:12">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2014-02-10/kobe-bryant-injury-update-lakers-news-knee-achilles-steve-nash-chris-kaman-nick-young-pau-gasol-trade-rumors</link><title>Kobe Bryant still expects to return to Lakers this season</title><description>Monday February 10, 2014 1:32 pm

Kobe Bryant is all too familiar with the Lakers' recent struggles, as he has watched from the sidelines... Still, Bryant has no intent to slow down his return to the basketball court. MORE: Rare photos of Steve... stage for Bryant is to be re-evaluated next week after the All-Star Game. Bryant is not aware what effect</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7404-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7404_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:48:14">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2014-01-29/kobe-bryant-injury-update-setback-hurt-knee-lakers-news-steve-nash-mike-dantoni</link><title>Kobe Bryant down about setback, ready to throw bike in the pool</title><description>Wednesday January 29, 2014 2:46 pm

Kobe Bryant is expected to miss more time due to continued pain and swelling in his injured left knee,... saying Bryant will be out for at least three extra weeks before he is re-examined. "[I'm] down about... injury, but Bryant will be out much longer. Bryant will continue with a program of light exercise, including</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7404-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7404_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:50:12">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2014-01-28/kobe-bryant-knee-injury-update-status-when-will-he-play-lakers-torn-achilles-pau-gasol-steve-nash</link><title>Kobe Bryant out at least another three weeks, Lakers say</title><description>Tuesday January 28, 2014 11:48 pm

... announced that Kobe Bryant would be out for about three more weeks because the pain and swelling in his knee had... UPDATE: Kobe Bryant was examined tonight &amp; still has pain and swelling in his left knee. Examined again... 2014 Bryant will continue with a program of non-weight bearing exercise, consisting mostly of working</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7404-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7404_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:51:36">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2014-01-28/kobe-bryant-injured-knee-being-evaluated-in-weeks-not-days-lakers-steve-nash-mike-dantoni</link><title>Kobe Bryant's injured knee being evaluated in 'weeks, not days'</title><description>Tuesday January 28, 2014 2:54 pm

Kobe Bryant is set to have his injured knee reevaluaed on Tuesday, but expectations have been tempered... Lakers. Bryant, who has yet to do anything more than bike exercises, is being measured on a weekly basis,... team. Kobe's timeline for return is being measured in "weeks, not days" according to the Lakers. He'll</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7404-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7404_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:53:09">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2014-01-28/lakers-kobe-bryant-expected-to-miss-all-star-game</link><title>Lakers' Kobe Bryant expected to miss All-Star game</title><description>Wednesday January 29, 2014 12:44 am

ANGELES (AP) Kobe Bryant is expected to miss the NBA All-Star game due to continued pain and swelling in his... saying Bryant will be out for at least three more weeks before he is re-examined. Bryant was voted a... injury, but Bryant will be out much longer. Bryant will continue with a program of light exercise, including</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7404-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7404_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:54:45">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2014-02-24/kobe-bryant-jason-collins-gay-nba-player-nets-lakers-nba-fine-david-stern-adam-silver</link><title>Kobe Bryant believes Jason Collins' historic moment will have domino effect</title><description>Monday February 24, 2014 1:35 pm

... guard Kobe Bryant was not on the court Sunday when Brooklyn Nets center Jason Collins made NBA history.... injury, Bryant watched from the sidelines. Although he wasn't playing on this night, Bryant was aware... part of Bryant's statement is the progress he has made on the subject. Bryant was fined $100,000 for directing</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7404-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7404_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:56:04">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2014-01-26/kobe-bryant-knee-evaluation-exercise-rehab-torn-achilles-lakers-news</link><title>Lakers' Kobe Bryant eager to ramp up exercise efforts</title><description>Sunday January 26, 2014 4:10 pm

Kobe Bryant will have his injured left knee evaluated on Monday to determine whether he is healthy enough... bike," Bryant told the LA Times . "That's killing me. Absolutely killing me." Kobe played only six... Grizzlies. Bryant needs medical clearance before he can ramp up his rehab regiment. That process begins when</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7404-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7404_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:57:07">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2014-02-03/australian-dante-exum-agent-kobe-bryant-rob-pelinka-nba-draft-2014-cecil-exum-michael-jordan-andrew-bogut-patty-mills</link><title>Australian Dante Exum picked agent for Kobe Bryant ties</title><description>Monday February 3, 2014 5:43 pm

... he has Kobe Bryant, and he's been through this when he came into the NBA," Exum told The Canberra Times... agent said Kobe knows who I am and he said he'd definitely have a chat to me." The 18-year old Australian... works as Kobe Bryant's manager. Exum did consider playing one season in college, but he is now expected</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7404-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7404_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:57:57">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2014-02-16/kobe-bryant-los-angeles-lakers-knee-injury-tibia-steve-nash-nba-all-star-anthony-davis-james-harden</link><title>Still uncertain of return, Kobe Bryant's future remains up in the air</title><description>Sunday February 16, 2014 9:33 pm

... guard Kobe Bryant, sidelined since mid-December with a fracture in his left tibia, still isnt sure when... value for Bryant, and that is assuming that Bryant can fully return from the knee injury. He has only played... stubbornness of Bryants injuriesand whether this really is it for Bryantonly makes it more difficult.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7404-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7404_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:59:13">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2014-02-22/kobe-bryant-injury-update-knee-exam-los-angeles-la-lakers-achilles</link><title>Kobe Bryant injury update: Knee still hurting; next exam in three weeks</title><description>Saturday February 22, 2014 6:23 am

... out for Kobe Bryant as he tries to return from his knee injury this season. Lakers team physician Stephen... Friday. Bryant still has pain, swelling and soreness in his knee and will be re-evaluated in three weeks,... that." Bryant said during All-Star Weekend that his rehab has been "coming slowly." Bryant has only</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>