<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7415">most anticipated games of 2013</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:08:22" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7415-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7415_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:08:23">http://www.sportingnews.com/fantasy/mlb/story/2014-02-18/tampa-bay-rays-2014-fantasy-baseball-team-preview-evan-longoria-david-price</link><title>Tampa Bay Rays 2014 fantasy baseball team preview</title><description>Tuesday February 18, 2014 12:59 pm

... berth in 2013. They were involved in a pair of trades, including a three-team deal with Arizona and Cincinnati... missed 117 games from 2011-12 and has now topped 150 games in just three of six seasons. PROSPECT WATCH:... logged most of his games at second base (34) last year, but he also played 3B (11), SS (11) and OF (13).</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7415-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7415_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:10:32">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2013-09-30/13-nationals-go-bust-need-to-hire-new-skipper</link><title>'13 Nationals go 'bust'; need to hire new skipper</title><description>Monday September 30, 2013 4:16 pm

... than many anticipated, there are plenty of key questions facing the club, most importantly: How to replace... are out of our hands," reliever Tyler Clippard said. "The only thing I ask of whoever makes the decisions... finished 10 games behind the Braves, and four games out of the NL's last postseason spot. Said Harper: "We</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7415-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7415_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:12:21">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2013-03-23/ncaa-tournament-2013-saturday-games-michigan-vcu-syracuse-louisville-gonzaga</link><title>NCAA Tournament 2013: Michigan vs. VCU gets Saturday started</title><description>Saturday March 23, 2013 11:50 am

Goliaths of March Madness find their way, or will the Davids of college basketball continue their winning... Round of 32 , Saturday's action in the 2013 NCAA Tournament. Track live: Saturday games on Sporting... day's most anticipated game, it will pit a team that briefly was No. 1 in national polls against a team</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7415-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7415_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:14:23">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2013-06-28/muhammad-takes-dad-out-of-hoops-life-to-enter-nba</link><title>Muhammad takes dad out of hoops life to enter NBA</title><description>Friday June 28, 2013 7:54 pm

... construction of AAU teams that allowed his son to become one of the most heavily recruited prep stars in the... three games of the season and repay $1,600 in impermissible benefits after the NCAA and UCLA found that... revelation of his true age. "I think he handled adversity extremely well and he had a lot of it," Howland</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7415-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7415_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:15:57">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2013-06-26/blue-jays-red-sox-preview</link><title>Blue Jays-Red Sox Preview</title><description>Wednesday June 26, 2013 10:53 pm

6 1/2 games with the Blue Jays winning 12 of 14\. Farrell, who managed the Blue Jays for two years before... fully anticipated them scoring a lot of runs, but over the stretch that they're on, you can point to... last 14 games and its starters have one of the best ERAs in baseball over that stretch at 2.86. Lester</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7415-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7415_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:16:52">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2012-11-03/mlb-hot-stove-2013-cleveland-indians-terry-francona-asdrubal-cabrera-carlos-sant</link><title>MLB Hot Stove 2013: Cleveland Indians report</title><description>Saturday November 3, 2012 6:49 am

... firing of manager Manny Acta. There is a sense of optimism following the hiring of Terry Francona, but... plenty of free agents who would be affordable upgrades. -- Free agency: Full list of players available... first half of his tenure, Hafner was plagued by injuries the past five seasons (playing more than 94 games</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7415-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7415_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:18:40">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2013-03-17/ncaa-tournament-2013-field-of-68-bubble-watch-selection-sunday-louisville-indian</link><title>Field of 68: Make Louisville, Indiana, Duke, Kansas the No. 1 seeds</title><description>Sunday March 17, 2013 1:45 pm

Sunday, one of the greatest and most anticipated days of the year for sports fans across the country. There... Field of 68 projection. The differences between the resumes of bubble teams is negligible, but there... won 10 of their last 11 conference games and then swept through the Big East Tournament to shoot back</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7415-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7415_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:21:28">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2013-03-25/mike-trout-bryce-harper-second-year-performance-preview-2013-sophomore-slump</link><title>Mike Trout, Bryce Harper push encore envelope</title><description>Monday March 25, 2013 2:28 pm

... up to most expectations as rookies in 2012, and in Trout's case, he exceeded them by miles as he established... Rookie of the Year awards. Both have become household baseball names and two of the faces of Major League... Trout said of how he will approach his highly anticipated sophomore season. "When I play baseball, I'm not</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7415-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7415_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:22:32">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/feed/2013-02/team-previews-2013/story/spring-training-colorado-rockies-preview-todd-helton-troy-tulowitzki-cargo-gonza</link><title>Spring training: Colorado Rockies preview</title><description>Friday February 22, 2013 10:08 am

... rural part of Colorado outside of Denver. He was enjoying watching his kids grow up and had gotten involved... players of is we have the greatest home-field advantage in all of baseball, and I don't think there is... three of the four most active relievers in the National League. 2013 OUTLOOK What could go right:</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7415-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7415_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:24:28">http://www.sportingnews.com/nhl/story/2013-01-14/nhl-lockout-news-devils-season-tickets-ilya-kovalchuk-lou-lamoriello-jeff-vander</link><title>How do you sell hockey the day after the NHL lockout?</title><description>Monday January 14, 2013 10:32 am

... plans of 10 games and 13 games. With a projected condensed schedule of 24 home games and 24 away, a 13-game... schedule 2013: Games, dates to remember The rest of the crew supports the plan. While the 13-game plan... 41 home games. During Christmas week, Weinbach and her staff of three went through the roster of sponsors</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>