<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7432">ticket to mars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:43:19" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7432-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7432_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:43:22">http://www.sportingnews.com/nhl/story/2014-02-03/russell-wilson-wisconsin-super-bowl-commercials-budweiser-puppy-love-bruno-mars-halftime</link><title>Who had the best Super Bowl ever? Kyle Turris, apparently</title><description>Monday February 3, 2014 1:28 pm

Bruno Mars fan and a puppy fan  so yes, Super Bowl Sunday went well for him. Turris, a center for the... Wilson to end at some point.  Bobby Ryan (@b_ryan9) February 3, 2014 @b_ryan9 just pulling for a... Super Bowl to Brady's three. "It kind of helps with that status, between him and Peyton," Turris said. Since</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7432-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7432_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:45:00">http://www.sportingnews.com/nhl/story/2012-10-15/nhl-lockout-news-2012-glow-pucks-foxtrax-rfid-chips-instant-replay-soccer</link><title>NHL lockout: Use science to improve game--with a 'glow puck' assist</title><description>Monday October 15, 2012 1:47 pm

... cities to celebrate its retirement from service, NASA has landed the Curiosity probe on Mars, and Felix... ideas to hockey fans right now, there is more for hockey to take from humanity's latest explorative exploits... violation to automatically trigger a sound or a notification to a referee to blow his whistle, the NHL could</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7432-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7432_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:47:30">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2012-02-04/doleman-helps-gridiron-greats</link><title>Doleman helps Gridiron Greats</title><description>Saturday February 4, 2012 2:48 am

... fans bid to have a former NFL star come to an event, with proceeds going to charity. "It shows you how... aspire to being," he said. "How else would these people be able to talk to a Hall of Famer?" Doleman... willing to take to be comfortable. I'm not really worried about jamming my finger and not being able to</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7432-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7432_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:50:05">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2011-12-02/wisconsin-again-standing-in-michigan-states-rose-bowl-path</link><title>Wisconsin again standing in Michigan State's Rose Bowl path</title><description>Friday December 2, 2011 2:39 pm

... but had to stomach UW going to Pasadena. In 2011, MSU is the Big Ten's lone once-beaten team, but now must... directly to the Badgers' hard-to-believe scoring differential of nearly 30 points per game. MSU is motivated... was able to find go-to receiver B.J. Cunningham when he needed to\--Badgers cornerback Antonio Fenelus had</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7432-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7432_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:52:02">http://www.sportingnews.com/nascar/story/2011-06-03/pockys-paddock-internal-discipline-for-kyle-busch-unlikely-to-be-harsh</link><title>Pocky's Paddock: Internal discipline for Kyle Busch unlikely to be harsh</title><description>Friday June 3, 2011 12:00 am

... remains to be seen, but it will be in his best interest to do some goodwill to help lessen the outcry of... NASCAR to open that can of worms. So it's up to the team to make a decision on discipline. Considering... hopes to have another that Raikkonen can run, if he wants to do it, and the two sides can agree to the</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7432-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7432_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:53:53">http://www.sportingnews.com/nascar/story/2010-07-14/nascar-promotion-grocery-chain-success</link><title>NASCAR promotion at grocery chain a success</title><description>Wednesday July 14, 2010 5:26 pm

$30,000 in ticket sales being attributed to Rev Up, which equates to more than 400 tickets sold. Consumers... value back to NASCARs official partners. To encourage its stores to play along, Brookshires created an... they want to see. Its a big boost to be able to tie in with NASCAR and we see increases in the number of</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7432-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7432_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:54:22">http://www.sportingnews.com/nascar/story/2010-05-10/hall-fame-has-openings-for-more-sponsors</link><title>Hall of Fame has openings for more sponsors</title><description>Monday May 10, 2010 3:24 pm

Special to the Sporting News NASCAR Wire Service When customers enter the $200 million NASCAR Hall of... $200,000 to $700,000 annually and go from three to five years in length. NASCAR receives a 10 percent cut... year. Ticket prices range from $12.95 to $19.95. Michael Smith is a reporter with SportsBusiness Journal.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7432-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7432_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:55:57">http://www.sportingnews.com/nascar/story/2009-11-10/nascar-addresses-needs-its-partners</link><title>NASCAR addresses needs of its partners</title><description>Tuesday November 10, 2009 5:22 pm

... programs to freshen its business-to-business council and create more retail opportunities for its consumer... million to $3 million a year.   Its been newfound business that was brought to us on a plate, Coca-Colas... races and ticket sales leading up to events in that area.   NASCAR officials wouldnt divulge the financial</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>