<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7438">facebook privacy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:14:11" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7438-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7438_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:14:12">http://www.sportingnews.com/sport/story/2013-03-18/tiger-woods-lindsey-vonn-dating-girlfriend-boyfriend-photos-facebook-announcemen</link><title>Tiger Woods, Lindsey Vonn confirm they are dating on Facebook</title><description>Monday March 18, 2013 1:21 pm

... announcement on Facebook on Monday. Woods posted a photo album on Facebook titled "Lindsey Vonn and Tiger Woods... respecting our privacy. We want to continue our relationship, privately, as an ordinary couple and continue to</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7438-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7438_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:16:19">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2012-03-27/jonathan-holton-rhode-island-facebook-video-sexual-encounters</link><title>Rhode Island's Jonathan Holton charged with posting sex videos to Facebook</title><description>Tuesday March 27, 2012 3:57 pm

... videos to Facebook. The freshman was arrested by campus police Tuesday and charged with two felony counts... posted to Facebook and forwarded to about 30 people. Holton, 21, was released on personal recognizance and... rights and privacy of all of our community members is paramount. Campus police and Student Affairs are involved</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7438-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7438_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:18:58">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-07-11/bengals-cheerleader-lawsuit-case-sex-posts-cincinnati-defamation</link><title>Ex-Bengals cheerleader wins defamation lawsuit, awarded damages</title><description>Thursday July 11, 2013 10:47 pm

... websites like Facebook because Richie has admitted to screening submissions and adding his own comments, rather... liberties and privacy issues in the digital age. "I think Richie would have very solid grounds for an appeal,"</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7438-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7438_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:20:53">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2013-05-06/jonathan-holton-commits-west-virginia-facebook-video-voyeurism-rhode-island</link><title>West Virginia extends Jonathan Holton a scholarship if he's cleared of felony charges</title><description>Monday May 6, 2013 2:02 pm

... videos to Facebook. Holton's arrest occurred after two female students complained separately to school officials... posted to Facebook and forwarded to about 30 people. "These are disturbing allegations that strike at the... rights and privacy of all of our community members is paramount. Campus police and Student Affairs are involved</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7438-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7438_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:22:19">http://www.sportingnews.com/sport/story/2013-03-25/tiger-woods-no-1-ranking-mouth-win-bay-hill-arnold-palmer-invitational-masters</link><title>Tiger Woods may be No. 1 again, but his mouth gets a zero</title><description>Monday March 25, 2013 5:40 pm

... said. Mr. Privacy would naturally say that, but the Facebook pictures were a further sign of healing. If</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7438-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7438_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:23:41">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2013-01-24/manti-teo-interview-with-katie-couric-is-teo-gay-fake-girlfriend-tuiasosopo</link><title>Manti Te'o interview with Katie Couric: Time to wash off all the gossipy muck</title><description>Thursday January 24, 2013 7:15 pm

... her on Facebook with a sob story about a female cousin being in a car accident and sent her pictures of... protection and privacy laws," O'Meara said on the "Today" show. Maybe there will be something tangible that comes</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7438-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7438_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:25:50">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2012-07-12/nick-saban-daughter-lawsuit-kristen-saban-sorority-fight</link><title>Nick Saban's daughter sued by sorority sister over fight</title><description>Thursday July 12, 2012 2:11 pm

... over a Facebook post after a night of drinking. The lawsuit was filed late last month in Tuscaloosa by... posted to Facebook: "No one likes Sarah! Yayyyyy!" Confronted by Grimes, Kristen Saban deleted the post,... citing privacy rules. The suit said Grimes was hurt so badly she suffered a concussion, an increase in</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7438-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7438_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:27:23">http://www.sportingnews.com/olympics/story/2012-06-07/kenrick-monk-nick-darcy-guns-australia-london-2012-summer-olympics</link><title>Australian swimmers posts photos posing with guns on social media sites</title><description>Thursday June 7, 2012 1:38 pm

... off his Facebook page, also apologized. "I deeply am sorry and I'm sorry if I offended anyone out there,"... thing as privacy on social media. Anything that is put up will be in the public domain." D'Arcy is a medal</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7438-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7438_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:28:54">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2012-04-23/isaac-arzate-boy-12-dies-while-playing-baseball-months-after-surviving-heart-att</link><title>Boy, 12, dies while playing baseball months after surviving heart attack suffered while playing basketball</title><description>Monday April 23, 2012 9:16 pm

... us on Facebook | Follow on Twitter | Circle on Google Plus | Get the iPad app In a statement,... citing privacy laws. Last week, when paramedics responded again to an emergency call from Scott Elementary,... citing privacy laws. The Oregonian reported in January that a vessel stemming from the boy's aorta wound</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7438-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7438_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:31:17">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2012-05-08/defense-in-penn-st-case-digs-into-accusers-pasts</link><title>Defense in Penn St. case digs into accusers' pasts</title><description>Tuesday May 8, 2012 6:36 pm

... histories, Facebook account details, employment-related documents and cellphone and Twitter records. Prosecutors... what the privacy interests are," said Fortunato N. Perri Jr., a Philadelphia defense lawyer and former prosecutor.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>