<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7440">barcelona real madrid</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:46:47" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7440-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7440_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:46:48">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2012-10-18/spanish-league-barcelona-real-madrid-have-defensive-worries</link><title>Spanish league: Barcelona, Real Madrid have defensive worries</title><description>Thursday October 18, 2012 9:46 pm

MADRID \-- Deportivo La Coruna and Celta Vigo will look to capitalize on Barcelona and Real Madrid's defensive... break. Barcelona travels to face Deportivo with an eight-point advantage over Madrid. The Catalan team... Atletico Madrid will look to continue its unbeaten start and stay at the top alongside Barcelona when it</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7440-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7440_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:48:02">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2012-12-19/uefa-champions-league-draw-barcelona-real-madrid</link><title>UEFA Champions League: Spanish powers Barcelona, Real Madrid headline draw</title><description>Wednesday December 19, 2012 12:59 pm

... favorite Barcelona and nine-time European champion Real Madrid are among nine former winners in the last-16... Arsenal, Barcelona, Bayern and Madrid. United returns to the last 16 after its group-stage elimination... Unseeded clubs: AC Milan, Arsenal, Celtic, Galatasaray, Porto, Real Madrid, Shakhtar Donetsk, Valencia.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7440-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7440_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:49:02">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2012-11-08/spanish-league-barcelona-real-madrid-aim-to-rebound-from-champions-league-flops</link><title>Spanish league: Barcelona, Real Madrid aim to rebound from Champions League flops</title><description>Thursday November 8, 2012 4:06 pm

BARCELONA, Spain -- Barcelona and Real Madrid will look to rebound from disappointing Champions League... 2-2 at Madrid on Wednesday. Barcelona is enjoying a club-record start of nine wins and a draw to open... champion Madrid. Second-place Atletico Madrid is three points adrift of Barcelona and hosts Getafe on Sunday</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7440-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7440_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:51:21">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2013-04-12/bayern-munich-to-face-barcelona-real-madrid-draws-dortmund-in-champions-league-s</link><title>Bayern to face Barcelona, Real Madrid draws Dortmund in Champions League semifinals</title><description>Friday April 12, 2013 7:24 am

... will face Barcelona in the semifinals of the Champions League, while Real Madrid has been paired with Borussia... Meanwhile, Barcelona, semifinalists for the sixth year in a row, is seeking its third Champions League title... former Barcelona player and manager Pep Guardiola's old side against the one he is set to take over at</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7440-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7440_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:52:37">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2014-02-12/lionel-messi-cristiano-ronaldo-real-madrid-barcelona-copa-del-rey-final</link><title>From Civil War to Messi's tears: Barcelona and Madrid's Copa del Rey finals</title><description>Wednesday February 12, 2014 7:21 pm

Real Madrid 3-3 Barcelona. The Copa del Rey has produced six Clasico finals in its 112-year history and... Barca beat Real Sociedad 3-1 on aggregate to join Madrid in April's big cup clash. On Tuesday night, Carlo... meeting with Madrid on April 19, sealing their spot in the showpiece thanks to a 1-1 draw at Real Sociedad on</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7440-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7440_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:54:04">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2014-02-22/real-madrid-spain-la-ligaclub-history</link><title>Ancelotti's Madrid on second best run in club history</title><description>Saturday February 22, 2014 2:03 pm

Ancelotti's Real Madrid has impressed in 2013-14 and the Blancos' 3-0 win at home to lowly Elche on Saturday... September. Then Madrid went down to its fiercest foe, Barcelona, in a 2-1 defeat at Camp Nou a little less than... past two Madrid players. Despite that disappointment, the Dutchman led Madrid to La Liga and the Copa del</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7440-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7440_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:56:13">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2013-03-14/spanish-league-preview-barcelona-targets-real-madrids-point-record</link><title>Spanish league preview: Barcelona targets Real Madrid's point record</title><description>Thursday March 14, 2013 12:33 pm

BARCELONA, Spain -- Back on track in Europe, Barcelona will return to chasing history in the Spanish league with Real Madrid's point record still in reach. Barcelona is well on its way to dethroning Madrid for... Atletico Madrid, which visits Osasuna on Sunday. Madrid ended Barcelona's three-year reign of the domestic</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7440-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7440_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 18:59:06">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2014-02-18/yaya-toure-manchester-city-barcelona-champions-league-epl</link><title>Why Barcelona decided to sell Yaya Toure</title><description>Tuesday February 18, 2014 11:59 am

... subject in Barcelona right now. However, with the Catalans taking on Manchester City in the Champions League,... stayed at Barcelona. I did not want to go and wanted to end my career at Barcelona. However, he had no faith... transfer to Real Madrid in 2012 by explaining that such a move would be unthinkable given he still considered</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7440-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7440_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:01:19">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2013-03-03/spanish-league-real-madrid-beats-barcelona-prepares-for-manchester-united</link><title>Spanish league: Real Madrid beats Barcelona, prepares for Manchester United</title><description>Sunday March 3, 2013 12:47 pm

MADRID \-- Real Madrid beat Barcelona for the second time in five days, a 2-1 win Saturday that will do... arguments from Barcelona players. Defending Spanish league champion Real Madrid (17-5-4) pulled within 13 points of first-place Barcelona (22-2-2) and within one point of second-place Atletico Madrid (18-5-2). Real won 3-1</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7440-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7440_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:02:48">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2014-02-16/manchester-city-barcelona-uefa-champions-league</link><title>Dominant Manchester City gave itself boost before Barcelona match</title><description>Sunday February 16, 2014 9:59 pm

... view. Barcelona, with a resurgent Lionel Messi, is next up at the Etihad, which had been somewhat of... to the Real Madrid incarnation. Spiky, curt, defensive. He had just watched his side lose deservedly.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>