<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7441">barcelona real madrid goal messi</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:04:45" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7441-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7441_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:04:46">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2014-02-12/lionel-messi-cristiano-ronaldo-real-madrid-barcelona-copa-del-rey-final</link><title>From Civil War to Messi's tears: Barcelona and Madrid's Copa del Rey finals</title><description>Wednesday February 12, 2014 7:21 pm

Real Madrid 3-3 Barcelona. The Copa del Rey has produced six Clasico finals in its 112-year history and... Barca beat Real Sociedad 3-1 on aggregate to join Madrid in April's big cup clash. On Tuesday night, Carlo... single goal after advancing with a 5-0 aggregate win over last year's winner Atletico. But Barcelona's</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7441-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7441_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:06:46">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2014-02-10/lionel-messi-barcelona-cristiano-ronaldo-real-madrid-la-liga</link><title>Cristiano who? Messi back in business as rival takes a break</title><description>Monday February 10, 2014 10:58 am

Lionel Messi. Had he really lost his passion for football? Barcelona's former assistant coach Angel Cappa... well. Messi dropped deep into midfield to look for the ball as Barcelona enjoyed the early possession... looked like Messi had lost his passion at all. "I would never risk speaking ill of Messi," Gerardo Martino</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7441-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7441_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:08:19">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2013-09-28/lionel-messi-barcelona-real-madrid-scoring-record</link><title>Messi has scored more goals than any player in the history of Real Madrid</title><description>Saturday September 28, 2013 1:03 pm

Lionel Messi has now scored more competitive goals than any player in the entire history of Real Madrid... fantastic goal at Almeria on Saturday has now seen him surpass the former Madrid favorite. Messi's 324 strikes... goals for Real Madrid came in 741 games over 16 seasons at the Santiago Bernabeu. Messi, meanwhile, has hit</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7441-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7441_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:09:09">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2013-08-18/messi-barcelona-neymar-levante-la-liga-spain</link><title>Messi scores twice as Barcelona takes impressive win over Levante</title><description>Sunday August 18, 2013 3:58 pm

BARCELONA, Spain -- Lionel Messi scored two goals and set up another Sunday to help mark the debut of... scoring, Messi claimed Barcelona's second goal, stole possession to create the third, and passed for Pedro... letting Messi drill in the spot kick in the 41st. Xavi poked in the sixth goal in the 45th. Barcelona</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7441-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7441_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:10:36">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2013-05-05/messi-barcelona-betis-two-goals</link><title>Messi returns, scores two in Barcelona win</title><description>Sunday May 5, 2013 6:22 pm

... the 60-goal mark in all competitions for the second straight season. "We know Messi is the best," Barcelona... champion Real Madrid drops points against Malaga on Wednesday. Messi has been hampered for the past month... Bilbao, Messi looked fit enough as he again tilted the match in Barcelona's favor. Messi's double gave</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7441-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7441_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:12:04">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2013-03-03/spanish-league-real-madrid-beats-barcelona-prepares-for-manchester-united</link><title>Spanish league: Real Madrid beats Barcelona, prepares for Manchester United</title><description>Sunday March 3, 2013 12:47 pm

MADRID \-- Real Madrid beat Barcelona for the second time in five days, a 2-1 win Saturday that will do... Benzema put Real Madrid ahead in the sixth minute off a cross from 20-year-old Alvaro Morata, but Lionel Messi... his 18th goal in the clasico rivalry, Messi tied the record set by Real's Alfredo Di Stefano in the 1950s</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7441-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7441_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:12:31">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2013-10-02/lionel-messi-barcelona-uefa-champions-league-spain-la-liga</link><title>Barcelona searching for answers when missing Messi</title><description>Wednesday October 2, 2013 10:23 am

Barcelona was happy in the end. Cesc Fabregas headed home to hand the Catalan club a second-straight... Lionel Messi missing through injury, this team still struggles. The Argentine attacker limped off just... former Real Madrid boss Jose Mourinho told Andres Iniesta last season as he hit back from criticism over</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7441-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7441_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:13:23">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2013-03-09/lionel-messi-scores-in-barcelona-win-before-milan-match</link><title>Lionel Messi scores in Barcelona win before Milan match</title><description>Saturday March 9, 2013 6:05 pm

BARCELONA, Spain-- Lionel Messi extended his Spanish league record by scoring in 17 straight games to cap Barcelona's 2-0 win over last-place Deportivo La Coruna on Saturday. Messi started on the Camp... finish of Barcelona's 2-1 loss at Real Madrid last weekend. Even with the lineup shuffle, the 51-point gap</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7441-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7441_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:15:12">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2012-10-18/spanish-league-barcelona-real-madrid-have-defensive-worries</link><title>Spanish league: Barcelona, Real Madrid have defensive worries</title><description>Thursday October 18, 2012 9:46 pm

MADRID \-- Deportivo La Coruna and Celta Vigo will look to capitalize on Barcelona and Real Madrid's defensive... break. Barcelona travels to face Deportivo with an eight-point advantage over Madrid. The Catalan team... Lionel Messi, who has scored 12 goals for Barcelona this season, continued his early season scoring spree</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7441-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7441_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:17:05">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2014-02-16/manchester-city-barcelona-uefa-champions-league</link><title>Dominant Manchester City gave itself boost before Barcelona match</title><description>Sunday February 16, 2014 9:59 pm

... front of goal and the creativity were totally absent. City was given an unexpected boost, too, by sneaking... view. Barcelona, with a resurgent Lionel Messi, is next up at the Etihad, which had been somewhat of... to the Real Madrid incarnation. Spiky, curt, defensive. He had just watched his side lose deservedly.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>