<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7445">marathon training</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:56:50" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7445-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7445_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:56:53">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2014-02-04/alan-faneca-former-lineman-nfl-runs-marathon-new-orleans-rock-and-roll-cardinals-steelers</link><title>Former NFL lineman drops 100 lbs., runs marathon in under four hours</title><description>Tuesday February 4, 2014 7:36 pm

... running a marathon. After speaking to some of his former Steel City teammates, Faneca decided to register... &amp; Roll Marathon and began training intensively. Faneca weighed in at 320 lbs. during his playing days,... finishing a marathon, etc. but he looks about 65 years old now... pic.twitter.com/QagqWVXa0C  Jeremy Dorn</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7445-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7445_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:59:03">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2014-02-24/weekend-sports-in-brief</link><title>Weekend Sports In Brief</title><description>Monday February 24, 2014 5:23 am

... spring training in Florida. TAMPA, Fla. (AP) - Outfielder Brett Gardner and the New York Yankees agreed... spring training instructor The Giants say Bonds is expected to arrive during the second week of March.... Tokyo Marathon on Sunday in a race record time of 2 hours, 5 minutes, 42 seconds. ALBUQUERQUE, N.M.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7445-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7445_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:00:41">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2014-02-13/jackson-warriors-feeling-pressure-of-expectations</link><title>Jackson, Warriors feeling pressure of expectations</title><description>Thursday February 13, 2014 4:13 pm

NBA's marathon season enters the stretch run. The Warriors (31-22), who talked about contending for... title in training camp, are tied for the final playoff spot entering the All-Star break. While they're one</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7445-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7445_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:03:17">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-04-12/soldier-honored-for-shadow-marathon-in-iraq</link><title>Soldier honored for 'shadow marathon' in Iraq</title><description>Friday April 12, 2013 10:07 pm

Freeman was training for the 2005 Boston Marathon when his New Hampshire Army National Guard unit shipped out... "shadow marathon" at their military base outside Nasiriyah, Iraq. "At that time, Iraq wasn't a very friendly... run on Marathon Monday and sent off an email to the B.A.A. to let them know his plan. The marathon organizers</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7445-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7445_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:06:00">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2013-10-31/boston-rejoices-in-world-series-victory-at-home</link><title>Boston rejoices in World Series victory at home</title><description>Thursday October 31, 2013 4:26 am

Boston Marathon. The morning after he cheered the victory inside Fenway Park, Ed Carlson returned Thursday to the marathon finish line he had crossed months earlier, 20 minutes before the bombs went off, and then... at the marathon and then to be there for the World Series - I still tear up thinking about it." The success</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7445-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7445_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:06:52">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2012-11-02/nyc-marathon-off-wade-donates-to-relief-effort</link><title>NYC Marathon off, Wade donates to relief effort</title><description>Friday November 2, 2012 7:52 pm

York City Marathon is off, and a marathon ride into the city prompted Dwyane Wade to help those still dealing... of the marathon on Friday, just hours after insisting that the race needed to be run Sunday as scheduled... affect the marathon, and some of those registered to run on Sunday were being urged to donate their rooms</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7445-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7445_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:08:28">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2013-09-17/how-roy-williams-presence-helped-charity-event-explode-north-carolina-basketball</link><title>How Roy Williams' presence helped charity event explode</title><description>Tuesday September 17, 2013 12:26 pm

... already was training for an October marathon, planned the event to help her friend Amy Louthan pay for medical... running a marathon that day, but Williams' presence also helped. Cash donations and money raised from a barbeque</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7445-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7445_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:11:08">http://www.sportingnews.com/sport/story/2011-10-10/woman-gives-birth-after-running-chicago-marathon</link><title>Woman gives birth after completing Chicago Marathon</title><description>Monday October 10, 2011 7:26 pm

... first marathon while pregnant. In May, the Westchester woman ran the Wisconsin Marathon in 4:23:07 while... weeks. Marathon world-record holder Paula Radcliffe ran 14 miles a day while pregnant and resumed training... starting marathon training for the first time. For pregnant runners, close monitoring by a doctor is recommended.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7445-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7445_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:12:49">http://www.sportingnews.com/sport/story/2012-11-02/hurricane-sandy-fallout-marathon-canceled-relief-efforts-get-up-and-running</link><title>Hurricane Sandy fallout: Marathon canceled, relief efforts get up and running</title><description>Friday November 2, 2012 7:18 pm

York City Marathon is off, and a marathon ride into the city prompted Dwyane Wade to help those still dealing... of the marathon on Friday, just hours after insisting that the race needed to be run Sunday as scheduled... affect the marathon, and some of those registered to run on Sunday were being urged to donate their rooms</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7445-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7445_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:15:20">http://www.sportingnews.com/nhl/story/2012-11-18/ian-laperriere-marathon-philadelphia-flyers-post-concussion-syndrome</link><title>Ian Laperriere runs Philadelphia Marathon, still feels effects of puck to face</title><description>Sunday November 18, 2012 7:21 pm

Philadelphia Marathon in 3 hours, 42 minutes, 23 seconds on Sunday. "Running is the one thing I can do," he... started training. "I wanted to do (a marathon)," Laperriere said. "It's something inside me. "I need to</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>