<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7446">cycling on the mont ventoux</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:16:54" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7446-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7446_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:16:55">http://www.sportingnews.com/sport/story/2013-07-21/chris-froome-rides-to-victory-in-100th-tour-de-france</link><title>Chris Froome rides to victory in 100th Tour de France</title><description>Sunday July 21, 2013 1:55 pm

... later on the cobbles of the Champs-Elysees as the sun cast golden hues over the peloton and the shadows... until the pace picked up sharply on the Champs-Elysees. Marcel Kittel won the final sprint on that famous... suffocate the race. Froome's three stage victories -- in the Pyrenees, on Mont Ventoux in Provence and in</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7446-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7446_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:17:41">http://www.sportingnews.com/sport/story/2013-07-21/tour-de-france-a-look-at-how-chris-froome-won</link><title>Tour de France: A look at how Chris Froome won</title><description>Sunday July 21, 2013 5:28 pm

... later on in the stage, when organizers changed the finish line area at the last minute because a team... Once the race hit the high mountains of the Pyrenees, Froome launched a devastating attack on the last... burst on the last climb up Mont Ventoux in Provence, one of the Tour's most famed climbs. Froome showed</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7446-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7446_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:18:39">http://www.sportingnews.com/sport/story/2013-06-27/tour-de-france-2013-numbers-to-know-for-races-100th-year</link><title>Tour de France 2013: Numbers to know for race's 100th year</title><description>Thursday June 27, 2013 12:49 pm

The iconic yellow jersey will be up for grabs once again when the Tour de France begins on June 29. ... begin the race in Corsica but it is unlikely that all of them will be there for the finish on the Champs-Elysees... will be the longest at 242.km. The riders will race from Givors to Mont Ventoux on July 14. 35 --The</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7446-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7446_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:20:24">http://www.sportingnews.com/sport/story/2013-06-27/tour-de-france-2013-stage-by-stage-guide</link><title>Tour de France 2013: Stage-by-stage guide</title><description>Thursday June 27, 2013 12:43 pm

... tracks the exact route the riders will be confronted with in the 100th edition of the race: Stage 1:... Stage 5: The longest stage of the Tour to date takes place on the fifth day. From Cagnes-sur-Mer to Marseille presents the riders with 228.5km on largely flat surfaces. Expect the lead men to hold the advantage for</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7446-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7446_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:21:10">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2012-07-14/friday-s-sports-in-brief</link><title>Friday's Sports in Brief</title><description>Saturday July 14, 2012 5:25 am

... million the first year, the person told The Associated Press on condition of anonymity because financial... Simpson, the first Briton to wear yellow, died on the slopes of the Mont Ventoux after using a lethal mix... Dolgopolov in the semifinals of the Croatia Open on Saturday. For the first time since the inaugural tournament</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>