<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7448">running shoes boston</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:41:28" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7448-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7448_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:41:29">http://www.sportingnews.com/sport/story/2013-05-04/triple-crown-kentucky-derby-2013-churchill-downs-rick-pitino-wet-mud-adds-bettin</link><title>Kentucky Derby 2013: Churchill Downs hums ahead of 139th Run for the Roses</title><description>Saturday May 4, 2013 5:36 pm

139th running of the Kentucky Derby: QUICK QUOTE: RICK PITINO "You think about it: A state of 3 million... to his shoes, with one exception -- socks covered in sometimes neon-colored daisies. "They give me a... at the Boston Marathon last month. Kentucky National Guardsmen searched bags and passed metal detecting</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7448-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7448_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:42:06">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2008-03-03/all-shoes-to-fill-team-offense</link><title>All-Shoes-To-Fill Team: Offense</title><description>Tuesday March 4, 2008 4:51 am

... offensive All-Shoes-To-Fill Team. On Wednesday, I'll unveil a defensive All-Shoes-To-Fill Team. WR Malcolm Kelly,... Ryan, Boston College. Chris Crane will get first crack at leading the Eagle attack. But he figures to... other running back with more than one carry. RB Rashard Mendenhall, Illinois. Troy Pollard, Daniel</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7448-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7448_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:43:25">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2012-06-28/nba-draft-2012-picks-recap-results-anthony-davis-thomas-robinson-bradley-beal</link><title>NBA Draft 2012: Pick-by-pick recap, analysis</title><description>Thursday June 28, 2012 6:35 pm

6-5 in shoes, so certainly he is tall enough to be considered to play shooting guard in the NBA. If he... Carolina's running game. He is an extremely capable shooter from the elbow, which makes sense given that... website. 21. Boston Celtics. Jared Sullinger, Ohio State. Wide-bodied players with limited athleticism lately</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7448-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7448_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:43:52">http://www.sportingnews.com/olympics/story/2012-06-14/karl-towns-london-2012-summer-olympics-kentucky-basketball-dominican-national-te</link><title>Young but wise phenom Karl Towns has Dirk Nowitzki's game</title><description>Thursday June 14, 2012 3:00 pm

We're running plays with shot-clock, and you've got pressure down your throat." As a freshman at St.... size 20 shoes, suggesting he still might have room to grow. As he gains strength with age and training,... run the Boston Marathon. "As a bench, we haven't played in a while. I went out strong and came out really</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7448-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7448_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:45:09">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2012-06-14/karl-towns-kentucky-basketball-dominican-national-team-prep-phenom-john-calipari</link><title>Young but wise phenom Karl Towns has Dirk Nowitzki's game</title><description>Thursday June 14, 2012 2:17 pm

We're running plays with shot-clock, and you've got pressure down your throat." As a freshman at St.... size 20 shoes, suggesting he still might have room to grow. As he gains strength with age and training,... run the Boston Marathon. "As a bench, we haven't played in a while. I went out strong and came out really</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7448-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7448_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:46:04">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2012-05-14/chris-bosh-injury-strained-abdominal-muscle-miami-heat-lebron-james-dwyane-wade</link><title>Chris Bosh's injury casts doubt on Miami Heat's championship aspirations</title><description>Monday May 14, 2012 1:58 pm

... plague running through the NBA playoffs. Wrong. Chris Bosh caught the bug Sunday in Game 1 of the East... by the Boston Celtics, assuming they can beat the Philadelphia 76ers. The Heat are not going to beat... now.) The shoes Bosh leaves to fill are way too big, even though he gets far too little credit. The rest</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7448-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7448_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:47:24">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2012-04-27/colts-take-stanford-qb-andrew-luck-to-open-draft</link><title>Colts take Stanford QB Andrew Luck to open draft</title><description>Saturday April 28, 2012 12:00 am

... really. Huge shoes to try and fill if you're trying to do that. ... If one day I can be mentioned alongside... getting running back Trent Richardson of national champion Alabama. Minnesota received picks in the fourth,... selected Boston College linebacker Luke Kuechly, the nation's leading tackler. Buffalo chose cornerback</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7448-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7448_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:49:15">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2012-01-29/kyrie-irving-redeems-himself-finishes-off-celtics</link><title>Kyrie Irving redeems himself, finishes off Celtics</title><description>Sunday January 29, 2012 10:12 pm

BOSTON\--It was a month ago, on the road against the Pacers, that Cavaliers rookie Kyrie Irving had an... clock running down, Irving used a high screen from center Anderson Varejao, bolted into the paint and... went to Boston University), and some childhood friends, Irving was in a similar situation--ball in his</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7448-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7448_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:50:28">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2012-01-29/thunder-top-warriors-120-109-to-start-road-trip</link><title>Thunder top Warriors 120-109 to start road trip</title><description>Monday January 30, 2012 12:00 am

... black shoes. "See this tension in the locker room?" Durant said, smiling at a small group of reporters... Westbrook's running layup extended Oklahoma City's lead to 85-77 entering the final period, and the Warriors... chest running back on defense, waving to fans and taunting his one-time Thunder teammates. The celebration</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7448-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7448_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:52:40">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2011-08-28/college-footballs-best-luck-lattimore-lead-the-way</link><title>College football's best: Luck, Lattimore lead the way</title><description>Sunday August 28, 2011 11:12 am

Broncos running back Doug Martin says. "Calm and cool. Nothing fazes him. Smart guy, talented player; he... Award (running backs) Winner: Marcus Lattimore, Soph., South Carolina The Ol' Ball Coach wasn't afraid... yards of running, 50 yards up and 50 yards back, and we do a certain number of those. It gets you in shape</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>