<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7457">the music man lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:03:14" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7457-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7457_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:03:15">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2014-02-14/mlb-2014-mvp-cy-young-rookie-eric-church-outsiders-clayton-kershaw-yasiel-puig</link><title>'The Outsiders' guide to MLB's 2014 awards</title><description>Friday February 14, 2014 4:42 pm

... dive in. The album begins with the titular track, and a twang of a guitar, and the lyrics: "They're the... victories the past two years seemed to be on the basis of the Detroit Tigers making the playoffs and the... comes to the Rookie of the Year. The lead candidates in the American League this year seem pretty easily</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7457-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7457_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:05:21">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2014-01-23/nl-east-justin-bieber-arrested-dui-drag-racing-nationals-braves-mets-marlins-phillies</link><title>NL East 2014: Like Justin Bieber, this race might be a drag</title><description>Thursday January 23, 2014 3:44 pm

... to cut the Mets' deficit to a run. That's the clinching game of the World Series, and here's where the... sea, but the general ideas work, like the carrier picking the Yankees up for free and no mention of the... about the Mets that resonate through the culture, although if you haven't seen the 1986 music video "Let's</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7457-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7457_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:06:13">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-08-13/parker-looks-to-emerge-from-tough-year-in-big-easy</link><title>Parker looks to emerge from tough year in Big Easy</title><description>Tuesday August 13, 2013 4:28 am

... heart for the game and for the opportunity." The fourth-year pro is back in the NFL and showing signs that... one with the Saints and one with the New York Jets - for the rest of 2012. Although the Saints decided... who said the first TD on a hard, low throw to the back of the end zone was "as difficult a catch as you're</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7457-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7457_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:08:12">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2009-04-20/cavs-smith-mixes-hoops-music</link><title>Cavs' Smith mixes hoops, music</title><description>Tuesday April 21, 2009 12:36 am

... back on the quest for a title," Smith rhymed, spitting out the words while keeping the beat in his head.... ... See the president, 'Bron James the King; and Anderson Varejao, they call him the Wild Thing. ..." ... It was the type of hustle play the Cavs have come to expect from Smith, who returned to the Cavs in March</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7457-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7457_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:10:08">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2012-09-02/proud-psu-fans-show-strength-support-lions-lose</link><title>Proud PSU fans show strength, support; Lions lose</title><description>Monday September 3, 2012 12:00 am

... football. By the end, as the Nittany Lions trudged off the field, a battered fan base would need at least another... ready for "the next chapter." When the team arrived at the stadium, O'Brien, the former offensive coordinator... roars for the players as they exited the bus. Clearly, the fans showed they will stand by the players that</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7457-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7457_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:11:46">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2008-10-14/jets-jones-leader-field-and-music-biz</link><title>Jets' Jones a leader on field and in music biz</title><description>Tuesday October 14, 2008 9:57 pm

... knows the right thing to say to get the team going and get everybody in the right mind-set to take care... I'm in the locker room and on the field, I like to be vocal with the guys," he said, "because I know what... always the one calling us up, breaking the team down. After a tough loss, he's the first one to speak</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7457-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7457_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:12:35">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/feed/2010-09/nfl-labor-talks/story/nfl-lockout-got-you-bummed-sporting-news-lists-100-reasons-to-love-the-game</link><title>NFL lockout got you bummed? Sporting News lists 100 reasons to love the game</title><description>Monday May 30, 2011 3:24 pm

... love of the game wins out over the love of money. 2. We love that for all the consternation about the... important a man in the NFL today as he was with the Packers in 1992. 30. We love the genius of Bill Belichick... Films. The old-school highlights. Ed and Steve Sabol. The music. The old uniforms. The mud. The classic</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7457-08"><link>http://aol.sportingnews.com/125/story/2011-01-17/sn-conversation-everybody-was-a-bears-fan-back-then</link><title>SN Conversation: 'Everybody was a Bears fan back then'</title><description>Monday January 17, 2011 3:20 pm

... immortality. You, the fan, can vote for the NFL's Greatest Team. Monday's voting concluded with the first round and... to that music. But it stuck. DENT: The Shuffle, man. When I first heard the beat, I said, "That's a pretty... throwing the ball off the side of his foot. When he throws the ball outside the numbers, he tries to do</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7457-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7457_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:15:43">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2010-01-29/louisiana-players-living-dream-saints</link><title>Louisiana players living dream with Saints</title><description>Saturday January 30, 2010 1:00 am

... know, the Saints don't go to the playoffs,"' he recalled. "I was like, 'I've been in the playoffs every... heads in the Superdome. They heard about how the lovable losers from New Orleans wouldn't win the Super... Blow the whistle. So official. Our screaming fans. The 12th man. Soon after, he got the call to join</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7457-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7457_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:17:46">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2007-12-28/big-fav-gets-lyrical-about-bcs-championship-his-hometown</link><title>Big Fav gets lyrical about BCS championship in his hometown</title><description>Friday December 28, 2007 11:18 pm

... reverence for the Louisiana Superdome, home to the NFL's Saints, the Sugar Bowl and six Super Bowls. During... Most of the fans in the dome wore LSU purple and gold when the Tigers defeated the Green Wave 34-9. That... out in the lyrics in my song, the emotion I have for New Orleans," Favorite said, before offering the</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>