<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7482">popular twitter stars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:05:52" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7482-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7482_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:05:55">http://www.sportingnews.com/fantasy/mlb/story/2014-02-11/biogenesis-steroids-suspension-ryan-braun-everth-cabrera-nelson-cruz-jhonny-peralta-bartolo-colon-melky-cabrera-yasmani-grandal</link><title>Biogenesis Boys come with considerable risk for fantasy baseball owners</title><description>Tuesday February 11, 2014 9:11 am

... suspension via Twitter \-- and antagonizing accusers and skeptics along the way -- Rodgers went so far as to bet... including All-Stars Nelson Cruz , Jhonny Peralta and Everth Cabrera . The Yankees' Alex Rodriguez had... which stars had been cheating, much less how they performed after getting caught -- until 2013. Melky</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7482-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7482_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:06:22">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2014-02-11/duke-vs-north-carolina-marcus-smart-fans-yelling-casey-prather-wiggins-tip-in</link><title>Starting 5: North Carolina facing potential beat Duke-or-die situation</title><description>Tuesday February 11, 2014 6:24 pm

... playing like stars. That always helps. MORE: Emotions (and elbows) run high among Duke, UNC managers The... follows my Twitter feed knows thats not the case for me. Im still a ticket-buying fan of the Steelers, Penguins... fuss on Twitter of Andrew Wiggins tip-in to force overtime at Kansas State. More overhype for the Kansas</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7482-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7482_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:07:30">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2014-01-31/remembering-what-stern-did-and-how-he-did-it</link><title>Remembering what Stern did, and how he did it</title><description>Friday January 31, 2014 4:32 am

... most NBA stars. But try to find an NBA legacy more lasting than David Stern's. The game is about the players,... the most popular in the world, a $5.5 billion industry with the highest-paid team athletes in sports. Now... contributed to this report. --- Follow Brian Mahoney on Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/Briancmahoney</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7482-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7482_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:09:13">http://www.sportingnews.com/nba/story/2014-01-23/4-first-timers-voted-to-start-nba-all-star-game</link><title>4 first-timers voted to start NBA All-Star game</title><description>Thursday January 23, 2014 8:30 pm

NBA All-Stars Thursday, putting four first-time starters in the Feb. 16 game in New Orleans. Bryant was... "Hey, I'm popular now," Love joked. "It's very humbling to me to be starting in the All-Star game. I tip... contributed to this report. --- Follow Brian Mahoney on Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/Briancmahoney</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7482-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7482_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:11:06">http://www.sportingnews.com/nascar/story/2013-10-30/jeff-gordon-fans-cheers-martinsville-win-popular-boos-dale-earnhardt-hendrick</link><title>Once hated, Jeff Gordon becoming a fan favorite</title><description>Wednesday October 30, 2013 1:53 pm

... beating such popular stars as Dale Earnhardt and Rusty Wallace, fans quickly turned on him. Though he carried... no most popular driver awards  he never has  and, through no fault of his own, became the sports biggest... traditional stars as Richard Petty, David Pearson, Bobby Allison, Darrell Waltrip, Earnhardt and the rest.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7482-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7482_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:12:20">http://www.sportingnews.com/nascar/story/2012-11-30/dale-earnhardt-jr-vs-danica-patrick-nascar-most-popular-driver-award</link><title>Dale Earnhardt Jr. vs. Danica Patrick: Could Danica unseat Junior as most popular?</title><description>Friday November 30, 2012 9:34 am

NASCAR Most Popular Driver award Thursday. The mark for consecutive awards ties NASCAR legend Bill Elliott,... 16 most popular awards. But Earnhardt knows his streak could end at any time. And he knows there is one... NASCAR's most popular stars. With more than 670,000 Twitter followers, she has attracted a big following, especially</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7482-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7482_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:13:49">http://www.sportingnews.com/nascar/story/2013-07-05/tony-stewart-soda-cookies-commercial-stretching-mobil-1-male-gymnast</link><title>Tony Stewart didn't do stretching in "Ësoda cookies' commercial</title><description>Friday July 5, 2013 4:34 pm

... in his popular Mobil 1/soda cookies commercial, he didn't. Stewart had a male gymnast do his stretching... which also stars Formula One star Jensen Button, Stewart is shown stretching on a carpet in his living room.... commentary on Twitter. He says he never reads scripts beforehand because he would never remember them. "I get</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7482-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7482_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:14:56">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-04-27/10-things-to-know-about-nfl-draft</link><title>10 things to know about NFL draft</title><description>Saturday April 27, 2013 10:59 am

... were not popular in the first round, and not too popular in the second- and third-rounds, either. After... course, stars such as Tom Brady, Drew Brees and even Russell Wilson weren't first-rounders, either. 8.... six first-rounders. --- Follow Richard Rosenblatt on Twitter at: http://www.twitter.com/rosenblattap</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7482-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7482_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:16:03">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-04-27/10-things-to-know-about-the-nfl-draft</link><title>10 things to know about the NFL draft</title><description>Saturday April 27, 2013 4:21 am

... were not popular in the first round, and not too popular in the second- and third-rounds, either. After... course, stars such as Tom Brady, Drew Brees and even Russell Wilson weren't first-rounders, either. 1.... six first-rounders. --- Follow Richard Rosenblatt on Twitter at: http://www.twitter.com/rosenblattap</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7482-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7482_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:16:46">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2013-04-01/bracketracket-last-4-ware-s-injury-odds-galore</link><title>BracketRacket: Last 4, Ware's injury, odds galore</title><description>Monday April 1, 2013 4:59 am

... biggest rock stars at the time. With Chris Webber, Jalen Rose, Juwan Howard, Ray Jackson and Jimmy King, the... angle. On Twitter and Reddit, the reaction was swift, wide reaching and prolonged. Twitter hashtags "PrayforWare"... for The Associated Press in Honolulu. He can be reached on Twitter at http://twitter.com/oskargarcia</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>