<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7486">board games teenagers</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:38:45" name="Sporting news" id="FW14-e165"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e165-7486-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7486_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:38:46">http://www.sportingnews.com/nhl/story/2013-04-28/nhl-playoffs-2013-matchups-west-blues-kings-kevin-shattenkirk-alex-pietrangelo</link><title>NHL playoffs: For Blues' Kevin Shattenkirk, progress is passion</title><description>Sunday April 28, 2013 9:00 am

... least 30 games this season. "He was drafted and projected as an offensive player, and I think the one thing... seven games. "I've played against him a bunch in Colorado and St. Louis, and he's a solid player back... on the board, it's no secret we want to key on him and make it tough for him. "The biggest compliment</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7486-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7486_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:39:58">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2013-03-16/friday-s-sports-in-brief</link><title>Friday's Sports In Brief</title><description>Saturday March 16, 2013 5:25 am

... in 132 games with Detroit last season. He was released by the Tigers on Wednesday. New York will be without... Three teenagers granted immunity from prosecution have testified that a 16-year-old girl who says she... executive board. Squash and wrestling are among the sports that will make presentations to the IOC board</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7486-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7486_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:42:25">http://www.sportingnews.com/mlb/story/2012-10-15/matheny-grateful-giants-treated-concussion-trouble</link><title>LCS notebook: Matheny grateful Giants treated concussion trouble</title><description>Monday October 15, 2012 9:28 pm

1,305 games for Milwaukee (1994-98), Toronto (1999), St. Louis (2000-04) and the Giants (2005-06). He... across the board. And I think people are starting to get to the point to realize this is a brain injury. And... two were teenagers and Babe Ruth opponents on the baseball field. Descalso believes Crawford on all of</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7486-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7486_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:43:33">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-basketball/story/2012-10-22/gorgui-dieng-louisville-cardinals-center-ncaa-tournament-big-east-rick-pitino</link><title>Louisville center Gorgui Dieng enjoying basketball, life with Cardinals</title><description>Monday October 22, 2012 11:07 am

... other teenagers in similar situations. Even with the language barrier, he left an impression on people.... to the board and write his answer. Outside of class, Dieng found other ways to communicate. Edwards was... school games, Louisville coach Rick Pitino tried to gauge Dieng's interest in going to Louisville. Dieng</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7486-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7486_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:44:43">http://www.sportingnews.com/olympics/story/2012-07-31/olympics-2012-us-womens-gymnastics-gold-medal-results-jordyn-wieber-gabby-dougla</link><title>Olympics 2012: U.S. women's gymnastics claims team gold as Jordyn Wieber bounces back</title><description>Tuesday July 31, 2012 1:14 pm

Summer Games. Team members of the U.S., which led the competition from the start, held hands as they... Some teenagers might find that pressure tough to bear, but the Americans reveled in it. When they saw... takeoff board, back handspring onto the table and 2.5 twisting somersaults before landing. It's got a start</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7486-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7486_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:46:18">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/story/2012-06-27/column-pay-for-play-should-be-in-football-playoff</link><title>Column: Pay for play should be in football playoff</title><description>Wednesday June 27, 2012 8:47 pm

... semifinal games around New Year's, a move that gives them some traditional roots and should be a ratings... added games, but mostly stems from the insatiable appetite for televised sports and the increased competition... room and board. While their coaches make additional millions, players get tuition and a pat on the back.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7486-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7486_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:48:25">http://www.sportingnews.com/soccer/story/2012-07-20/don-garber-mls-commissioner-sporting-news-conversation</link><title>Don Garber, MLS commissioner, discusses state of league in SN Conversation</title><description>Friday July 20, 2012 9:36 pm

11-member board of directors). It's chaired by Dave Richards, who's the chairman of the (English) Premier... investing in teenagers in the development academy and we've got the senior teams, but there really isn't anywhere... those games. It's perhaps providing them with some flexibility with their rosters. There's a number of</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7486-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7486_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:50:20">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2012-06-27/tuesday-s-sports-in-brief</link><title>Tuesday's Sports in Brief</title><description>Wednesday June 27, 2012 7:51 am

... those games will rotate among six bowls. The Rose Bowl in Pasadena, Calif., is guaranteed a spot, and... record. Teenagers claimed the next three fastest times, as well - 18-year-old Rachel Bootsma, 17-year-old... quarterly board meeting scheduled for Thursday after 40 members of its staff were forced to evacuate their</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7486-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7486_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:52:22">http://www.sportingnews.com/nfl/story/2012-06-28/wednesday-s-sports-in-brief</link><title>Wednesday's Sports in Brief</title><description>Thursday June 28, 2012 7:19 am

... off two teenagers. Eighteen-year-old Rachel Bootsma got past the 11-time Olympic medalist, as well, claiming... quarterly board meeting scheduled for Thursday in San Jose, Calif. FOOTBALL MIAMI (AP) - Former NFL executive... postseason games since 2004. EDMONTON, Alberta (AP) - The Edmonton Oilers have promoted assistant Ralph Krueger</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e165-7486-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e165/7486_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:53:47">http://www.sportingnews.com/ncaa-football/feed/2011-11/penn-state-scandal/story/penn-state-officials-head-to-court-on-perjury-charges</link><title>Penn State officials head to court on perjury charges</title><description>Monday November 7, 2011 11:36 am

... of the board of trustees, university President Graham Spanier announced that Athletic Director Tim Curley... young teenagers \-- over a 15-year period. State Attorney General Linda Kelly and state police Commissioner... winning games, including two national championships, and largely steering clear of trouble. In a statement</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>