<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7461">navalni trial latest news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:28:33" name="Ask" id="FW14-e052"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e052-7461-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e052/7461_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:28:34">http://navalny-en.livejournal.com/</link><title>The blog of Navalny in English</title><description>This case, laughed at so much in the beginning, eventually caused ecologist Suren .... to adopt the newest principals and traditions of Russia's domestic policy , so it hasn't ... You have probably heard the news and read some articles about it .</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e052-7461-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e052/7461_02.pdf" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:29:18">http://tampub.uta.fi/bitstream/handle/10024/95205/978-951-44-9451-2.pdf?sequence=1</link><title>The Blogization of Journalism - TamPub</title><description>Mar 25, 2014 ... opens a valuable framework in which one can study ongoing symbolic ... premises of transitology – a research perspective that frames the recent history of ... Third, I conceptualize news making by journalists and by bloggers as a social ..... Luvussa tarkastellaan Aleksei Navalni ja Leonid Parfenovin ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e052-7461-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e052/7461_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:29:49">http://reason.com/blog/2014/01/27/take-a-look-inside-the-wasteful-spending</link><title>Take a Look Inside the Wasteful Spending of the Most Expensive ...</title><description>Jan 27, 2014 ... Free-market-loving, pro-transparency, anti-corruption activist and former Moscow mayoral candidate Alexei Navalni has launched a stellar ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e052-7461-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e052/7461_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:30:56">http://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/showthread.php?744058-A-Trade-focused-AAR-with-The-Hansa-(not-interactive-at-all-but-advices-are-welcome)</link><title>A Trade-focused AAR with The Hansa (not interactive at all but ...</title><description>Edit a posteriori : here is the up-to-date outline of this AAR Part I ... That's bad news, but I cannot really afford to play frenemies with them now. .... My only consideration would be that the Naval NI is probably more suitable for .... But that was no more the case, as you can notice from the figures : 6,58 D$ lost ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e052-7461-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e052/7461_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:33:23">http://council.smallwarsjournal.com/showthread.php?p=155556</link><title>Ukraine (catch all) - Page 68 - Small Wars Council</title><description>16 hours ago ... I don't think any administration in recent memory would have responded much differently. ... You could argue that in the case of the Cold War in Eastern Europe, appeasement did work. ... Even more ironical the fact that vigilant corruption- fighter Navalni .... http://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-26866989</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e052-7461-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e052/7461_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:33:56">http://council.smallwarsjournal.com/showthread.php?p=155564</link><title>Ukraine (catch all) - Page 69 - Small Wars Council</title><description>13 hours ago ... Join Date: Dec 2006 ... What I will say is that in the case of Germany this is no ability to ... Even more ironical the fact that vigilant corruption-fighter Navalni ... Small Wars Council Book Club, The Whole News, Blog Watch ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e052-7461-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e052/7461_07.pdf" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:34:35">http://www.chathamhouse.org/sites/default/files/19412_0511ppmonaghan.pdf</link><title>The Russian Vertikal: the Tandem, Power and the ... \- Chatham House</title><description>Khodorkovsky trials and verdicts, and the firings and appointments of senior officials – notably that of Moscow Mayor Yuri Luzhkov in 2010 and Medvedev's recent order that state officials ..... http://premier.gov.ru/events/news/13666/. 25 ..... 'Aleksei Navalni: Medvedev tozhe 'plokhoi politseiski'', Radio Svoboda, 13 May 2011.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e052-7461-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e052/7461_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:34:58">http://www.euronews.com/2013/04/17/navalny-trial-adjourned-in-russia/</link><title>Navalny trial adjourned in Russia | euronews, world news</title><description>Apr 17, 2013 ... world news \- Anti-corruption campaigner Alexei Navalny has accused the Russian ... of laying trumped up charges of embezzlement against him at the start of his trial. ... euronews LIVE; euronews RADIO; Latest Bulletin.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e052-7461-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e052/7461_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 08:36:05">http://www.debatingeurope.eu/2014/04/08/eu-partly-blame-crisis-ukraine/</link><title>Is the EU partly to blame for the crisis in Ukraine? — Debating Europe</title><description>Apr 8, 2014 ... Did you know that the Russian journalist Alexei Navalni is currently ... But in case any young people are reading this, please listen to me! ..... Next on the line is the state of press freedom and why all russian news outlets praise Putin. ..... is not able to punch him in the nose for breaking into other countries.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>