<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7009">linkedin engineering</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:07:33" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7009-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7009_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:07:34">http://www.business2community.com/linkedin/turn-linkedin-profile-career-video-0725665</link><title>How to Turn Your LinkedIn Profile into a Career Video</title><description>* How to Turn Your LinkedIn Profile into a Career Video 
, Engineering and Finance professionals although the tool can be used by anyone that has an English-language LinkedIn profile. You […] The good news: recruiters use LinkedIn to find candidates for jobs. The bad news: there are 260 million LinkedIn […] profiles out there, making it rather difficult to stand out. Here’s a solution: new tool Resu-ME transforms your LinkedIn

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7009-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7009_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:08:55">http://venturebeat.com/2013/12/31/stealthy-tech-company-intelligent-portal-systems-raises-4-3m/</link><title>Stealthy tech company Intelligent Portal Systems raises $4.3M</title><description>* Stealthy tech company Intelligent Portal Systems raises $4.3M 
Simulation, according to his LinkedIn profile . Russell also provides high-level information about Intelligent Portal Systems […] on his LinkedIn page: IPS was founded in the fall of 2011 to develop advanced web-based, general purpose expert […] systems technologies, initially for users in the worldwide markets of education and the engineering sciences. As its

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7009-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7009_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:13:59">http://venturebeat.com/2013/12/26/former-twitter-engineers-raise-1m-for-stealthy-startup-pushd/</link><title>Former Twitter engineers raise $1M for stealthy startup Pushd</title><description>* Former Twitter engineers raise $1M for stealthy startup Pushd 
Sanford previously led international engineering at Twitter after he joined from Summize, according to his LinkedIn profile […] , according to his LinkedIn profile . Eric Jensen, a Summize cofounder who joined Twitter alongside Chowdhury, has worked on […] Pushd, including as its chief technology officer, although it’s listed as past experience on his LinkedIn profile . It

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7009-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7009_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:17:59">http://venturebeat.com/2013/12/24/23andme-lost-its-chief-legal-counsel-months-before-fdas-legal-crackdown/</link><title>23andMe lost its chief legal counsel months before FDA’s legal…</title><description>* 23andMe lost its chief legal counsel months before FDA’s legal… 
Gould’s absence, the legal team continues to report to Andy Page, a new hire who was tasked with product and engineering […] May, just a few months after Gould would accept a new job at biotech firm Hyperion Therapeutics,  according to LinkedIn

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7009-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7009_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:21:17">http://thenextweb.com/dd/2013/12/17/future-api-design-orchestration-layer/</link><title>The future of API design: The orchestration layer</title><description>* The future of API design: The orchestration layer 
Daniel Jacobson ( Twitter  |  LinkedIn ), is currently director of engineering for the  Netflix   API . Prior to […] down the hall from the API team, a contracted company hired to develop an iPhone app, or an engineering team in a

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7009-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7009_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:22:52">http://thenextweb.com/dd/2013/12/23/draw-best-computer-science-interns-company/</link><title>How to draw in the best computer science interns to your company</title><description>* How to draw in the best computer science interns to your company 
employers. Connect with Nathan and InternMatch on  Facebook ,  LinkedIn , and  Twitter It’s no secret that the field of […] fields during this decade – which includes everything from engineering to the social sciences – will be in computer science

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7009-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7009_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:28:15">http://www.searchenginejournal.com/managing-company-blog-10-biggest-mistakes-smartest-ways-correct/79965/</link><title>Managing a Company Blog? The 10 Biggest Mistakes – And the Smartest Ways …</title><description>* Managing a Company Blog? The 10 Biggest Mistakes – And the Smartest Ways … 
at GetLinksPro Kannav Chaudhary is an SEO manager with GetLinksPro. He is an engineering graduate and brings an […] , Kronos. Twitter Google+ LinkedIn The post Managing a Company Blog? The 10 Biggest Mistakes – And the Smartest Ways

15 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>