<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7015">the raven</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:24:48" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7015-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7015_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:24:49">http://fansided.com/2013/12/27/sundays-game-last-michael-oher-raven/</link><title>Could Sunday’s game be the last for Michael Oher as a Raven?</title><description>* Could Sunday’s game be the last for Michael Oher as a Raven? 
Baltimore’s week 17 game against the Cincinnati Bengals is important for many reasons. They have a shot to make the […] postseason with the last AFC spot available, however, if they don’t make the playoffs, it could be the last game in a Ravens […] jersey for a few players, including Michael Oher. According to ESPN, Oher, […] Could Sunday’s game be the last for Michael

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7015-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7015_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:28:32">http://bostonherald.com/sports/columnists/ron_borges/2013/12/borges_pats_in_tough_with_raven_ous_rivals</link><title>Borges: Pats in tough with Raven-ous rivals</title><description>* Borges: Pats in tough with Raven-ous rivals 
BALTIMORE — Timing is everything in life and this is not the time the Patriots want to see the Baltimore Ravens. Who […] thought it would come to this? Who thought just a few weeks ago, despite all the injuries and all the flaws, the Patriots […] might face a must-win situation next weekend at home against the Buffalo Bills if they can’t find a way to take care of

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7015-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7015_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:32:09">http://www.brainpickings.org/index.php/2014/01/07/poe-tales-of-the-macabre-benjamin-lacombe/</link><title>French Artist Benjamin Lacombe’s Haunting Illustrations for Poe’s Tales …</title><description>* French Artist Benjamin Lacombe’s Haunting Illustrations for Poe’s Tales … 
1919 illustrations and shortly after the stunning graphic novel for Lou Reed’s adaptation of The Raven , French artist […] Lorenzo Mattotti’s take on The Raven . Donating = Loving Bringing you (ad-free) Brain Pickings takes hundreds of hours […] “Either the memory of past bliss is the anguish of to-day, or the agonies which are, have their origin in the ecstasies

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7015-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7015_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:35:53">http://bookriot.com/2014/01/10/mrs-poe-burden-historical-fiction/</link><title>MRS. POE and the Burden of Historical Fiction</title><description>* MRS. POE and the Burden of Historical Fiction 
something of a celebrity thanks to recent works like “The Raven,” which rendered him a hit with the local literary scene […] , or that his poem “The Raven” was so popular, he would be invited to parties and then harassed to give recitations of it […] successful poet who is being pushed to write more “gothic,” dark poems along the lines of Edgar Allan Poe, who has become

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7015-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7015_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:39:55">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/12/30/2013-animated-gifs_n_4520043.html</link><title>2013 Summed Up In One Trippy Animated Minute</title><description>* 2013 Summed Up In One Trippy Animated Minute 
Watch Animation Domination High-Def (ADHD) present all the highlights of 2013 in one minute of GIFs. Its all here […] \-- everything from twerking to Obamacare to "Breaking Bad" to the government shutdown to Amanda Bynes meltdown to a revival of our […] love for "Thats So Raven." More...

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7015-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7015_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:43:26">http://www.buzzfeed.com/briangalindo/15-cartoons-from-the-80s-you-probably-forgot-existed</link><title>15 Cartoons From The ‘80s You Probably Forgot Existed</title><description>* 15 Cartoons From The ‘80s You Probably Forgot Existed 
Beverly Hills. Like all great ‘80s TV shows, it even had an awesome villain, the raven-haired Bianca Dupree, who, of course […] Sure, you remember The Smurfs, Jem, and Transformers , but what about Beverly Hills Teens ? C […] Federal Agent from the FBI, who forms and leads a special police task force, C.O.P.S. (Central Organization of Police

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7015-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7015_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:48:20">http://hollywoodlife.com/2014/01/07/ravenswood-caleb-returns-winter-premiere-recap/</link><title>‘Ravenswood’ Recap: Remy’s Dreams Offer A Clue About The Curse</title><description>* ‘Ravenswood’ Recap: Remy’s Dreams Offer A Clue About The Curse 
. Also, I’m fairly certain the preacher in Remy’s nightmare turned into a raven and flew away, like freakin’ Charal from […] The ‘Ravenswood’ winter premiere offered up answers about the mysterious curse — and, of course, a million more […] questions. Following his three-day stint in Rosewood, Caleb ( Tyler Blackburn ) returned “home” on the Jan. 7 winter premiere

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7015-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7015_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:51:40">http://directorblue.blogspot.nl/2014/01/larwyns-linx-bombshell-documents-obama.html</link><title>Larwyns Linx: Bombshell Documents: Obama and Hillary lied completely …</title><description>* Larwyns Linx: Bombshell Documents: Obama and Hillary lied completely … 
Force : Camp o the Saints Share One of These to Let the President Know You Havent Forgotten : Heritage House GOP May […] -Gun Group Member Gets Jail for Gun Crime : MenRec Economy Corey Booker Falls Below 130% of the Intellectual Poverty Line […] : Ace Holder, Duncan Unveil Race-based School Discipline Guidelines : Raven Clabough Government blew $175 million of

13 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7015-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7015_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:52:26">http://www.buzzfeed.com/caitlincowie/the-9-best-cat-vines-of-2013</link><title>The 9 Best Cat Vines Of 2013</title><description>* The 9 Best Cat Vines Of 2013 
Raven Hammond / Via vine.co How to outshine your dance partner Josh Swensen / Via vine.co How

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7015-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7015_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:55:20">http://www.dailykos.com/story/2014/01/08/1267830/-Cheers-and-Jeers-Wednesday</link><title>Cheers and Jeers: Wednesday</title><description>* Cheers and Jeers: Wednesday 
the balance of my time to NN14 Executive Director Raven Brooks: In the coming year, activists around the country […] From the GREAT STATE OF MAINE Dreaming of Warmer Days Ahead Six months from nine days from now, Michigan […] Republicans will tremble as the 2014 Netroots Nation convention gets underway. It may warm your tootsies to know that the

14 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>