<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7031">Thomas test</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:26:28" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7031-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7031_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:26:29">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1915940-until-barry-bonds-rogers-clements-are-voted-in-the-hall-of-fame-remains-a-joke</link><title>Until Bonds and Clemens Are Voted In, the Baseball Hall of Fame Remains …</title><description>* Until Bonds and Clemens Are Voted In, the Baseball Hall of Fame Remains … 
trip to Cooperstown this summer—a hearty congratulations , by the way, to Greg Maddux, Tom Glavine and Frank Thomas, who […] in the games history they like to call The Steroid Era. Part of me thinks Frank Thomas was a first-ballot selection not […] just for his numbers but because he is the anti-Bonds. Thomas was vociferous in his disdain for performance-enhancing drugs

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7031-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7031_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:29:47">http://www.businessinsider.com/thomas-jefferson-dean-admits-to-missteps-2013-12</link><title>Dean Of California Law School Thats Being Trashed In The Press Admits …</title><description>* Dean Of California Law School Thats Being Trashed In The Press Admits … 
The new dean of the embattled Thomas Jefferson Law School has written a frank letter to alumni admitting the […] schools own missteps have caused many of its "troubles." The letter from dean Thomas Guernsey — which JDUnderground and […] its credit rating to junk-bond status . Thomas Jefferson has also been sued for allegedly misleading prospective

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7031-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7031_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:30:26">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1905926-2014-nfl-free-agents-best-playmakers-set-to-hit-the-market</link><title>2014 NFL Free Agents: Best Playmakers Set to Hit the Market</title><description>* 2014 NFL Free Agents: Best Playmakers Set to Hit the Market 
organization might choose to let a dynamic player test the market or even walk without an offer rather than lock him up long term […] didnt lead his team in any statistical category, save for a tie with Demaryius Thomas with 19 catches of 20-plus yards […] ; Thomas has him beat in receptions, yards, yards per catch and yards after catch, while both Demaryius and Julius Thomas

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7031-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7031_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:32:48">http://reason.com/blog/2014/01/10/when-youre-covering-the-krokodil-epidemi</link><title>When Youre Covering the Bogus Krokodil Epidemic, Even Rumors of a Rumor …</title><description>* When Youre Covering the Bogus Krokodil Epidemic, Even Rumors of a Rumor … 
Up in Utah ." Reporter PatReavy asked Sue Thomas, supervisory special agent for the DrugEnforcement Administration in […]  Utah, about krokodil , andThomas responded with an over-the-top recital of potential sideeffects that was partly true but mixed up […] theresult of krokodil, they were minor reactions, and there is nosure test. Actually, there is a suretest : If someone has

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7031-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7031_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:35:41">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1891736-panthers-defense-could-be-the-story-of-the-nfl-season-but-big-test-awaits</link><title>Panthers Defense Could Be the Story of the NFL Season, but Big Test …</title><description>* Panthers Defense Could Be the Story of the NFL Season, but Big Test … 
, Luke Kuechly and Star Lotulelei, arent even halfway to being vested for their pensions. The third, Thomas Davis, is the

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7031-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7031_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:36:32">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/jamie-raskin/scalia-predicted-it-equal_b_4519730.html</link><title>Jamin Raskin: Scalia Predicted It: Equal Rights Means Equal Rights</title><description>* Jamin Raskin: Scalia Predicted It: Equal Rights Means Equal Rights 
Social Tradition: The Supreme Courts Test in the Marriage Cases," Justice Scalia chastised Justice OConnor back in 2003 for […] , Clarence Thomas, and Samuel Alito -- will feel Utahs pain intensely, and Chief Justice John Roberts is likely to want

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7031-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7031_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:38:55">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1900904-bowl-games-2013-14-breaking-down-most-underrated-non-bcs-battles</link><title>Bowl Games 2013-14: Breaking Down Most Underrated Non-BCS Battles</title><description>* Bowl Games 2013-14: Breaking Down Most Underrated Non-BCS Battles 
offense in this game.   Hyundai Sun Bowl: Virginia Tech vs. UCLA Brett Hundley and Logan Thomas are two quarterbacks […] pocket. He can hone in his accuracy and work on his timing. He will get a serious test against Virginia Tech and the No. 8 […] the other hand, Thomas will not have that chance to return to school after completing his senior season. The 66

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7031-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7031_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:40:15">http://www.deadline.com/2014/01/william-morris-agency-retreat-sheryl-sandberg-michael-hayden-nsa/</link><title>Who’s Who Of NSA And Tech Heavyweights Brought Together At WME Annual …</title><description>* Who’s Who Of NSA And Tech Heavyweights Brought Together At WME Annual … 
into (along with Genetech). It produces direct-to-consumer personal genome test kits that can determine inherited traits […] . This year’s lineup is said to include Deputy NSA Advisor Thomas Donilon, who stepped down in June 2013 and has worked with

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7031-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7031_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:44:09">http://www.sbnation.com/2014/1/10/5294880/raiders-free-agency-2014-jared-veldheer</link><title>Raiders free agency 2014: LT Jared Veldheer really wants to stay in …</title><description>* Raiders free agency 2014: LT Jared Veldheer really wants to stay in … 
graded out as third best overall offensive tackle, period, behind Trent Williams and Joe Thomas. Its unclear whether he […] keep them from being consensus top 10 picks, however. If either or both test well this offseason, they could quickly rise

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7031-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7031_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:46:37">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1911590-fa-cup-2014-fourth-round-draw-full-list-of-fixtures-and-dates</link><title>FA Cup 2014 Fourth Round Draw: Full List of Fixtures and Dates</title><description>* FA Cup 2014 Fourth Round Draw: Full List of Fixtures and Dates 
of the campaign. Arsene Wenger fielded a weakened side, handing the likes of Lukasz Fabianski, Serge Gnabry, Thomas […] of Yeovil Town thats next on the agenda, the second Championship test for the south-coast outfit in succession and a

14 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>