<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7034">sony vaio laptop</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:14:18" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7034-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7034_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:14:19">http://liliputing.com/2014/01/closer-look-sony-vaio-flip-11a-convertible-tablet-digital-pen.html</link><title>Closer look at the Sony Vaio Flip 11a convertible tablet (and digital …</title><description>* Closer look at the Sony Vaio Flip 11a convertible tablet (and digital … 
The Sony Vaio Flip 11a is a notebook with an 11.6 inch, full HD display that bends over backward to become a tablet […] a third is the support for a pressure-sensitive digital pen. When I got my first look at the Sony Vaio Flip 11a , the […] . Sony calls the digital pen a Vaio Active Pen. The tablet has an active digitizer which means it supports pressure

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7034-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7034_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:19:06">http://liliputing.com/2014/01/hands-sony-vaio-flip-11a.html</link><title>Hands-on: Sony Vaio Flip 11a</title><description>* Hands-on: Sony Vaio Flip 11a 
Sony’s Vaio Flip 11A is notebook with an 11.6 inch display that you can flip over so that it’s flat against the […] -1 tablet in late February. Hands-on: Sony Vaio Flip 11a is a post from: Liliputing […] keyboard, allowing you to use the computer as a tablet. Sony has offered larger Flip models since 2013, but the company

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7034-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7034_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:22:35">http://mashable.com/2013/12/17/laptop-wish-list/</link><title>Which Laptop Is on Your Holiday Wish List?</title><description>* Which Laptop Is on Your Holiday Wish List? 
for ultimate portability, the Sony Vaio Pro 11 may be your best bet. Read more... More about Apple , Sony , Dell […] that would be perfect for you going into 2014. If youre considering a new laptop , there are quite a few to consider […] display this year, starting at $1,299, which could fit your needs See also: How to Clean Your Laptop But if you have

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7034-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7034_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:25:19">http://liliputing.com/2014/01/favorites-ces-2014.html</link><title>A few favorites from CES 2014</title><description>* A few favorites from CES 2014 
around in. Sony Vaio Flip 11 convertible tablet On the other hand, Sony’s new 11.6 inch convertible might be a better […] laptop with a 15.6 inch display — most feel more like desktop replacements than mobile devices. But this Samsung Ativ Book 9 […] option for portability. It’s an 11.6 inch laptop with a display that flips over so you can use the device as a tablet. It

14 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>