<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7044">song of ice and fire</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:58:19" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7044-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7044_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:58:20">http://www.metafilter.com/135414/A-Song-of-Fire-and-Ice</link><title>A Song of Fire and Ice</title><description>* A Song of Fire and Ice 
Photo gallery: Happys Pizza in Ann Arbor burns in subzero temperatures

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7044-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7044_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:00:46">http://www.tor.com/blogs/2013/12/a-read-of-ice-and-fire-the-sworn-sword-part-1</link><title>A Read of Ice and Fire: “The Sworn Sword” Part 1</title><description>* A Read of Ice and Fire: “The Sworn Sword” Part 1 
.R. Martin’s epic fantasy series A Song of Ice and Fire. Today’s entry is Part 1 of “The Sworn Sword: A Tale of the Seven […] Welcome back to A Read of Ice and Fire! Please join me as I read and react, for the very first time, to George R […] Kingdoms,” which originally appeared in the anthology Legends II: New Short Novels By The Masters of Modern Fantasy , edited

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7044-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7044_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:02:27">http://www.buzzfeed.com/jacelacob/season-4-of-game-of-thrones-finally-has-a-launch-date</link><title>Season 4 Of "Game Of Thrones" Finally Has A Launch Date</title><description>* Season 4 Of "Game Of Thrones" Finally Has A Launch Date 
eagerly awaited fourth season of Game of Thrones , based on the A Song of Ice and Fire novels by George R.R. Martin, which […] Sophie Turner. The same night will see the launches of Season 3 of Veep at 10 p.m. and HBOs new Mike Judge comedy Silicon […] new Season 4 trailer this Sunday evening before the launch of HBOs superlative new mystery thriller True Detective

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7044-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7044_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:04:24">http://www.ibtimes.com/hbos-game-thrones-season-4-return-date-revealed-network-bid-goodbye-boardwalk-empire-after-season-5</link><title>HBO’s ‘Game Of Thrones’ Season 4 Return Date Revealed; Network To Bid …</title><description>* HBO’s ‘Game Of Thrones’ Season 4 Return Date Revealed; Network To Bid … 
Ice and Fire,” a series of fantasy novels by George R.R. Martin. HBO made the announcement at the Television Critics […] The fantasy drama series “Game of Thrones” kicks off its fourth season on April 6. The series is based on “A Song of […] Association press tour in Pasadena, Calif., on Jan. 9 and the first trailer of the new season will be unveiled this Sunday

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7044-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7044_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:06:26">http://www.geeksaresexy.net/2014/01/09/7-year-old-girl-asks-scientists-to-breed-her-a-dragon/</link><title>7-Year-Old Girl Asks Scientists To Breed Her a Dragon</title><description>* 7-Year-Old Girl Asks Scientists To Breed Her a Dragon 
/A Song of Fire and Ice. [ CSIRO | Via ] […] has never ventured into dragons of the mythical, fire breathing variety. And for this Australia, we are sorry. You can […] Stuart. I would keep it in my special green grass area where there are lots of space. I would feed it raw fish and I would

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7044-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7044_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:09:37">http://www.theawl.com/2013/12/the-top-ten-least-annoying-metal-albums-of-2013</link><title>The Top Ten Least Annoying Metal Albums Of 2013</title><description>* The Top Ten Least Annoying Metal Albums Of 2013 
I hate rock and roll. It is in this hateful spirit, then, that I offer the following list of the top ten metal albums […] Chemical Brothers joint. Now I see that’s part of its genius. Imagine a collaboration between Nine Inch Nails and Hawkwind […] . This doesn’t sound anything like that, but it’s the best I could do. (One song kind of sounds like Geffen-era Sonic Youth

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7044-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7044_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:11:35">http://www.business2community.com/celebrity/kaley-cuoco-says-wedding-greatest-night-entire-life-0730450</link><title>Kaley Cuoco Says Her Wedding Was the ‘Greatest Night of My Entire …</title><description>* Kaley Cuoco Says Her Wedding Was the ‘Greatest Night of My Entire … 
. Their New Year’s Eve wedding was fire-and-ice themed and took place at Hummingbird Nest Ranch in Santa Susana, California […] , confirms People . The Big Bang Theory hottie Instagrammed a photo of her and her new hubby engulfed in her pink Vera […] wedding day is one of the most exciting milestones you’ll reach. Everyone deserves for their big day to be as special and

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7044-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7044_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:14:45">http://www.inquisitr.com/1066263/game-of-thrones-season-4-glimpse-in-hbos-look-ahead-to-2014-trailer/</link><title>‘Game Of Thrones’ Season 4 Glimpse In HBO’s Look Ahead To 2014 Trailer</title><description>* ‘Game Of Thrones’ Season 4 Glimpse In HBO’s Look Ahead To 2014 Trailer 
dealer, enabler) that brings us Game of Thrones —based on the epic fantasy series A Song of Ice and Fire by George R. R […] favorite shows this year, including The Newsroom, Boardwalk Empire, True Blood and Veep . Naturally, Game of Thrones was […] Game of Thrones imp, bound in manacles. Next is King Joffrey, looking smug and scheming (at a wedding?). Then Ser Jaime

17 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>