<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7057">web of science</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:58:17" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7057-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7057_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:58:18">http://www.businessinsider.com/spiders-make-bizarre-web-towers-in-the-amazon-2014-1</link><title>You Wont Believe What Is Making These Bizarre Webs In The Amazon</title><description>* You Wont Believe What Is Making These Bizarre Webs In The Amazon 
. The team located about 45 of the web towers and observed and dissected some of them, but their results were inconclusive […] constructing the towers, so they still dont know how the structures are made. They did observe lots of mites around the sticky web […] the thin strands of web create a perimeter around the center tower containing the egg in the image below. This is

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7057-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7057_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:59:34">http://gigaom.com/2014/01/11/as-sites-and-services-become-product-aware-the-age-of-pervasive-commerce-begins/</link><title>As sites and services become product aware, the age of pervasive commerce …</title><description>* As sites and services become product aware, the age of pervasive commerce … 
mention of a product in a blog or a web site and provide the potential customer with product details and offers that are […] instance of a product or product attribute mentioned anywhere on the web, and then automatically, without human intervention or […] science will be in dynamically matching the preferences of the prospective buyer with the attributes of the product in the

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7057-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7057_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:00:41">http://www.patheos.com/blogs/friendlyatheist/2014/01/10/richard-dawkins-foundation-for-reason-and-science-names-new-executive-director/</link><title>Richard Dawkins Foundation for Reason and Science Names New Executive …</title><description>* Richard Dawkins Foundation for Reason and Science Names New Executive … 
applauded for these views since they are out of step with the majority of Americans, but neither should I be despised for them […] . Yet, I will be. I can already imagine the torrent of hate mail, with readers accusing me of all sorts of vile human […] in religion and as such I expect to be bombarded by it. I take no issue with the right of religious people to proselytize

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7057-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7057_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:06:43">http://venturebeat.com/2014/01/03/the-basis-smart-fitness-watch-is-going-to-get-a-lot-smarter-and-prettier/</link><title>The Basis smart fitness watch will tell you exactly how much good-quality …</title><description>* The Basis smart fitness watch will tell you exactly how much good-quality … 
week in Las Vegas, and they show that Basis Science is starting to figure out its audience. It has a loyal following of […] . 21 with the release of the Basis app 2.0 version for iOS, Android and the Web. “Best Buy is important because 80 […] information will be visible in your web and mobile dashboards. “No other tracker is able to provide this level of insight

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7057-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7057_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:10:05">http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2013/12/18/reddit-science-forum-has-been-banning-climate-change-denialism/</link><title>Reddit Science Forum Has Been Banning Climate Change Denialism</title><description>* Reddit Science Forum Has Been Banning Climate Change Denialism 
outsized influence in the media and the public” and therefore the /r/science moderators “felt that to allow a handful of […] climate science deniers as much as it is our subreddit reflects the current scientific consensus in the form of only allowing […] , Martin said “they have always been pretty strict” with what they’ll allow to be posted. “Some of the subreddits like science

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7057-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7057_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:11:41">http://www.businessinsider.com/facebook-and-pinterest-bulk-up-their-big-data-teams-2014-1</link><title>Facebook And Pinterest Bulk Up Their Big Data Teams</title><description>* Facebook And Pinterest Bulk Up Their Big Data Teams 
.  Pinterest isnt the only social Web company that is building out its data science team. Facebook recently  hired  deep learning […]   BI Intelligence  subscribers.  Sign up for a free trial of BI Intelligence today . PINTEREST READY TO DECIPHER […] experts from the field of big data to Pinterest. VisualGraph CEO Kevin Jing helped build Googles first machine vision

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7057-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7057_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:15:04">https://intelligence.businessinsider.com/welcome</link><title>SOCIAL INSIGHTS: Facebook Announces Major Improvements To Ad Targeting</title><description>* SOCIAL INSIGHTS: Facebook Announces Major Improvements To Ad Targeting 
years.  Between 2006 and 2008, the majority of content on Reddit was related to programming, science, and politics, which […] topics range from the mainstream to the obscure, representative of Reddit evolving into a mainstream web property, a place […] : Amazons collection of cloud computing services (AWS) are a favorite among top web properties, such as Netflix, Pinterest

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7057-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7057_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:17:14">http://www.slashgear.com/roboearth-is-the-web-for-robots-testing-underway-15313271/</link><title>RoboEarth is the web for robots, testing underway</title><description>* RoboEarth is the web for robots, testing underway 
A lot of work is being done on robots to serve various uses around the world. DARPA is holding a robotics challenge to […] push the development of robots that can … Continue reading

13 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7057-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7057_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:20:22">http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2014/01/09/twitter-account-speaks-from-beyond-the-grave/</link><title>Twitter Account Speaks From Beyond the Grave</title><description>* Twitter Account Speaks From Beyond the Grave 
. (Image source: @billcomeans/Twitter) These are the words of a tweet posted Tuesday on an unusual account with the handle […] account is part of an effort by the family of Comeans to try and find new leads that could help solve the cold case. “I was […] Mobile Web (M5) Reply Retweet Favorite @BillComeans Bill Comeans #bbpBox_421059408496300032 a

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7057-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7057_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:24:35">http://www.businessinsider.com/google-makes-strides-as-a-social-login-provider-2014-1</link><title>Google+ Makes Strides As A Social Login Provider</title><description>* Google+ Makes Strides As A Social Login Provider 
SHIFTS: Google+ is powering an increasing number of user logins across the Web. Google+s share of social logins hit its […]   BI Intelligence  subscribers.  Sign up for a free trial of BI Intelligence today . SOCIAL LOGIN LANDSCAPE […] highest level since 2010 in the fourth quarter of 2013, according to Janrain. Facebook remains the most popular login

15 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>