<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7063">Spanish unemployment</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:33:08" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7063-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7063_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:33:09">http://www.zerohedge.com/news/2014-01-08/spain-youth-unemployment-rises-record-577-surpasses-greece</link><title>Spain Youth Unemployment Rises To Record 57.7%, Surpasses Greece</title><description>* Spain Youth Unemployment Rises To Record 57.7%, Surpasses Greece 
that according to the official European statistics keeper, Spanish unemployment in November was 26.7%: tied for the all […] unemployment was "only" 54.8% as of September. And now, buy Spanish bonds and stocks, because "the recovery." Source […] There has been much speculation recently about some immaculately conceived Spanish economic recovery. And while it has

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7063-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7063_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:35:16">http://www.zerohedge.com/news/2013-12-18/spanish-bad-loans-jump-new-record-banks-come-clean-over-mortgage-defaults</link><title>Spanish Bad Loans Jump To New Record As Banks Come Clean Over Mortgage …</title><description>* Spanish Bad Loans Jump To New Record As Banks Come Clean Over Mortgage … 
Spanish loan delinquencies as a percentage of the total have risen for the 8th straight month to a new record high of […] 13.00% (even as sovereign bond spreads continue to plunge to multi-year lows signaling all is well). With unemployment […] rates stuck stubbornly high, however, reality is starting to dawn in the Spanish banking system as mortgage defaults are

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7063-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7063_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:38:13">http://www.zerohedge.com/news/2014-01-09/equity-futures-stong-ecb-day-ahead-earnings-season-start-market-summary</link><title>Equity Futures Stong On ECB Day Ahead Of Earnings Season Start: Market …</title><description>* Equity Futures Stong On ECB Day Ahead Of Earnings Season Start: Market … 
, supported by solid demand for Portuguese 5y bond syndication, as well as oversubscribed debt auctions by the Spanish Treasury […] the same time, having been propped up by touted redemption flows ahead of Spanish and French bond auctions, absorption of […] April 2011 following over-subscribed Spanish bond auctions. Despite the USD index trading lower, USD/JPY remains bid and

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7063-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7063_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:40:43">http://www.zerohedge.com/news/2014-01-03/75-spaniards-dont-believe-rajoys-economic-recovery-meme</link><title>75% Of Spaniards Dont Believe Rajoys "Economic Recovery" Meme</title><description>* 75% Of Spaniards Dont Believe Rajoys "Economic Recovery" Meme 
With unemployment stuck at record highs and loan delinquencies surging (as we discussed here , here and here ), it […] recovering (and with Spanish stocks and bonds back near pre-crisis levels), a massive 75% of the Spanish people believe their […] two thirds of the Spanish population momentum promised by the leader of the executive is not created.   This emerges

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7063-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7063_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:42:21">http://www.zerohedge.com/news/2014-01-07/deep-freeze-day-market-summary</link><title>Deep Freeze Day Market Summary</title><description>* Deep Freeze Day Market Summary 
tightening, with smaller Italian and Spanish banks gaining around 4%. Following the successful placement, IR/GE 10y bond yield […] rates. The Spanish and Italian markets are the best-performing larger bourses, Swedish the worst. The euro is stronger […] against the dollar. Japanese 10yr bond yields fall; Spanish yields decline. Commodities gain, with wheat, silver

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7063-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7063_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:42:57">http://www.zerohedge.com/news/2014-01-10/jobs-day-market-summary</link><title>Jobs Day Market Summary</title><description>* Jobs Day Market Summary 
aggressive tightening observed earlier in the week amid solid Spanish bond auctions, as well as syndications by Ireland and […] +195K; unemployment rate 7.0% (14:30) Fed speakers Lacker (14:45); Bullard (19:00) POMO: $2.50 - $3.50 billion in 10 […] unemployment rate held at 7.0%. Numerous firms have raised payrolls forecast after better than expected ADP report on Jan. 9

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7063-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7063_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:44:21">http://consumerist.com/2013/12/26/american-express-to-refund-59-5-million-over-bad-billing-deceptive-marketing/</link><title>American Express To Refund $59.5 Million Over Bad Billing &amp; Deceptive …</title><description>* American Express To Refund $59.5 Million Over Bad Billing &amp; Deceptive … 
events like unemployment of or temporary disability. However, the CFPB says that Amex marketers misled some customers into […] Spanish, Amex failed to provide its Spanish-speaking sales reps with a uniform script for enrolling customers and all the

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7063-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7063_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:47:57">http://www.zerohedge.com/news/2014-01-03/snow-day-market-summary</link><title>Snow Day Market Summary</title><description>* Snow Day Market Summary 
weaker against the dollar. Portuguese 10yr bond yields fall; Spanish yields decline. Commodities little changed, with zinc […] money supply and Spanish/Italian CPI readings. December auto sales is the main data release in the US. Bernanke, Lacker

15 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>