<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7067">used kindle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:17:33" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7067-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7067_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:17:34">http://liliputing.com/2014/01/people-arent-buying-nooks-like-used.html</link><title>People aren’t buying NOOKs like they used to</title><description>* People aren’t buying NOOKs like they used to 
leading to Cyber Monday was the best ever for Kindle Fire and Kindle eReader sales. Amazon has a habit of not actually […] providing solid figures for Kindle sales, so it’s hard to make an apples to apples comparison here, but it’s pretty clear that a […] easy to install apps that aren’t in the Amazon Appstore on a Kindle Fire tablet, and if you want to read an EPUB book on a

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7067-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7067_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:20:38">http://www.theverge.com/2014/1/9/5293090/amazon-puts-kindle-vending-machine-in-vegas-airport-to-tempt-ces</link><title>Amazon puts Kindle vending machine in Vegas airport to tempt CES…</title><description>* Amazon puts Kindle vending machine in Vegas airport to tempt CES… 
Electronics Show, which ends tomorrow and where Amazon was not present. Theyre the same ones the company used in a temporary pop

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7067-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7067_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:23:19">http://gigaom.com/2014/01/02/surface-kindle-fire-are-likely-holiday-winners-but-ipad-still-rules-the-web-surfing-roost/</link><title>Surface, Kindle Fire are likely holiday winners, but iPad still rules …</title><description>* Surface, Kindle Fire are likely holiday winners, but iPad still rules … 
’s Kindle and Microsoft’s Surface tablets were used quite a bit online as 2013 came to a close. On the phone side, only […] Chitika pegs at 5.9 percent. Among the Android devices, Amazon’s Kindle Fire is still hot. It saw a small 0.6 percent […] bump in holiday web surfing and holds nearly 10 percent of web traffic. While the Kindle Fire is rightly seen as a more

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7067-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7067_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:24:45">http://gigaom.com/2013/12/26/amazon-was-a-prime-shopping-source-this-holiday-gaining-1m-more-subscribers/</link><title>Amazon was a Prime shopping source this holiday, gaining 1M more…</title><description>* Amazon was a Prime shopping source this holiday, gaining 1M more… 
 Monday holiday shopping weekend was the best ever for Kindle Fire tablets and Kindle e-readers. Amazon says “millions of customers unwrapped […] Kindle e-readers and Kindle Fire tablets this holiday season.” A total of 36.8 million items were ordered through Amazon on […] of its customers shopped using a mobile device this holiday. That’s a tipping point of sorts as the mobile web was used

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7067-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7067_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:28:39">http://venturebeat.com/2014/01/10/two-pictures-that-illustrate-12-years-of-change-in-technology-and-the-increasing-irrelevance-of-ces/</link><title>Two pictures that illustrate 12 years of change in technology (and the …</title><description>* Two pictures that illustrate 12 years of change in technology (and the … 
in my living room today — the iPad Mini, Kindle Fire HDX, Chromecast, Apple TV, and Roku — weren’t introduced at CES. The […] the TuneIn app. I used to collect DVDs; I’ve all but stopped. I don’t want more physical stuff to haul around. But […] marketplace seller (36 cents plus $3.99 shipping). I could have bought the Kindle edition, but that is $16. With print books

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7067-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7067_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:30:22">http://www.dailykos.com/story/2014/01/09/1268334/-Midday-open-thread-Rodman-apologizes-gamers-hallucinate-Reddit-branding-sells-guns</link><title>Midday open thread: Rodman apologizes, gamers hallucinate, Reddit branding …</title><description>* Midday open thread: Rodman apologizes, gamers hallucinate, Reddit branding … 
store and ask for it. You don’t have to conspicuously pull it out on the commuter train—it can be neatly hidden by a Kindle […] Führer on your Kindle, but Amazon sure as hell does.”  Enjoy your illusions of privacy until your “recommendations” scare the […] have included nearly 100 AR-15s engraved with Reddits alien logo, which was used on the assault rifles with explicit

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7067-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7067_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:32:54">http://www.theverge.com/2014/1/7/5286544/this-giant-499-e-ink-clock-will-cost-you-time-and-money</link><title>This giant $499 E Ink clock will cost you time and money</title><description>* This giant $499 E Ink clock will cost you time and money 
Every year, E Ink (the company most famous for the screen on your Kindle) trots out a number of unusual prototype […] devices to show how its technology can be used in other ways besides e-readers — but this years definitely takes the cake

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7067-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7067_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:34:55">http://gigaom.com/2014/01/04/android-this-week-small-acer-tablets-pandora-wakes-you-galaxy-s-5-design-ideas/</link><title>Android this week: Small Acer tablets; Pandora wakes you; Galaxy S 5 …</title><description>* Android this week: Small Acer tablets; Pandora wakes you; Galaxy S 5 … 
camera; just a front-facing sensor for video chat. While I’d likely spend a little more on a Kindle Fire or Nexus 7 over […] -based cameras as well, but more intriguing to me are the  patented Samsung design images floating around , which could be used for […] materials Samsung has typically used. Perhaps we’ll hear more about that at CES but I won’t know if I oversleep and miss my

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7067-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7067_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:40:45">http://thenextweb.com/entrepreneur/2013/12/20/self-publishing-battle-royale-amazon-vs-indie-sales-platforms/</link><title>Self-publishing battle royale: Amazon vs. indie sales platforms</title><description>* Self-publishing battle royale: Amazon vs. indie sales platforms 
around 70 percent to authors. The main reason I used KDP for the third book is because I hadn’t used it before, and have a […] up on Amazon and 72 hours to “sync” with the Kindle version (so you can see both the Kindle and paperback version on the […] paperback and Kindle versions a few days before I announce the book is launching, which is a simple and easy remedy (even if you

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7067-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7067_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:43:41">http://gigaom.com/2014/01/07/toshiba-chromebook-hands-on-a-solid-effort-with-more-roominess/</link><title>Toshiba Chromebook hands-on: A solid effort with more roominess</title><description>* Toshiba Chromebook hands-on: A solid effort with more roominess 
they’re not terrible. And overall, I think the screen is a step up from the panel that Acer has used of late on its C720 […] Disruptapalooza 2011: how Amazon’s Kindle is changing the portable media game How to deliver the next-generation web experience

14 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>