<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7078">count in korean</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:34:37" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7078-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7078_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:34:38">http://www.businessinsider.com/political-scientists-explain-how-kim-jong-un-is-consolidating-power-2013-12</link><title>Political Scientists Explain How Kim Jong-Un Is Consolidating Power</title><description>* Political Scientists Explain How Kim Jong-Un Is Consolidating Power 
Korean Studies at the Council on Foreign Relations, said more factors would have to come into play in order to tell if the […] person in the nuclear-armed nation, may have little to do with his supposed crime of planning a coup. Bruce Bueno De […] in the first few weeks when a new leader assumes power, everyone is scared," Smith said.  New leaders can shake up the

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7078-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7078_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:38:37">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1907950-scouting-international-players-we-cant-wait-to-see-in-the-majors</link><title>Scouting International Players We Cant Wait to See in the Majors</title><description>* Scouting International Players We Cant Wait to See in the Majors 
four guys we cant wait to see in the major leagues, and a look at what theyd be bringing to whatever team opted to sign […] them.   RHP Raicel Iglesias After a failed attempt to defect in September, right-hander Raciel […] Iglesias successfully escaped Cuba back in November, according to Ben Badler of  Baseball America . He has the added

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7078-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7078_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:41:02">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1909860-mexico-how-can-el-tri-benefit-from-facing-south-koreas-b-team</link><title>Mexico: How Can El Tri Benefit from Facing South Koreas B-Team</title><description>* Mexico: How Can El Tri Benefit from Facing South Koreas B-Team 
footballers from the Chinese, Japanese and Korean leagues because it is not an official FIFA date. In other words, this means […] player. In the goal, he can count on Moises Munoz, who despite not having much international experience, has Herrera’s trust […] the Alamodome in San Antonio, Texas. Hong Myung -bo released his 23-player list for the match, which only includes

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7078-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7078_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:45:26">http://jonathanturley.org/2014/01/09/john-marshall-law-professor-sues-school-for-failing-to-accommodate-his-inability-to-communicate-with-students-and-staff/</link><title>John Marshall Law Professor Sues School For Failing To Accommodate His …</title><description>* John Marshall Law Professor Sues School For Failing To Accommodate His … 
, if you just count boys, who are five times as likely to have one as girls). A South Korean study from last year put the […] address his depression and Asperger’s syndrome in violation the Americans with Disabilities Act. He claims that the school […] ignored his requests for assistance in his communications with staff and students after outbursts tied to his disabilities

14 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>