<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7083">I'm on the road again</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:30:43" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7083-01"><link>http://www.celebitchy.com/341643/ariana_grande_at_the_end_of_the_day_im_just_a_nice_italian_girl_from_boca/</link><title>Ariana Grande: ‘At the end of the day, I’m just a nice Italian girl from …</title><description>* Ariana Grande: ‘At the end of the day, I’m just a nice Italian girl from … 
, like, turnt up? That’s kind of the road that I, as a lady, would like to go down.” On her first date with Nathan Sykes […] again, which is sad. She was a hazard in Amsterdam: “I never want to be the person who avoids my own fans, so I always […] that the manager of her hotel dubbed Grande a safety risk and forbade her from going out on her balcony to wave to them. “I

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7083-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7083_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:34:07">http://www.archdaily.com/462086/the-indicator-on-the-road-again/</link><title>The Indicator: On the Road Again</title><description>* The Indicator: On the Road Again 
.9 FM KCRW out of Los Angeles. Follow Guy on Twitter  @GuyHorton . The Indicator: On the Road Again […] Architectural street gang and provocateurs, On the Road , named (I would like to think anyway) for Jack Kerouac […] out, and that wasn’t the case I’m told, but oh imagine if it were just some giant fabrication to get people out on a

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7083-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7083_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:34:46">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1910898-cotton-bowl-2014-henry-joseys-incredible-road-back-to-superstardom</link><title>Cotton Bowl 2014: Henry Joseys Incredible Road Back to Superstardom</title><description>* Cotton Bowl 2014: Henry Joseys Incredible Road Back to Superstardom 
on the sidelines. Again, after a scary scene, he got up. He kept getting up and the team kept producing. His comeback […] people in my life. It’s a big decision. But I’m just staying in the moment right now and focusing on the football game […] notion of simply being able to walk. On Friday in the Cotton Bowl, Josey walked into the end zone three times, capping off a

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7083-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7083_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:36:34">http://www.zerohedge.com/contributed/2013-12-31/journey-and-destination</link><title>The Journey and the Destination</title><description>* The Journey and the Destination 
road off of a back road up on the beautiful Blue Ridge Plateau of Southwestern Virginia. God’s country as I’m fond of say […] and a Virginia scenic byway. There are several points on the Destination road in either direction where we can […] wonderfully scenic. On the other hand the Destination road is just the opposite, narrow and twisty and demanding of my attention

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7083-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7083_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:39:47">http://blog.us.playstation.com/2014/01/08/the-audio-of-road-not-taken/</link><title>The Audio of Road Not Taken</title><description>* The Audio of Road Not Taken 
extends into the music you will hear in Road Not Taken. There is nothing that can sound quite like the real thing. I’m very […] very first time. I’m not done iterating on some of the stuff you hear in there, but by the time this video was released, I […] We recently added the first batch of sounds to Road Not Taken, and the team got really excited, like the game was

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7083-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7083_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:41:35">http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2013/12/31/watch-the-2009-video-that-has-phil-robertson-under-fire-yet-again/</link><title>Watch the 2009 Video That Has Phil Robertson Under Fire Yet Again</title><description>* Watch the 2009 Video That Has Phil Robertson Under Fire Yet Again 
for disparaging comments he made to GQ magazine about gay people but was reinstated by the network on Friday, Dec. 27. In […] cooks,” he said. “Make sure she carries her Bible — that will save you a lot of trouble down the road. And if she picks your […] difference between the two statements is quite significant, though many media outlets reporting on the video don’t appear to be

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7083-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7083_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:44:58">http://hollywoodlife.com/2014/01/02/selena-gomez-justin-bieber-back-together-couple-segways/</link><title>Selena Gomez Spotted With Justin Bieber Again — See The New Pic</title><description>* Selena Gomez Spotted With Justin Bieber Again — See The New Pic 
Are Selena and Justin back on the road to romance? The on-again, off-again couple were spotted riding Segways together […] in Justin’s gated community in Calabasas, Calif. on Jan. 2. And this isn’t the first time the pair have hung out in the […] , 19, might be kicking off 2014 as a couple! We told you Selena may have canceled her Australian tour to get over the

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7083-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7083_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:49:12">http://grist.org/food/ask-umbra-which-milk-alternative-is-the-lightest-on-the-land/</link><title>Ask Umbra: Which milk alternative is the lightest on the land?</title><description>* Ask Umbra: Which milk alternative is the lightest on the land? 
your cereal based on untested claims. I’m also going to dodge the question of taste differences between the options and […] the worldwide dairy industry has a substantial impact on the environment. First, there’s the production of all that […] impact on the planet than an animal-based one for the usual reasons: Veggie production uses far fewer resources than

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7083-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7083_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:52:25">http://www.deadline.com/2013/12/oscars-alexander-payne-nebraska-interview/</link><title>OSCARS Q&amp;A: Alexander Payne Returns Home For ‘Nebraska’</title><description>* OSCARS Q&amp;A: Alexander Payne Returns Home For ‘Nebraska’ 
characters, and hands-on again to offer suggestions. Related: OSCARS Q&amp;A: June Squibb On The Road To ‘Nebraska […] reason why I selected those people. So I’m hands-on in selecting the cast, hands-off to see what they do with their […] state—the gap allowed him to distance himself from his other road-trip movie, Sideways , and get Paramount behind his

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7083-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7083_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:56:01">http://www.bleedingcool.com/2014/01/07/visiting-your-friendly-neighborhood-rebellion-during-a-mini-apocalypse/</link><title>Visiting Your Friendly Neighborhood Rebellion – During a…</title><description>* Visiting Your Friendly Neighborhood Rebellion – During a… 
realized, really, given that where I’m staying is directly on a river and out my window I can hear and see the roar of […] me again of what I’d noticed back home in the USA at my local comic shop: that the offerings of trades from Rebellion had […] staying on the ground floor myself. Heading out to visit Rebellion, I suddenly found myself confronted with a good two to

14 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>