<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7091">don't listen to a word i say</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:05:20" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7091-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7091_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:05:21">http://www.webpronews.com/candace-cameron-bure-submissive-yet-open-to-hooker-2014-01</link><title>Candace Cameron Bure: Submissive Yet Open to Hooker</title><description>* Candace Cameron Bure: Submissive Yet Open to Hooker 
the story? Is something going to be taught? If the answer is yes, then absolutely I’ll play a hooker.” No word on if her […] , “It really depends on the story because I am an actress. I don’t want to play myself otherwise I would be a host, so I can […] : “I am not a passive person, but I chose to fall into a more submissive role in our relationship because I wanted to do

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7091-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7091_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:07:47">http://www.buzzfeed.com/vibills/12-essential-things-no-one-teaches-in-high-school-hfde</link><title>12 Important Things No One Teaches You When Learning A Language</title><description>* 12 Important Things No One Teaches You When Learning A Language 
don’t have time to correct every stinking kid who pronounces a word poorly, but that pronunciation can make the very key […] How do you say, “How you doing” in Italian? How to pick up cuties. Let’s face it, “tu es caliente” isn […] pop star. Via childhood-gifs.tumblr.com How to count. Oh yeah, I know TECHNICALLY, “Ein zwei drei” was

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7091-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7091_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:12:50">http://www.zerohedge.com/contributed/2014-01-10/sheer-absurdity-recovery-story</link><title>The Sheer Absurdity of the Recovery Story</title><description>* The Sheer Absurdity of the Recovery Story 
” continue to believe this stuff. I don’t get it. Is it mass delusion or are people really willing to believe a lie rather than […] that all of these arguments are grade “A” BS.   We are now five years into the “recovery.” The single and I mean SINGLE […] ? Nope. But for some reason people listen to the Fed and media make absurd proclamations and no one says anything.   At

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7091-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7091_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:14:28">http://www.webpronews.com/candace-cameron-bure-defines-submission-2014-01</link><title>Candace Cameron Bure Defines Submission</title><description>* Candace Cameron Bure Defines Submission 
itself out in her marriage definitely softens the sound of the rather foreboding term. “Listen, I love that my man is a […] submissive to your own husbands so that even if any of them are disobedient to the word, they may be won without a word by the […] ’t mean I don’t voice my opinion and it doesn’t mean I don’t have an opinion – I absolutely do but it is very difficult to

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7091-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7091_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:17:16">http://www.valuewalk.com/2014/01/behavioral-finance-pain-and-pleasure/</link><title>Behavioral Finance: Controlling the Investment Lizard Brain</title><description>* Behavioral Finance: Controlling the Investment Lizard Brain 
of those I listed have not .  But don’t take my word for it…listen or read the words of other experienced investors […] thing you should do is turn off the TV. And by turning off the TV, I mean stop listening to talking head commentators […] “wannabes”. Sure, you could throw my name into the list of people to ignore if you wanted to, but the difference is, at least I

14 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>