<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7098">tour moscow</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:25:05" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7098-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7098_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:25:06">http://venturebeat.com/2013/12/24/kazakhstani-businessman-kenges-rakishev-leads-3-7-million-round-in-moscow-startup-iqcard/</link><title>Kazakhstani businessman Kenges Rakishev leads $3.7 million round in …</title><description>* Kazakhstani businessman Kenges Rakishev leads $3.7 million round in … 
IQCard IQcard, a Moscow-based startup offering multifunction bank cards, has raised $3.7 million in a Series B round […] interest. IQCard has also partnered with tour operator TUI, book shop network Respublika, and other companies. Fastlane […] Ventures and Direct Group are Moscow-based investment companies controlled by French businessman Pascal Clément. One year ago

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7098-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7098_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:27:30">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/01/09/chuck-hagel-nuclear-missile-forces_n_4572058.html</link><title>Chuck Hagel Praises U.S. Nuclear Missile Forces, Reminded Of Morale …</title><description>* Chuck Hagel Praises U.S. Nuclear Missile Forces, Reminded Of Morale … 
-day tour of nuclear arms installations in New Mexico and Wyoming. Major General Michael Carey was fired as […] delegation to Moscow for talks on nuclear security. Speaking at F.E. Warren after touring the missile site in […] secretary said. Hagel said he had come away from his tour of the missile alert facility, which was across the 

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7098-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7098_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:30:33">http://venturebeat.com/2013/12/18/2-european-travel-startups-join-forces-to-become-world-leader-in-travel-activities/</link><title>2 European travel startups join forces to become world leader in travel …</title><description>* 2 European travel startups join forces to become world leader in travel … 
. Munich-based Excursiopedia has acquired Moscow-based Travelatus , in an effort to become a leader in helping travelers […] find local activities. Interestingly, both startups presented at DEMO Europe in Moscow earlier this year, and apparently […] also highly fragmented. There are thousands upon thousands of local tour companies, tour guides, and service providers, but

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7098-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7098_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:32:21">http://digbysblog.blogspot.nl/2013/12/ole-buckyll-be-back-before-you-can-say.html</link><title>Ole Buckyll be back before you can say "Blast Off"</title><description>* Ole Buckyll be back before you can say "Blast Off" 
Inspector General report released Thursday sheds more light into the case. It details the events of a July trip to Moscow in […] continued in Moscow, according to the report. While there, Carey and an unidentified man walked to a nearby hotel to meet "two […] minutes late in joining a delegation to the Moscow suburb of Sergiyev Posad, according to the report. He attributed the

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7098-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7098_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:35:29">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1897460-roy-jones-jr-vs-zine-eddine-benmakhlouf-winner-scorecard-and-analysis</link><title>Roy Jones Jr. vs. Zine Eddine Benmakhlouf: Winner, Scorecard and…</title><description>* Roy Jones Jr. vs. Zine Eddine Benmakhlouf: Winner, Scorecard and… 
Benmakhlouf (17-4) in Moscow. He earned the unanimous decision win. Here are the official scorecards, per BoxRec .com :  120 […] rang.  Jones Jr. was clearly on a victory tour of sorts the moment the 12th and final round concluded. He took selfies

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7098-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7098_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:37:33">http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2013/12/20/air-force-general-drank-excessively-fraternized-with-women-misbehaved-during-official-trip-to-russia-report/</link><title>Air Force General Drank Excessively, Fraternized With Women &amp; Misbehaved …</title><description>* Air Force General Drank Excessively, Fraternized With Women &amp; Misbehaved … 
concluded . The report details how Carey was drinking heavily during his official four day stay in Moscow and notes how him and […] who are in business to be kind of conveniently in the same place where we’re at, it seemed odd to me.” During a tour

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7098-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7098_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:38:52">http://hypebeast.com/2013/12/fresh-off-the-boat-with-eddie-huang-london-part-1</link><title>Fresh Off The Boat With Eddie Huang: London - Part 1</title><description>* Fresh Off The Boat With Eddie Huang: London - Part 1 
Following from an escapade in Moscow, this episode of Fresh Off The Boat sees Eddie Huang get a personal guided […] tour through Londons East End with former gangster Dave Courtney and local creative Alis Pelleschi. The group visit an old

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7098-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7098_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:41:41">http://www.balloon-juice.com/2013/12/17/onward-to-sochi/</link><title>Onward to Sochi</title><description>* Onward to Sochi 
put pressure on Moscow. Instead, IOC officials are pointing to statements by Mr. Putin that gay athletes and spectators […] man kissing another man ,” said [tour guide] Andrei. “Sooner or later, we’ll all follow your footsteps, but it’s not going

17 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>