<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7115">pittsburgh steelers news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:08:59" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7115-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7115_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:09:00">http://www.inquisitr.com/1078578/pittsburgh-steelers-coach-mike-tomlin-no-one-to-blame-but-ourselves/</link><title>Pittsburgh Steelers Coach Mike Tomlin: No One To Blame But Ourselves</title><description>* Pittsburgh Steelers Coach Mike Tomlin: No One To Blame But Ourselves 
Mike Tomlin, head coach of the Pittsburgh Steelers, has every right to be angry. With 7-8 Pittsburgh considered a long […] North’s punching bag, the Cleveland Browns, 20-7 at home in Pittsburgh’s own Heinz Field. Then the Steelers got the breaks […] win. Had Succop been given another kick—from 36 yards—and made it, the Pittsburgh Steelers would be watching the playoffs

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7115-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7115_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:10:09">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1902075-pittsburgh-steelers-a-closer-look-at-the-steelers-playoff-long-shot</link><title>Pittsburgh Steelers: A Closer Look at the Steelers Playoff Long Shot</title><description>* Pittsburgh Steelers: A Closer Look at the Steelers Playoff Long Shot 
AFC. And the Pittsburgh Steelers are among four teams working hard as the season wraps up. Had the Steelers handled […] Steelers, it is this one. Thats because there is news that the Chiefs might  rest some of their starters prior to the playoffs […] odds of the Steelers claiming the final AFC wild-card spot are long. This kind of late-season drama is just what the NFL

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7115-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7115_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:14:32">http://fansided.com/2013/12/22/pittsburgh-steelers-playoff-scenarios-pittsburgh-holds-slim-chance/</link><title>Pittsburgh Steelers playoff scenarios: Pittsburgh holds very slim …</title><description>* Pittsburgh Steelers playoff scenarios: Pittsburgh holds very slim … 
The Pittsburgh Steelers have a very slim chance of making the postseason after a slow start to the regular season, but […] plenty of help. Obviously, the Steelers need to win out in order to make […] Pittsburgh Steelers playoff scenarios […] : Pittsburgh holds very slim chance - FanSided - FanSided - Sports News, Entertainment, Lifestyle &amp; Technology - 240+ Sites

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7115-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7115_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:15:44">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1891113-what-to-expect-from-eddie-lacy-the-green-bay-packers-offense-in-week-16</link><title>Pittsburgh Steelers vs. Green Bay Packers: Looking Ahead to Sundays …</title><description>* Pittsburgh Steelers vs. Green Bay Packers: Looking Ahead to Sundays … 
The 7-6-1 Green Bay Packers will have a huge game against the 6-8 Pittsburgh Steelers at snowy Lambeau Field on […] destiny. If the Packers can win their last two games of the regular season versus the Steelers on Sunday and then a week […] injury, the Packers placed him on the injured reserve, designated to return list. The good news for the Packers is that both

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7115-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7115_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:19:45">http://www.inquisitr.com/1078235/pittsburgh-steelers-miss-playoffs-after-refs-blow-chargers-chiefs-call/</link><title>Pittsburgh Steelers Miss Playoffs After Refs Blow Chargers-Chiefs Call</title><description>* Pittsburgh Steelers Miss Playoffs After Refs Blow Chargers-Chiefs Call 
The Pittsburgh Steelers will be watching the playoffs from home this season, and they have a mistake by referees at the […] , there was a glimmer of hope. Playoff hopes for the Pittsburgh Steelers would rest on the Chargers losing against the Chiefs […] admitted to the error , but for the Pittsburgh Steelers the damage is already done. They reached the doorstep of the

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7115-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7115_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:23:31">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1917872-did-the-pittsburgh-steelers-leak-a-picture-of-a-chrome-alternate-helmet</link><title>Did the Pittsburgh Steelers Leak a Picture of a Chrome Alternate…</title><description>* Did the Pittsburgh Steelers Leak a Picture of a Chrome Alternate… 
The official Pittsburgh Steelers Instagram account posted this photo Thursday of a partially chrome helmet and facemask […] week. Maybe theyre for practice; maybe theyre just for show. One things for sure: Theyre a far cry from the Steelers image

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7115-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7115_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:25:46">http://fansided.com/2014/01/16/pittsburgh-steelers-may-cut-preseason-ticket-prices/</link><title>Pittsburgh Steelers may cut preseason ticket prices</title><description>* Pittsburgh Steelers may cut preseason ticket prices 
little time that the starters spend playing. One of the ways to resolve the […] Pittsburgh Steelers may cut preseason […] ticket prices - FanSided - FanSided - Sports News, Entertainment, Lifestyle &amp; Technology - 240+ Sites

13 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7115-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7115_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:26:46">http://www.balloon-juice.com/2013/12/29/i-wish-all-steelers-haters-could-watch-the-pittsburgh-news-tonight/</link><title>I Wish All Steelers Haters Could Watch the Pittsburgh News Tonight</title><description>* I Wish All Steelers Haters Could Watch the Pittsburgh News Tonight 
hard. The Steelers had no business in the playoffs this year. The Chargers won, I took down my 11′ flag, put up the Pens […] flag, and moved on. But man, people in the ‘burgh are not handling things well. Every 11 o’clock news cast has this

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7115-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7115_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:30:00">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1896261-steelers-vs-packers-examining-top-fantasy-stars-and-playoff-implications</link><title>Steelers vs. Packers: Examining Top Fantasy Stars and Playoff…</title><description>* Steelers vs. Packers: Examining Top Fantasy Stars and Playoff… 
The Pittsburgh Steelers and Green Bay Packers are still alive in the playoff chase heading into their Week 16 clash […] get some help elsewhere. The good news is that a home game with the Cleveland Browns, who the Steelers beat by 16 on the […] Talk gives a quick synopsis of what must happen for Pittsburgh: Ultimately, the Steelers need to go 2-0 while the Jets go

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7115-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7115_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:31:27">http://fansided.com/2014/01/03/pittsburgh-steelers-fire-offensive-line-coach/</link><title>Pittsburgh Steelers fire offensive line coach</title><description>* Pittsburgh Steelers fire offensive line coach 
After just a single season, Pittsburgh Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin has fired the team’s offensive line coach, Jack […]  Maurkice Pouncey (torn ACL) in the opener. They had to deal with in-game injuries, it seemed, on a […] Pittsburgh Steelers fire […] Bicknell Jr. According to ESPN, The Steelers lost two starting centers during the course of the season, including Pro Bowler

15 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>