<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7119">chocolate photo</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:41:29" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7119-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7119_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:41:30">http://www.buzzfeed.com/christinebyrne/boozy-hot-chocolate-kit</link><title>How To Make A Boozy Hot Chocolate Gift Kit</title><description>* How To Make A Boozy Hot Chocolate Gift Kit 
Makes 1 gift in a wide-mouth, 16-oz clip jar (pictured here) INGREDIENTS For Hot Chocolate Mix ½ cup unsweetened cocoa […] chopped mexican chocolate 1 cup marshmallows For Gift Assembly 1 quart-sized, wide mouth jar Parchment paper Twine or […] powder, then sugar, then cayenne, then chopped chocolate, then cardamom pods. Lay the cinnamon sticks and vanilla bean on top

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7119-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7119_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:45:16">http://eater.com/archives/2013/12/31/shake-shacks-second-boston-location-opens-this-week.php</link><title>Shack Attack: Shake Shacks 2nd Boston-Area Location Opens This Week</title><description>* Shack Attack: Shake Shacks 2nd Boston-Area Location Opens This Week 
Shake Shack Chestnut Hill, Boston. [Photo: Rachel Leah Blumenthal/Eater Boston] Happy New Year, Boston, youre […] blended with a slice of crimson red velvet cake from South End Buttery Bakery" while MInT Chocolate will feature "chocolate […] frozen custard blended with minted marshmallow sauce and chocolate truffle cookie dough." There are several other domestic

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7119-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7119_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:49:16">http://www.refinery29.com/foodie-underground/4</link><title>This Gluten-Free Chocolate Cakes Surprising Ingredient</title><description>* This Gluten-Free Chocolate Cakes Surprising Ingredient 
Photo: Courtesy of Foodie Underground . Foodie Underground , a project curated in part by Anna Brones, explores our […] beginners guide to pesto. Hungry yet? Ive made a lot of jokes about putting kale into a chocolate cake. Most of my friends don […] : Mix It Up With This Hazelnut And Kale Pesto Putting kale in a chocolate cake might not be your first choice in recipe

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7119-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7119_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:52:57">http://www.refinery29.com/peppermint-bark-recipe</link><title>An Easy &amp; Delicious Homemade Gift For One Last Holiday Hurrah</title><description>* An Easy &amp; Delicious Homemade Gift For One Last Holiday Hurrah 
Photo: Courtesy of Liz McAvoy/What Dress Code? With the chaos of the holiday season wrapping up, some much-needed time […] . Ingredients 2 sleeves Saltine crackers 1 cup butter (2 sticks) 1 cup sugar 1 tsp vanilla 1 bag chocolate chips (try half […] semisweet and half dark chocolate) 12 miniature candy canes, roughly crushed Preheat oven to 300 degrees; line a baking sheet

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7119-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7119_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:55:59">http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2013/12/25/get-ready-for-a-holiday-treat-straight-from-the-glenn-beck-recipe-box/</link><title>Get Ready for a Holiday Treat Straight From the Glenn Beck Recipe Box</title><description>* Get Ready for a Holiday Treat Straight From the Glenn Beck Recipe Box 
lactose intolerant. Photo credit: Shutterstock Here’s the recipe: Glenn’s Coma Hot Chocolate 5 pints of LIGHT CREAM […] image via Shutterstock. Cozying up with a steaming mug of hot chocolate is a holiday tradition in the Beck household, as […] Glenn Beck himself has mentioned in the past. But be forewarned, Beck’s hot chocolate is not for the faint of heart — or the

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7119-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7119_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:00:37">http://www.refinery29.com/new-potato/49</link><title>ABCs New Leading Lady Shares Her Fave NYC Eats</title><description>* ABCs New Leading Lady Shares Her Fave NYC Eats 
Photo: Courtesy of The New Potato . On a quest for the next big thing in the food industry, sisters Danielle and Laura […] questionnaires, the world of dining has reached a whole new level of delish. This week, the ladies lend us Cat Coras insane chocolate […] family make their own organic goat cheese, Santa Gadea, on a farm in Spain. No wonder she wanted her photo-shoot at BKLYN

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7119-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7119_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:04:52">http://eater.com/archives/2013/12/26/listage-229.php</link><title>Listage: Chefs Add Catering Arms; White Chocolate: Trendy</title><description>* Listage: Chefs Add Catering Arms; White Chocolate: Trendy 
Hello Robin, Seattle [Photo: S. Pratt/Eater Seattle] ] · Celebrity Chefs Add Catering Arm to Boost Revenue […] [Dallas Morning News] · White Chocolate, a Blank Slate for Flavor, Wins Converts [WSJ] · The New Rush to Dine Out on

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7119-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7119_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:05:33">http://www.refinery29.com/60584</link><title>5 Things To Know This AM</title><description>* 5 Things To Know This AM 
Get to know your favorite chocolate bar — behind the scenes at the Willy Wonka Mast Brothers Chocolate Factory in […] , shorts, and more will be up to 70% off online and in store! #UsefulRhymes ( Courtshop ) Photo: Courtesy of Courtshop

13 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7119-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7119_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:08:08">http://consumerist.com/2014/01/07/easter-creep-spreads-to-cvs-looks-delicious/</link><title>Easter Creep Spreads To CVS, Looks Delicious</title><description>* Easter Creep Spreads To CVS, Looks Delicious 
chocolate eggs and plastic bunnies hit store shelves before all of the unsold Christmas decorations are off the clearance shelf […] . Normally, Kroger does some very innovative things in the Easter Creep field. In 2011, they even dragged out the chocolate eggs […] during the first week of December . You know, for your Easter stocking . Reader Gail sent us the above photo from her local

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7119-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7119_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:10:28">http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2013/12/25/how-to-take-unforgettable-pictures-this-christmas/</link><title>How To Take Unforgettable Pictures This Christmas</title><description>* How To Take Unforgettable Pictures This Christmas 
amazing.” Author and photographer George Lange appears on CBS This Morning. (Photo: CBS This Morning) So what can we do […] This Morning. (Photo: CBS This Morning) But what can be done about family photos? Instances where the photographer must […] the other night, we had profiteroles downtown in New York, and afterwards there was all this chocolate sauce around on the

16 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>