<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7131">golf games</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:26:06" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7131-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7131_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:26:07">http://www.businessinsider.com/highest-paid-golfers-2014-1</link><title>CHART: The 20 Highest-Paid Golfers</title><description>* CHART: The 20 Highest-Paid Golfers 
Golf Digest has released its 11th annual " Golf Digest 50 money list " which looks at the total earnings for golfers […] total earnings, some of the other names at the top of the list may be a surprise to many. According to GolfDigest.com, off […] -course earnings includes "endorsements, bonuses, appearance fees, corporate outings, speaking engagements, licensing fees (video games

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7131-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7131_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:30:31">http://www.sbnation.com/golf/2014/1/3/5267252/hyundai-tournament-of-champions-2014-streaming-online-tv-schedule-friday</link><title>How to watch 2014 Tournament of Champions online, TV schedule and more</title><description>* How to watch 2014 Tournament of Champions online, TV schedule and more 
slate (as opposed to say, a mishmash of guys playing at CordeValle in October). Golf Channel has the unfortunate task of […] towards the backend of the tee sheet. So while we all freeze in the eastern U.S., some of the games best will begin the 2014 […] Round -- Friday, Jan. 3 Television Golf Channel 4:30 p.m. to 10 p.m. ET Streaming NBC/Golf Channel Live

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7131-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7131_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:33:31">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1916062-sony-open-2014-tee-times-date-and-tv-schedule</link><title>Sony Open 2014: Tee Times, Date and TV Schedule</title><description>* Sony Open 2014: Tee Times, Date and TV Schedule 
and breathtaking layout of this gorgeous course, but their games are treated to the course that proved to be  the easiest […] , Honolulu, Hawaii TV Schedule:  Golf Channel has the broadcast for all four rounds from 9 a.m. to 12:30 p.m. ET Tee Times […] -10s in one of the best rookie seasons golf fans have seen in years: The 20-year-old does not look ready to fall

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7131-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7131_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:35:14">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1866412-julie-chu-olympic-profile-of-us-hockey-hopeful-for-sochi-2014</link><title>Julie Chu: Olympic Profile of US Hockey Hopeful for Sochi 2014</title><description>* Julie Chu: Olympic Profile of US Hockey Hopeful for Sochi 2014 
Crash course:   Julie Chu is a forward preparing to play in her fourth Olympic games in Sochi , Russia […] her 129-game college career at Harvard, where she majored in psychology. She has played 25 games with the U.S. national […] coaching hockey, Chu likes to play golf , cook and read. You can follow the Harvard grad on Twitter @JulieChu13  and

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7131-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7131_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:37:55">http://www.slashgear.com/wii-u-sports-club-golf-now-available-19309388/</link><title>Wii U Sports Club Golf now available</title><description>* Wii U Sports Club Golf now available 
I always thought that some of the best games on the original Nintendo Wii were the Wii Sports Mini games that came with

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7131-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7131_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:39:03">http://www.macrumors.com/2014/01/10/ibeacons-gaming/</link><title>Apples iBeacon Technology Brings New Possibilities for Location-Based …</title><description>* Apples iBeacon Technology Brings New Possibilities for Location-Based … 
Apples iBeacons have a lot of potential for inclusion in location-based games, according to The Tap Lab CEO Dave […] incorporated into a whole new category of games that offer multiplayer interactions and other features at specific real […] on, is also a promising technology for upcoming games. Pkpkt , a game released in mid-December, utilizes Bluetooth LE

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7131-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7131_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:43:07">http://www.sbnation.com/2014/1/7/5283534/lindsey-vonn-injury-2014-winter-olympics-sochi</link><title>2014 Winter Olympics: Lindsey Vonn announces she will not compete due …</title><description>* 2014 Winter Olympics: Lindsey Vonn announces she will not compete due … 
medalist Lindsey Vonn  announced on Tuesday that she will not compete at the 2014 Winter Games in Sochi due to setbacks in her […] her Olympic debut at age 17 when she competed in the 2002 Winter Games in Salt Lake City, but finished no better than […] World Cup titles and the gold medal in downhill at the 2010 Winter Games, as well as the bronze in Super-G. At the 2013

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7131-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7131_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:45:17">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1915053-zach-johnson-overcomes-dustin-johnson-plus-three-major-champs-on-maui</link><title>Zach Johnson Overcomes Dustin Johnson Plus Three Major Champs on Maui</title><description>* Zach Johnson Overcomes Dustin Johnson Plus Three Major Champs on Maui 
contention because so much is going to happen," he explained. In his last two tournaments, Zach Johnson has taken on the games […] , Jordan Spieth , the next big thing in golf, put up a good fight, but a bobble near the end, where he chipped and had the

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7131-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7131_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:50:03">http://www.webpronews.com/nintendo-reveals-new-zelda-game-in-nintendo-direct-2013-12</link><title>Nintendo Reveals New Zelda Game In Nintendo Direct</title><description>* Nintendo Reveals New Zelda Game In Nintendo Direct 
games in a new Nintendo Direct. While most of the information was about games we already knew about, Nintendo took some time […] to reveal some brand new games as well. Starting off, Nintendo revealed that it’s working with Tecmo Koei on a new […] game will be similar to past Kirby games, but will take advantage of the 3DS by allowing Kirby to switch between planes

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7131-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7131_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:51:47">http://www.webpronews.com/penn-state-coach-likely-to-be-vandys-james-franklin-2014-01</link><title>Penn State Coach Likely to be Vandy’s James Franklin</title><description>* Penn State Coach Likely to be Vandy’s James Franklin 
the offer to keep @jamesfranklinvu here.. Free golf lessons for life if he stays.. Impossible to turn down […] Commodores to a 24-15 record, winning 16 of his last 20 games as head coach while leading Vanderbilt to 3 consecutive Bowl Games […] . Before Franklin, Vanderbilt had won a total of 13 SEC conference games in 10 years and had

14 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>