<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7133">museum of natural history</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:57:35" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7133-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7133_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:57:36">http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2013/12/18/museum-removes-gods-creatures-quote-from-exhibit-following-atheistic-evolution-professors-complaints/</link><title>Museum Removes ‘God’s Creatures’ Quote From Exhibit</title><description>* Museum Removes ‘God’s Creatures’ Quote From Exhibit 
The Natural History Museum of Los Angeles County removed a quote that references “God’s creatures” from one of its […] the Natural History Museum, a public institution. Credit: Jerry Coyne/Why Evolution Is True Blog “Given the quotation […] personal statements in such a manner has the potential to cause confusion,” read a statement from The Natural History Museum

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7133-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7133_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:59:44">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/12/27/dinosaur-feathers-species-scales-armor_n_4508734.html</link><title>Dinosaur Feathers Study Suggests Most Species Had Scales Or Armor</title><description>* Dinosaur Feathers Study Suggests Most Species Had Scales Or Armor 
Paul Barrett of the Natural History Museum in London and David Evans of the Royal Ontario Museum in Toronto created a […] Birds evolved from dinosaurs, and dinosaur fossils are often covered with impressions of feathers, which made some […] palaeontologists speculate whether feathers were a common trait that appeared early in their history. Now a team analyzing feathers on

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7133-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7133_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:03:47">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/01/07/cockroach-fossils-insects-evolution-timeline_n_4554160.html</link><title>Cockroach Fossils Found In Colorado Shed Light On Insects Evolutionary …</title><description>* Cockroach Fossils Found In Colorado Shed Light On Insects Evolutionary … 
Labandeira of the Smithsonian Institutions National Museum of Natural History said in a statement. "But the discovery in Colorado […] fossil findings. More than 70 species of cockroaches in the genus Ectobius currently crawl through Europe and Africa […] , making them amongst the most common cockroaches in that part of the world. They measure only about 0.25 to 0.5 inches long (6

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7133-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7133_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:08:21">http://www.ibtimes.com/kate-middleton-pregnant-again-duchess-expecting-royal-baby-no-2-prince-william-report-1525152</link><title>Kate Middleton Pregnant Again? Duchess Expecting Royal Baby No. 2 With …</title><description>* Kate Middleton Pregnant Again? Duchess Expecting Royal Baby No. 2 With … 
Natural History Museum Alive 3D" at the Natural History Museum in London last month. […] The Duke and Duchess of Cambridge,Prince William and his wife Kate Middleton, at a screening of "David Attenboroughs

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7133-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7133_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:09:51">http://grist.org/living/a-poison-aficionados-guide-to-6-killer-chemicals/</link><title>A poison aficionado’s guide to 6 killer chemicals</title><description>* A poison aficionado’s guide to 6 killer chemicals 
about lead risks in your home, see this  infographic  or  click here . Aram Dulyan Native arsenic from the Natural History […] Museum, London. 2. Arsenic.  Another naturally occurring heavy metal, arsenic may not be the favored tool of criminal […] Steve and Sarah Emry Antifreeze is a favorite of today’s poisoners, because of its sweet taste. This episode of

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7133-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7133_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:13:37">http://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2014-01/pp-mrp010914.php</link><title>Minimalistic raiding parties of a slave-hunting ant crack castles</title><description>* Minimalistic raiding parties of a slave-hunting ant crack castles 
A group of scientists from the University of Mainz and the Senckenberg Museum of Natural History Goerlitz, headed by

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7133-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7133_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:15:48">http://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2014-01/amon-rur010714.php</link><title>Researchers unveil rich world of fish biofluorescence</title><description>* Researchers unveil rich world of fish biofluorescence 
A team led by scientists from the American Museum of Natural History has released the first report of widespread […] biofluorescence in fishes, identifying more than 180 species that glow in a wide range of colors and patterns. Published today in PLOS

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7133-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7133_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:19:55">http://grist.org/list/bone-worm-dick-head-osedax-mucofloris/</link><title>This weird deep-sea worm has a dick on its head</title><description>* This weird deep-sea worm has a dick on its head 
!) Plus, it looks like a fluffy pink cloud. Well, a cloud with a giant dick blossoming out of it: Natural History Museum […] ,” says Dr. Adrian Glover, a marine biologist with London’s Natural History Museum. As opposed to a less-extreme example […] makes it easier to fertilize the females’ eggs.) “It’s an extreme example of males being reduced to simply a bag of sperm

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7133-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7133_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:24:26">http://www.archdaily.com/461783/heneghan-peng-architects-selected-to-design-contemporary-arts-center-in-moscow/</link><title>Heneghan Peng Architects Selected to Design Contemporary Arts Center in …</title><description>* Heneghan Peng Architects Selected to Design Contemporary Arts Center in … 
though layers of gallery. The landscape proposal responds to the scale of the park, and to its history as an airfield […] naturalistic landscape. In the middle of all this development, on the edge of this large city, an intense natural environment is […] . Creating an awareness of all of the Museum’s activities for the visitor. As with any travel plan, the main issue is how

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7133-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7133_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:25:49">http://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2014-01/esoa-sns010114.php</link><title>7 new species of nearctic wasps described and illustrated</title><description>* 7 new species of nearctic wasps described and illustrated 
After studying specimens from the Nearctic deposited in the United States National Museum of Natural History and some […] specimens in the Canadian National Collection of Insects, researchers have found 16 new species of wasps from the Nearctic

15 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>