<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7141">Cambridge must do</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:11:01" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7141-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7141_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:11:02">http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2013/12/17/harvard-student-accused-of-making-campus-bomb-hoax-to-get-out-of-final-exam/</link><title>Harvard Student Accused of Making Campus Bomb Hoax to Get Out of Final …</title><description>* Harvard Student Accused of Making Campus Bomb Hoax to Get Out of Final … 
of the Harvard Crimson newspaper, according to a criminal complaint filed by the U.S. attorney’s office. CAMBRIDGE, MA […] – DECEMBER 16: A police car seals off Quincy Street at Harvard University during a bomb scare December 16, 2013 in Cambridge […] Cambridge, just outside Boston, were shut down for hours before investigators determined there were no explosives. Kim, who

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7141-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7141_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:15:33">http://venturebeat.com/2014/01/06/csr-fashions-wearable-bluetooth-smart-jewelry/</link><title>Bluetooth Smart jewelry is the next fusion of fashion and tech</title><description>* Bluetooth Smart jewelry is the next fusion of fashion and tech 
? Cambridge, England-based chip maker CSR, best known for its wireless chips, will test the limits as it fuses fashion and […] technology devices must look good, and 67 percent admit that it is important that the wearables fit with their own personal style […] could do with this technology. The possibilities for truly wearable technology devices are endless and we’re looking forward

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7141-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7141_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:16:42">http://www.refinery29.com/2014/01/60354/kate-middleton-birthday</link><title>How Wed Spend Kate Middletons Birthday Cash</title><description>* How Wed Spend Kate Middletons Birthday Cash 
of England, plain and simple. Which means that a birthday for the duchess of Cambridge — she turns the big 3-2 today […] family each year. So, just imagine how many Middleton must receive, not to mention the spoils her doting husband and royal […] relatives will likely bestow. Were talking a serious payday. But, whats a duchess to do with it all? Well, we decided to spend

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7141-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7141_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:19:15">http://www.zerohedge.com/news/2014-01-01/bill-de-blasio-inaugurated-109th-mayor-new-york-city-live-webcast</link><title>Bill de Blasio Inaugurated As 109th Mayor Of New York City - Live …</title><description>* Bill de Blasio Inaugurated As 109th Mayor Of New York City - Live … 
take on the new mayor. In de Blasio, New York voters chose a Cambridge, Massachusetts-bred Boston Red Sox fan who […] increase would be $973 a year, according to the Independent Budget Office, a municipal agency.   “We must first admit that […] the affordability crisis exists, and then resolve, together, to do something about it,” he said in an October speech to

15 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>