<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7146">why do leaves fall</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:24:09" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7146-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7146_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:24:10">http://hollywoodlife.com/2014/01/06/revenge-homecoming-emily-belongs-with-aiden/</link><title>‘Revenge’: Emily Thorne Needs To Only Date Aiden From Now On</title><description>* ‘Revenge’: Emily Thorne Needs To Only Date Aiden From Now On 
ever dated anyone but Aiden ever again. Here’s why. Throughout Season 1 of Revenge , we all wanted to see Emily Thorne […] Daniel could easily make a girl go weak in the knees — and make her quick to forgive even the most heinous of crimes — but do […] ’s a dealbreaker, lady!” Indeed it is. After years of a “will she or won’t she actually fall in love with Daniel” plot

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7146-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7146_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:26:14">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1907198-lay-off-him-la-clippers-deandre-jordan-is-actually-underrated</link><title>Lay Off Him, LA Clippers DeAndre Jordan Is Actually Underrated</title><description>* Lay Off Him, LA Clippers DeAndre Jordan Is Actually Underrated 
unable or unwilling (which might be more accurate) to protect the rim defensively, all the duties fall on Jordan. Ryan […] of Jordans caliber that come at a substantially better value.    Getting Better Another big reason why Jordan […] , and his individual post defense leaves something to be desired.  Ultimately, though, most teams would happily take a 7

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7146-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7146_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:28:14">http://www.refinery29.com/2014/01/60090/engagements-spike-during-holidays</link><title>Twas The Season To Get Engaged, Apparently</title><description>* Twas The Season To Get Engaged, Apparently 
? So, lets see. That leaves approximately 330 days to meet someone, fall in love, charm the family, buy a ring, and pop the […] pros written down right in front us, getting engaged during the holidays kind of feels like the only way to do it, right […] some more R29 goodness, right here? Polyamory: 3 Fascinating &amp; True Stories The Science Of Why You Tell

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7146-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7146_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:32:36">http://www.zerohedge.com/news/2013-12-18/real-numbers-behind-americas-phony-recovery</link><title>The Real Numbers Behind Americas Phony Recovery</title><description>* The Real Numbers Behind Americas Phony Recovery 
, waiting to find out what the Fed will do. Taper? No taper? Or maybe it will taper on the tapering off? Our guess is the Fed […] leaves office. Hell want to go out on a high note… …and that means guaranteeing more liquidity. Investors dont seem […] growth and innovation, they say. Compared to emerging markets, it is a paragon of stability and confidence. How much do

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7146-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7146_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:36:18">http://www.business2community.com/online-marketing/use-wordpress-avoid-garbage-truck-risk-0729173</link><title>Use WordPress and Avoid the Garbage Truck Risk.</title><description>* Use WordPress and Avoid the Garbage Truck Risk. 
. Unfortunately, in my experience, many small businesses fall prey to this scenario. If any one person, who has unique knowledge and […] expertise that only he/she has, leaves the company, “cracks” begin to develop. Tasks begin to get dumped on to other employees […] for those companies who do not have the proper resources needed to develop and maintain a website built from scratch. The

15 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>