<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7174">seal team 6</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:54:12" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7174-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7174_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:54:13">http://espn.go.com/blog/nflnation/post/_/id/109999/rams-seal-second-pick-from-redskins</link><title>Rams seal second pick from Redskins</title><description>* Rams seal second pick from Redskins 
everywhere that his team would not hold the second pick in the NFL draft again under his watch.That’s a promise Fisher will be […] happy to break after his team added the No. 2 selection in the 2014 NFL draft to the ever-growing haul it received from the […] Washington Redskins on Sunday.The Redskins’ 20-6 loss to the New York Giants dropped them to 3-13 on the year, the second worst

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7174-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7174_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:55:25">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1903531-where-exactly-did-it-go-wrong-for-the-new-york-giants</link><title>Where Exactly Did It Go Wrong for the New York Giants?</title><description>* Where Exactly Did It Go Wrong for the New York Giants? 
interest in this team will look too fondly on in years to come.   Perhaps in retrospect, warning signs  of a collapse were […] first team in Super Bowl history to participate in the sport’s biggest game hosted in their home venue. Whatever the […] the outcome would have been much different. We know about the 0-6 start—its gong to take a long time to erase that memory

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7174-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7174_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:56:36">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1914656-syracuse-basketball-how-orange-should-adjust-when-trevor-cooney-goes-cold</link><title>Syracuse Basketball: How Orange Should Adjust When Trevor Cooney Goes …</title><description>* Syracuse Basketball: How Orange Should Adjust When Trevor Cooney Goes … 
basket. He has made 75.6 percent of his shots (31 out of 41) on the season, which leads the team. If he gets good post […] struggled, but the defense carried the team to a 49-44 win over the visiting Hurricanes. Notable in its absence was the net […] late free throws to help seal the win, but he just didnt have it from deep. Syracuse fans had been spoiled by Cooney s 50

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7174-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7174_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:00:22">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1904937-panthers-defense-not-cam-newton-will-make-or-break-panthers-super-bowl-run</link><title>Panthers Defense, Not Cam Newton, Will Make or Break Panthers Super Bowl …</title><description>* Panthers Defense, Not Cam Newton, Will Make or Break Panthers Super Bowl … 
opposing team’s total yardage eclipse the 400-yard mark. On offense, the Panthers and Newton have been both hot and cold […] . Between Weeks 6 and 9, Carolina’s offense was humming, thumping teams by an average of 20.5 points per game. In each of those […] games, it scored at least 30 points. Newton had a coming-out party of sorts. In Carolina’s Week 6 win over Minnesota

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7174-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7174_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:01:23">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1900626-nfl-playoff-picture-2013-postseason-outlook-for-afc-and-nfc-teams-in-contention</link><title>NFL Playoff Picture 2013: Postseason Outlook for AFC and NFC Teams in …</title><description>* NFL Playoff Picture 2013: Postseason Outlook for AFC and NFC Teams in … 
for each team still in contention, courtesy of NFL.com .   AFC Playoff Spots Heading into Week 17, only a […] Kansas City Chiefs have already clinched berths. This leaves four teams fighting for the No. 6 seed in the AFC with […] amazingly no team controlling its own destiny. The Dolphins are likely in the drivers seat at this point because they would get

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7174-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7174_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:03:07">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1907933-auburn-vs-fsu-top-nfl-prospects-in-bcs-national-championship-game</link><title>Auburn vs. FSU: Top NFL Prospects in BCS National Championship Game</title><description>* Auburn vs. FSU: Top NFL Prospects in BCS National Championship Game 
was a big mistake. Hes in the top 10, 15 easy if he comes out. Robinson can make a name for himself on Jan. 6 on […] they do in the trenches on a weekly basis. The way he fights on every snap to create gaps for his running back or seal up […] game, which makes him the perfect fit for a team like the Kansas City Chiefs at No. 24. Alex Smith could use another weapon

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7174-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7174_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:05:31">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1900842-nfl-power-rankings-league-wide-assessment-heading-into-week-17</link><title>NFL Power Rankings: League-Wide Assessment Heading into Week 17</title><description>* NFL Power Rankings: League-Wide Assessment Heading into Week 17 
Seattles two recent losses to San Francisco and Arizona fool you into thinking the Seahawks arent the best team in the NFL […] .  Theyll prove it with authority in Week 17 when they host the St. Louis Rams. Look for a big response from Pete Carrolls team […] Falcons team that wanted to play spoiler on Monday Night Football in Week 16, winning their fifth straight game in the

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7174-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7174_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:06:40">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1904741-premier-league-scores-week-19-breaking-down-biggest-results-from-weekend</link><title>Premier League Scores Week 19: Breaking Down Biggest Results from …</title><description>* Premier League Scores Week 19: Breaking Down Biggest Results from … 
Tom Huddlestone . The team then added two more later in the contest to seal a decisive 6-0 victory. Hull City has been […] this point.   Hull City Destroys Fulham , 6-0 Hull City and Fulham are two teams likely going nowhere this […] would be detrimental to the teams successes in the upcoming weeks. Chelsea didnt come away unscathed, either. Team leader

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7174-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7174_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:07:43">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1907666-iowa-vs-lsu-score-grades-and-analysis-from-2014-outback-bowl</link><title>Iowa vs. LSU: Score, Grades and Analysis from 2014 Outback Bowl</title><description>* Iowa vs. LSU: Score, Grades and Analysis from 2014 Outback Bowl 
total yards and a 6-of-19 showing on third down.    It was apparent on the first drive of the game how LSU would attack the […] allowed Jennings to kneel the ball to seal the win, 21-14.    Key Player Grades Jeremy Hill, RB, LSU: A It was […] Rudock, QB, Iowa: C Rudock was either going to make or break the game for the Hawkeyes, as the team offensively was

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7174-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7174_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:08:58">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1901283-houston-rockets-vs-san-antonio-spurs-postgame-grades-and-analysis</link><title>Houston Rockets vs. San Antonio Spurs: Postgame Grades and Analysis</title><description>* Houston Rockets vs. San Antonio Spurs: Postgame Grades and Analysis 
Southwest Division showdown.  All five Rockets starters scored in double figures on a night when the team collectively shot 52 […]  Ari Temkin .  With the win, the Rockets became the fourth road team through four games to capture a victory on Christmas […] straight points helped seal the deal for Houston.  Grade: A+   Dwight Howard , Houston Rockets, Center In a 40-point

16 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>