<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7176"> weather in nyc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:37:21" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7176-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7176_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:37:22">http://www.zerohedge.com/news/2014-01-05/jfk-shuts-down-after-plane-skids-ice-skating-rink-runway-entire-nation-blanketed-sub</link><title>JFK Shuts Down After Plane Skids Off "Ice Skating Rink" Runway: Entire …</title><description>* JFK Shuts Down After Plane Skids Off "Ice Skating Rink" Runway: Entire … 
werent frigid enough, the wind chill in much of Midwest and Great Plains could drop to minus 50, the National Weather Service […] digits.   To put things in perspective, the weather in Atlanta on Monday will be colder than in Anchorage, Alaska, CNN […] below," the National Weather Services Twin Cities office in Minnesota said. Forecasters there warned of "the coldest air in

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7176-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7176_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:40:41">http://hollywoodlife.com/2014/01/07/freezing-temperatures-us-celebs-react-twitter/</link><title>Freezing Temperatures Around The Nation — Celebs React</title><description>* Freezing Temperatures Around The Nation — Celebs React 
) January 7, 2014 How cold is it where you are right now? It’s 6 here in NYC. Feels like -15. — Carson Daly (@Carson […] Longeretta More Weather News: Snow Boots — Survive The Winter Weather In Style SHOP Stylish, Cold Weather Accessories […] January 6, Chicago, Illinois set a record for lowest temperature ever hitting minus 16 degrees! Meanwhile in New York on Jan

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7176-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7176_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:43:42">http://hollywoodlife.com/2014/01/03/snow-boots-for-women-nyc-weather-snow/</link><title>Snow Boots — Survive The Winter Weather In Style</title><description>* Snow Boots — Survive The Winter Weather In Style 
fashionable snow boots if you want to brave the blizzard in style. Here in NYC, we are feeling the wrath of Hercules — the first […] where you have to go safely in the winter weather, but they will also keep you looking seriously stylish if you step out in […] Winter is here in full force — but that doesn’t mean you have to sacrifice your sense of style! SHOP these durable yet

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7176-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7176_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:46:35">http://www.inquisitr.com/1082147/weather-ravages-eastern-u-s-9-die-and-snow-tops-2-feet/</link><title>Weather Ravages Eastern U.S., 9 Die And Snow Tops 2 Feet</title><description>* Weather Ravages Eastern U.S., 9 Die And Snow Tops 2 Feet 
A weather nightmare is ringing in the New Year on a frigid and dangerous note as some areas in the northeast United […] , another merciless Arctic blast is sweeping in from Canada , bringing what the National Weather Service describes at […] inches of snowfall in some regions, ordered three major highways in New York temporarily shut down as the National Weather

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7176-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7176_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:50:17">http://www.zerohedge.com/news/2014-01-03/jfk-roads-closed-northeast-paralyzed-after-20-inches-snow-drop-wind-chill-hits-40</link><title>JFK, Roads Closed, Northeast Paralyzed After Up To 20 Inches Of Snow …</title><description>* JFK, Roads Closed, Northeast Paralyzed After Up To 20 Inches Of Snow … 
Snow and cold weather... in the Northeast... in January. Surely, such an unprecedented development in the New Normal […] inches.   Winter weather and wind-chill advisories were in effect in at least 22 states, stretching from Chicago through […] should predictably justify explaining away at least a 1% miss of Q1 GDP (which when inventory destocking is factored in, will

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7176-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7176_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:54:11">http://wmpoweruser.com/weather-hound-update-wide-tile-added/</link><title>Weather Hound Update – Wide Tile Added!</title><description>* Weather Hound Update – Wide Tile Added! 
weather feels Show wind direction on lockscreen, in app and on the live tile Even more beautiful lockscreen Various minor […] A simple and beautiful weather experience – Wide Tile Added! New Features and Updates Wide Tile […] Added Option to show current location on the lockscreen and in the app Option to use ‘apparent’ temperature, how the

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7176-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7176_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:55:58">http://hollywoodlife.com/2014/01/06/miley-cyrus-fur-coat-rihanna-fur-coat-nye-outfit-pictures/</link><title>Miley Cyrus V. Rihanna: It’s A Fierce Fur Face Off On New Year’s Eve</title><description>* Miley Cyrus V. Rihanna: It’s A Fierce Fur Face Off On New Year’s Eve 
Both stars made a major statement in NYC on NYE when they stepped out in bold fur coats — but who do YOU think rocked […] the trend better? VOTE. Both Miley Cyrus and Rihanna spent their New Year’s Eve in NYC in floor-length fur coats […] crisp NYC weather by throwing on her fur. While it was similar to Miley’s it definitely gave off a different vibe. Rihanna

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7176-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7176_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:59:00">http://www.refinery29.com/2014/01/60098/weather-kitty-app</link><title>New Weather Kitty App Might Make This Arctic Blast Slightly Less…</title><description>* New Weather Kitty App Might Make This Arctic Blast Slightly Less… 
of just browsing your local weather forecast and feeling imminent doom (as anyone in New York City certainly has this […] considering the upcoming weather forecast for NYC .) The Weather Kitty app is available to iOS and Android users, and yes, it […] Photo courtesy of Weather Kitty .Two facts: The weather outside is frightful, and kittens are so delightful. And

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7176-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7176_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:59:50">http://animalnewyork.com/2014/nyc-snowstorms-1800s-toilsome-affairs/</link><title>NYC Snowstorms in the 1800s Were Toilsome Affairs</title><description>* NYC Snowstorms in the 1800s Were Toilsome Affairs 
, than some of our citizens for fall of snow. From the first day that cold weather has fairly set in, sleighs of most […] Railroad Company should run sleighs, and not break it up to run their cars.” The post NYC Snowstorms in the 1800s Were […] in 1851\. Just remember, next time you’re complaining about your commute: at least there aren’t dead horses littering the

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7176-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7176_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:02:26">http://www.businessinsider.com/whats-the-weather-in-new-york-2014-1</link><title>Now The East Coast Is Being Hit With Ridiculously Low Temperatures</title><description>* Now The East Coast Is Being Hit With Ridiculously Low Temperatures 
, temperatures in NYC right now are 9 or 10 degrees, depending on where youre measuring. With the wind chill it feels between -7 or […] -12. This map from the National Weather Service shows the range of temperatures across the Northeast. Meanwhile in

14 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>