<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7402">little johnny</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:14:13" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7402-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7402_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:14:14">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1917987-lebron-james-discusses-relationship-with-new-business-associate-johnny-manziel</link><title>LeBron James Discusses Relationship with New Business Associate Johnny …</title><description>* LeBron James Discusses Relationship with New Business Associate Johnny … 
NEW YORK — LeBron James has always seen Johnny Manziel as a kindred spirit, consistently overanalyzed […] only college kid that ever had fun. But obviously, hes Johnny Manziel so its blown out of proportion." It was more […] , incidentally, went up for auction  a little over a week ago.) "When the opportunity was brought to me, I basically just told

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7402-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7402_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:16:45">http://www.tmz.com/2014/01/03/johnny-depp-settles-lawsuit-concert-iggy-pop-bodyguards/</link><title>Johnny Depp Settles Up In Concert Brawl Lawsuit</title><description>* Johnny Depp Settles Up In Concert Brawl Lawsuit 
Johnny Depp decided its better to pay a little cash to rid himself of a woman who claims the actors bodyguard beat the

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7402-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7402_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:19:19">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1907368-chick-fil-a-bowl-2013-of-course-johnny-manziel-gets-his-storybook-ending</link><title>Chick-fil-A Bowl 2013: Of Course Johnny Manziel Gets His Storybook …</title><description>* Chick-fil-A Bowl 2013: Of Course Johnny Manziel Gets His Storybook … 
You didnt think Johnny Manziel would let a New Years Eve stage go by without putting on a show, did you? The […] little bit of trouble, because I looked down and somebody from Duke was staring right up at me laying on the ground," he said

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7402-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7402_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:21:02">http://fansided.com/2014/01/09/johnny-manziel-fran-tarkenton-love-see-qb-minnesota-vikings-uniform/</link><title>Johnny Manziel: Fran Tarkenton would love to see QB in a Minnesota …</title><description>* Johnny Manziel: Fran Tarkenton would love to see QB in a Minnesota … 
professional level. Shortly after the announcement, we got a little bit of insight from one […] Johnny Manziel: Fran Tarkenton […] On Wednesday, Texas A&amp;M Heisman-winning quarterback Johnny Manziel officially declared that he will be heading to

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7402-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7402_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:23:10">http://mashable.com/2013/12/20/johnny-depp-transcendence-teaser/</link><title>See the First Teaser for Johnny Depps Transcendence</title><description>* See the First Teaser for Johnny Depps Transcendence 
The first teaser trailer for the upcoming Johnny Depp movie, Transcendence , has arrived The enigmatic trailer […] reveals very little about the movie — a narrator explains the concept of singularity, a theoretical point in humanitys future […] Nolans Space Film Interstellar Johnny Depp plays Dr. Will Caster, an AI researcher whos trying to build a sentient machine

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7402-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7402_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:25:18">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1912856-gaudreau-paces-boston-college-in-4-3-frozen-fenway-win</link><title>Gaudreau Paces Boston College in 4-3 Frozen Fenway Win</title><description>* Gaudreau Paces Boston College in 4-3 Frozen Fenway Win 
Leave it to the little man—again. Junior forward Johnny Gaudreau scored two goals on Saturday night, including the […] a close-in shot between the pads of Irish goaltender Steve Summerhays to break a 3-3 tie. "Johnny got a really nice

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7402-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7402_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:28:19">http://thinkprogress.org/alyssa/2014/01/08/3132631/harry-belafonte-12-years-slave/</link><title>What A Powerful Speech From Harry Belafonte Tells Us About The Meaning …</title><description>* What A Powerful Speech From Harry Belafonte Tells Us About The Meaning … 
] looked to see the human beauty of Johnny Weissmuller swinging through the trees, jump off, and there spring to life, while […] forests with wild animals. Not until Johnny Weissmuller stepped into a scene did we know who we were, according to cinema […] ’ve been granted, or that you’ve accepted for yourself. But if you live in a world where you have little power or influence

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7402-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7402_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:29:21">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1906885-tennessee-football-recruiting-2014-legacy-class-a-throwback-to-the-glory-days</link><title>Tennessee Football Recruiting: 2014 Legacy Class a Throwback to the …</title><description>* Tennessee Football Recruiting: 2014 Legacy Class a Throwback to the … 
moving forward. While Kellys and Creamers fathers roamed the field during Johnny Majors heyday of the 1980s and early 90s […] he simply feels something different when it comes to Tennessee. Ever since I was little, I always wanted to follow in […] really felt like Im at home or felt as comfortable as I have been at Tennessee. Its that little something, whenever you step

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7402-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7402_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:32:15">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1925204-2014-nfl-draft-predictions-mid-round-picks-who-will-make-immediate-impact</link><title>2014 NFL Draft Predictions: Midround Picks Who Will Make Immediate …</title><description>* 2014 NFL Draft Predictions: Midround Picks Who Will Make Immediate … 
quarterback position that has been dissected from every angle with Teddy Bridgewater and Johnny Manziel being shifted […] likely need to add a little more girth before being effective at the next level. But with talent as a vertical threat for

13 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7402-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7402_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:34:16">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1907116-chick-fil-a-bowl-2013-most-important-keys-for-duke-vs-texas-am</link><title>Chick-fil-A Bowl 2013: Most Important Keys for Duke vs. Texas A&amp;M</title><description>* Chick-fil-A Bowl 2013: Most Important Keys for Duke vs. Texas A&amp;M 
of the eyes tuning in to the game will be doing so to check out what Aggies quarterback Johnny Manziel will do in […] heat up.     Duke: Get Pressure on Johnny Manziel Manziel is going to make plays. In two seasons, hes […] remains the same. Williams, Ben Malena and Tra Carson should have little trouble finding running room against a middling Duke

15 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>