<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7403">usc trojans</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:37:11" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7403-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7403_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:37:12">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1897612-fresno-state-vs-usc-score-grades-and-analysis-from-2013-las-vegas-bowl</link><title>Fresno State vs. USC: Score, Grades and Analysis from 2013 Las Vegas …</title><description>* Fresno State vs. USC: Score, Grades and Analysis from 2013 Las Vegas … 
his second score of the day, giving the Trojans an insurmountable 45-20 lead. The win moves USC to 10-4 on the season […] for the Trojans.   Clay Helton, head coach, USC: A As previously noted, there was a lot of uncertainty surrounding […] USC capped off a drama-filled year with an impressive 45-20 victory over Fresno State in the Royal Purple Las Vegas

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7403-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7403_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:38:34">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1897590-las-vegas-bowl-win-shows-usc-will-be-back-in-2014-for-real-this-time</link><title>Las Vegas Bowl Win Shows USC Will Be Back in 2014, for Real This Time</title><description>* Las Vegas Bowl Win Shows USC Will Be Back in 2014, for Real This Time 
After the season USC went through, the Trojans could have crumbled, but they didnt. After losing beloved interim head […] -six, Fresno State was wholly incapable of getting any kind of leverage against the Trojans. USC looked the best it has all season […] coming at him. In their final act of the season, the USC Trojans played with every ounce of talent they had, and even with

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7403-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7403_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:40:28">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1910582-usc-football-how-marqise-lee-declaring-for-nfl-draft-impacts-trojan-offense</link><title>USC Football: How Marqise Lee Declaring for NFL Draft Impacts Trojan …</title><description>* USC Football: How Marqise Lee Declaring for NFL Draft Impacts Trojan … 
the Trojans. He led USC in receptions and touchdowns in 2013, and we can expect him to do the same next year.  Aside from […] in 2014. Because USC wont have Lee as a deep threat anymore, the Trojans running backs will have to step their game up […] Late Friday night, USC wide receiver Marqise Lee announced that he will forgo his senior year and enter the 2014

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7403-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7403_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:42:08">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1900918-usc-trojans-football-the-road-back-to-glory</link><title>USC Trojans Football: The Road Back to Glory</title><description>* USC Trojans Football: The Road Back to Glory 
, "Wait until next year." Of course, not many programs are USC, and certainly there are few who not only have to overcome […] what the Trojans will face next year as they try to overcome a change of coaching staff as well as deal with the last year […] change was needed following a poor finish by former head coach Lane Kiffin , only those who truly despise the Trojans would

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7403-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7403_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:43:57">http://www.sbnation.com/college-football/2013/12/18/5209852/las-vegas-bowl-2013-usc-fresno-state-football-preview</link><title>2013 Las Vegas Bowl breakdown: If USC brings its A-game, Trojans should …</title><description>* 2013 Las Vegas Bowl breakdown: If USC brings its A-game, Trojans should … 
Motivation matters double in bowl games; does USC have it? Playing for their second interim coach of the season, the […] Trojans can win their 10th game of the season, but after last years egg-laying in El Paso, they have to prove they want to be […] after Lane Kiffins firing, USC got whipped at home by UCLA, lost Orgeron after the full-time hiring of Steve Sarkisian, and

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7403-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7403_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:45:59">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1909854-usc-football-recruiting-analyzing-the-jordan-poland-decommittment</link><title>USC Football Recruiting: Analyzing the Jordan Poland Decommitment</title><description>* USC Football Recruiting: Analyzing the Jordan Poland Decommitment 
Trojans but has placed them low on his interest list because USC has yet to offer. That may soon change though, as […] USC needs offensive linemen in this class. Also, Poland was the first Trojan verbal commitment in the 2013 class and […] .com . From Polands perspective, it made sense for him to look around since USC made little—if any—effort to keep in contact with

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7403-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7403_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:47:08">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1912744-john-plattenburg-flips-commitment-from-ucla-to-usc</link><title>John Plattenburg Flips Commitment from UCLA to USC</title><description>* John Plattenburg Flips Commitment from UCLA to USC 
Steve Sarkisian continues to do well for himself on recruiting, as the USC Trojans reportedly have flipped UCLA […] commitment to USC is a godsend for the Trojans, who have just two other defensive backs in the ranks for 2014. With Dion Bailey […] , USC secures more depth, and in return he gets the chance for early playing time.  The Trojans now have 17 of their 19

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7403-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7403_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:48:11">http://www.sbnation.com/college-football/2014/1/8/5289266/pac-12-2014-football-schedule-best-games</link><title>Full 2014 Pac-12 football schedule, plus the best game of each weekend</title><description>* Full 2014 Pac-12 football schedule, plus the best game of each weekend 
Trojans head coach. Can USC play up to the extraordinary talent level on their roster? Honorable Mention: August 30 […] at WASHINGTON STATE (1) Sat., Aug 30 UNLV at ARIZONA Fresno State at USC UCLA at Virginia COLORADO vs. Colorado […] Davis at STANFORD Sat., Sept. 6 ARIZONA at Texas-San Antonio ARIZONA STATE at New Mexico USC at STANFORD Memphis at

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7403-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7403_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:49:07">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1899596-first-major-recruit-steve-sarkisian-can-bring-to-usc-is-ed-orgeron</link><title>First Major Recruit Steve Sarkisian Can Bring to USC Is Ed Orgeron</title><description>* First Major Recruit Steve Sarkisian Can Bring to USC Is Ed Orgeron 
New USC head coach Steve Sarkisian has six weeks until national signing day, but hes working to land his first major […] recruit now: Ed Orgeron . The importance of Sarkisian bringing Orgeron back to USC was scrawled out in the block letters […] the former Trojans defensive line and interim head coach.    Orgeron ingratiated himself to current Trojans, and was a

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7403-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7403_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:51:27">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1912535-national-signing-day-2014-programs-with-the-most-to-gain</link><title>National Signing Day 2014: Programs with the Most to Gain</title><description>* National Signing Day 2014: Programs with the Most to Gain 
Steve Sarkisian leaving the Washington Huskies for greener pastures with the USC Trojans, several questions remain for the […] Trojans Steve Sarkisian has been considered a recruiting guru for years whether it was as an assistant coach at USC or […] three programs that can potentially lock up great recruits who will change their team over the next few seasons.   USC

14 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>