<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7405">light therapy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:14:37" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7405-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7405_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:14:38">http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2014/01/02/parents-set-up-hidden-camera-to-monitor-autistic-sons-therapy-sessions-what-they-saw-happening-in-real-time-is-gut-wrenching/</link><title>Parents Set Up Hidden Camera to Monitor Autistic Son’s Therapy Sessions …</title><description>* Parents Set Up Hidden Camera to Monitor Autistic Son’s Therapy Sessions … 
When Stephanie Lowe and her husband didn’t see any improvements in their autistic toddler after he started therapy […] source: WISN-TV) Image source: WISN-TV “It’s about my son. He deserves the therapy he was promised. And he deserves […] , told WISN it is evaluating its other therapists in light of this incident. (H/T: WPEC-TV ) – Other Must-Read Stories

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7405-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7405_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:15:37">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/01/02/science-2014_n_4523341.html</link><title>10 Big Science Initiatives To Watch For In 2014</title><description>* 10 Big Science Initiatives To Watch For In 2014 
tumours. In early tests, the drugs evoked a better level of response in patients than ipilimumab, a similar therapy that was […] launched in 2011 to treat advanced melanoma. Renewable revolution Semiconductors known as perovskites convert light energy […] array of HIV types quickly cleared an HIV-related virus in monkeys. The therapy will be tested in people who carry HIV, with

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7405-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7405_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:16:54">http://www.inquisitr.com/1081787/hidden-webcam-catches-autistic-child-allegedly-abused-by-therapist-video/</link><title>Hidden Webcam Catches Autistic Child Allegedly Abused By Therapist …</title><description>* Hidden Webcam Catches Autistic Child Allegedly Abused By Therapist … 
. Caeden Lowe’s parents grew concerned that he didn’t seem to be making much progress in his in-home therapy sessions, so they […] the head, throwing him on the couch, and even head-butting him during the therapy sessions in the family basement. The […] therapist in question now faces charges of abusing a child during a therapy session. Police say the investigation into the

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7405-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7405_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:18:44">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1904349-chris-weidman-what-might-2014-have-in-store-for-him</link><title>Chris Weidman: What 2014 Might Have in Store for Him?</title><description>* Chris Weidman: What 2014 Might Have in Store for Him? 
2012 were truly off mark. Since that setback, "The Phenom"—some say only with the aid of testosterone replacement therapy […] (No. 6 middlweight) with a spinning heel kick at UFC on FX 8 before serving Dan Henderson (No. 7 light heavyweight) his […] crack. On the same card Souza fights Carmont, fourth-ranked middleweight and former light heavyweight champ Lyoto Machida

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7405-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7405_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:19:55">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1912600-chris-weidman-ray-longo-sound-off-on-vitor-belforts-trt-usage</link><title>Chris Weidman, Ray Longo Sound Off on Vitor Belforts TRT Usage</title><description>* Chris Weidman, Ray Longo Sound Off on Vitor Belforts TRT Usage 
. 1 contender Vitor Belfort s usage of testosterone replacement therapy.  Tentatively set to face off with "The Phenom […] United States—the ex-light heavyweight champ hasnt fought on American soil since he scored a knockout win over Yoshihiro

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7405-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7405_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:22:35">http://www.archdaily.com/459571/medical-resort-bad-schallerbach-architects-collective-zt-gmbh-ac/</link><title>Medical Resort Bad Schallerbach / Architects Collective ZT-GmbH (AC)</title><description>* Medical Resort Bad Schallerbach / Architects Collective ZT-GmbH (AC) 
. Additionally, the architects created a 4,200-square-foot extension with a hotel rooms, therapy area, pool and dining room. A […] lot of light and natural materials Die Bad Schallerbach VAEB combines a visionary concept based on a harmonious exchange […] the surrounding natural environment and use of natural materials throughout. The therapy pool, with its dramatic

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7405-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7405_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:24:46">http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2014/01/01/with-recreational-marijuana-sales-now-legal-in-colorado-how-did-the-first-day-of-business-go/</link><title>With Recreational Marijuana Sales Now Legal in Colorado, How Did the …</title><description>* With Recreational Marijuana Sales Now Legal in Colorado, How Did the … 
and strummed folk tunes for about 20 people waiting outside one dispensary for sales to begin, as light snow fell at times […] going up. Laura Kriho of the Cannabis Therapy Institute said she worries prices will spike and patients will be left paying

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7405-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7405_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:27:49">http://hollywoodlife.com/2014/01/07/kim-kardashian-cleavage-picture-tank-top-tight-skirt-shopping-outfit/</link><title>Kim Kardashian Shows Off Most Cleavage Ever In Tiny Plunging Top</title><description>* Kim Kardashian Shows Off Most Cleavage Ever In Tiny Plunging Top 
you’ve got it, flaunt it is definitely Kim Kardashian ‘s motto. The new mom indulged in retail therapy at Barneys New […] with a light teal knit skirt that extended past her knees and clung to her signature curves. The high-waisted silhouette

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7405-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7405_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:30:02">http://www.archdaily.com/459558/centro-socio-sanitari-martijulia-pinearq/</link><title>Elderly Healthcare Building / Pinearq</title><description>* Elderly Healthcare Building / Pinearq 
wards with only a ground floor and a basement for general services.In order to have light and a natural atmosphere in all […] ’s therapy units. The interior layout helps the users to recognize at any time, spaces in which they live and allow them to […] get their bearings within the building: natural light from the skylights and from the interior patios, the views of the

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7405-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7405_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:30:57">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1893309-has-kobe-bryants-love-for-the-game-reached-a-new-zenith-at-age-35</link><title>Has Kobe Bryants Love for the Game Reached a New Zenith at Age 35?</title><description>* Has Kobe Bryants Love for the Game Reached a New Zenith at Age 35? 
stiffness that had been setting into his left ankle joint during recent games by doing more intricate manual therapy that […] who have something happen to them amid the light of tunnel’s end to provide fresh perspective on re-loving the game

17 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>