<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7407">kim kardashian pregnant</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:34:11" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7407-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7407_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:34:11">http://hollywoodlife.com/2014/01/08/kim-kardashian-natural-makeup-beauty-how-to-blonde-hair/</link><title>Kim Kardashian: Why I Love Natural Makeup</title><description>* Kim Kardashian: Why I Love Natural Makeup 
makeup look! If you have been keeping up with the Kardashians, you have noticed that 33-year-old  Kim Kardashian , has […] -established. Do you like Kim’s natural look? She spills why she is wearing a more natural look below. Kim Kardashian: Natural […] Proposes To Kim Kardashian Video Full Take Our Poll Do you agree that the blonde hair looks better with a natural face

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7407-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7407_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:35:12">http://hollywoodlife.com/2014/01/17/kim-kardashian-ellen-interview-north-west-pictures-tough-pregnancy/</link><title>Kim Kardashian Reveals Cute North West Pics &amp; ‘Tough’ Pregnancy…</title><description>* Kim Kardashian Reveals Cute North West Pics &amp; ‘Tough’ Pregnancy… 
thoughts in the comments! – Shannon Miller More Kim Kardashian News: Kim Kardashian Wants To Be Pregnant Bride Kanye […] So adorable! Kim Kardashian revealed her most intimate, adorable pictures of baby North yet on ‘Ellen’ on Jan. 17, but […] video interview below! Kim Kardashian , Kanye West , and baby North West seem to be the perfect family, but Kim

13 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7407-03"><link>http://www.celebitchy.com/343495/kim_kardashian_denies_photoshopping_selfies_i_am_so_disciplined_work_so_hard/</link><title>Kim Kardashian denies Photoshopping selfies: ‘I am so disciplined &amp; work …</title><description>* Kim Kardashian denies Photoshopping selfies: ‘I am so disciplined &amp; work … 
Here are some new photos of Kim Kardashian out and about on Friday (white jeans) and Saturday (white skirt). You know […] ! Kim Kardashian is not very happy with the rumors that her recent selfies with Blac Chyna — in which she shows off her […] for 2014!” [From Us Weekly] This is so stupid, I’m not even going to waste my energy explaining to Kim Kardashian why

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7407-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7407_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:40:31">http://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2013/12/kim-kardashian-and-kanye-west-thg-celebrity-of-the-year-finalist/</link><title>Kim Kardashian &amp; Kanye West: THG Celebrity of the Year Finalist #2</title><description>* Kim Kardashian &amp; Kanye West: THG Celebrity of the Year Finalist #2 
announcement here: Kim Kardashian Pregnant: The Announcement From there, it was pretty much all Kimye all the time […] KARDASHIAN AND KANYE WEST! Kim and Kanye: 2013 in Review Yes, 2013 was the year in which the worlds most vapid reality […] the couple celebrate! Kanye West Proposes to Kim Kardashian! When will the pair get married? Some time in 2014

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7407-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7407_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:42:38">http://www.inquisitr.com/1091741/kendall-jenner-photobombs-kim-kardashians-latest-booty-selfie/</link><title>Kendall Jenner Photobombs Kim Kardashian’s Latest Booty Selfie</title><description>* Kendall Jenner Photobombs Kim Kardashian’s Latest Booty Selfie 
Kendall Jenner photobombed Kim Kardashian as she looked to take her latest booty selfie. Jenner tried to rival her […] to the world, while they also donned tight leggings and trainers for their workout session too. Kim Kardashian has spent […] Friday morning. The 18-year-old decided to upload the photo that showcased her and Kim’s bottoms to her Instagram

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7407-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7407_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:44:22">http://hollywoodlife.com/2014/01/09/lamar-odom-khloe-kardashian-home-listed-divorce-mansion-for-sale/</link><title>Khloe Kardashian &amp; Lamar Odom Put Mansion Up For Sale For $5.5 Million</title><description>* Khloe Kardashian &amp; Lamar Odom Put Mansion Up For Sale For $5.5 Million 
looking to cash in on all the pain Lamar put her through over the last year. Kim Kardashian’s Sexiest Selfies Take Our […] Is Back’ Khloe Kardashian Pregnant With Lamar Odom’s Baby? Truth Revealed […] ! Less than one month after  Khloe Kardashian   filed for a divorce from  Lamar Odom   on Dec. 13, the reality star has

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7407-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7407_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:45:28">http://hollywoodlife.com/2014/01/12/chic-pregnancy-fashions-kim-kardashian-kate-middleton-2013/</link><title>Kim Kardashian, Kate Middleton &amp; More Chic 2013 Pregnancy Fashions</title><description>* Kim Kardashian, Kate Middleton &amp; More Chic 2013 Pregnancy Fashions 
right in 2013. Check out all the fashion-foward pics and VOTE on your favorite looks! Celeb mommas like  Kim Kardashian […] fashions of 2013! Chicest Pregnancy Fashions Of 2013: Kim Kardashian, Kate Middleton &amp; More Kim Kardashian showed […] rocked heels and sexy frocks, just like she does when she’s not pregnant. Maternity Must-Haves: Flattering Dresses

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7407-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7407_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:47:36">http://hollywoodlife.com/2014/01/05/celebrity-weight-loss-2013-stars-diet-tips-kim-kardashian/</link><title>Biggest Weight Loss Stories of 2013 — Kim Kardashian, Snooki &amp; More</title><description>* Biggest Weight Loss Stories of 2013 — Kim Kardashian, Snooki &amp; More 
different, Khloe Kardashian , Christina Aguilera , Miranda Lambert , Kim Kardashian , Jessica Simpson , Kate […] While Kim, Jessica, and Snooki dined for two while pregnant — they sure had to make some serious adjustments after they […] yourself is difficult, but these women managed to do it — and do it with style! Kim lost the weight thanks to the Atkins diet

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7407-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7407_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:48:47">http://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2013/12/snooki-to-media-leave-pregnant-new-mom-celebrities-alone/</link><title>Snooki to Media: Leave Pregnant, New Mom Celebs Alone!</title><description>* Snooki to Media: Leave Pregnant, New Mom Celebs Alone! 
are pregnant and/or new parents. Yes, Snooki wrote a book and its called that. She cites Kim Kardashian as an […] fat, lazy loser.” As an example, she pointed out “how Jessica Simpson and Kim Kardashian … were tracked and criticized […] outspoken in knocking coverage of Kim’s weight gain and fashion choices during her pregnancy with North West. Kate Middleton

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7407-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7407_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:49:30">http://bossip.com/894230/gimmie-50-feet-kim-kardashian-supports-petition-to-protect-children-from-thirsty-paparazzi-it-needs-to-be-safe-for-our-kids/</link><title>Gimmie 50 Feet: Kim Kardashian Supports Petition To Protect Children …</title><description>* Gimmie 50 Feet: Kim Kardashian Supports Petition To Protect Children … 
Kim Kardashian Supports Petition Limiting Paparazzi Access To Kids Kim Kardashian has officially joined in on the […] lengths that the paps will go to for a photo since becoming pregnant with her daughter North was even born, but she recently […] limiting paparazzi access to kids: While Kim and other celebrities do often bring overly-aggressive attention from

14 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>