<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7409">rihanna chris brown</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:16:35" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7409-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7409_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:16:37">http://hollywoodlife.com/2013/12/29/chris-brown-rihanna-message-instagram-post-love-diss/</link><title>Rihanna Posts Romantic Message — Talking To Chris Brown?</title><description>* Rihanna Posts Romantic Message — Talking To Chris Brown? 
’t live without. So which one is Chris? Has  Rihanna   returned to her old ways of sending  Chris Brown   messages via […] wondering if she was dissing her ex or revealing her undying love for him. Rihanna: Sending A Message To Chris Brown? It […] @AndrewGrutt More Rihanna &amp; Chris Brown News: Rihanna’s Visit To Chris Brown In Rehab — The Truth Revealed Chris

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7409-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7409_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:18:06">http://hollywoodlife.com/2014/01/07/rihanna-wants-mychal-kendricks-reason-crush-nfl-star/</link><title>Rihanna: The Real Reason Why She Has A ‘Crush’ On Mychal Kendricks</title><description>* Rihanna: The Real Reason Why She Has A ‘Crush’ On Mychal Kendricks 
, HollywoodLifers ? Should Rihanna go out with Mychal? Let us know! – Eric Ray More Rihanna News: Chris Brown: ‘Never […] Forget Who Supported You’ — Dissing Rihanna? Chris Brown: His Shocking Reaction To Rihanna Burning His Love Letter […] Rihanna: Why She’s Selling The Gold Necklace Chris Brown Gave Her

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7409-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7409_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:20:21">http://hollywoodlife.com/2014/01/07/chris-brown-diss-rihanna-never-forget-who-supported-you-karrueche-tran/</link><title>Chris Brown: ‘Never Forget Who Supported You’ — Dissing Rihanna?</title><description>* Chris Brown: ‘Never Forget Who Supported You’ — Dissing Rihanna? 
Chris Brown is remembering who supported him through all the troubles — and it isn’t Rihanna. After she recently burnt […] message. Chris Brown Disses Rihanna In New Tweet In the early morning hours of January 7, Chris tweeted: Work hard to […] continued to entertain her guests.” Chris Brown ‘Moving On’ From Rihanna However, Chris was hurt by her actions — but he knows

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7409-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7409_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:23:13">http://hollywoodlife.com/2013/12/27/karrueche-tran-denied-club-rihanna-pink-elephant-nyc-feud/</link><title>Karrueche Tran Denied By NYC Club Because Rihanna Was There</title><description>* Karrueche Tran Denied By NYC Club Because Rihanna Was There 
there first! Looks like things might still be awkward between Chris Brown ‘s ex,   Rihanna , and his current girlfriend […] other clubs allow rivals to drink and dance together. Chris Brown and Drake , anyone ? Rihanna Kisses Drake After MTV […] and Rihanna still feel bitterness toward each other? Let us know! – Amanda Michelle More Chris Brown &amp; Karrueche

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7409-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7409_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:25:17">http://hollywoodlife.com/2014/01/07/mychal-kendricks-rihanna-crush-philadelphia-eagles-chris-brown/</link><title>Mychal Kendricks: Rihanna Calls Philadelphia Eagles Player ‘Crush’</title><description>* Mychal Kendricks: Rihanna Calls Philadelphia Eagles Player ‘Crush’ 
think Mychal looks like Chris in this pic? – Kristine Hope Kowalski More Rihanna News: Chris Brown: His Shocking […] Reaction To Rihanna Burning His Love Letter Rihanna Burned Chris Brown’s New Year’s Apology Letter Rihanna’s New Year […] type, because in the photo she chose to share, Mychal’s facial expression looks just like Chris Brown’s signature pout

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7409-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7409_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:28:27">http://www.inquisitr.com/1086412/chris-brown-letter-burned-by-rihanna-rumors-make-the-rounds-online/</link><title>Chris Brown Letter Burned By Rihanna? Rumors Make The Rounds Online</title><description>* Chris Brown Letter Burned By Rihanna? Rumors Make The Rounds Online 
Did you hear that one of Chris Brown’s letters to Rihanna was supposedly burned by the “Diamonds” singer? Were you […] Life . According to an anonymous source, Chris Brown sent Rihanna a letter from rehab on New Year’s Eve that served as an […] -free year. And she’s done with bulls*** from the men in her life. She’s over games.” Although this Chris Brown-Rihanna story

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7409-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7409_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:29:47">http://www.gossipcop.com/rihanna-burned-chris-brown-apology-letter-fire/</link><title>HollywoodLife Spreads Fake Story About Rihanna Burning Chris Brown …</title><description>* HollywoodLife Spreads Fake Story About Rihanna Burning Chris Brown … 
claims that Chris Brown  allegedly sent Rihanna an apology letter on New Year’s Eve, and that she subsequently burned […] it. This never happened . The blog — which repeatedly gets stories about Brown and Rihanna wrong […] holidays, “sending her a letter apologizing for all the pain he’s caused her.” But Rihanna supposedly “made it clear that he

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7409-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7409_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:31:06">http://bossip.com/891098/phuck-yo-remorse-did-rihanna-burn-up-an-apology-letter-she-got-from-breezy-on-new-years-eve/</link><title>Phuck Yo Remorse: Did Rihanna Burn Up An Apology Letter She Got From …</title><description>* Phuck Yo Remorse: Did Rihanna Burn Up An Apology Letter She Got From … 
Did Rihanna Burn Up Apology Letter From Chris Brown? Former long-time lovers Chris Brown and Rihanna seem to have […] Rihanna and Chris Brown‘s relationship just went up in smoke. A source close to the Unapologetic singer told Hollywood […] clearly too little, too late. “She put Chris to bed last year for good,” the source said. And Rihanna, never one to shy away

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7409-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7409_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:33:36">http://hollywoodlife.com/2013/12/17/chris-brown-song-loyal-lil-wayne-french-montana/</link><title>Chris Brown Drops New Track ‘Loyal’ With Lil Wayne &amp; French Montana</title><description>* Chris Brown Drops New Track ‘Loyal’ With Lil Wayne &amp; French Montana 
’ and we can’t help but wonder who he’s talking about! Is Chris Brown calling out his ex-girlfriend Rihanna ? It […] Karrueche? – Chloe Melas More Chris Brown News: Chris Brown — His Shocking Reaction To Rihanna’s AMA Icon Award Win […] Rihanna Vs. Karrueche Tran: Chris Brown’s Girlfriends’ Sexiest Looks Chris Brown’s Mom Still Supports Him: They’re ‘Working

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7409-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7409_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:35:18">http://www.gossipcop.com/chris-brown-rihanna-hollywoodlife-rumor-burned-letter/</link><title>Chris Brown’s “Shocking Reaction” to Rihanna: Another Fake HollywoodLife …</title><description>* Chris Brown’s “Shocking Reaction” to Rihanna: Another Fake HollywoodLife … 
story about Rihanna supposedly burning an apology letter from Chris Brown , now has a follow-up fake story […] . According to the webloid, Brown had a “shocking reaction” to Rihanna’s actions. Again, just to recap: None of this actually […] comes to Brown and Rihanna. Anyway, one alleged insider says that Brown “thinks she’s crazy” in the aftermath of the letter

14 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>