<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7415">most anticipated games of 2013</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:47:21" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7415-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7415_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:47:23">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1917266-50-most-anticipated-college-football-games-for-2014-season</link><title>50 Most Anticipated College Football Games for 2014 Season</title><description>* 50 Most Anticipated College Football Games for 2014 Season 
The 2013 college football season brought enough thrilling finishes, shocking upsets and electric battles for three […] seasons—but that doesnt mean 2014 cant be just as anxiety-inducing. Here is a very early look at 50 of the biggest tilts […] coming next season—50 battles that will shape the national and conference title races. Well start off with a round of

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7415-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7415_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:48:56">http://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2013-01-02-developers-most-anticipated-games-of-2014</link><title>Developers Most Anticipated Games of 2014</title><description>* Developers Most Anticipated Games of 2014 
Luckey and Jonathan Blow, complete with Twitter bios, for their most anticipated games of 2014\. Peter Molyneux : A […] forward to in 2014? Weve already asked them for their games of 2013. Now its time to ask the likes of Peter Molyneux, Palmer […] the mainstream. And with a raft of crowdfunded games due out over the next 12 months, 2014 should tell us whether all that

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7415-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7415_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:51:46">http://www.inquisitr.com/1080799/the-hunger-games-mockingjay-is-most-anticipated-film-of-2014/</link><title>‘The Hunger Games: Mockingjay’ Is Most Anticipated Film Of 2014</title><description>* ‘The Hunger Games: Mockingjay’ Is Most Anticipated Film Of 2014 
The Hunger Games: Mockingjay, Part 1 tops Fandango’s most anticipated films of 2014, followed by The Hobbit: Here […] anticipated film of 2013. You can look at the complete list of most anticipated films and stars of 2014 here . Will The Hunger […] : Mockingjay’ Is Most Anticipated Film Of 2014 is a post from: The Inquisitr News

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7415-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7415_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:53:45">http://venturebeat.com/2013/12/20/the-deanbeat-the-10-most-anticipated-games-of-2014-poll/</link><title>The DeanBeat: The 10 most anticipated games of 2014 (poll)</title><description>* The DeanBeat: The 10 most anticipated games of 2014 (poll) 
anticipated games of 2013 , and the year before that for the most anticipated games of 2012 . I’m sure there will be a Call of […] anticipated games in order, with my favorite at No. 1. And for the sake of comparison, here’s last year’s list of the most […] most anticipated games of 2012\. I have no clue what this game is about, and I have no idea when it will arrive. I also have

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7415-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7415_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:55:15">http://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2014-01-07-most-anticipated-the-witness</link><title>Most Anticipated: The Witness</title><description>* Most Anticipated: The Witness 
There are three simple reasons why The Witness is my most anticipated game of 2014\. The first is Jonathan Blow. His […] risk of reigniting the smouldering embers of old arguments, one of my biggest disappointments of 2013 was Phil Fish […] lights of thoughtful indie development apparently falling prey to the same sequelitis that is choking the mainstream games

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7415-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7415_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:57:31">http://screenrant.com/most-anticipated-movies-2014/</link><title>Screen Rant’s 20 Most Anticipated Movies of 2014</title><description>* Screen Rant’s 20 Most Anticipated Movies of 2014 
movie ... Click to continue reading Screen Rant’s 20 Most Anticipated Movies of 2014 The post Screen Rant’s 20 Most […] of the films debuting in theaters in 2014 and narrowed down a list of 20 that we’re most anticipating. From familiar […] Anticipated Movies of 2014 appeared first on Screen Rant .

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7415-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7415_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:59:55">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1900904-bowl-games-2013-14-breaking-down-most-underrated-non-bcs-battles</link><title>Bowl Games 2013-14: Breaking Down Most Underrated Non-BCS Battles</title><description>* Bowl Games 2013-14: Breaking Down Most Underrated Non-BCS Battles 
With so many bowl games at the end of the college football season, it is easy to overlook the good ones. However, there […] Missouri. Still, there are a few contests that might be skipped at first glance but should be among the best games of the bowl […] are quite a few interesting matchups that will be better than most anticipate. Obviously, fans across the country will be

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7415-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7415_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:01:03">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1903274-bowl-games-2013-14-college-football-showcases-that-will-come-down-to-the-wire</link><title>Bowl Games 2013-14: College Football Showcases That Will Come Down to …</title><description>* Bowl Games 2013-14: College Football Showcases That Will Come Down to … 
games that figure to be decided in the final stages of the game. Heres a look at the remaining bowl schedule and analysis of […] , as these two schools possess some of the most potent offenses in the country. Leading the way for both teams are a co […] in college footballs marquee matchups. While there are certainly some blowouts in the making, there are also a host of

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7415-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7415_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:03:10">http://www.inquisitr.com/1079948/jennifer-lawrence-was-the-most-bankable-box-office-star-of-2013/</link><title>Jennifer Lawrence Was The Most Bankable Box Office Star Of 2013</title><description>* Jennifer Lawrence Was The Most Bankable Box Office Star Of 2013 
′s most bankable box office star? Jennifer Lawrence Was The Most Bankable Box Office Star Of 2013 is a post from: The […] Jennifer Lawrence made a lot of money for the Hollywood machine during 2013. If you’re tired of reading about the […] to the folks over at Quigley Publishing Company, Jennifer Lawrence was the top money-making star of 2013 . A lot of this

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7415-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7415_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:06:22">http://venturebeat.com/2013/12/20/new-gamesbeat-weekly-roundup-zelda-gets-hacky-consoles-for-queens-and-troubling-call-of-duty-sales/</link><title>NEW: GamesBeat weekly roundup: Zelda gets hacky, consoles for queens, …</title><description>* NEW: GamesBeat weekly roundup: Zelda gets hacky, consoles for queens, … 
. Looking back (and forward) The DeanBeat: The 10 most anticipated games of 2014 (poll) These are the games you played […] Activision Call of Duty: Ghosts in action. We only have a couple of weeks left in 2013, which means GamesBeat has […] one day Americans will spend $20.5B on games in 2013, with 65% of that via digital channels Marvel’s ‘The Avengers

17 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>