<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7430">conflict mali</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:25:23" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7430-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7430_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:25:24">http://www.zerohedge.com/news/2013-12-19/facing-triple-dip-recession-france-set-deploy-us-made-drones-west-africa</link><title>Facing Triple-Dip Recession, France Set To Deploy US-Made Drones In West …</title><description>* Facing Triple-Dip Recession, France Set To Deploy US-Made Drones In West … 
scapegoating and the now generic false flags, and let it all simmer in the latest global conflict in which the uninvited west has […] ".   Frances military intervention in Mali in January exposed its shortage of surveillance drones suitable for modern warfare […] in the region. Le Drian said pockets of militants remained in Mali, whom Paris would go after. They included veteran

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7430-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7430_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:28:49">http://www.algemeiner.com/2013/12/28/obamas-disengagement-is-having-dangerous-consequences/</link><title>Obama’s Disengagement is Having Dangerous Consequences</title><description>* Obama’s Disengagement is Having Dangerous Consequences 
, however, terrorists in Mali are again on the move. In the Central African Republic, religious conflict between Muslims and […] ’s conflict escalates rapidly toward outright civil war, President Obama has shown precious little interest. He has rightly […] thereafter, Al Qaeda-affiliated terrorists, who had already gained control over much of northern Mali, threatened the central

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7430-03"><link>http://www.webpronews.com/boko-haram-priest-kidnapped-in-cameroon-set-free-2014-01</link><title>Boko Haram: Priest Kidnapped in Cameroon Set Free</title><description>* Boko Haram: Priest Kidnapped in Cameroon Set Free 
Syria and Mali. Since 2009, The Boko Haram Islamic movement has terrorized and killed thousands of Christians. Recently 12 […] forms of violence, hatred and conflict in the tormented regions of Africa be stamped out, as well as elsewhere in the world

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7430-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7430_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:33:47">http://www.zerohedge.com/news/2013-12-21/us-aircraft-un-helicopter-attacked-south-sudan</link><title>US Aircraft, UN Helicopter Attacked In South Sudan</title><description>* US Aircraft, UN Helicopter Attacked In South Sudan 
Africa, focusing on Mali and the Central African Republic, where they are "peacekeeping" (with the support of US drones […] Americans from spiraling conflict in South Sudan and four U.S. military service members were wounded.   Nearly a week of

17 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>