<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7432">ticket to mars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:36:00" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7432-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7432_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:36:01">http://www.inquisitr.com/1079059/bruno-mars-rihanna-among-the-years-most-pirated-artists/</link><title>Bruno Mars, Rihanna Among The Year’s Most Pirated Artists</title><description>* Bruno Mars, Rihanna Among The Year’s Most Pirated Artists 
Bruno Mars and Rihanna are this year’s most popular artist among music pirates. When it comes to illegal downloads […] ,000 times. That number is like to keep growing. Joining Bruno Mars, Rihanna, and Beyonce on this year’s list are Justin […] Independent reports that neither Bruno Mars nor Rihanna released any new albums this year. However, this didn’t stop for pirates

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7432-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7432_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:38:55">http://www.newser.com/story/180065/1k-make-first-cut-for-one-way-trip-to-mars.html</link><title>1K Make First Cut for One-Way Trip to Mars</title><description>* 1K Make First Cut for One-Way Trip to Mars 
still in the running for a one-way ticket to Mars . The Mars One project to send average Joes to colonize the red planet has

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7432-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7432_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:41:00">http://www.geeksaresexy.net/2013/12/25/gas-news-what-happened-next-march-2013/</link><title>GaS news — what happened next: March 2013</title><description>* GaS news — what happened next: March 2013 
orbit Mars . To keep weight down, the urine and fecal liquid of the passengers would be filtered to provide drinking water […] August 2018 Mars orbit and a May 2019 return to Earth, noting the alignment of planets meant this would be the last time a […] craft could reach Mars so quickly until 2031. CERN announced that it only had one factor to eliminate (whether the “spin

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7432-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7432_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:42:16">http://www.inquisitr.com/1079975/dubai-fireworks-2014-include-400000-pyrotechnics-set-guinness-world-record/</link><title>Dubai Fireworks 2014 Include 400,000 Pyrotechnics, Set Guinness World …</title><description>* Dubai Fireworks 2014 Include 400,000 Pyrotechnics, Set Guinness World … 
experts who worked a total of 5,000 hours to ensure that the display was perfect. It even attracted the president of Guinness […] World Records to make a trip from London to see it personally. “The scale of this record attempt is truly impressive and […] from the only city to kick off 2014 with a huge display. In London, the fireworks were mixed with confetti that needs no

15 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>