<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7438">facebook privacy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:49:35" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7438-01"><link>http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/01/03/todays-scuttlebot-facebook-privacy-and-sharks-on-twitter/</link><title>Today’s Scuttlebot: Facebook Privacy and Sharks on Twitter</title><description>* Today’s Scuttlebot: Facebook Privacy and Sharks on Twitter 
Fridays highlights from around the web include looks at the National Security Agencys efforts to crack all encryption, why people skills -- not only computer skills -- are important for founders of start-ups and a shark-tracking by Twitter post.

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7438-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7438_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:50:41">http://socialmediatoday.com/philbutler/2052976/facebook-class-action-fears-how-deep-privacy-runs</link><title>Facebook Class Action Fears: How Deep the Privacy Runs</title><description>* Facebook Class Action Fears: How Deep the Privacy Runs 
This latest Facebook lawsuit brought by two social network users, Matthew Campbell and Michael Hurley, could end in a […] over a month ago the courts ruled investors could lay claim against Facebook’s $16 billion IPO proceeds. read more

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7438-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7438_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:52:08">http://www.slashgear.com/facebook-hit-with-lawsuit-for-reportedly-breaching-messages-privacy-02310771/</link><title>Facebook hit with lawsuit for reportedly breaching messages privacy</title><description>* Facebook hit with lawsuit for reportedly breaching messages privacy 
In a complaint filed late last month, two Facebook users filed a lawsuit against the social network, claiming it scans

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7438-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7438_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:53:09">http://bgr.com/2014/01/03/facebook-class-action-suit-messages-privacy/</link><title>Facebook sued for invading users’ privacy</title><description>* Facebook sued for invading users’ privacy 
Two Facebook users this week filed a class action complaint against the social network, Ars Technica reports […] , alleging that the messaging system inside Facebook is not as private as it’s advertised to be, and that the company actively […] mines for data from personal messages and generates likes based on the content exchanged between users. Facebook described

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7438-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7438_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:55:50">http://lifehacker.com/facebook-chat-pro-customizes-notifications-privacy-for-1489078617</link><title>Facebook Chat Pro Customizes Notifications, Privacy for Messenger</title><description>* Facebook Chat Pro Customizes Notifications, Privacy for Messenger 
Chrome: Much like how FBPrivacy gives you more control over your Facebook Messengers settings on jailbroken i […] OS devices, Facebook Chat Pro lets you control whether others can see if you read a message, change the notification pop-ups and

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7438-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7438_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:56:51">http://thenextweb.com/insider/2013/12/23/us-judge-rules-privacy-lawsuit-claiming-hulu-gave-user-data-facebook-comscore-can-proceed/</link><title>US judge rules privacy lawsuit claiming Hulu gave user data to Facebook …</title><description>* US judge rules privacy lawsuit claiming Hulu gave user data to Facebook … 
A US judge in San Francisco has ruled that a privacy lawsuit against Hulu will move forward. Reuters reports that in […] issue of the class-action lawsuit is a claim that Hulu is illegally sharing its users viewing history with Facebook and […] market research and analytics firm comScore — a violation of the Video Privacy Protection Act of 1988. Customers in

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7438-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7438_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:57:57">http://gigaom.com/2014/01/02/facebook-reads-private-messages-to-boost-likes-lawsuit-claims/</link><title>Facebook reads private messages to boost “Likes,” lawsuit claims</title><description>* Facebook reads private messages to boost “Likes,” lawsuit claims 
Facebook is facing a new class action lawsuit that accuses the social network of violating state and federal privacy […] Facebook users send to one another in private. The purpose of the scanning is allegedly to increase the number of “Likes” to […] those websites, and in turn make Facebook more popular with advertisers. The lawsuit cites recent research by a Swiss

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7438-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7438_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 19:58:57">http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2014/01/10/creepy-facial-recognition-app-pushes-pretty-serious-privacy-boundaries/</link><title>Creepy Facial Recognition App Pushes ‘Pretty Serious Privacy…</title><description>* Creepy Facial Recognition App Pushes ‘Pretty Serious Privacy… 
offender registry and criminal histories is raising privacy concerns. Developed by FacialNetwork.com, the NameTag app scans […] ’s raising privacy concerns among some. (Image source: NameTag) “I believe that this will make online dating and offline social […] a statement . “It’s much easier to meet interesting new people when we can simply look at someone, see their Facebook

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7438-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7438_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:01:07">http://thenextweb.com/facebook/2014/01/03/facebook-facing-lawsuit-claiming-scans-users-private-messages-without-consent/</link><title>Facebook facing lawsuit claiming it scans users’ ‘private’ messages …</title><description>* Facebook facing lawsuit claiming it scans users’ ‘private’ messages … 
filed documents with the court alleging that Facebook violated two privacy laws, specifically the Electronics Communication […] Facebook is finding itself the target of a lawsuit , this time claiming that the social networking company spied on […] Privacy Act and the California Invasion of Privacy Act. Campbell and Hurley cite August 2013 findings from Swiss security

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7438-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7438_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:02:25">http://lifehacker.com/absterge-and-facebook-timeline-cleaner-purge-your-faceb-1497109433</link><title>Absterge and Facebook Timeline Cleaner Purge Your Facebook Activity</title><description>* Absterge and Facebook Timeline Cleaner Purge Your Facebook Activity 
Chrome/Firefox: Facebooks privacy settings are, quite frankly, a mess . The only thing harder than figuring out whats

14 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>