<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7439">make crown</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:03:16" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7439-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7439_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:03:17">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1898893-eagles-vs-cowboys-for-nfc-east-crown-is-the-best-possible-ending</link><title>Eagles vs. Cowboys for NFC East Crown Is the Best Possible Ending</title><description>* Eagles vs. Cowboys for NFC East Crown Is the Best Possible Ending 
"Were from Philadelphia and we fight." If Chip Kelly doesnt make the playoffs, he can always fall back on an obviously […] —who picked the Eagles to make the playoffs. Of course, he then changed his prediction to the Cowboys when the same group

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7439-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7439_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:05:38">http://www.mlbdailydish.com/2014/1/4/5271986/standing-pat-have-the-reds-done-enough-to-be-a-real-threat-to-the-nl</link><title>Standing pat: Have the Reds done enough to be a real threat for the NL …</title><description>* Standing pat: Have the Reds done enough to be a real threat for the NL … 
Edgar Renteria in 2003. **Since 2004, St. Louis has failed to make the postseason just three times. During that span

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7439-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7439_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:07:27">http://blog.us.playstation.com/2013/12/20/dragons-crown-new-difficulty-and-dungeon-available-now/</link><title>Dragon’s Crown: New Difficulty and Dungeon Available Now</title><description>* Dragon’s Crown: New Difficulty and Dungeon Available Now 
to it. It’s been a while since Dragon’s Crown launched, but we haven’t stopped working to make it better. We added cross […] a new Dragon’s Crown patch out. The players are all partying in the tavern with cheer, Because “Holy Crap!” a new […] play, improved the game balance, and tweaked many things to make the game even more fun. You would think we were done by

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7439-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7439_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:09:20">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1900413-nfl-playoff-scenarios-2013-breaking-down-every-outcome-ahead-of-week-17</link><title>NFL Playoff Scenarios 2013: Breaking Down Every Outcome Ahead of Week …</title><description>* NFL Playoff Scenarios 2013: Breaking Down Every Outcome Ahead of Week … 
make that happen.   AFC North The Bengals locked up the divisional crown, but still have plenty to play for. This […] in play when each of the 32 teams takes the field, broken down by division to make things easier to comprehend […] Baltimore Ravens aren ’t out of contention yet. The Super Bowl champions will have a chance at defending their crown if they

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7439-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7439_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:10:54">http://www.zerohedge.com/contributed/2014-01-09/500-years-history-shows-mass-spying-always-aimed-crushing-dissent</link><title>500 Years of History Shows that Mass Spying Is Always Aimed at Crushing …</title><description>* 500 Years of History Shows that Mass Spying Is Always Aimed at Crushing … 
history is largely a history of conflict between the Crown and the press. It was in enforcing the laws licensing the […] sixteenth, seventeenth, and eighteenth centuries . In Tudor England, officers of the Crown were given roving commissions to […] incorporated in 1557 to help implement that system, and was empowered   “to make search whenever it shall please them in any

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7439-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7439_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:13:40">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1915407-how-much-is-ray-horton-to-blame-for-the-browns-2013-collapse</link><title>How Much Is Ray Horton to Blame for the Cleveland Browns 2013…</title><description>* How Much Is Ray Horton to Blame for the Cleveland Browns 2013… 
the job. The Browns lost their final seven games in a row and 10 of their last 11—a team record—and needed to make a move […] defensive roster was made up of veterans who could either effectively make the switch to the 3-4 or had already done so in […] significant playing time, and that came as a result of Owens injury. And Clevelands free-agency crown jewel, linebacker Paul

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7439-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7439_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:15:47">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1920040-colts-vs-patriots-live-score-highlights-for-afc-divisional-game-2014</link><title>Colts vs. Patriots: Live Score and Highlights for AFC Divisional Game …</title><description>* Colts vs. Patriots: Live Score and Highlights for AFC Divisional Game … 
East crown.    After an incredible comeback in the Wild Card Round, when they outscored the Chiefs 35 to 13 in the […] most successful franchises of the past decade should make for great postseason theatre.    If either team gets down

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7439-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7439_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:16:37">http://www.nerdist.com/2014/01/star-wars-comics-to-make-kessel-run-from-dark-horse-to-marvel-in-2015/</link><title>STAR WARS Comics to Make Kessel Run from Dark Horse to Marvel in 2015</title><description>* STAR WARS Comics to Make Kessel Run from Dark Horse to Marvel in 2015 
will make the lightspeed jump back to Marvel, to begin a new age of adventures within the Star Wars universe.” The news […] . Star Wars has been the crown jewel of this approach. We began chasing the title as far back as 1989, and with the launch […] . Will they take the place of Star Wars ? That’s a tall order, but we will do our best to make that happen. In the meantime

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7439-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7439_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:18:15">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1900615-nfl-standings-week-17-updated-win-loss-records-and-postseason-scenarios</link><title>NFL Standings Week 17: Updated Win-Loss Records and Postseason…</title><description>* NFL Standings Week 17: Updated Win-Loss Records and Postseason… 
One week remains in the 2013 NFL  regular season, meaning potential playoff teams have one last chance to make a move […] ? The Chicago Bears host the Green Bay Packers in their Week 17 game that will crown the NFC North champion. The Dallas […] with a victory or San Francisco loss; the inverse is true to give the 49ers the crown. For now, the 49ers hold the No. 5

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7439-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7439_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:20:55">http://www.businessinsider.com/tipranks-best-analysts-of-2013-2014-1</link><title>The 12 Best Stock Pickers You Read About On The Internet</title><description>* The 12 Best Stock Pickers You Read About On The Internet 
success of market analysts based on comments they make in the media, to find out who on Wall Street made the best calls last […] -House (China) (EJ), Noah Holdings (NOAH), Melco Crown (MPEL), China Distance Education, Holdings Ltd. (DL), New Oriental Education

15 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>