<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7441">barcelona real madrid goal messi</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:36:06" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7441-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7441_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:36:07">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1919813-atletico-madrid-vs-barcelona-score-grades-and-post-match-reaction</link><title>Atletico Madrid vs. Barcelona Score, Grades and Post-Match Reaction</title><description>* Atletico Madrid vs. Barcelona Score, Grades and Post-Match Reaction 
Atletico Madrid and Barcelona played to a thrilling scoreless draw on Saturday in a match-up of La Liga title […] contenders at Atletico s Estadio Vicente Calderon. Barcelona remained atop the table on goal difference ahead of […] Atletico . Both teams now have 50 points, six more than third-placed Real Madrid.  The result ended Atletico s 100

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7441-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7441_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:37:26">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1915221-la-liga-statistical-comparison-barcelona-atletico-madrid-real-madrid</link><title>La Liga Statistical Comparison: Barcelona, Atletico Madrid and Real …</title><description>* La Liga Statistical Comparison: Barcelona, Atletico Madrid and Real … 
La Liga has, for the most part, been a two-horse race. Barcelona and Real Madrid have battled each other for years at […] goal if given a yard of space. Barcelonas key man, Lionel Messi, has been missing for quite a while with injury but is set […] statistics from Squawka , Messi has completed 19 key passes from his 11 games, placing him third at Barcelona.  Diego Costa has

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7441-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7441_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:39:25">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1919303-atletico-madrid-vs-barcelona-date-time-live-stream-tv-info-and-preview</link><title>Atletico Madrid vs. Barcelona: Date, Time, Live Stream, TV Info and …</title><description>* Atletico Madrid vs. Barcelona: Date, Time, Live Stream, TV Info and … 
. Although Barcelona have the slight advantage in goal differential to remain in first place, Atletico Madrid have stayed […] two clubs have dominated the scene for a long time: Barcelona and Real Madrid . In the past five years, these two giants […] was a 1-0 road win over Real Madrid at the end of September. While the victories kept coming, a bad loss to Barcelona

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7441-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7441_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:40:53">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1894821-cesc-fabregas-claims-anti-lionel-messi-agenda-hints-at-real-madrid-jealousy</link><title>Cesc Fabregas Claims Anti-Lionel Messi Agenda, Hints at Real Madrid …</title><description>* Cesc Fabregas Claims Anti-Lionel Messi Agenda, Hints at Real Madrid … 
Cesc Fabregas believes those criticising Lionel Messi have grown "tired of Barcelona always winning" and hints the […] condemnation coming out of Spains capital could be a source of jealousy from Real Madrid. As reported by Mundo Deportivo , and […] via Dermot Corrigan of ESPN FC, the Barcelona midfielder believes Messi is subject to abuse from those who wish to paint

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7441-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7441_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:41:54">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1896065-lionel-messi-attacks-barcelona-director-denies-pay-rise-request-allegations</link><title>Lionel Messi Attacks Barcelona Director, Denies Pay Rise Request…</title><description>* Lionel Messi Attacks Barcelona Director, Denies Pay Rise Request… 
Lionel Messi has launched a stinging message toward Barcelona board member Javier Faus , calling the director […] time and now Messi has hit back. Barcelona president Sandro Rosell previously stated Messi hadnt requested a pay […] rise back in September, claiming the invaluable player "hasnt said anything" after Real Madrid awarded Cristiano Ronaldo a

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7441-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7441_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:44:36">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1917001-ballon-dor-the-evolution-of-cristiano-ronaldo-from-2008-to-2013</link><title>Ballon DOr: The Evolution of Cristiano Ronaldo from 2008 to 2013</title><description>* Ballon DOr: The Evolution of Cristiano Ronaldo from 2008 to 2013 
have done much more to deserve it. However, Messi ’s own genius at the heart of a universally popular Barcelona side […] them for just a moment: He scored at an average of more than a goal a game.  By way of comparison, Messi ’s statistics […] goals in 221 appearances for  Real Madrid . He has become the fastest player to 50,100, 150 and 200 goals at Real Madrid

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7441-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7441_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:45:12">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1904448-building-the-perfect-la-liga-player</link><title>Building the Perfect La Liga Player</title><description>* Building the Perfect La Liga Player 
cheap. Real Madrid’s No. 7 scores goal after goal, penalty after penalty and free-kick after free kick—so help any […] : Cristiano Ronaldo (Real Madrid) Who else? If Cristiano Ronaldo’s right foot was to take out insurance, it wouldn ’t be […] (Real Valladolid )   Left foot: Gareth Bale (Real Madrid) On the opposite side to Ronaldo is Gareth Bale, a

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7441-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7441_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:47:32">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1915390-can-simeones-atletico-madrid-beat-barcelona-with-unorthodox-narrow-4-4-2</link><title>Can Simeones Atletico Madrid Beat Barcelona with Unorthodox, Narrow …</title><description>* Can Simeones Atletico Madrid Beat Barcelona with Unorthodox, Narrow … 
a positive goal difference of 36. When they won 1-0 away to Real Madrid  earlier in the season, for instance […] , Atletico had only 37 percent of the ball . Real played with what was effectively a 4-4-2 that day, so Barcelona may have […] this season, it’s the usual set-up for  Manchester City , Paris St-Germain and Atletico Madrid . All three play

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7441-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7441_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:49:11">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1920134-andres-iniesta-injury-updates-on-barcelona-stars-knee-and-return</link><title>Andres Iniesta Injury: Updates on Barcelona Stars Knee and Return</title><description>* Andres Iniesta Injury: Updates on Barcelona Stars Knee and Return 
Points may not have been the only thing Barcelona lost in the 0-0 draw with Atletico Madrid on Jan. 11. The […] lead over third-place Real Madrid dwindle to three points by the time Sundays action is through. […] Lionel Messi at halftime. Per Barcas website : Andr és Iniesta didn ’t participate in the

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7441-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7441_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 20:50:46">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1898369-cristiano-ronaldos-goal-in-3-2-win-vs-valencia-caps-remarkable-2013</link><title>Cristiano Ronaldos Goal in 3-2 Win vs. Valencia Caps Remarkable 2013</title><description>* Cristiano Ronaldos Goal in 3-2 Win vs. Valencia Caps Remarkable 2013 
’s goal had already added to an extraordinary year. It was his 59th goal for Real Madrid this season, which helped him […] as Real Madrid beat Valencia. It all amounted to setting the stage for Cristiano Ronaldo to finish the year as top dog […] Lionel Messi , who only managed 28 in an injury-struck year, and 11 more than Diego Costa, who has enjoyed a real breakout

17 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>