<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7447">running shoes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:30:03" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7447-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7447_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:30:04">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/12/24/barefoot-running-injuries_n_4493686.html</link><title>More Evidence To Make Your Transition To Barefoot Running Shoes A Gradual …</title><description>* More Evidence To Make Your Transition To Barefoot Running Shoes A Gradual … 
A small new study adds to the body of evidence that switching to barefoot running shoes isnt as simple as it sounds […] . During a 12-week training program, runners wearing minimalist shoes were more likely to experience an injury than runners

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7447-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7447_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:31:40">http://www.businessinsider.com/nyc-subways-buses-prepare-for-blizzard-2014-1</link><title>These Jet-Powered Snow Throwers Keep New Yorks Mass Transit Running In …</title><description>* These Jet-Powered Snow Throwers Keep New Yorks Mass Transit Running In … 
are purged of moisture to prevent them from freezing; electric trains are fitted with special third rail shoes with holes […] in them to prevent snow from sticking, exposed shoes are treated with de-icers and exposed couplers are covered to keep

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7447-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7447_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:34:01">http://deadspin.com/sneakers-gym-shoes-tennis-shoes-jumpers-sand-shoes-1488708194</link><title>Sneakers, gym shoes, tennis shoes, jumpers, sand shoes (?)</title><description>* Sneakers, gym shoes, tennis shoes, jumpers, sand shoes (?) 
Sneakers, gym shoes, tennis shoes, jumpers, sand shoes (?), running shoes, runners, or trainers? The New York Times […] has an interactive survey on local dialects, and its accurate to a really creepy level. But really, who says sand shoes

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7447-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7447_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:35:35">http://lifehacker.com/change-up-your-running-shoe-lacing-technique-to-improve-1495551389</link><title>Change Up Your Running Shoe Lacing Technique to Improve Comfort</title><description>* Change Up Your Running Shoe Lacing Technique to Improve Comfort 
Running shoes are made so they fit snuggly and comfortably around your feet, but the way you lace them up changes how

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7447-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7447_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:36:12">http://gigaom.com/2014/01/02/heapsylons-smart-socks-score-a-deal-with-vivobarefoot/</link><title>Heapsylon’s smart socks score a deal with Vivobarefoot</title><description>* Heapsylon’s smart socks score a deal with Vivobarefoot 
. Vivobarefoot is well-known for shoes that are optimized for barefoot running (only with shoes!). Getting the socks in stores that […] company Vivobarefoot to sell its Sensoria socks alongside the Vivo shoes. The socks track how a runner places his or her […] sell Vivo shoes will target the well-heeled runners that are most likely to buy the socks. The Sensoria socks come with an

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7447-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7447_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:37:19">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1909404-sugar-bowl-2014-derrick-henry-is-the-next-great-alabama-rb</link><title>Sugar Bowl 2014: Derrick Henry Is the Next Great Alabama RB</title><description>* Sugar Bowl 2014: Derrick Henry Is the Next Great Alabama RB 
offseason, the future at the running back position is looking brighter than the morning sun. Derrick Henry saved the last game […] something to think about. Sorry Yeldon , but Henry has to be the new starting running back.  At 63", 238 pounds, Henry is […] the modern-day Bo Jackson. This complete package hasnt quite been seen before. A running back this massive, fast, athletic

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7447-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7447_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:37:58">http://www.businessinsider.com/jr-smith-room-service-in-china-story-2014-1</link><title>JR Smith Ordered $3,000 In Room Service Just To See If They Would Keep …</title><description>* JR Smith Ordered $3,000 In Room Service Just To See If They Would Keep … 
repeatedly untying opponents shoes during games. In his article, Wojnarowski calls Smith "a soft, spoiled suburban jump […] greatest excess of idiocy had been a weekend of running a room service bill into the proximity of $3,000, a source with direct

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7447-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7447_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:40:06">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/01/04/taylor-swift-short-skirt_n_4541732.html</link><title>Taylor Swift Rocks A Short Skirt As She Runs Errands In Hollywood</title><description>* Taylor Swift Rocks A Short Skirt As She Runs Errands In Hollywood 
Taylor Swift sure knows how to look put together while running errands. The 24-year-old songstress rocked a short […] plaid skirt, tights and yellow shoes as she left the gym and headed out shopping in Hollywood. Swift finished off her

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7447-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7447_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:43:54">http://techcrunch.com/2014/01/07/yahoo-girds-its-loins-for-the-battle-over-your-home-screen/</link><title>Yahoo Girds Its Loins For The Battle Over Your Home Screen</title><description>* Yahoo Girds Its Loins For The Battle Over Your Home Screen 
grid design was used in many early smartphones running Palm and Symbian and Windows Mobile. But the iPhone really launched […] eyes of a lot of people — both iPhone users and people who picked up other smartphones running on other operating systems […] home screen that customizes itself to you, personally, feels as inevitable as a well-worn pair of shoes. Tech

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7447-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7447_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 21:45:12">http://gigaom.com/2014/01/03/ces-preview-technogym-google-glass-treadmill/</link><title>CES Preview: Technogym’s Google Glass controlled treadmill</title><description>* CES Preview: Technogym’s Google Glass controlled treadmill 
I had already planned to bring my running shoes to next week’s Consumer Electronics Show; now that I’ve seen this […] running nirvana. The Unity console already works with third-party software apps such as Withings, RunKeeper and and Map […] MyFitness, which is promising. But more exciting to me is using Glass as a running interface and seeing real-time fitness data in the

15 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>