<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7457">the music man lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:11:47" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7457-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7457_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:11:48">http://filmschoolrejects.com/news/bob-the-musical-allan-loeb.php</link><title>‘Bob the Musical’ Taps Allan Loeb to Rewrite Story of Man Living Our …</title><description>* ‘Bob the Musical’ Taps Allan Loeb to Rewrite Story of Man Living Our … 
one man’s reluctant relationship with the music playing in his mind  – and his apparently very serious cranial injury […] . The film would follow Bob, an average Joe who suffered a blow to the head and started hearing constant music and singing […] script . If you were one of the many probably cringing after reading the name of that musical, fear not —   Bob ‘s music

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7457-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7457_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:13:38">http://www.openculture.com/2014/01/cartoonist-r-crumb-offers-his-blunt-thoughts-on-21-cultural-figures.html</link><title>Cartoonist R. Crumb Assesses 21 Cultural Figures, from Dylan &amp; Hitchcock, …</title><description>* Cartoonist R. Crumb Assesses 21 Cultural Figures, from Dylan &amp; Hitchcock, … 
Any fan of “underground” comic artist Robert Crumb knows that the man has no shyness about his preferences: not in jazz […] music, not in politics, and certainly not in the female form. Alex Wood, co-operator of the official R. Crumb site […] ,” Wood writes. “We all know he loves old music from the early part of the last century, and doesn’t like rock music. But then

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7457-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7457_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:14:42">http://www.nerdist.com/2014/01/top-10-a-music-geeks-favorite-albums-of-2013/</link><title>Top 10: A Music Geek’s Favorite Albums of 2013</title><description>* Top 10: A Music Geek’s Favorite Albums of 2013 
lives as a family man, awarded him with his own holiday — August 28th — and the Liberty Bell Award — the city’s highest […] represented this underground dance music so well to the outside. As an ambassador of this evolution of what was once called juke […] , that pushed the listener to parse her lyrics and lean on her glistening voice for resolution. This sort of listening

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7457-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7457_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:16:16">http://consequenceofsound.net/2014/01/album-review-stephen-malkmus-and-the-jicks-wig-out-at-jagbags-2/</link><title>Album Review: Stephen Malkmus and the Jicks – Wig Out at Jagbags</title><description>* Album Review: Stephen Malkmus and the Jicks – Wig Out at Jagbags 
seeking their inner child through indie rock’s poster boy/man. Jagbags has the overarching feel of a party full of nostalgia […] . On the album’s second single, “Lariat”, Malkmus essentially proposes a toast: “We grew up listening to the music of the […] consideration of identity has given way to the simple gratitude of still being able to write guitar licks and lyrics for Jicks songs

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7457-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7457_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:17:10">http://hollywoodlife.com/2013/12/30/drake-trophies-new-song-listen/</link><title>Drake Releases New Song ‘Trophies’ — Listen</title><description>* Drake Releases New Song ‘Trophies’ — Listen 
Apparently the holidays are the perfect time for Drake to release music! On Dec. 29, he released his track ‘Trophies […] if someone else is doing [it].” Drake Releases ‘Trophies’ — Full Lyrics Listen to the new hit song and read the lyrics […] A bunch of handshakes from the fakes But n– I do not want to be friends though I told y’all maf—as, man, this sh-t is

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7457-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7457_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:18:54">http://consequenceofsound.net/aux-out/a-gray-matter-on-donald-glover-and-post-blackness/</link><title>A Gray Matter: On Donald Glover and Post-Blackness</title><description>* A Gray Matter: On Donald Glover and Post-Blackness 
West—a man who has actually attacked the ideas of blackness through his fashion and music. Also, Kanye has paved the road […] Component is a section of Aux.Out. for one-off pieces, special editorials, and lost orphans of the music discussion […] . Today, H. Drew Blackburn discusses Childish Gambino and the effect the polarizing rap artist can have on the individual

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7457-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7457_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:20:13">http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2013/12/25/the-christmas-rendition-of-hallelujah-that-youll-have-on-repeat-after-just-one-listen/</link><title>The Christmas Rendition of ‘Hallelujah’ That You’ll Have on Repeat After …</title><description>* The Christmas Rendition of ‘Hallelujah’ That You’ll Have on Repeat After … 
for good reason. Originally uploaded in 2012, the official music video for “A Hallelujah Christmas” by Cloverton has been […] four members, altered the lyrics to Leonard Cohen’s “Hallelujah” to transform it into a Christmas tune. The song has since […] utterly breathtaking,” yet one more individual wrote. “Thank you for that.” Watch the music video: – Follow Oliver

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7457-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7457_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:21:21">http://www.towleroad.com/2014/01/news.html</link><title>News: Pig, Lady Gaga, Liquor Habits, Mennonites, Sean Strub</title><description>* News: Pig, Lady Gaga, Liquor Habits, Mennonites, Sean Strub 
through in 2014? The Guardian s music writers think so . Boy Culture interviews Sean Strub about his new book Body […] , but I think its silly because the lyrics were written by me as an expression of urban youths having fun at the YMCA. The […] about your politics . Bethenny Frankel frolicking in the surf with a slab of beef . Where does the LGBT movement go

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7457-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7457_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:22:43">http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2013/12/18/pop-princess-appears-to-have-been-caught-majorly-lip-syncing-during-awards-show/</link><title>Pop Princess Appears to Have Been Caught Majorly Lip-Syncing During …</title><description>* Pop Princess Appears to Have Been Caught Majorly Lip-Syncing During … 
Pop singer Katy Perry appeared to suffer a lip-sync gaffe over the weekend at NRJ Music Awards in Cannes, France, but a […] the best,” the man interrupting Perry’s performance said, according to The Wrap , translated from French. But it didn […] tone of her voice is not what we are used to. When the lyrics started, she could not get back in sync either with the words

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7457-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7457_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:23:45">http://www.webpronews.com/star-spangled-banner-to-be-displayed-at-smithsonian-2014-01</link><title>Star-Spangled Banner To Be Displayed At Smithsonian</title><description>* Star-Spangled Banner To Be Displayed At Smithsonian 
original, handwritten manuscript of “The Star-Spangled Banner” and the flag that inspired the lyrics. These pieces of history […] poem eventually had a title change, was set to music, and became the national anthem of America in 1931. The quill and ink […] Armistead, the commander of Fort McHenry. Armistead was also the man who commissioned the flag with 15 stars and 15 stripes to

14 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>