<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7458">rice recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:25:34" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7458-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7458_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:25:35">http://www.buzzfeed.com/christinebyrne/reasons-singapore-is-the-most-delicious-place-on-earth</link><title>27 Reasons Singapore Is The Most Delicious Place On Earth</title><description>* 27 Reasons Singapore Is The Most Delicious Place On Earth 
mop up every last bit of sauce. Heres a recipe . seafoodparadise.com.sg 100Plus WHAT IT IS […] need to taste it for yourself to really understand the appeal. 100plus.com.sg Hainanese Chicken Rice […] WHAT IT IS: Chicken is poached with ginger and pandan leaves, then the rice is toasted in oil and cooked in the super

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7458-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7458_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:28:45">http://directorblue.blogspot.nl/2013/12/susan-rice-stars-as-pajamaboy.html</link><title>Susan Rice Stars as Pajamaboy on "60 Minutes"</title><description>* Susan Rice Stars as Pajamaboy on "60 Minutes" 
" broadcast on Sunday instead of Susan Rice. The current national security adviser and former U.S. ambassador to the United […] , it was deja vu all over again. Rice went on five Sunday talk shows on Sept. 16, 2012, five days after an al […] ." Rice did have time, though, to repeat the line that she subbed for Secretary Hillary Clinton that Sunday because Clinton

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7458-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7458_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:29:50">http://www.refinery29.com/foodie-underground/4</link><title>This Gluten-Free Chocolate Cakes Surprising Ingredient</title><description>* This Gluten-Free Chocolate Cakes Surprising Ingredient 
: Mix It Up With This Hazelnut And Kale Pesto Putting kale in a chocolate cake might not be your first choice in recipe […] anyone scoffs at you for making something vegan or gluten-free, it’s just because they haven’t tried a good recipe. All […] recipe to guests. You always want to make sure you have tasted what you are serving first. But, there was no other dessert on

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7458-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7458_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:31:36">http://www.inquisitr.com/1071893/low-cholesterol-recipes-for-happy-healthy-holidays/</link><title>Low-Cholesterol Recipes For Happy, Healthy Holidays</title><description>* Low-Cholesterol Recipes For Happy, Healthy Holidays 
great, hummus also has zero cholesterol , making it even more enjoyable. Try this recipe from Dave Lieberman , courtesy of […] -conscious, but this grain packs more nutrition with it than most starches, including brown rice . And it brings no cholesterol to […] cooker Spicy Black-Eyed Peas recipe might change your mind about which to choose and comes out to just 10 mg of cholesterol

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7458-05"><link>http://www.celebitchy.com/342236/gwyneth_paltrows_annual_new_years_detox_features_solid_food_once_a_day/</link><title>Gwyneth Paltrow’s annual New Year’s detox features solid food… once a …</title><description>* Gwyneth Paltrow’s annual New Year’s detox features solid food… once a … 
, especially since her new thing seemed to be starving her children of eggs, pasta, rice, eggs and milk (although she later […] . And at 1:30, her recipe for lunch — which serves four! — includes just one cup of chickpeas, six cups of water, one large

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7458-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7458_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:35:37">http://www.refinery29.com/new-potato/43</link><title>Orange Is The New Black s Kate Mulgrew Would Host One Hell Of A Dinner …</title><description>* Orange Is The New Black s Kate Mulgrew Would Host One Hell Of A Dinner … 
cake recipe. Netflix’s Orange is the New Black, a darkly comedic show that takes place in a women’s prison, has become TV […] perfect 17-minute rice and Italian broccoli, or a couple of rib-eye steaks with a gorgeous bitter salad of radicchio, arugula

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7458-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7458_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:37:12">http://www.refinery29.com/elizabeth-street/13</link><title>Powerhouse DKNY PR Girl On How She Does It All</title><description>* Powerhouse DKNY PR Girl On How She Does It All 
, I know it will all get done if I sacrifice an hour of sleep." What is your go-to recipe that you know your kids will […] in the skillet. Add steamed broccoli, and a side of rice and youve got a 15-minute meal that the whole family will eat

17 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>