<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7460">kobe bryant news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:39:34" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7460-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7460_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:39:35">http://www.inquisitr.com/1067945/kobe-bryant-back-on-the-sidelines-in-tough-break-for-lakers/</link><title>Kobe Bryant Back On The Sidelines In Tough Break For Lakers</title><description>* Kobe Bryant Back On The Sidelines In Tough Break For Lakers 
to find out what he can do,” the Lakers’ former general manager told TMZ . How devastating is the news of Kobe Bryant […] up and retire? Kobe Bryant Back On The Sidelines In Tough Break For Lakers is a post from: The Inquisitr News […] Kobe Bryant will miss the next 6 weeks worth of the L.A. Lakers season with a fracture in his left knee, the team

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7460-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7460_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:41:01">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1901333-kobe-bryant-more-locked-in-now-than-ive-been-my-entire-career-as-return-nears</link><title>Kobe Bryant More Locked in Now Than Ive Been My Entire Career as Return …</title><description>* Kobe Bryant More Locked in Now Than Ive Been My Entire Career as Return … 
LOS ANGELES – Six weeks. That’s what this is to Kobe Bryant . It’s not an old man breaking down. It’s not a song […] and so inspirational to his legions of fans. Neither Bryant nor his fanbase is in any way ready for Kobe to become a […] has embraced all broken-body challenges to the point that Phil Jackson cited Bryant as beyond Michael Jordan in sheer guts

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7460-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7460_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:42:02">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1895821-kobe-bryant-will-be-just-fine-but-la-lakers-left-to-pick-up-the-pieces</link><title>Kobe Bryant Will Be Just Fine, but LA Lakers Left to Pick Up the…</title><description>* Kobe Bryant Will Be Just Fine, but LA Lakers Left to Pick Up the… 
with their latest deflating news Thursday, when an MRI exam revealed a fracture of the lateral tibial plateau in Kobe […] Bryant ’s left leg. After failing to win a third consecutive NBA title in 2011, the Lakers were immediately force-fed the […] death of Lakers owner Jerry Buss on Feb. 18, 2013, shaking the entire foundation of the franchise. Along the way, Bryant

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7460-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7460_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:43:04">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1895577-challenges-and-obstacles-kobe-bryant-faces-in-knee-injury-recovery</link><title>What You Need to Know About Kobe Bryants Knee Injury</title><description>* What You Need to Know About Kobe Bryants Knee Injury 
News broke late Thursday that Kobe Bryant has another injury to his leg. The Los Angeles  Lakers Twitter account […]  gave us the bad news. He was diagnosed with a fracture to the lateral tibial plateau : The first thing we should do is […] of those are true exactly for Bryant. This NBA .com video shows the likely incident where his knee was injured

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7460-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7460_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:45:21">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1893309-has-kobe-bryants-love-for-the-game-reached-a-new-zenith-at-age-35</link><title>Has Kobe Bryants Love for the Game Reached a New Zenith at Age 35?</title><description>* Has Kobe Bryants Love for the Game Reached a New Zenith at Age 35? 
MEMPHIS, Tenn. — Love what you do. Love what you do and youll have a chance to do it as long and as well as Kobe […] Bryant is doing his job. Where does Bryant stand now as far as his love for the game goes, I ask Tuesday night. “It […] ’s probably a little bit more now than it’s ever been,” Bryant answers, “because there’s a finality to it.” The end is likely

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7460-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7460_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:47:18">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1895527-kobe-bryant-injury-update-lakers-star-out-6-weeks-with-fracture-in-knee</link><title>Kobe Bryant Injury Update: Lakers Star Out 6 Weeks with Fracture in …</title><description>* Kobe Bryant Injury Update: Lakers Star Out 6 Weeks with Fracture in … 
Kobe Bryant s comeback from a ruptured Achilles tendon lasted all of six games. The Los Angeles Lakers announced on […] Twitter that Bryant will miss six weeks with a knee injury: Injury Update: Kobe Bryant has a fracture of the lateral tibial […] all of this, however, as Ken Berger of CBS passes along: Kobe Bryant will not need surgery on his leg fracture, league

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7460-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7460_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:48:23">http://www.sbnation.com/nba/2014/1/10/5296528/nba-news-kobe-bryant-eric-bledsoe-injury</link><title>NBA news roundup: Lakers re-evaluating Kobe Bryant and Steve Nash, Eric …</title><description>* NBA news roundup: Lakers re-evaluating Kobe Bryant and Steve Nash, Eric … 
another team loses its starting point guard for an extended period. The Los Angeles Lakers will re-evaluate both Kobe […] Bryant and Steve Nash after their annual "Grammy" road trip,  reports Dave McMenamin of ESPN . The Lakers next three games

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7460-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7460_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:49:18">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1895569-kobe-bryant-injury-another-massive-disappointment-for-nba-fans</link><title>Kobe Bryant Injury Another Massive Disappointment for NBA Fans</title><description>* Kobe Bryant Injury Another Massive Disappointment for NBA Fans 
The Kobe Bryant injury bombshell dropped on Thursday, proving to NBA loyalists across the globe that hope is a very […] extending his career after an injury that had ended so many others. Lakers fans, in particular, needed Bryant to play. Kobe […] dangerous thing. Per a Los Angeles Lakers press release , Bryant will be sidelined for an extended period with a knee injury

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7460-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7460_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:51:09">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1893176-kobe-bryant-injury-updates-on-lakers-stars-knee-and-recovery</link><title>Kobe Bryant Injury: Updates on Lakers Stars Knee and Recovery</title><description>* Kobe Bryant Injury: Updates on Lakers Stars Knee and Recovery 
Los Angeles Lakers guard Kobe Bryant suffered a minor left knee injury in the teams 96-92 victory over the Memphis […] Bryant after the contest, who claimed that he "twisted" the knee after bumping into Tony Allen midway through the third […] quarter: Bryant told me that he "twisted" his knee "a little bit," and that its "a little stiff." Should be OK for Friday vs

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7460-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7460_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:52:55">http://bleacherreport.com/articles/1919467-kobe-bryant-can-barely-watch-clippers-beat-down-his-lakers</link><title>Kobe Bryant Can Barely Watch Clippers Beat Down His Lakers</title><description>* Kobe Bryant Can Barely Watch Clippers Beat Down His Lakers 
beat-down —not the fans, not the players and certainly not  Kobe Bryant .  Unfortunately for Kobe, their were plenty of […] , Bryant has tried to show his courageous, competitive side to the public. After hearing news of the injury, he tweeted […] later against the Memphis Grizzlies . At the time, Bryant was expected to miss six weeks.  Since the latest setback

14 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>