<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7463">hollywood actress</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:55:56" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7463-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7463_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:55:57">http://www.algemeiner.com/2014/01/09/actress-meryl-streep-blasts-walt-disney-as-anti-semitic-zoa-condemns-actress-emma-thompson/</link><title>Actress Meryl Streep Blasts Walt Disney as Anti-Semitic; ZOA Condemns …</title><description>* Actress Meryl Streep Blasts Walt Disney as Anti-Semitic; ZOA Condemns … 
Walt Disney, in 1954. Photo: WikiCommons. Hollywood actress Meryl Streep blasted Walt Disney as an anti […] . Ironically, Streep’s nine-minute speech was to honor the actress who portrayed ‘Mary Poppins’ creator P.L. Travers in The Walt […] ’t stop flowing until the Hollywood Foreign Press Association’s gala on Sunday. But this year’s ceremony will forever be

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7463-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7463_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:56:39">http://www.buzzfeed.com/alisonvingiano/saturday-night-live-hires-lakendra-tookes-and-le</link><title>"Saturday Night Live" Hires LaKendra Tookes And Leslie Jones, Both …</title><description>* "Saturday Night Live" Hires LaKendra Tookes And Leslie Jones, Both … 
Starting Monday, Jan. 13, LaKendra Tookes and Leslie Jones will join SNL as writers, according to The Hollywood […] , and scarce." Earlier this year, when actress Kerry Washington hosted SNL , the show directly address its limited […] diversity during the episodes " cold open ." But there were also concerns about the narrow roles the Scandal actress played on

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7463-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7463_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:57:34">http://hollywoodlife.com/2013/12/27/breaking-bads-anna-gunn-lupus-is-behind-her-dramatic-weight-loss/</link><title>‘Breaking Bad’ Star Anna Gunn: Lupus Behind Her Dramatic Weight Loss</title><description>* ‘Breaking Bad’ Star Anna Gunn: Lupus Behind Her Dramatic Weight Loss 
‘Breaking Bad’ actress had lost so much weight, and now an insider has revealed to HollywoodLife.com EXCLUSIVELY that the award […] , HollywoodLife.com  EXCLUSIVELY learned that Breaking Bad ‘s Anna Gunn also has the disease. Sources close to the actress […] source close to the actress told HollywoodLife.com EXCLUSIVELY. When asked about her weight loss at the Governor’s Ball

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7463-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7463_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 22:58:50">http://www.inquisitr.com/1087831/emmy-nominated-actress-carmen-zapata-dies-at-86/</link><title>Emmy-Nominated Actress Carmen Zapata Dies At 86</title><description>* Emmy-Nominated Actress Carmen Zapata Dies At 86 
Actress in a segment of Medical Center and Carola on Hollywood TV Theatre. She received a star on the Hollywood Walk of […] Emmy-nominated actress Carmen Zapata died Sunday of heart problems, colleagues said. She was 86. Zapata died in her […] mother, Carmen Zapata co-founded the Bilingual Foundation in 1973 with Cuban-born actress and playwright Margarita Galban

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7463-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7463_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:00:23">http://www.inquisitr.com/1092806/amy-adams-wins-golden-globes-best-actress-award-gushes-over-3-year-old-daughter/</link><title>Amy Adams Wins Golden Globes Best Actress Award, Gushes Over 3-Year-Old …</title><description>* Amy Adams Wins Golden Globes Best Actress Award, Gushes Over 3-Year-Old … 
Amy Adams confirmed her status as one of Hollywood’s best modern actresses by picking up the Golden Globe for Best […] Actress in a Comedy last night. Adams was awarded the gong for her turn in David O Russell’s highly celebrated, American […] the 70s drama, Jennifer Lawrence , also won the Best Supporting Actress accolade for her role as Christian Bale’s wife

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7463-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7463_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:01:07">http://www.deadline.com/2014/01/michelle-obama-reschedules-hollywood-fundraiser-at-phil-rosenthals-place-that-got-nixed-by-government-shutdown/</link><title>Michelle Obama Reschedules Hollywood Fundraiser At Phil Rosenthal’s …</title><description>* Michelle Obama Reschedules Hollywood Fundraiser At Phil Rosenthal’s … 
DNC fundraiser at the Hancock Park home of Everybody Loves Raymond creator Phil Rosenthal and his wife, actress […] shutdown made it seem icky — FLOTUS glad-handing Hollywood types who’d forked over $1,250 to $32,400 for the privilege, while […] pulled the plug on a planned San Francisco fundraiser. Related: First Lady Subs For President Obama At Hollywood

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7463-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7463_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:02:36">http://www.inquisitr.com/1082258/juanita-moore-pioneering-african-american-actress-dies-at-99/</link><title>Juanita Moore, Pioneering African-American Actress, Dies At 99</title><description>* Juanita Moore, Pioneering African-American Actress, Dies At 99 
Juanita Moore, a 1959 Academy Award nominee who blazed a trail for African-American actresses in Hollywood, died on New […] actress long believed. At the time, African-American actresses were rarely cast as characters who were not maids or servants […] Hollywood fame. Believing she’s better than her upbringing, the daughter pretends to be white and rejects her hurting mother

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7463-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7463_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:04:05">http://www.inquisitr.com/1089572/anna-paquin-true-blood-actress-ready-to-move-behind-the-camera/</link><title>Anna Paquin: ‘True Blood’ Actress Ready To Move Behind The Camera</title><description>* Anna Paquin: ‘True Blood’ Actress Ready To Move Behind The Camera 
-year-old Oscar-winning actress is starring in the upcoming movie Free Ride along with husband and True Blood co […] same as everybody else’s childhood, but she’s this incredible survivor.” Anna hasn’t had so much luck in Hollywood lately […] season would be the final one for the show. Anna Paquin: ‘True Blood’ Actress Ready To Move Behind The Camera is a post 

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7463-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7463_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:05:31">http://www.americanthinker.com/2014/01/the_hypocrisy_of_hollywood.html</link><title>The Hypocrisy of Hollywood</title><description>* The Hypocrisy of Hollywood 
Polar Vortex Establishing a U.S. State Religion The Hypocrisy of Hollywood Going Through the Motions on Military Suicide […] desperationPresident Obama Targets Promise ZonesVenezuela rocked by murder of popular soap opera actress and former Miss Venezuela

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7463-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7463_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:07:02">http://www.webpronews.com/alicia-rhett-film-actress-dies-at-age-98-2014-01</link><title>Alicia Rhett, Film Actress, Dies At Age 98</title><description>* Alicia Rhett, Film Actress, Dies At Age 98 
Another member of the Hollywood community has been hit with the recent death of Alicia Rhett. She never achieved the […] , is Olivia De Havilland, who recently mourned the loss of Joan Fontaine, her sister, and an actress she had a feud with […] leaving Hollywood, developing a reputation as a talented artist. Image via Wikimedia Commons

15 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>