<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7477">china bird flu</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:55:25" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7477-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7477_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:55:26">http://www.businessinsider.com/new-h10n8-bird-flu-infecting-humans-2013-12</link><title>Chinese Woman Killed By Third New Bird Flu Strain To Jump To Humans This …</title><description>* Chinese Woman Killed By Third New Bird Flu Strain To Jump To Humans This … 
For the third time this year a new strain of bird flu virus has been found to infect people. The flu virus, H10N8 […] journalist  Alan Dove wrote on Twitter: "People have probably been dying of sporadic bird flu spillovers for eons, but we only […] infect birds.  Another new bird flu, of the strain H6N1 also infected a human for the first time this year. That person

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7477-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7477_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:57:24">http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/01/10/china-h7n9-bird-flu-death_n_4574483.html</link><title>China Reports Another H7N9 Bird Flu Death</title><description>* China Reports Another H7N9 Bird Flu Death 
BEIJING, Jan 10 (Reuters) - China reported one more death from the H7N9 strain of bird flu in eastern Fujian province […] strain of bird flu in the past week, taking to around 150 the total number of cases so far. The H7N9 bird […] flu emerged last year in China and has infected around 150 people there and in Taiwan and Hong Kong, killing at least 45

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7477-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7477_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:58:04">http://www.zerohedge.com/news/2013-12-22/chicken-sales-plummet-china-hong-kong-after-bird-flu-returns</link><title>Chicken Sales Plummet in China, Hong Kong After Bird Flu Returns</title><description>* Chicken Sales Plummet in China, Hong Kong After Bird Flu Returns 
well. As Japans NHK reports, H7N9 bird flu strain is once again spreading in southern China, claiming the 148th victim of […] authorities in southern China are increasing measures against the spread of the H7N9 bird flu. They are warning that the chance of […] already plunged by 40% on just the several hushed bird flu stories alone. Chicken was absent from many local dinner

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7477-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7477_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 23:59:45">http://www.webpronews.com/h5n1-bird-flu-found-in-canada-2014-01</link><title>H5N1 Bird Flu Found In Canada – Victim From Bejing</title><description>* H5N1 Bird Flu Found In Canada – Victim From Bejing 
The H5N1 Bird Flu had found its way to North America and the first fatal case of the flu was confirmed in Canada […] . According to Canadian health officials , the victim was traveling from China to Canada when he began to experience flu […] being monitored and so far, none of them have tested positive for the Bird Flu. “The patient’s family is not showing any

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7477-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7477_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:00:40">http://www.webpronews.com/new-bird-flu-strain-claims-human-life-2013-12</link><title>New Bird Flu Strain Claims Human Life</title><description>* New Bird Flu Strain Claims Human Life 
The new H10N8 strain of the bird flu, which had previously not been known to infect humans has been confirmed as the […] yet to confirm the death is related to the new strain of bird flu, the World Health Organization (WHO) told Reuters that […] concerned due to another recent outbreak of bird flu, namely the H7N9 strain that has infected at least 140 people this spring

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7477-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7477_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:01:30">http://www.ibtimes.com/first-human-infection-h10n8-bird-flu-strain-discovered-china-killing-one-1514150</link><title>First Human Infection Of H10N8 Bird Flu Strain Discovered In China, …</title><description>* First Human Infection Of H10N8 Bird Flu Strain Discovered In China, … 
Yet another new strain of avian influenza, or bird flu, has been discovered to affect humans, taking the life of one […] person in China. An elderly woman from central China’s Jiangxi province has been the first confirmed victim of the disease

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7477-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7477_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:03:54">http://www.ibtimes.com/china-reports-first-case-h10n8-new-strain-bird-flu-infection-humans-womans-death-could-be-related</link><title>China Reports First Case Of H10N8, A New Strain Of Bird Flu Infection …</title><description>* China Reports First Case Of H10N8, A New Strain Of Bird Flu Infection … 
China confirmed the first case of infection from H10N8 -- a strain of bird flu previously not reported in humans -- in […] respiratory failure on Dec. 6, who was later confirmed to have been infected by H10N8, one of the 15 known bird flu strains

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7477-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7477_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:07:28">http://bostonherald.com/news_opinion/international/asia/2013/12/china_says_woman_died_from_bird_flu_new_to_humans</link><title>China says woman died from bird flu new to humans</title><description>* China says woman died from bird flu new to humans 
the H10N8 bird flu virus, a strain that had not previously been found in people, the Jiangxi province health department […] BEIJING — Chinese authorities said Wednesday that a 73-year-old Chinese woman died after being infected with a bird […] flu strain that had sickened a human for the first time, a development that the World Health Organization called

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7477-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7477_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:08:46">http://www.businessinsider.com/infectious-disease-outbreak-preparedness-2013-12</link><title>These States Are Totally Unprepared For A Major Virus Outbreak</title><description>* These States Are Totally Unprepared For A Major Virus Outbreak 
considering the recent outbreak in China of three new strains of bird flu , and a new SARS-like virus in the Middle East […] America: The flu About 20% of Americans get the seasonal flu each year and generate about $10 billion in medical […] expenses. Most people are not getting the flu vaccine every year: Only about 42% of adults were vaccinated in 2012. Thats

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7477-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7477_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:10:35">http://www.webpronews.com/h5n1-victims-family-speaks-out-2014-01</link><title>H5N1 Victim’s Family Members Speak Out</title><description>* H5N1 Victim’s Family Members Speak Out 
North America’s first bird flu related death happened in Canada on January 3, 2014. Details about the victim are […] . After she was admitted to the hospital it was discovered that she had H5N1 or Bird Flu. Health workers assured the public […] daughter and wife. The family was not willing to release the victim’s name but said she was in her 20′s and grew up in China

14 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>