<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7478">protect kids online</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:12:38" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7478-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7478_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:12:39">http://thenextweb.com/insider/2014/01/11/9-predictions-kids-tech-2014/</link><title>9 predictions for kids’ tech in 2014</title><description>* 9 predictions for kids’ tech in 2014 
legislation to protect kids and teens. Toca Boca signs its first TV deal Toca Boca – one of the most surprising kids tablet […] Dylan Collins ( @MrDylanCollins ) is CEO of SuperAwesome , the largest digital kids marketing platform in the UK. He […] is also an investor with Hoxton Ventures and sits on the board of Brown Bag Films (the award-winning kids animation

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7478-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7478_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:13:37">http://www.patheos.com/blogs/friendlyatheist/2014/01/06/how-to-ruin-your-gay-kids-life-inside-linda-harveys-book-maybe-hes-not-gay/</link><title>How to Ruin Your Gay Kid’s Life: Inside Linda Harvey’s Book ‘Maybe He’s …</title><description>* How to Ruin Your Gay Kid’s Life: Inside Linda Harvey’s Book ‘Maybe He’s … 
Amazon left the option open to put it back online and that she and her publisher “will probably re-post it in the near future […] .” Jeremy Hooper reported that while the book costs around $10, the toll it will take on the LGBT kids who have to deal with […] , why does it matter if it’s a choice or not? Many people choose to be religious, and yet we constitutionally protect them

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7478-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7478_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:15:44">http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2013/12/31/watch-how-her-face-dramatically-changes-in-different-light-settings/</link><title>Watch How Her Face Dramatically Changes in Different Light Settings</title><description>* Watch How Her Face Dramatically Changes in Different Light Settings 
An online video purports to reveal how the looks of an individual’s face can change in different light settings. The […] Grandpa Pushing Wife in Wheelchair Has Run-In With Two of the ‘Scummiest Things’ He’s Ever Seen After Trying to Protect the […] Neighbor Kids

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7478-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7478_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:16:59">http://reason.com/blog/2013/12/20/uks-new-online-porn-filters-blocking-sex</link><title>UK’s New Online Porn Filters Blocking Sex Ed, Health Websites</title><description>* UK’s New Online Porn Filters Blocking Sex Ed, Health Websites 
porn online, there were plenty of critics. TheElectronic Frontier Foundation, for instance, speculated that under the […] weeks. Cameron said the reason for requiring Internet users to have to opt-into porn viewing is to "protect our children […] and their innocence."(The measure also bans "extreme," or violent, pornography.) So,while softcore online pornography has

17 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>