<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7482">popular twitter stars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:22:35" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7482-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7482_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:22:36">http://www.towleroad.com/2014/01/popular-russian-actor-calls-on-putin-to-criminalize-gay-sex.html</link><title>Popular Russian Actor Calls on Putin to Criminalize Gay Sex</title><description>* Popular Russian Actor Calls on Putin to Criminalize Gay Sex 
Ivan Okhlobystin, the popular Russian actor, sci fi writer, aspiring politician, and creative director of the phone […] of service, according to the Twitter of the site’s creator Stuart Gibson, who is openly gay. But the statement caused a […] opposition activist Ksenia Sobchak. This is not the first instance of gay-bashing from Okhlobystin, who stars in “Interns,” a

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7482-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7482_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:23:13">http://www.mediaite.com/tv/we-should-ridicule-duck-dynasty-stars-views-on-homosexuality-but-suspend-him-come-on/</link><title>We Should Ridicule Duck Dynasty Star’s Views on Homosexuality; But …</title><description>* We Should Ridicule Duck Dynasty Star’s Views on Homosexuality; But … 
ridiculous. The Duck Dynasty brand is down-home social conservatism and Bible worship. Many people tune in for the stars […] there is a “gay agenda” coming after “good Christians” in popular culture. While they inflate that so-called “war” to a […] reductive, knee-jerked anti-gay rhetoric of social conservatism. – – &gt;&gt; Follow Andrew Kirell (@AndrewKirell) on Twitter

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7482-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7482_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:24:29">http://www.inquisitr.com/1091412/roddy-piper-wants-wrestlemania-30-match-with-hulk-hogan/</link><title>Roddy Piper Wants Wrestlemania 30 Match With Hulk Hogan</title><description>* Roddy Piper Wants Wrestlemania 30 Match With Hulk Hogan 
will not only be an homage to the very first Wrestlemania, but it will also feature two of the most popular WWE stars of […] Roddy Piper wants to fight Hulk Hogan at Wrestlemania 30 , and he’s taken to his Twitter account to try and generate […] of his Twitter followers to erupt with excitement: @R_Roddy_Piper at WM30, the two guys that were the reason Mania

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7482-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7482_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:25:58">http://www.niemanlab.org/2013/12/find-starters-not-stars/</link><title>Find starters, not stars</title><description>* Find starters, not stars 
2013 was a big year for “stars” in the news industry — Nate Silver (and Jason Whitlock and Keith Olbermann) to ESPN […] bold branding move for a media company. However, between the small number of true individual stars (ones who combine […] there than bonafide stars. There are plenty of examples of starters in news media from the past year (or two), and if the

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7482-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7482_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:26:36">http://www.inquisitr.com/1085836/justin-bieber-miley-cyrus-jennifer-lawrence-on-forbes-2014-30-under-30-list/</link><title>Justin Bieber, Miley Cyrus, J-Law, Shine Bright On Forbes’ 2014 ’30 …</title><description>* Justin Bieber, Miley Cyrus, J-Law, Shine Bright On Forbes’ 2014 ’30 … 
. The popular star’s latest film American Hustle has been described as this year’s Argo. This past weekend the film […] “the brightest stars” under the age of 30 who are “reinventing the world right now.” The list includes 15 different […] up over 10 million more Twitter followers. He also raised funds and contributed significantly to a number of charitable

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7482-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7482_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:27:42">http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2013/12/21/is-this-bank-robber-impersonating-duck-dynasty-cast-member/</link><title>Is This Bank Robber Impersonating ‘Duck Dynasty’ Cast Member?</title><description>* Is This Bank Robber Impersonating ‘Duck Dynasty’ Cast Member? 
worn by cast members of the popular television series that’s attracted controversy this week. Image source: Twitter […] . One lingering question: Was he impersonating Santa…or a ‘Duck Dynasty’ cast member? Image source: Twitter […] Image source: Twitter On Wednesday, A&amp;E placed cast member Phil Robertson on indefinite hiatus following a number of

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7482-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7482_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:29:28">http://hollywoodlife.com/2013/12/31/miley-cyrus-new-years-eve-2014-outfit-performance-pics/</link><title>Miley Cyrus’ Sexy Gold New Year’s Eve Performance Outfit — See It Here</title><description>* Miley Cyrus’ Sexy Gold New Year’s Eve Performance Outfit — See It Here 
she shared her popular hits with the crowd — but it was her outfit that really had us do a double-take. Miley loves […] , she’s just being Miley! It looks like she saved the best look for last. Miley, who admitted on Twitter that she was sick […] — Her Big Year: 2013 was definitely the star’s year to shine. Not only did she debut a brand new look and release her

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7482-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7482_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:32:16">http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2013/12/23/today-i-did-something-incredibly-dangerous-incredibly-stupid-all-for-your-entertainment/</link><title>‘Today I Did Something Incredibly Dangerous &amp; Incredibly Stupid, All …</title><description>* ‘Today I Did Something Incredibly Dangerous &amp; Incredibly Stupid, All … 
inspired by an image he saw on popular website Reddit two weeks ago and that he did not fear for his safety. “I am confident […] video had roughly 120,000 views on YouTube. – Follow Oliver Darcy ( @oliverdarcy ) on Twitter Other Must […] -Read Stories: So, this Ted Cruz video is pretty inspiring Video: The year’s biggest YouTube stars come together for #2013

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7482-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7482_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:33:20">http://www.webpronews.com/paranormal-activity-the-marked-ones-tops-friday-box-office-with-8-7m-2014-01</link><title>‘Paranormal Activity: The Marked Ones’ Tops Friday Box Office With …</title><description>* ‘Paranormal Activity: The Marked Ones’ Tops Friday Box Office With … 
million. While the numbers were quite impressive, the ever-popular scare film series did suffer a minor setback, due to the […] flagship that producers are looked to develop into a new film franchise. The film which stars, Andrew Jacobs and Gabrielle […] Twitter | Paranormal Activity    Wikimedia Commons | Paranormal Activity: Marked Ones

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7482-10"><link>http://www.webpronews.com/jenny-mccarthy-says-no-to-smoking-in-2014-2013-12</link><title>Jenny McCarthy Says No to Smoking in 2014</title><description>* Jenny McCarthy Says No to Smoking in 2014 
Eve pic.twitter.com/uDv0gz7E5Y — Good Morning America (@GMA) December 31, 2013 “In a world where people are on […] stars admit that the cold weather is the worst part of it all. “It’s a good 15-hour day, but we will get cuddle time in […] in a letter to McCarthy: “My guess is that Big Tobacco offered you upwards of $1 million to pitch their popular brand of

15 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>