<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7483">facebook paying?</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:35:56" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7483-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7483_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:35:57">http://www.businessinsider.com/facebooks-mobile-first-moves-are-paying-off-with-developers-2013-12</link><title>Facebooks Mobile-First Moves Are Paying Off With Developers</title><description>* Facebooks Mobile-First Moves Are Paying Off With Developers 
Intelligence  subscribers.  Sign up for a free trial of BI Intelligence today . MOBILE DEVELOPERS LIKE FACEBOOK : Mobile […] developers thoughts on Facebook have seen a complete turnaround. In a survey released yesterday,  Appcelerator found that 66% of […] developers said they connect their mobile apps to Facebook.  Twitter was at a distant second at 53%. Whats interesting is

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7483-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7483_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:36:40">https://intelligence.businessinsider.com/welcome</link><title>MOBILE INSIGHTS: Facebooks Mobile-First Moves Are Paying Off With …</title><description>* MOBILE INSIGHTS: Facebooks Mobile-First Moves Are Paying Off With … 
DEVELOPERS LIKE FACEBOOK : Mobile developers thoughts on Facebook have seen a complete turnaround. In a survey released yesterday […] ,  Appcelerator found that 66% of developers said they connect their mobile apps to Facebook.  Twitter was at a distant second at 53 […] %. Whats interesting is that just over a year ago, two-thirds of developers told Appcelerator they thought Facebook was in

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7483-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7483_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:37:56">http://www.businessinsider.com/2014s-biggest-threat-to-facebook-2013-12</link><title>This Irate Cookbook Author Represents A Swelling Threat To Facebooks $6 …</title><description>* This Irate Cookbook Author Represents A Swelling Threat To Facebooks $6 … 
Facebook. Stiavetti knows that as an author and writer, she is a one-woman brand — and that she needs to market her brand as […] . One place online where Stiavetti has decided to be less active about promoting herself is Facebook. Thats pretty […] surprising, for two reasons:  Facebook is by far the worlds biggest social network, with almost a billion people using it

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7483-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7483_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:40:01">http://www.businessinsider.com/why-snapchat-should-apologize-2014-1</link><title>Why Snapchat Should Apologize</title><description>* Why Snapchat Should Apologize 
Nothing on the Internet is free. Yes, Facebook charges you $0 to use its apps and services. Same goes for Google […] stuff like Gmail and Maps.  But youre still paying a price. Youre still giving up a tiny bit of yourself to these […] companies in exchange for some useful or entertaining services. To use Facebook, you must agree to let it know how old you are

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7483-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7483_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:42:04">http://techcrunch.com/2013/12/27/nine-big-music-labels-plan-to-sue-vkontakte-the-facebook-of-russia-over-6000-illegal-music-tracks/</link><title>Nine Music Labels Plan To Sue Vkontakte, The Facebook Of Russia, Over …</title><description>* Nine Music Labels Plan To Sue Vkontakte, The Facebook Of Russia, Over … 
Vkontakte , a social networking site known as the “Facebook of Russia”, is facing legal action from nine music labels […] charging users directly nor by paying the licensing fee directly. But that does not mean that the social network is not […] find it hard to find paying users, when free (but illegal) content is so easy to get. But with companies like Apple

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7483-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7483_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:43:07">https://intelligence.businessinsider.com/welcome</link><title>Facebook Pages Have Been Enjoying Record Engagement Levels, But Thats …</title><description>* Facebook Pages Have Been Enjoying Record Engagement Levels, But Thats … 
.  Earlier this month, Facebook warned page managers that they will have to begin paying out of pocket to continue promoting […] Interactions on the most-followed Facebook pages reached all-time highs in recent months, but that could all change now […] that Facebook is pressuring brands to pay for exposure on the social network.  The top 1,000 Facebook pages averaged

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7483-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7483_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:43:58">http://www.buzzfeed.com/charliewarzel/online-but-off-the-grid-why-27-percent-of-online-adults-skip</link><title>Online, But Off The Grid: Why 27% Of Online Adults Skip Social…</title><description>* Online, But Off The Grid: Why 27% Of Online Adults Skip Social… 
. Neither one is on Facebook; they have never shown any real interest in signing up, and likely never will. Over the holidays […] , when the subject of Twitter and Facebook came up, they werent so much dismissive of the services as they were uninterested […] . But for those who never had occasion to join Facebook in its early years — back before photo galleries and News Feed, when

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7483-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7483_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:45:36">http://www.businessinsider.com/a-google-programmer-blew-off-a-500000-salary-at-startup--because-hes-already-making-3-million-every-year-2014-1</link><title>A Google Programmer Blew Off A $500,000 Salary At A Startup — Because …</title><description>* A Google Programmer Blew Off A $500,000 Salary At A Startup — Because … 
Google was currently paying him $3 million per year in cash and restricted stock units. (Restricted stock units, or  "RSUs […] . Before he took over Google as CEO in 2011, the company was losing a lot of people to startups like Facebook and Twitter. Now

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7483-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7483_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:46:30">https://intelligence.businessinsider.com/welcome</link><title>MOBILE INSIGHTS: For Mobile-Social Apps, Advertising Is Winning As The …</title><description>* MOBILE INSIGHTS: For Mobile-Social Apps, Advertising Is Winning As The … 
relying on revenue from ads.  MASSIVE VALUATIONS : In the past year, well-established mobile-social networks like Facebook […] is paying off. For example, over 70% of Twitters global revenue comes from mobile .  By incorporating some ad space […] -Pacific audience, while Facebook brings in over $0.80 per user in the same region from ads. Tinders move toward an ad revenue model is

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7483-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7483_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:47:03">https://intelligence.businessinsider.com/welcome</link><title>SOCIAL INSIGHTS: Media Buyers Say Facebook Video Ads Cost $2 Million …</title><description>* SOCIAL INSIGHTS: Media Buyers Say Facebook Video Ads Cost $2 Million … 
PRICEY : Media buyers sources are telling the Wall Street Journal that Facebook video ads are being priced at $2 […] surprisingly high," reports the paper. Plus, the targeting isnt completely there: " ... Facebook currently allows advertisers to […] media turned into paying customers in the third quarter. For comparison, search has hovered around a 1.79% conversation

17 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>