<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7499">gold price</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:39:53" name="Technorati" id="FW14-e170"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e170-7499-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7499_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:39:55">http://www.zerohedge.com/contributed/2014-01-10/%E2%80%9Cprice-gold-crashes%E2%80%9D-diversify-and-buy-gold-long-term</link><title>“Price Of Gold Crashes” - Diversify And Buy Gold For Long Term</title><description>* “Price Of Gold Crashes” - Diversify And Buy Gold For Long Term 
by $5 from $1,233/oz to $1,227.75/oz which is fraction below the opening price today. Then almost instantaneously, gold […] and Chinese demand. “Price Of Gold Crashes” - Diversify And Buy Gold For Long Term This negative sentiment towards gold […] has been seen in a large number of articles in recent days. Many have focused on gold’s poor price performance in 2013

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7499-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7499_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:41:25">http://www.zerohedge.com/news/2014-01-03/physical-gold-demand-soared-gold-price-tumbled-2013</link><title>Physical Gold Demand Soared As Gold Price Tumbled In 2013</title><description>* Physical Gold Demand Soared As Gold Price Tumbled In 2013 
Sales of gold coins are booming even as the precious metals price is falling (and its not just central banks). Despite […] gold for years or decades, many see the recent drop as an opportunity to buy more at a cheaper price, he added. " Theyre […] gold futures 28% drop in 2013 (its worst since 1981), the WSJ reports that demand for gold coins shot up 63% ti 241

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7499-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7499_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:42:38">http://www.zerohedge.com/news/2013-12-24/gold-rush-spreads-china-and-india-saudi-arabia</link><title>The Gold Rush Spreads From China And India To Saudi Arabia</title><description>* The Gold Rush Spreads From China And India To Saudi Arabia 
In the "west", the higher the price of gold rose, the more demand there seemingly was by momentum-chasing gamblers […] the price of gold rose, the lower the demand was for physical, which for that extinct breed of deranged gambler known as […] -driven price collapse and load up on as much gold as possible. From the Saudi Gazette : The gold shops in Jeddah are now

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7499-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7499_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:43:55">http://www.zerohedge.com/contributed/2014-01-03/gold-down-28-2013-despite-skyrocketing-demand-perth-mint-sales-surge-41</link><title>Gold Down 28% In 2013 Despite "Skyrocketing Demand" - Perth Mint Sales …</title><description>* Gold Down 28% In 2013 Despite "Skyrocketing Demand" - Perth Mint Sales … 
Televisions "Money Moves" that gold has fallen in price in 2013 despite “skyrocketing demand.” Rickards said that the price fell […] Gold and silver prices surged higher today in the opening hours of trade in 2014. Gold rose 1.8% to $1,220/oz and […] silver surged over 3% to $20.02/oz. Gold fell 28% in 2013, while silver recorded a 36% decline. It was gold’s first annual

15 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7499-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7499_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:44:55">http://www.zerohedge.com/contributed/2013-12-26/gold-and-silver-sentiments-violently-diverged-2013</link><title>Gold and Silver Sentiments Violently Diverged in 2013</title><description>* Gold and Silver Sentiments Violently Diverged in 2013 
, to speculate. They buy with the expectation of a rising price. The gold price, measured in dollars, is really just the […] inverse of the dollar price measured in gold. As the Fed abuses its credit, the quality of its liability falls. This liability […] —the dollar—has been falling in quality and price for 100 years. Measured in gold, the dollar is now just under 26mg. Or, measured

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7499-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7499_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:46:09">http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2013/12/31/gold-poised-to-suffer-biggest-annual-loss-in-more-than-30-years/</link><title>Gold Poised to Suffer Biggest Annual Loss in More Than 30 Years</title><description>* Gold Poised to Suffer Biggest Annual Loss in More Than 30 Years 
equities and out of commodities,” he said. Image source: monex.com Since the beginning of 2013, the price of gold has […] interest rates, according to CNBC. Traditionally, the price of gold, often considered to be a hedge against inflation, rises […] in the price of gold stopped correlating with announcements from the Fed. In fact, when the Fed announced last year that

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7499-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7499_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:47:03">http://www.businessinsider.com/gold-smuggling-spikes-in-india-2013-12</link><title>Gold Smuggling Spikes In India As Tax Meets Bridal Season</title><description>* Gold Smuggling Spikes In India As Tax Meets Bridal Season 
market price, hovering just under $1,200 an ounce. "The price of gold should be lower," Mehta complained. "This is a […] Hike in Indian gold tax to fight trade imbalance squeezes wedding budgets, spurs smuggling MUMBAI, India (AP) — With […] Indias wedding season in full swing, the glass sales counters in Mumbais famed Zhaveri gold bazaars are crowded with

16 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7499-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7499_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:48:41">http://blogs.reuters.com/felix-salmon/2014/01/11/10-reasons-barry-ritholtz-is-wrong-about-gold/</link><title>10 Reasons Barry Ritholtz Is Wrong About Gold</title><description>* 10 Reasons Barry Ritholtz Is Wrong About Gold 
the price of gold went up, and then it went down. His self-identification as “a gold agnostic” basically amounts to saying […] helpful. 3. He relies on tautology. Ritholtz goes into a lot of detail about the exact movements of the gold price, telling […] Barry Ritholtz has been receiving a lot of praise for his 2,500-word Bloomberg listicle “10 Reasons the Gold Bugs

14 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7499-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7499_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:50:18">http://www.zerohedge.com/contributed/2013-12-20/gold-buying-shanghai-gold-exchange-surges-again-sub-1200-gold</link><title>Gold Buying On Shanghai Gold Exchange Surges Again On Sub $1,200 Gold</title><description>* Gold Buying On Shanghai Gold Exchange Surges Again On Sub $1,200 Gold 
next level of support is $1,000/oz. Gold  rallied from its worst closing price in almost three years after the Feds […] bargain prices overnight after the 4% price fall this week and 29% fall this year. Gold volumes for the benchmark cash […] .16 and GBP 736.35 per ounce. Gold dropped $27 or 2.22% yesterday, closing at $1,191.50/oz. Silver slid $0.58 or 2

17 weeks ago</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e170-7499-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e170/7499_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 01:51:27">http://www.zerohedge.com/contributed/2014-01-08/global-currency-reset-amero-gold-silver-ratio-and-150-silver</link><title>Global Currency Reset, Amero, The Gold Silver Ratio and $150 Silver</title><description>* Global Currency Reset, Amero, The Gold Silver Ratio and $150 Silver 
on gold in terms of price. We continue to believe that silver will surpass its inflation adjusted high of $150/oz in the […] .92 and GBP 754.44 per ounce. Gold fell $6.50 or 0.52% Yesterday, closing at $1,232.30/oz. Silver slipped $0.30 or 1 […] .49% closing at $19.87/oz. Platinum dropped $3.01, or 0.2%, to $1,409.74/oz and palladium rose $3 or 0.4%, to $738.25/oz. Gold

14 weeks ago</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>