<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7014">Asian culture</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:13:03" name="KFUPM ePrints" id="FW14-e008"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e008-7014-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7014_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:13:06">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/80052/</link><title>ENERGY-EFFICIENT WINDOW DESIGN THROUGH THE INTEGRATION OF DAYLIGHTING AND ARTIFICIAL LIGHTING IN OFFICE BUILDINGS.</title><description>1.

Al-Ashwal, Nagib (2008) ENERGY-EFFICIENT WINDOW DESIGN THROUGH THE INTEGRATION OF DAYLIGHTING AND ARTIFICIAL LIGHTING IN OFFICE BUILDINGS. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7014-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7014_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:13:51">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10558/</link><title>HVAC system operation strategies for energy conservation and thermal comfort in commercial buildings in Saudi Arabia.</title><description>2.

Fasiuddin, Mohammed (2005) HVAC system operation strategies for energy conservation and thermal comfort in commercial buildings in Saudi Arabia. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7014-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7014_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:14:37">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138583/</link><title>English to Arabic Machine Translation Using a Phrase-based Approach.</title><description>3.

l English to Arabic Machine Translation Using a Phrase-based Approach. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7014-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7014_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:15:18">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138684/</link><title>MULTI-CRITERIA DECISION MAKING MODEL FOR THE SELECTION OF A/E PROFESSIONALS.</title><description>4.

l MULTI-CRITERIA DECISION MAKING MODEL FOR THE SELECTION OF A/E PROFESSIONALS. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7014-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7014_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:15:58">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138534/</link><title>Managing Risk and Resilience in Supply Chain &amp; 3PL: Conceptual Developments and Proposed Frameworks.</title><description>5.

l Managing Risk and Resilience in Supply Chain &amp; 3PL: Conceptual Developments and Proposed Frameworks. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7014-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7014_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:16:37">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138490/</link><title>THE ROLE &amp; IMPORTANCE OF COMPONENT DOCUMENTATION IN COMPONENT INTEGRATION PHASE: A SYSTEM INTEGRATOR’S PERSPECTIVE.</title><description>6.

l THE ROLE &amp; IMPORTANCE OF COMPONENT DOCUMENTATION IN COMPONENT INTEGRATION PHASE: A SYSTEM INTEGRATOR’S PERSPECTIVE. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7014-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7014_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:17:26">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138446/</link><title>Wall Compensation for High Resolution Ultra-wideband Obstructed Localization.</title><description>7.

l Wall Compensation for High Resolution Ultra-wideband Obstructed Localization. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>