<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7024">reinforcement learning</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:36:45" name="KFUPM ePrints" id="FW14-e008"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e008-7024-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7024_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:36:48">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136403/</link><title>Design of a Model University Classroom for Collaborative and Interactive LearningDesign of a Model University Classroom for Collaborative and Interactive Learning.</title><description>1.

MOHAMMED, MOHAMMED ALHAJI (2010) Design of a Model University Classroom for Collaborative and Interactive LearningDesign of a Model University Classroom for Collaborative and Interactive Learning. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7024-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7024_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:37:08">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136391/</link><title>Effect of Surface Modification of Carbon Nanotubes (CNT) on the Mechanical and Thermal Properties of Polypropylene/CNT Nanocomposites.</title><description>2.

Salihu, Adamu Girei (2010) Effect of Surface Modification of Carbon Nanotubes (CNT) on the Mechanical and Thermal Properties of Polypropylene/CNT Nanocomposites. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7024-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7024_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:37:34">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136353/</link><title>Routing prediction for probabilistic mobility model using neural networks for ad-hoc networks.</title><description>3.

Rafiq, Mohammad Rahil (2010) Routing prediction for probabilistic mobility model using neural networks for ad-hoc networks. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7024-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7024_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:38:00">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136222/</link><title>MULTI-OBJECTIVE OPTIMAL POWER FLOW IN DEREGULATED ENVIRONMENT.</title><description>4.

Zaro, Fouad (2010) MULTI-OBJECTIVE OPTIMAL POWER FLOW IN DEREGULATED ENVIRONMENT. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7024-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7024_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:38:30">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136212/</link><title>A Methodology for Identifying Learning Activity Settings and User Needs In Educational Facilities.</title><description>5.

Balfaqih, Hassan A. (2009) A Methodology for Identifying Learning Activity Settings and User Needs In Educational Facilities. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7024-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7024_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:38:51">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136198/</link><title>Estimation of Reservoir Properties from Seismic Attributes and Well Log Data using Artificial Intelligence.</title><description>6.

Sitouah, Mohamed (2009) Estimation of Reservoir Properties from Seismic Attributes and Well Log Data using Artificial Intelligence. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7024-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7024_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:39:14">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10674/</link><title>A learning approach for prioritized handoff channel allocation in mobile multimedia networks.</title><description>7.

El-Alfy, E.-S.M. and Yao, Y.-D. and Heffes, H. (2006) A learning approach for prioritized handoff channel allocation in mobile multimedia networks. IEEE Transactions on Wireless Communications, 5 (7). pp. 1651-1660. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7024-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7024_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:39:45">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10488/</link><title>Effect of environment on the fatigue and the tensile properties of glass fiber reinforced vinyl ester and epoxy thermosets.</title><description>8.

Shafeeq, Mohammed (2006) Effect of environment on the fatigue and the tensile properties of glass fiber reinforced vinyl ester and epoxy thermosets. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7024-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7024_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:40:20">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10509/</link><title>Collaborative autonomous interface agent for personalized web search.</title><description>9.

Al-Nazer, Ahmed Ali (2006) Collaborative autonomous interface agent for personalized web search. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7024-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7024_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:40:50">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/14851/</link><title>Infusing Critical Thinking Skill Compare and Contrast into Content of Data Structures Course.</title><description>10.

Faisal, Kanaan A (2006) Infusing Critical Thinking Skill Compare and Contrast into Content of Data Structures Course. In: Proc. of International Conference on Frontiers in Education: Computer Science and Computer Engineering (2006), FECS'06,, June 26-29, 2006, Las Vegas, Nevada, USA.

Preview</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>