<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7033">Porto</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:58:26" name="KFUPM ePrints" id="FW14-e008"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e008-7033-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7033_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:58:27">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136337/</link><title>Design Considerations for Wireless Sensor Network for Industrial Automation.</title><description>1.

Al-Moallem, Yousuf (2010) Design Considerations for Wireless Sensor Network for Industrial Automation. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7033-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7033_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:59:09">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136222/</link><title>MULTI-OBJECTIVE OPTIMAL POWER FLOW IN DEREGULATED ENVIRONMENT.</title><description>2.

Zaro, Fouad (2010) MULTI-OBJECTIVE OPTIMAL POWER FLOW IN DEREGULATED ENVIRONMENT. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7033-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7033_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-11 23:59:58">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136096/</link><title>Impacts of Distributed Generation on the Stability of Electrical Power Systems.</title><description>3.

ALBENSAAD, ABDULLAH M. (2009) Impacts of Distributed Generation on the Stability of Electrical Power Systems. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7033-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7033_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 00:00:39">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10509/</link><title>Collaborative autonomous interface agent for personalized web search.</title><description>4.

Al-Nazer, Ahmed Ali (2006) Collaborative autonomous interface agent for personalized web search. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7033-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7033_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 00:01:04">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138616/</link><title>CULTURING, ISOLATION AND GENETIC IDENTIFICATION OF ENDOLITHIC CYANOBACTERIA FOUND IN THE ARABIAN GULF.</title><description>5.

l CULTURING, ISOLATION AND GENETIC IDENTIFICATION OF ENDOLITHIC CYANOBACTERIA FOUND IN THE ARABIAN GULF. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7033-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7033_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 00:01:41">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138552/</link><title>Strategic Bidding for Load Serving Entity in Electricity Markets.</title><description>6.

l Strategic Bidding for Load Serving Entity in Electricity Markets. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7033-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7033_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 00:02:21">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138783/</link><title>TOWARDS AN INTEGRATED METAMODEL BASED APPROACH TO SOFTWARE REFACTORING.</title><description>7.

l TOWARDS AN INTEGRATED METAMODEL BASED APPROACH TO SOFTWARE REFACTORING. PhD thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>