<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7064">Korea weather</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-12 00:39:58" name="KFUPM ePrints" id="FW14-e008"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e008-7064-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7064_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 00:40:00">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136392/</link><title>Photovoltaic System Modeling and Analysis.</title><description>1.

Mir, Shahed Ali (2011) Photovoltaic System Modeling and Analysis. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7064-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7064_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 00:40:35">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136318/</link><title>Strategic Bidding For Load Serving Entity in Electricity Markets.</title><description>2.

Alzahrani, Hashim (2010) Strategic Bidding For Load Serving Entity in Electricity Markets. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7064-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7064_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 00:41:07">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136417/</link><title>The Impact of HVAC System Operation and Selection on Energy Efficiency in Office Buildings in Hot Climates.</title><description>3.

Mohammed, Abdul Najid (2010) The Impact of HVAC System Operation and Selection on Energy Efficiency in Office Buildings in Hot Climates. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7064-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7064_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 00:41:43">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/80052/</link><title>ENERGY-EFFICIENT WINDOW DESIGN THROUGH THE INTEGRATION OF DAYLIGHTING AND ARTIFICIAL LIGHTING IN OFFICE BUILDINGS.</title><description>4.

Al-Ashwal, Nagib (2008) ENERGY-EFFICIENT WINDOW DESIGN THROUGH THE INTEGRATION OF DAYLIGHTING AND ARTIFICIAL LIGHTING IN OFFICE BUILDINGS. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7064-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7064_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 00:42:21">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138730/</link><title>Development of Energy-efficient Algorithms for Wireless Sensor Networks.</title><description>5.

l Development of Energy-efficient Algorithms for Wireless Sensor Networks. PhD thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7064-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7064_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 00:42:57">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138443/</link><title>AN INTERVAL KALMAN FILTER, INTERVAL EM ALGORITHM WITH APPLICATION TO WEATHER PREDICTION.</title><description>6.

l AN INTERVAL KALMAN FILTER, INTERVAL EM ALGORITHM WITH APPLICATION TO WEATHER PREDICTION. PhD thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7064-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7064_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 00:43:29">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138785/</link><title>Load and Energy Analysis of a Commercial Building.</title><description>7.

l Load and Energy Analysis of a Commercial Building. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7064-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7064_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 00:43:54">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138534/</link><title>Managing Risk and Resilience in Supply Chain &amp; 3PL: Conceptual Developments and Proposed Frameworks.</title><description>8.

l Managing Risk and Resilience in Supply Chain &amp; 3PL: Conceptual Developments and Proposed Frameworks. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7064-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7064_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 00:44:27">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138560/</link><title>Modeling AND Optimization OF A Hybrid Solar Combined Cycle (HYCS).</title><description>9.

l Modeling AND Optimization OF A Hybrid Solar Combined Cycle (HYCS). Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7064-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7064_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 00:44:59">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138582/</link><title>PRODUCTION OF MEDIUM TO LOW STRENGTH CONCRETE UTILIZING INDIGENOUS WASTE PRODUCTS.</title><description>10.

l PRODUCTION OF MEDIUM TO LOW STRENGTH CONCRETE UTILIZING INDIGENOUS WASTE PRODUCTS. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>