<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7094">calculate inertia sphere</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:18:02" name="KFUPM ePrints" id="FW14-e008"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e008-7094-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7094_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:18:04">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136060/</link><title>Towards Optimal Design of Reinforced Concrete Structures for Corrosive Environments in Saudi Arabia.</title><description>1.

Yusuf, Moruf Olalekan (2009) Towards Optimal Design of Reinforced Concrete Structures for Corrosive Environments in Saudi Arabia. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7094-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7094_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:18:24">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10524/</link><title>Numerical investigation of erosion of a pipe protruded in a sudden contraction.</title><description>2.

Kabir, Muhammad Ehsanul (2005) Numerical investigation of erosion of a pipe protruded in a sudden contraction. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7094-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7094_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:18:47">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/9578/</link><title>Modelling of blood flow in a time-varying shape passage.</title><description>3.

Abdul Qaiyum, Shaik (2005) Modelling of blood flow in a time-varying shape passage. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7094-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7094_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:19:22">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138436/</link><title>MODELING OF THERMAL PERFORMANCE OF LIQUID FLOW WITH NANOSIZED PARTICLES OF PHASE CHANGE MATERIAL IN MICROCHANNELS.</title><description>4.

l MODELING OF THERMAL PERFORMANCE OF LIQUID FLOW WITH NANOSIZED PARTICLES OF PHASE CHANGE MATERIAL IN MICROCHANNELS. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7094-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7094_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:19:45">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138708/</link><title>Noise Reduction in Centrifugal Compressors using Helmholtz Resonators.</title><description>5.

l Noise Reduction in Centrifugal Compressors using Helmholtz Resonators. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>