<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7106">active learning survey</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:31:27" name="KFUPM ePrints" id="FW14-e008"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e008-7106-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7106_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:31:31">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136390/</link><title>DEPLOYING TRIPLE-PLAY SERVICES OVER EXISTING IP NETWORKS.</title><description>1.

Hamodi, Mr. Jamil (2013) DEPLOYING TRIPLE-PLAY SERVICES OVER EXISTING IP NETWORKS. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7106-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7106_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:31:54">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136432/</link><title>Anomaly Detection Technique for Honeynet Data Analysis.</title><description>2.

SYED, NAEEM FIRDOUS (2011) Anomaly Detection Technique for Honeynet Data Analysis. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7106-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7106_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:32:25">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136403/</link><title>Design of a Model University Classroom for Collaborative and Interactive LearningDesign of a Model University Classroom for Collaborative and Interactive Learning.</title><description>3.

MOHAMMED, MOHAMMED ALHAJI (2010) Design of a Model University Classroom for Collaborative and Interactive LearningDesign of a Model University Classroom for Collaborative and Interactive Learning. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7106-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7106_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:32:54">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136376/</link><title>Color Face Recognition Using Quaternion Principal Component Analysis (Q-PCA).</title><description>4.

Jaha, Emad (2010) Color Face Recognition Using Quaternion Principal Component Analysis (Q-PCA). Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7106-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7106_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:33:20">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136337/</link><title>Design Considerations for Wireless Sensor Network for Industrial Automation.</title><description>5.

Al-Moallem, Yousuf (2010) Design Considerations for Wireless Sensor Network for Industrial Automation. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7106-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7106_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:33:46">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136329/</link><title>Neural Network Based Detection of Partial Discharge in HV Motors.</title><description>6.

Asiri, Yahya A (2010) Neural Network Based Detection of Partial Discharge in HV Motors. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7106-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7106_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:34:13">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136318/</link><title>Strategic Bidding For Load Serving Entity in Electricity Markets.</title><description>7.

Alzahrani, Hashim (2010) Strategic Bidding For Load Serving Entity in Electricity Markets. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7106-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7106_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:35:03">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136300/</link><title>A Framework for Integration Specifications for Component-Based Software.</title><description>8.

Al-Qadhi, Mohammed Abdullah Ali (2010) A Framework for Integration Specifications for Component-Based Software. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7106-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7106_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:35:33">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136288/</link><title>SUBCONTRACTING STRATEGY IN INDUSTRIAL PROJECTS.</title><description>9.

GANIYU, ABIDEEN ADEKUNLE (2010) SUBCONTRACTING STRATEGY IN INDUSTRIAL PROJECTS. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7106-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7106_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:36:03">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136353/</link><title>Routing prediction for probabilistic mobility model using neural networks for ad-hoc networks.</title><description>10.

Rafiq, Mohammad Rahil (2010) Routing prediction for probabilistic mobility model using neural networks for ad-hoc networks. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>