<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7118">part time jobs texas city</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:51:24" name="KFUPM ePrints" id="FW14-e008"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e008-7118-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7118_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:51:27">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136409/</link><title>Custom Design and Implementation of a Wireless Sensor Node, Energy-Efficient MAC and Routing Protocols.</title><description>1.

Sultan, Farooq (2010) Custom Design and Implementation of a Wireless Sensor Node, Energy-Efficient MAC and Routing Protocols. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7118-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7118_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:51:45">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136212/</link><title>A Methodology for Identifying Learning Activity Settings and User Needs In Educational Facilities.</title><description>2.

Balfaqih, Hassan A. (2009) A Methodology for Identifying Learning Activity Settings and User Needs In Educational Facilities. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7118-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7118_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:52:08">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10498/</link><title>Envelope design for thermal comfort and reduced energy consumption in residential buildings.</title><description>3.

Al-Saadi, Saleh Nasser (2006) Envelope design for thermal comfort and reduced energy consumption in residential buildings. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7118-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7118_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:52:42">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10531/</link><title>Evaluation of performance measures for materials management process in industrial construction projects.</title><description>4.

Kashif ul Asad, Mohammed (2005) Evaluation of performance measures for materials management process in industrial construction projects. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7118-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7118_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:53:12">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138773/</link><title>THE EFFECTS OF WELL AND RESERVOIR PARAMETERS ON THE PERFORMANCE OF HORIZONTAL AND VERTICAL WELLS IN VOLUMETRIC DRY GAS RESERVOIRS.</title><description>5.

l THE EFFECTS OF WELL AND RESERVOIR PARAMETERS ON THE PERFORMANCE OF HORIZONTAL AND VERTICAL WELLS IN VOLUMETRIC DRY GAS RESERVOIRS. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7118-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7118_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:53:43">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138486/</link><title>EVOLUTIONARY OPTIMIZED HYBRID COMPUTATIONAL INTELLIGENCE MODEL FOR THE PREDICTION OF GAS COMPONENT.</title><description>6.

l EVOLUTIONARY OPTIMIZED HYBRID COMPUTATIONAL INTELLIGENCE MODEL FOR THE PREDICTION OF GAS COMPONENT. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7118-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7118_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:54:16">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138452/</link><title>Evaluation of Drilling Designs for Smart MRC Wells Applied in Saudi Aramco.</title><description>7.

l Evaluation of Drilling Designs for Smart MRC Wells Applied in Saudi Aramco. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7118-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7118_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 01:54:39">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138438/</link><title>MODELING AND ANALYSIS OF HYBRID PV/WIND OFF GRID POWER GENERATION SYSTEM IN THE KINGDOM OF SAUDI ARABIA.</title><description>8.

l MODELING AND ANALYSIS OF HYBRID PV/WIND OFF GRID POWER GENERATION SYSTEM IN THE KINGDOM OF SAUDI ARABIA. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>