<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7147">breast cancer review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-12 02:25:16" name="KFUPM ePrints" id="FW14-e008"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e008-7147-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7147_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 02:25:18">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136343/</link><title>Total Synthesis of Bioactive Natural Products.</title><description>1.

Haladu, Shamsuddeen Abdullahi (2010) Total Synthesis of Bioactive Natural Products. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7147-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7147_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 02:25:44">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136107/</link><title>REMOVAL OF LEAD &amp; CHROMIUM FROM WATER BY USING MODIFIED &amp; NONMODIFIED CARBON NANOTUBES.</title><description>2.

BAKATHER, OMER YAHYA (2009) REMOVAL OF LEAD &amp; CHROMIUM FROM WATER BY USING MODIFIED &amp; NONMODIFIED CARBON NANOTUBES. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7147-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7147_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 02:26:13">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136030/</link><title>A Novel Hybrid Computational Intelligence Model for the Characterization of Oil and Gas Reservoirs.</title><description>3.

Anifowose, Fatai Adesina (2009) A Novel Hybrid Computational Intelligence Model for the Characterization of Oil and Gas Reservoirs. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7147-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7147_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 02:26:36">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136042/</link><title>ADAPTIVE FUZZY LOGIC BASED FRAMEWORK FOR HANDLING IMPRECISION AND UNCERTAINTY IN PATTERN CLASSIFICATION OF BIOINFORMATICS DATASETS.</title><description>4.

Rasheed, Zeehasham (2009) ADAPTIVE FUZZY LOGIC BASED FRAMEWORK FOR HANDLING IMPRECISION AND UNCERTAINTY IN PATTERN CLASSIFICATION OF BIOINFORMATICS DATASETS. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7147-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7147_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 02:26:58">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136051/</link><title>Artificial Intelligence Techniques in Reservoir Characterization.</title><description>5.

Adeniran, A. A. (2009) Artificial Intelligence Techniques in Reservoir Characterization. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7147-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7147_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 02:27:19">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138558/</link><title>ANALYTICAL METHODS DEVELOPMENT FOR THE ANALYSES OF ORGANO-METALLIC AND ORGANIC MICRO-CONTAMINANTS IN ENVIRONMENTAL MATRICES.</title><description>6.

l ANALYTICAL METHODS DEVELOPMENT FOR THE ANALYSES OF ORGANO-METALLIC AND ORGANIC MICRO-CONTAMINANTS IN ENVIRONMENTAL MATRICES. PhD thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7147-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7147_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 02:27:38">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138433/</link><title>Prediction of Mobility Profile with Minimum Real Time Measurements using Artificial Intelligence.</title><description>7.

l Prediction of Mobility Profile with Minimum Real Time Measurements using Artificial Intelligence. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>