<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7150">senior java developer</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-12 02:32:53" name="KFUPM ePrints" id="FW14-e008"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e008-7150-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7150_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 02:32:54">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136431/</link><title>Design and Evaluation of a Reliable P2P Communication Protocol for IEEE 802.11b Networks.</title><description>1.

KHAN, IRFAN ALI (2011) Design and Evaluation of a Reliable P2P Communication Protocol for IEEE 802.11b Networks. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7150-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7150_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 02:33:15">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136292/</link><title>CLASSIFICATION OF REFACTORING METHODS FOR ASPECT ORIENTED PROGRAMMING BASED ON SOFTWARE QUALITY ATTRIBUTES.</title><description>2.

Al-Jamimi, Hamdi Ali (2010) CLASSIFICATION OF REFACTORING METHODS FOR ASPECT ORIENTED PROGRAMMING BASED ON SOFTWARE QUALITY ATTRIBUTES. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7150-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7150_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 02:33:40">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136223/</link><title>Handoff Performance for Voice over IP in WiMAX Networks.</title><description>3.

Mendahawi, Nayef (2010) Handoff Performance for Voice over IP in WiMAX Networks. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7150-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7150_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 02:34:16">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136045/</link><title>Classification of Refactoring Methods Based on Software Quality Attributes.</title><description>4.

Elish, Karim (2008) Classification of Refactoring Methods Based on Software Quality Attributes. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7150-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7150_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 02:34:50">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10542/</link><title>Package cohesion metric for object oriented systems.</title><description>5.

Hussain, Syed Manzoor (2005) Package cohesion metric for object oriented systems. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7150-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7150_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 02:35:25">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138783/</link><title>TOWARDS AN INTEGRATED METAMODEL BASED APPROACH TO SOFTWARE REFACTORING.</title><description>6.

l TOWARDS AN INTEGRATED METAMODEL BASED APPROACH TO SOFTWARE REFACTORING. PhD thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>