<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7167">aluminium extrusion</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-12 03:07:44" name="KFUPM ePrints" id="FW14-e008"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e008-7167-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7167_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 03:07:47">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136036/</link><title>FRICTION AND WEAR OF 20% VOLUME FRACTION SUBMICRON Al2O3/6061 ALUMINUM ALLOY COMPOSITE FOR BRAKE SYSTEM APPLICATION.</title><description>1.

Mirza, Murtuza Ali Baig (2009) FRICTION AND WEAR OF 20% VOLUME FRACTION SUBMICRON Al2O3/6061 ALUMINUM ALLOY COMPOSITE FOR BRAKE SYSTEM APPLICATION. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7167-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7167_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 03:08:08">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10548/</link><title>A study of the static and dynamic properties of Al-Based A1₂O₃ metal matrix composites.</title><description>2.

Hafeez, Syed (2005) A study of the static and dynamic properties of Al-Based A1₂O₃ metal matrix composites. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7167-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7167_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 03:08:47">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10536/</link><title>Structure-property relationships of metallocene linear low density polyethylene (LLDPE).</title><description>3.

Islam, Md. Ashraful (2005) Structure-property relationships of metallocene linear low density polyethylene (LLDPE). Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7167-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7167_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 03:09:13">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10525/</link><title>Effect of bolt layout on the mechanical behavior of bolted joint.</title><description>4.

Khurshid, Hassan (2004) Effect of bolt layout on the mechanical behavior of bolted joint. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7167-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7167_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 03:09:46">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/9870/</link><title>A Study of tensile and microhardness properties of m-LLDPE/LDPE blends.</title><description>5.

Faheem, Mohammad (2003) A Study of tensile and microhardness properties of m-LLDPE/LDPE blends. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7167-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7167_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 03:10:13">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10288/</link><title>Some quality and reliability aspcts of aluminium extrusion process.</title><description>6.

Raza, Muhammad Kamran (1998) Some quality and reliability aspcts of aluminium extrusion process. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7167-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7167_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 03:10:35">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138630/</link><title>Development and Characterization of Carbon Nanotubes (CNTs) And Silicon Carbide (SiC) Reinforced Al-based Nanocomposites.</title><description>7.

l Development and Characterization of Carbon Nanotubes (CNTs) And Silicon Carbide (SiC) Reinforced Al-based Nanocomposites. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7167-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7167_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 03:11:06">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138704/</link><title>NUMERICAL AND EXPERIMENTAL INVESTIGATIONS OF FRICTION STIR WELDING OF TUBE-TUBESHEET JOINTS.</title><description>8.

l NUMERICAL AND EXPERIMENTAL INVESTIGATIONS OF FRICTION STIR WELDING OF TUBE-TUBESHEET JOINTS. PhD thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7167-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7167_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 03:11:42">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138642/</link><title>SYNTHESIS AND WEAR BEHAVIOR OF ALUMINUM 6061 ALLOY REINFORCED WITH CARBON NANOTUBES.</title><description>9.

l SYNTHESIS AND WEAR BEHAVIOR OF ALUMINUM 6061 ALLOY REINFORCED WITH CARBON NANOTUBES. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>