<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7168">fabric glue</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-12 03:12:10" name="KFUPM ePrints" id="FW14-e008"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e008-7168-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7168_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 03:12:12">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136083/</link><title>EXPERIMENTAL INVESTIGATION AND MODELING OF PRESTRESSED PRECAST HOLLOW-CORE SLABS WITH A STRUT-AND-TIE MODEL.</title><description>1.

ABDO, MUNEER KAID SAID (2009) EXPERIMENTAL INVESTIGATION AND MODELING OF PRESTRESSED PRECAST HOLLOW-CORE SLABS WITH A STRUT-AND-TIE MODEL. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7168-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7168_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 03:12:57">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/9567/</link><title>Contaminant behavior and distribution in mechanically ventilated multi-zone building.</title><description>2.

Adamu, Zulfikar Aliyu (2006) Contaminant behavior and distribution in mechanically ventilated multi-zone building. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7168-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7168_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 03:13:25">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10490/</link><title>Strength and durability characteristics of aluminum joints bonded by rubber-modified and aluminum filled epoxy adhesive.</title><description>3.

Al-Shammari, Salam Khalifah (2006) Strength and durability characteristics of aluminum joints bonded by rubber-modified and aluminum filled epoxy adhesive. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7168-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7168_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 03:14:01">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10510/</link><title>The effect of environmental conditions on the hydrostatic burst pressure and impact performance of glass fiber reinforced thermoset pipes.</title><description>4.

Naik, Mohammed Khaliq (2005) The effect of environmental conditions on the hydrostatic burst pressure and impact performance of glass fiber reinforced thermoset pipes. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7168-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7168_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 03:14:26">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138632/</link><title>APPLICATION OF POLYELECTROLYTE MULTILAYER REVERSE OSMOSIS MEMBRANE IN SEAWATER DESALINATION.</title><description>5.

l APPLICATION OF POLYELECTROLYTE MULTILAYER REVERSE OSMOSIS MEMBRANE IN SEAWATER DESALINATION. PhD thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7168-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7168_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 03:14:58">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138652/</link><title>ENHANCING THE BIOFOULING RESISTANCE OF REVERSE OSMOSIS MEMBRANES BY A NOVEL SURFACE MODIFICATION TECHNIQUE.</title><description>6.

l ENHANCING THE BIOFOULING RESISTANCE OF REVERSE OSMOSIS MEMBRANES BY A NOVEL SURFACE MODIFICATION TECHNIQUE. PhD thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7168-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7168_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 03:15:28">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138445/</link><title>Internet Denial by Higher-tier ISPs: A NAT-Based Solution.</title><description>7.

l Internet Denial by Higher-tier ISPs: A NAT-Based Solution. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7168-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7168_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 03:16:01">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/1338/</link><title>Manufacturing.</title><description>8.

Siddiqui, Atiq and Khan, Mehmood Manufacturing. In: Technology for Business Students. none. (Unpublished)

Preview</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>