<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7207">earthquake</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-12 04:30:21" name="KFUPM ePrints" id="FW14-e008"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e008-7207-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7207_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 04:30:24">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136099/</link><title>INTRUSION DETECTION IN MOBILE AD-HOC NETWORK IMPLEMENTATION AND PERFORMANCE EVALUATION OF ADAPTIVE ACKNOWLEDGMENT APPROACH.</title><description>1.

Al-Roubaie, Anas A. (2011) INTRUSION DETECTION IN MOBILE AD-HOC NETWORK IMPLEMENTATION AND PERFORMANCE EVALUATION OF ADAPTIVE ACKNOWLEDGMENT APPROACH. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7207-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7207_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 04:30:53">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136298/</link><title>LIFE CYCLE COSTING FOR SELECTED STRUCTURAL MATERIALS FOR OFFSHORE PLATFORMS.</title><description>2.

Al-Kaldi, Ezeldine F.H (2010) LIFE CYCLE COSTING FOR SELECTED STRUCTURAL MATERIALS FOR OFFSHORE PLATFORMS. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7207-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7207_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 04:31:25">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136295/</link><title>WATER WAVE PROPAGATION ON NONUNIFORM BOTTOM.</title><description>3.

AL-SUWAIYEL, MOHAMMED A. (2010) WATER WAVE PROPAGATION ON NONUNIFORM BOTTOM. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7207-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7207_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 04:31:58">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136208/</link><title>Factors Affecting the Implementation of the Saudi Building Code.</title><description>4.

Al-Mudhei, Ali A (2009) Factors Affecting the Implementation of the Saudi Building Code. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7207-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7207_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 04:32:25">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136083/</link><title>EXPERIMENTAL INVESTIGATION AND MODELING OF PRESTRESSED PRECAST HOLLOW-CORE SLABS WITH A STRUT-AND-TIE MODEL.</title><description>5.

ABDO, MUNEER KAID SAID (2009) EXPERIMENTAL INVESTIGATION AND MODELING OF PRESTRESSED PRECAST HOLLOW-CORE SLABS WITH A STRUT-AND-TIE MODEL. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7207-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7207_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 04:33:07">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10516/</link><title>On some seismic inverse problems.</title><description>6.

Al-Muhiameed, Zeid (2005) On some seismic inverse problems. PhD thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7207-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7207_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 04:33:42">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10404/</link><title>Risk and hydraulic reliability analysis of water distribution systems.</title><description>7.

Syed, Juned Laiq (2003) Risk and hydraulic reliability analysis of water distribution systems. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7207-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7207_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 04:34:14">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/2118/</link><title>Risk and hydraulic reliability analysis of water distribution systems.</title><description>8.

Syed, Juned Laiq (2003) Risk and hydraulic reliability analysis of water distribution systems. Masters thesis, KFUPM.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7207-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7207_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 04:34:44">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138545/</link><title>ASSESSMENT OF SITE SELECTION CRITERIA FOR OFFICE BUILDINGS IN SAUDI ARABIA.</title><description>9.

l ASSESSMENT OF SITE SELECTION CRITERIA FOR OFFICE BUILDINGS IN SAUDI ARABIA. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7207-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7207_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 04:35:16">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138706/</link><title>Characterization of Fractured Basement Reservoir, Melut basin, Southeast Sudan.</title><description>10.

l Characterization of Fractured Basement Reservoir, Melut basin, Southeast Sudan. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>