<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7222">route 666</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-12 04:59:20" name="KFUPM ePrints" id="FW14-e008"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e008-7222-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7222_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 04:59:22">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136367/</link><title>Rheology &amp; Solid State Properties of Polyethylene/CNT Nanocomposites: Impact of CNT Characteristics and Surface Modification.</title><description>1.

Abbasi, Sarfraz / Initials (2010) Rheology &amp; Solid State Properties of Polyethylene/CNT Nanocomposites: Impact of CNT Characteristics and Surface Modification. PhD thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7222-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7222_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 04:59:51">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136302/</link><title>Effect of Electrodes Material on the Degradation of p-Cresol in Electrochemical Process.</title><description>2.

Abu-Eideh, M.M. (2010) Effect of Electrodes Material on the Degradation of p-Cresol in Electrochemical Process. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7222-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7222_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 05:00:19">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136136/</link><title>SEQUENTIAL INJECTION ANALYSIS (SIA) TECHNIQUE FOR THE ASSAY OF KETOCONAZOLE AND DICLOFENAC SODIUM IN DRUG FORMULATIONS WITH CHEMOMETRIC APPROACH.</title><description>3.

Dafalla, Hatim (2009) SEQUENTIAL INJECTION ANALYSIS (SIA) TECHNIQUE FOR THE ASSAY OF KETOCONAZOLE AND DICLOFENAC SODIUM IN DRUG FORMULATIONS WITH CHEMOMETRIC APPROACH. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7222-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7222_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 05:00:56">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136107/</link><title>REMOVAL OF LEAD &amp; CHROMIUM FROM WATER BY USING MODIFIED &amp; NONMODIFIED CARBON NANOTUBES.</title><description>4.

BAKATHER, OMER YAHYA (2009) REMOVAL OF LEAD &amp; CHROMIUM FROM WATER BY USING MODIFIED &amp; NONMODIFIED CARBON NANOTUBES. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7222-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7222_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 05:01:26">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10481/</link><title>Catalytic carbonylation of terminal alkyne with amine: computational and experimental investigations of regioselectivity.</title><description>5.

Al-Thagfi, Jameel (2004) Catalytic carbonylation of terminal alkyne with amine: computational and experimental investigations of regioselectivity. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7222-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7222_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 05:01:54">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/98/</link><title>AREA-TIME OPTIMAL ADDER WITH RELATIVE PLACEMENT GENERATOR.</title><description>6.

Farooqui, Aamir A. and Oklobdzija, Vojin G. and Sait, Sadiq M. (2003) AREA-TIME OPTIMAL ADDER WITH RELATIVE PLACEMENT GENERATOR. In: IEEE International Symposium on Circuits and Systems'', Bangkok, Thailand.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7222-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7222_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 05:02:47">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/659/</link><title>AE 427 PROJECT REPORT.</title><description>7.

SALMAN AL-FIFI, SALMAN AL-FIFI AE 427 PROJECT REPORT. Project Report. SALMAN AL-FIFI. (Unpublished)

Preview</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>