<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7439">make crown</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-12 10:41:23" name="KFUPM ePrints" id="FW14-e008"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e008-7439-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7439_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 10:41:25">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136031/</link><title>COLOR IRIS RECOGNITION AND MATCHING USING QUATERNION GABOR WAVELETS.</title><description>1.

Al-Qunaieer, Fares S (2009) COLOR IRIS RECOGNITION AND MATCHING USING QUATERNION GABOR WAVELETS. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7439-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7439_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 10:41:52">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/76170/</link><title>A Brief Illustrated Guide to Understanding Islam - Miracles of the Holy Quran.</title><description>2.

Islam, Islam (2008) A Brief Illustrated Guide to Understanding Islam - Miracles of the Holy Quran. Al-Muntada Al-Islami Centre - London - Tel.: 44 (0207) 736 9060.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7439-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7439_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 10:42:15">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10483/</link><title>Extraction of aromatics using green solvents based on ionic liquids.</title><description>3.

Sumon, Kazi Zamshad (2005) Extraction of aromatics using green solvents based on ionic liquids. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7439-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7439_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 10:42:40">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138613/</link><title>Authentication for Stateless Address Allocation in IPv6 Networks.</title><description>4.

l Authentication for Stateless Address Allocation in IPv6 Networks. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7439-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7439_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 10:43:02">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138751/</link><title>Estimation of Greenhouse Gases from Combustion Facilities in Jubail Industrial City (JIC) and Yanbu Industrial City (YIC).</title><description>5.

l Estimation of Greenhouse Gases from Combustion Facilities in Jubail Industrial City (JIC) and Yanbu Industrial City (YIC). Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7439-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7439_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 10:43:23">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138770/</link><title>Field Deployable Electrochemical Sensors for Simultaneous Determination of Cd, Pb and Zn Heavy Metals in Drinking Water.</title><description>6.

l Field Deployable Electrochemical Sensors for Simultaneous Determination of Cd, Pb and Zn Heavy Metals in Drinking Water. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7439-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7439_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 10:43:41">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138637/</link><title>IMPROVING QUALITY AND PRODUCTIVITY OF CASTING PROCESS BY USING ADVANCED SIMULATION AND RAPID PROTOTYPING TECHNOLOGY.</title><description>7.

l IMPROVING QUALITY AND PRODUCTIVITY OF CASTING PROCESS BY USING ADVANCED SIMULATION AND RAPID PROTOTYPING TECHNOLOGY. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>