<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7447">running shoes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-12 10:50:59" name="KFUPM ePrints" id="FW14-e008"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e008-7447-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7447_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 10:51:01">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136411/</link><title>Realtime Rate Allocation for multilaterals wells equipped with downhole valves and a PDHMS.</title><description>1.

ALMUBARAK, SAEED (2011) Realtime Rate Allocation for multilaterals wells equipped with downhole valves and a PDHMS. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7447-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7447_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 10:51:25">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136360/</link><title>FINITE ELEMENT MODELING OF RING SPLITTING TEST TO PREDICT RESIDUAL STRESSES IN SPIRAL WELDED PIPE.</title><description>2.

Al-Omari, Ahmed S. (2010) FINITE ELEMENT MODELING OF RING SPLITTING TEST TO PREDICT RESIDUAL STRESSES IN SPIRAL WELDED PIPE. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7447-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7447_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 10:51:47">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136212/</link><title>A Methodology for Identifying Learning Activity Settings and User Needs In Educational Facilities.</title><description>3.

Balfaqih, Hassan A. (2009) A Methodology for Identifying Learning Activity Settings and User Needs In Educational Facilities. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7447-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7447_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 10:52:13">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136036/</link><title>FRICTION AND WEAR OF 20% VOLUME FRACTION SUBMICRON Al2O3/6061 ALUMINUM ALLOY COMPOSITE FOR BRAKE SYSTEM APPLICATION.</title><description>4.

Mirza, Murtuza Ali Baig (2009) FRICTION AND WEAR OF 20% VOLUME FRACTION SUBMICRON Al2O3/6061 ALUMINUM ALLOY COMPOSITE FOR BRAKE SYSTEM APPLICATION. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7447-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7447_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 10:52:37">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/9770/</link><title>Ant colony multi-optimization algorithm for circuit bi-partitioning.</title><description>5.

Ba-Abbad, Emran A. (2005) Ant colony multi-optimization algorithm for circuit bi-partitioning. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7447-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7447_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 10:53:04">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10578/</link><title>Ant colony multi-optimization algorithm for circuit bi-partitioning.</title><description>6.

Ba-Abbad, Emran A. (2005) Ant colony multi-optimization algorithm for circuit bi-partitioning. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7447-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7447_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 10:53:30">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138542/</link><title>DESIGN &amp;FABRICATION OF TWO SEATED AIRCRAFT WITH AN ADVANCED ROTATING LEADING EDGE WING.</title><description>7.

l DESIGN &amp;FABRICATION OF TWO SEATED AIRCRAFT WITH AN ADVANCED ROTATING LEADING EDGE WING. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7447-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7447_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 10:53:54">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138452/</link><title>Evaluation of Drilling Designs for Smart MRC Wells Applied in Saudi Aramco.</title><description>8.

l Evaluation of Drilling Designs for Smart MRC Wells Applied in Saudi Aramco. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7447-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7447_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 10:54:18">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/659/</link><title>AE 427 PROJECT REPORT.</title><description>9.

SALMAN AL-FIFI, SALMAN AL-FIFI AE 427 PROJECT REPORT. Project Report. SALMAN AL-FIFI. (Unpublished)

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7447-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7447_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 10:54:39">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/1338/</link><title>Manufacturing.</title><description>10.

Siddiqui, Atiq and Khan, Mehmood Manufacturing. In: Technology for Business Students. none. (Unpublished)

Preview</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>