<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7478">protect kids online</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:28:08" name="KFUPM ePrints" id="FW14-e008"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e008-7478-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7478_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:28:09">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136403/</link><title>Design of a Model University Classroom for Collaborative and Interactive LearningDesign of a Model University Classroom for Collaborative and Interactive Learning.</title><description>1.

MOHAMMED, MOHAMMED ALHAJI (2010) Design of a Model University Classroom for Collaborative and Interactive LearningDesign of a Model University Classroom for Collaborative and Interactive Learning. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7478-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7478_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:28:33">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136212/</link><title>A Methodology for Identifying Learning Activity Settings and User Needs In Educational Facilities.</title><description>2.

Balfaqih, Hassan A. (2009) A Methodology for Identifying Learning Activity Settings and User Needs In Educational Facilities. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7478-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7478_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:28:56">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138772/</link><title>ATTACKING ANONYMOUS COMMUNICATION NETWORKS THROUGH PORT REDIRECTION.</title><description>3.

l ATTACKING ANONYMOUS COMMUNICATION NETWORKS THROUGH PORT REDIRECTION. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7478-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7478_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:29:21">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138513/</link><title>Optimal Feature Selection Using Mutual Information for Speech Recognition at Low SNR.</title><description>4.

l Optimal Feature Selection Using Mutual Information for Speech Recognition at Low SNR. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>