<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7496">why IEEE member</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:49:34" name="KFUPM ePrints" id="FW14-e008"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e008-7496-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7496_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:49:37">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136099/</link><title>INTRUSION DETECTION IN MOBILE AD-HOC NETWORK IMPLEMENTATION AND PERFORMANCE EVALUATION OF ADAPTIVE ACKNOWLEDGMENT APPROACH.</title><description>1.

Al-Roubaie, Anas A. (2011) INTRUSION DETECTION IN MOBILE AD-HOC NETWORK IMPLEMENTATION AND PERFORMANCE EVALUATION OF ADAPTIVE ACKNOWLEDGMENT APPROACH. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7496-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7496_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:49:59">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136403/</link><title>Design of a Model University Classroom for Collaborative and Interactive LearningDesign of a Model University Classroom for Collaborative and Interactive Learning.</title><description>2.

MOHAMMED, MOHAMMED ALHAJI (2010) Design of a Model University Classroom for Collaborative and Interactive LearningDesign of a Model University Classroom for Collaborative and Interactive Learning. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7496-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7496_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:50:23">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136377/</link><title>Fingerprint Matching using Moments and Moment Invariants.</title><description>3.

Alzahrani, Waleed (2010) Fingerprint Matching using Moments and Moment Invariants. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7496-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7496_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:50:44">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136337/</link><title>Design Considerations for Wireless Sensor Network for Industrial Automation.</title><description>4.

Al-Moallem, Yousuf (2010) Design Considerations for Wireless Sensor Network for Industrial Automation. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7496-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7496_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:51:03">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136329/</link><title>Neural Network Based Detection of Partial Discharge in HV Motors.</title><description>5.

Asiri, Yahya A (2010) Neural Network Based Detection of Partial Discharge in HV Motors. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7496-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7496_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:51:25">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136304/</link><title>Transmission Congestion Management.</title><description>6.

Al Wafi, Essam (2010) Transmission Congestion Management. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7496-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7496_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:51:46">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136300/</link><title>A Framework for Integration Specifications for Component-Based Software.</title><description>7.

Al-Qadhi, Mohammed Abdullah Ali (2010) A Framework for Integration Specifications for Component-Based Software. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7496-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7496_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:52:08">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136331/</link><title>Fault Tolerance Techniques for Sequential Circuits: a Design Level Approach.</title><description>8.

Al-Qahtani, Ayed Saad (2010) Fault Tolerance Techniques for Sequential Circuits: a Design Level Approach. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7496-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7496_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:52:29">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136342/</link><title>LOW COMPLEXITY BLIND EQUALIZATION FOR SISO SYSTEMS WITH GENERAL CONSTELLATIONS.</title><description>9.

Dahman, Ala' Ahmad (2010) LOW COMPLEXITY BLIND EQUALIZATION FOR SISO SYSTEMS WITH GENERAL CONSTELLATIONS. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7496-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7496_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:52:51">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136293/</link><title>A COMPREHENSIVE EMPIRICAL VALIDATION OF PACKAGE-LEVEL METRICS FOR OO SYSTEMS.</title><description>10.

Hashem, Ali (2010) A COMPREHENSIVE EMPIRICAL VALIDATION OF PACKAGE-LEVEL METRICS FOR OO SYSTEMS. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>