<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7499">gold price</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:55:17" name="KFUPM ePrints" id="FW14-e008"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e008-7499-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7499_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:55:20">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136236/</link><title>Process Targeting for Multi-stage Production System: A Network Approach.</title><description>1.

Al-Zu'bi, Walid (2010) Process Targeting for Multi-stage Production System: A Network Approach. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7499-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7499_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:55:39">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136367/</link><title>Rheology &amp; Solid State Properties of Polyethylene/CNT Nanocomposites: Impact of CNT Characteristics and Surface Modification.</title><description>2.

Abbasi, Sarfraz / Initials (2010) Rheology &amp; Solid State Properties of Polyethylene/CNT Nanocomposites: Impact of CNT Characteristics and Surface Modification. PhD thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7499-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7499_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:56:00">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136329/</link><title>Neural Network Based Detection of Partial Discharge in HV Motors.</title><description>3.

Asiri, Yahya A (2010) Neural Network Based Detection of Partial Discharge in HV Motors. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7499-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7499_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:56:15">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136267/</link><title>DEVELOPMENT AND INVESTIGATION OF ENVIRONMENTALLY DEGRADABLE PLASTIC BAGS IN SAUDI ARABIA.</title><description>4.

Ruhul, Amin (2010) DEVELOPMENT AND INVESTIGATION OF ENVIRONMENTALLY DEGRADABLE PLASTIC BAGS IN SAUDI ARABIA. PhD thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7499-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7499_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:56:33">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136301/</link><title>SYNTHESIS OF NEW GOLD(III) COMPLEXES WITH ALKYLDIAMINE AND CYANIDE LIGANDS AND THEIR INTERACTION WITH SOME BIOLOGICALLY IMPORTANT LIGANDS.</title><description>5.

Al Maythalony, B (2009) SYNTHESIS OF NEW GOLD(III) COMPLEXES WITH ALKYLDIAMINE AND CYANIDE LIGANDS AND THEIR INTERACTION WITH SOME BIOLOGICALLY IMPORTANT LIGANDS. PhD thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7499-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7499_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:56:56">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10488/</link><title>Effect of environment on the fatigue and the tensile properties of glass fiber reinforced vinyl ester and epoxy thermosets.</title><description>6.

Shafeeq, Mohammed (2006) Effect of environment on the fatigue and the tensile properties of glass fiber reinforced vinyl ester and epoxy thermosets. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7499-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7499_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:57:16">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/9162/</link><title>Adaptive admission/congestion control policies for CDMA-based wireless internet.</title><description>7.

Baroudi, Uthman and Elhakeem, Ahmed (2006) Adaptive admission/congestion control policies for CDMA-based wireless internet. WIRELESS COMMUNICATIONS AND MOBILE COMPUTING, 6 (1). pp. 1-15.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7499-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7499_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:57:36">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10531/</link><title>Evaluation of performance measures for materials management process in industrial construction projects.</title><description>8.

Kashif ul Asad, Mohammed (2005) Evaluation of performance measures for materials management process in industrial construction projects. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7499-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7499_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:57:57">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/10504/</link><title>Measurement based comparison between VoIPoMPLS and VoIP using software routers.</title><description>9.

Quadri, Itrat Rasool (2005) Measurement based comparison between VoIPoMPLS and VoIP using software routers. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7499-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7499_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:58:18">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/9726/</link><title>Effects of aggregate quality on reinforcement corrosion.</title><description>10.

Ali, Syed Imran (2003) Effects of aggregate quality on reinforcement corrosion. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>