<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7500">roof isolation</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:58:36" name="KFUPM ePrints" id="FW14-e008"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e008-7500-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7500_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:58:38">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136392/</link><title>Photovoltaic System Modeling and Analysis.</title><description>1.

Mir, Shahed Ali (2011) Photovoltaic System Modeling and Analysis. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7500-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7500_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:59:01">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136403/</link><title>Design of a Model University Classroom for Collaborative and Interactive LearningDesign of a Model University Classroom for Collaborative and Interactive Learning.</title><description>2.

MOHAMMED, MOHAMMED ALHAJI (2010) Design of a Model University Classroom for Collaborative and Interactive LearningDesign of a Model University Classroom for Collaborative and Interactive Learning. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7500-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7500_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:59:22">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136305/</link><title>"Reconfigurable Flight Control of a Fighter Aircraft, with Wind Tunnel Study" by Bilal A. Siddiqui, April 2010.</title><description>3.

Siddiqui, Bilal (2010) "Reconfigurable Flight Control of a Fighter Aircraft, with Wind Tunnel Study" by Bilal A. Siddiqui, April 2010. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Not available from this repository.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7500-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7500_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 11:59:42">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/136212/</link><title>A Methodology for Identifying Learning Activity Settings and User Needs In Educational Facilities.</title><description>4.

Balfaqih, Hassan A. (2009) A Methodology for Identifying Learning Activity Settings and User Needs In Educational Facilities. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7500-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7500_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 12:00:02">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/9567/</link><title>Contaminant behavior and distribution in mechanically ventilated multi-zone building.</title><description>5.

Adamu, Zulfikar Aliyu (2006) Contaminant behavior and distribution in mechanically ventilated multi-zone building. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals.

Preview</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7500-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7500_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 12:00:28">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138542/</link><title>DESIGN &amp;FABRICATION OF TWO SEATED AIRCRAFT WITH AN ADVANCED ROTATING LEADING EDGE WING.</title><description>6.

l DESIGN &amp;FABRICATION OF TWO SEATED AIRCRAFT WITH AN ADVANCED ROTATING LEADING EDGE WING. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e008-7500-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e008/7500_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-12 12:00:43">http://eprints.kfupm.edu.sa/138697/</link><title>Voltage Control of a Photovoltaic Connected Power Grid.</title><description>7.

l Voltage Control of a Photovoltaic Connected Power Grid. Masters thesis, King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals. Item availablity restricted.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>