<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7007">Allen Ginsberg Howl review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:50:53" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7007-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7007_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:50:54">http://www.medicinenet.com/image-collection/peutz-jeghers_syndrome_picture/picture.htm</link><title>Picture of Peutz-Jeghers Syndrome</title><description>Scattered dark brown macules appear on the lips and buccal mucosa of a child with Peutz-Jeghers...of Pediatric Dermatology Kay Shou-Mei Kane, Jen Bissonette Ryder, Richard Allen Johnson, Howard P.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7007-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7007_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:51:49">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=52259</link><title>Power to the People</title><description>Online management tools and other technology put patients in control of their health...a car, bid on antique furniture, pay bills, check your cholesterol levels, review your biopsy results, schedule...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7007-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7007_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:54:39">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=155571</link><title>Heart Failure Patients Urged to Discuss Care With Docs</title><description>An open dialogue can inform decisions on treatment options...process should be proactive, anticipatory and patient-centered," lead author Dr. Larry Allen, an assistant professor of medicine at the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7007-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7007_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:59:13">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=157686</link><title>Type 2 Diabetes in Kids a Challenge to Control</title><description>...children and teens, says University of Wisconsin professor of pediatrics David B. Allen, MD.In September of 2010, while the trial was under way, the...Avandia part of the study continued taking the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7007-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7007_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:02:20">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=122668</link><title>Acid-Reducing Drugs May Not Be Risky in Pregnancy</title><description>...and it is generally reassuring about use of PPIs in pregnancy," says Allen A. Mitchell, MD, director of the Slone Epidemiology Center at the Boston...individualized assessment about how much...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>