<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7027">prefered or preferred</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:16:15" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7027-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7027_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:16:16">http://www.medicinenet.com/infant_formulas/article.htm</link><title>Infant Formulas</title><description>Though human milk is the preferred feeding for infants, parents may consider formula-feeding if there is an inadequate supply of...infant formula? So, what types of formula should parents give to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7027-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7027_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:19:12">http://www.medicinenet.com/metabolic_syndrome/article.htm</link><title>Metabolic Syndrome</title><description>...syndrome include insulin resistance, hypertension (high blood pressure), cholesterol abnormalities, and an increased risk for...sedentary lifestyle. Lifestyle modification is the preferred...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7027-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7027_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:21:18">http://www.medicinenet.com/asthma_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Asthma Pictures Slideshow: An Inflammatory Disorder of the Airways</title><description>Watch this slideshow on asthma and learn about this chronic inflammation disorder of the bronchiole tubes (airways) resulting in...Treatment of Asthma Most asthma medications work by relaxing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7027-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7027_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:24:50">http://www.medicinenet.com/home_allergy_quiz_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Home Allergy Quiz Pictures Slideshow: Is Your Home Allergy-Proof?</title><description>Take this home allergy slideshow quiz from MedicineNet and test your knowledge on allergens, dust...Home Allergy Quiz - Question 2 2. True or false?Beds should be placed near air vents for good air...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7027-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7027_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:25:26">http://www.medicinenet.com/brucellosis_facts/article.htm</link><title>Brucellosis</title><description>...disease in humans. Symptoms and signs include fatigue, fever, sweating, and appetite loss. The preferred treatment is doxycycline...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7027-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7027_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:29:27">http://www.medicinenet.com/image-collection/heart_catheter_picture/picture.htm</link><title>Picture of Heart Catheter</title><description>...they involve only a needle puncture in the skin where the catheter is inserted into a vein or an artery. See a picture of Heart...a lot in the past 20 years. They have become the preferred way to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7027-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7027_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:32:43">http://www.medicinenet.com/digestive_disease_myths_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Digestive Disease Myths Pictures Slideshow: Common Misconceptions</title><description>Watch this slideshow on digestive disease myths and learn about common misconceptions such as "Does spicy food cause ulcers?" and...In fact, some physicians feel that enemas are preferred over...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7027-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7027_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:36:10">http://www.medicinenet.com/hemorrhoids_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Hemorrhoids Pictures Slideshow: Causes, Symptoms, and Treatment</title><description>Watch this slideshow on Hemorrhoids. Learn about causes, symptoms and treatments for these painful...to be managed with non-surgical techniques. Non-operative treatment is preferred because it is...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7027-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7027_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:37:16">http://www.medicinenet.com/metabolic_syndrome_quiz/quiz.htm</link><title>Metabolic Syndrome Quiz: Test Your Medical IQ</title><description>Metabolic syndrome is serious and you should be concerned. Learn the causes, symptoms, treatments,...modification Explanation: Lifestyle modification is the preferred treatment of metabolic syndrome.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7027-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7027_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:39:55">http://www.onhealth.com/asthma/article.htm</link><title>Asthma</title><description>Asthma is a condition in which hyperreactive airways constrict and result in symptoms like wheezing, coughing, and shortness of...treatment of asthma? Most asthma medications work by relaxing...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>