<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7031">Thomas test</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:23:39" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7031-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7031_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:23:40">http://www.medicinenet.com/healthy_seniors_pictures_slideshow_exercise_aging/article.htm</link><title>Healthy Seniors Pictures Slideshow: Exercise for Successful Aging</title><description>Senior exercise for healthy and successful aging. Learn what happens to our bodies as we age, the...individuals in the study who did not exercise on the following tests: a six-minute walk test (they...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7031-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7031_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:26:31">http://www.medicinenet.com/diverticulitis_diverticulosis_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Diverticulitis (Diverticulosis) Pictures Slideshow</title><description>Watch this slideshow on diverticulitis (diverticulosis) - a condition in which the diverticulum...the diagnosis of diverticular disease can be confirmed by a variety of tests. Many patients do not...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7031-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7031_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:27:13">http://www.medicinenet.com/mucormycosis/article.htm</link><title>Mucormycosis</title><description>Mucormycosis (zygomycosis) is a fungal infection caused by Zygomycetes. Symptoms and signs include fever, headache, coughing,...A definitive diagnosis is difficult. Although tests such as CT or MRI may...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7031-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7031_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:27:59">http://www.medicinenet.com/beta_thalassemia/article.htm</link><title>Beta Thalassemia</title><description>Beta Thalassemia is the most familiar type of thalassemia. Thalassemia is not just one disease but rather a complex series of...first described in 1925 by the American pediatrician Thomas Cooley.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7031-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7031_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:28:34">http://www.medicinenet.com/pictures_slideshow_foods_to_boost_male_health/article.htm</link><title>Men's Health Pictures Slideshow: Foods to Boost Male Health</title><description>Watch and learn about foods that boost male health including oysters, cherries, and ginger which...Essential Screening Tests Every Man Needs Embarrassing Male Body Problems 15 Cancer Symptoms Men...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7031-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7031_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:31:42">http://www.medicinenet.com/infertility_treatments_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Infertility Pictures Slideshow: Which Treatment Is Right for You?</title><description>Watch this slideshow on infertility to see methods available to get pregnant. Treatments from IVF to...the best time for sex), you can use over-the-counter ovulation tests. These detect a hormonal...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7031-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7031_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:33:49">http://www.medicinenet.com/urinary_tract_infection/article.htm</link><title>Urinary Tract Infections (UTIs)</title><description>A urinary tract infection (UTI) is an infection of the bladder, kidneys, ureters, or urethra. E. coli, a type of bacteria that...preferably within 24 hours. Most medical offices can test urine for...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7031-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7031_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:34:41">http://www.medicinenet.com/asperger_syndrome/article.htm</link><title>Asperger's Syndrome (Asperger Syndrome, Asperger Disorder)</title><description>Asperger's syndrome (AS, Asperger syndrome, Asperger disorder) is an autism spectrum disorder. Asperger's syndrome is...including Mozart, Albert Einstein, Benjamin Franklin, Thomas Jefferson, and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7031-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7031_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:39:00">http://www.medterms.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=10301</link><title>Bayes theorem</title><description>Bayes theorem: A probability principle set forth by the English mathematician Thomas Bayes (1702-1761). Bayes' theorem is of value in medical decision-making...of a particular diagnosis given the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7031-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7031_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:43:00">http://www.medterms.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=18884</link><title>Ricin</title><description>...husband by contaminating his food with ricin. In 1997, a Wisconsin resident, Thomas Leahy, was arrested and charged with possession with intent to use ricin...US Senate office of the majority...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>