<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7033">Porto</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:47:23" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7033-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7033_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:47:24">http://www.medicinenet.com/image-collection/port_wine_stain_picture/picture.htm</link><title>Picture of Port Wine Stain</title><description>A mark on the skin that resembles port wine (porto) in its rich ruby red color. See a picture of...Port wine stain: A mark on the skin that resembles port wine (porto) in its rich ruby red color. Due...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7033-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7033_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:49:26">http://www.medicinenet.com/image-collection/port-wine_stain_neck_picture/picture.htm</link><title>Picture of Port-Wine Stain (Neck)</title><description>This is an extensive port-wine stain on the right side of the neck of a young female. See a picture...A port-wine stain is a mark on the skin that resembles port wine (porto) in its rich ruby red...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7033-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7033_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:51:59">http://www.medterms.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=5005</link><title>Port wine stain</title><description>Port wine stain: A mark on the skin that resembles port wine (porto) in its rich ruby red color. Due to an abnormal aggregation of capillaries, a port wine stain is a type of vascular malformation...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7033-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7033_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:54:51">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=94429</link><title>Fall Babies at Higher Risk for Asthma</title><description>...viral infections in early life in the causation of childhood asthma," writes Renato T. Stein, MD, PhD, of the PontifÃ cia Universidade Catolica in Porto Alegre, Brazil, in an editorial published...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7033-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7033_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:58:05">http://www.medicinenet.com/image-collection/port-wine_stain_after_laser_treatment_picture/picture.htm</link><title>Picture of Port-Wine Stain after Laser Treatment</title><description>There is a marked resolution of the port-wine stain after multiple treatments with pulsed dye laser...A port-wine stain is a mark on the skin that resembles port wine (porto) in its rich ruby red color.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>