<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7037">how to write journalistic review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:58:21" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7037-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7037_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:58:23">http://www.medicinenet.com/dyslexia/article.htm</link><title>Dyslexia</title><description>Dyslexia affects a person's ability to spell, read, write, or even speak. It's considered the most common learning disability in...disability that can hinder a person's ability to read, write, spell,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7037-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7037_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:59:43">http://www.medicinenet.com/living_tips_adult_adhd_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>ADHD Pictures Slideshow: Daily Living Tips for Adult ADHD</title><description>...for Adult ADHD (Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder). If you have ADHD or you just need to get yourself and your family...insurance information, checks, and bank statements. Review this pile...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7037-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7037_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:01:23">http://www.medicinenet.com/beauty_product_dangers_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Skin and Beauty Pictures Slideshow: The Truth About Beauty Product Dangers</title><description>Watch this slideshow on The Truth About Beauty Product Dangers. Hair straighteners, dyes, shampoos, creams, and cosmetics are bad...still need an eye exam. The doctor can write a prescription for you...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7037-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7037_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:02:30">http://www.medicinenet.com/walking/article.htm</link><title>Walking</title><description>Walking has numerous health benefits. Learn how walking can help you, how much you need to do to gain benefits, types of walking...sticking with it. Planning increases compliance. Write down the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7037-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7037_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:04:16">http://www.medicinenet.com/iv_drug_infusion_faqs/article.htm</link><title>IV Drug Infusion FAQs</title><description>Ankylosing spondylitis, Behcet's disease, cancer, Crohn's disease, juvenile rheumatoid arthritis, multiple sclerosis, and...to your health condition or questions about your medication and infusion...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7037-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7037_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:06:23">http://www.onhealth.com/breast_cancer/article.htm</link><title>Breast Cancer</title><description>Breast cancer is the most common cancer in women and the second most common cause of cancer death in women in the U.S. Symptoms...the patient's doctor on an individual basis. What follows is a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7037-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7037_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:08:05">http://www.medicinenet.com/aerobic_exercise/article.htm</link><title>Aerobic Exercise</title><description>Aerobic exercise is any form of exercise that can be sustained for more than a few minutes while your heart, lungs, and muscles...article and probably five others just like it to review all of the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7037-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7037_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:09:28">http://www.medicinenet.com/chemotherapy/article.htm</link><title>Chemotherapy</title><description>...fluid retention, mouth and throat problems) are important to understand when undergoing chemotherapy treatment. It is important to...Some people keep a "running list" and write down new questions...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7037-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7037_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:13:49">http://www.medicinenet.com/learning_disability/article.htm</link><title>Learning Disabilities</title><description>Learning disabilities can cause an individual to have trouble learning and using skills such as reading, listening, writing,...may manifest itself in an imperfect ability to listen, think, speak,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7037-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7037_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:17:14">http://www.medicinenet.com/exercise_and_activity/article.htm</link><title>Fitness</title><description>Regular physical activity can reduce the risk of disease. Regular exercise can also reduce the...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>