<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7043">rhapsody in blue sheet piano</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:27:45" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7043-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7043_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:27:46">http://www.medicinenet.com/eyeglasses_sunglasses_and_magnifiers/article.htm</link><title>Eyeglasses, Sunglasses, and Magnifying Glasses</title><description>Nonprescription eyeglasses are available over the counter (OTC) and are typically used by people who can no longer read fine print...shaving at the bathroom mirror, or reading piano music while...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7043-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7043_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:32:22">http://www.medicinenet.com/alzheimers_disease_causes_stages_and_symptoms/article.htm</link><title>Alzheimer's Disease</title><description>Alzheimer's disease is a common cause of dementia. Symptoms and warning signs of Alzheimer's disease include memory loss,...be able to do math but still may be able to read a magazine with pleasure.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7043-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7043_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:33:52">http://www.medicinenet.com/depression_triggers_as_you_age_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Depression Pictures Slideshow: Sneaky Depression Triggers as You Age</title><description>Watch this slideshow on Sneaky Depression Triggers as You Age. From too little vitamin B12 to too much time alone, look at these...If you're older, you're more at risk for the B12 blues because you...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7043-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7043_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:38:42">http://www.medicinenet.com/headache_and_migraine_triggers_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Headache Pictures Slideshow: Surprising Headache and Migraine Triggers</title><description>What triggers headaches and migraines? Watch this slideshow to learn some surprising causes of...Trigger: Cheese A migraine trigger for some people is aged cheese, including blue cheese, cheddar,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7043-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7043_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:41:33">http://www.medicinenet.com/gorgeous_hair_color_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Hair and Beauty Pictures Slideshow: Tips for Gorgeous Hair Color</title><description>Watch this Hair and Beauty slideshow on Tips for Gorgeous Hair Color. If you're a hair dye beginner or looking for your next color...so mind a few tips: Stay away from blue reds -- they tend to look...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7043-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7043_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:44:13">http://www.medicinenet.com/lungs_design_and_purpose/article.htm</link><title>Lung Anatomy</title><description>...for the exchange of oxygen and carbon dioxide between the air we breathe and the blood. Eliminating carbon dioxide from the blood...The major muscle of respiration is a sheet-like dome shaped...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7043-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7043_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:46:03">http://www.medicinenet.com/sids/article.htm</link><title>Sudden Infant Death Syndrome (SIDS)</title><description>The cause of sudden infant death syndrome (SIDS) is unknown. The risk of SIDS peaks in infants 2-4 months of age. SIDS is more...a firm mattress in a safety-approved crib with a tight fitting sheet...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7043-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7043_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:49:12">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=53173</link><title>Tornado Safety</title><description>...doesn't fade in a few seconds like thunder. Night - Small, bright, blue-green to white flashes at ground level near a thunderstorm (as opposed...sleeping bag. Know where very heavy objects rest on...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7043-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7043_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:54:34">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=19711</link><title>Asbestos Exposure - FAQs</title><description>...fibers that are light gray to pale brown in color); Crocidolite, or blue asbestos (straight blue fibers); and Anthophyllite (brittle white fibers). Chrysotile asbestos, with...or have contained...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7043-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7043_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:56:32">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=78846</link><title>Exercise Tubing and Bands</title><description>...more. The difference between tubing and bands is that bands are flat sheets of thin elastic rubber, usually six to eight inches wide, and come...you can get a training effect if you use them.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>