<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7045">Natural Parks America</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:35:24" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7045-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7045_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:35:25">http://www.medicinenet.com/alzheimers_disease_causes_stages_and_symptoms/article.htm</link><title>Alzheimer's Disease</title><description>Alzheimer's disease is a common cause of dementia. Symptoms and warning signs of Alzheimer's disease include memory loss,...Impairment of the senses Driving Natural disaster safety Who would take care of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7045-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7045_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:38:09">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=57306</link><title>Doctor's Pulse 2005 Archive</title><description>...thyroid Pain: Kill pain and stress the natural way! Panic Attack: How-to-tell symptoms...swimming in your pool or local water park? Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder: Katrina survivors &amp;amp...you...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7045-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7045_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:39:07">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=53985</link><title>Hiking: Play it Safe on the Trails with Sally Grimes</title><description>Are you heading to a national or state park for your family vacation? Join Sally Grimes of the...you heading to a national or state park for your family vacation? Join Sally Grimes...looked when...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7045-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7045_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:42:32">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=50564</link><title>Moving Meditation: Tai Chi for Arthritis Relief</title><description>Gentle movements of the ancient Chinese exercise tai chi are one of many alternatives to help...small cities in China - and increasingly in America's parks, hospitals, and community centers -...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7045-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7045_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:44:26">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=50602</link><title>Pain: Sting the Pain Away</title><description>Louise Chirasello of Brewster, New York, was suffering intractable pain from her two hip replacement operations. She tried to get...used in Eastern Europe, Asia and South America. Treatments...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7045-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7045_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:46:01">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=62308</link><title>Chefs' Tips and Recipes for Healthier Cooking</title><description>4 top chefs share tips and recipes for lighter dishes that don't scrimp on taste and style...the best prices, but you add a natural variety to your diet that is extremely...As one of the Culinary...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7045-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7045_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:48:15">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=165716</link><title>Flesh-Eating Fungal Infection Can Follow Natural Disasters, Study Finds</title><description>Five people died from mucormycosis after 2011 Joplin, Mo., tornado...Flesh-Eating Fungal Infection Can Follow Natural Disasters, Study FindsBy Amy NortonHealthDay ReporterWEDNESDAY, Dec...a year," said...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7045-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7045_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:49:48">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=55757</link><title>Kids' Favorite Foods: Lighter, Healthier Recipes</title><description>The good news is that the healthy-eating movement in America is gaining momentum. Shucks, even cereal giants have launched...is that the healthy-eating movement in America is gaining momentum.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7045-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7045_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:52:16">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=159988</link><title>Deadly Black Widow Spider Edged Aside in California</title><description>Study finds less-toxic brown widow variety may be taking over...Although they are relatively new to North America, a new study found that brown widow...searches in various habitats, such as developed...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7045-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7045_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:53:57">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=51171</link><title>What's So Great About Kissing?</title><description>Finally, something that feels good that's not bad for you. In fact, say our lip service experts,...DDS, a private practice dentist in Fairview Park, Ohio, and consumer advisor for the American...kiss...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>