<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7059">doctor Amsterdam</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:26:06" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7059-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7059_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:26:07">http://www.medicinenet.com/aids_retrospective_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>AIDS Retrospective Pictures Slideshow: A Pictorial Timeline of the HIV/AIDS Pandemic</title><description>Get a historical overview of the HIV/AIDS pandemic from human contraction to the present through...of AIDS. Elizabeth Taylor addresses the International AIDS Conference in Amsterdam. A monumental...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7059-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7059_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:30:47">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=51511</link><title>Health: For Your Health, Assert Yourself</title><description>Taking a more active role can help older people get the care they need. Here's how to get started...Reviewed by Dr. Craig H. Kliger --&gt; March 26, 2001 -- After doctors diagnosed Richard Farrell with...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7059-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7059_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:35:17">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=50732</link><title>Nutrition: Wine and Your Health</title><description>Studies suggest that moderate wine consumption can have some benefits. Here are a few tips...and Behavior, scientists at the Institute for Research in Extramural Medicine in Amsterdam tested 275 men and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7059-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7059_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:37:52">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=80902</link><title>Clot-Preventing Drug Improves Heart Blood Flow After Angioplasty</title><description>But doctors question whether the practice results in long-term benefits...clot-preventing drugs such as Plavix, for example.Most significant, the Turkish doctors did extensive measurements of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7059-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7059_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:39:18">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=53999</link><title>Sexuality Education and Pregnancy Prevention</title><description>How influential are the media and TV with the sexual attitudes of youth? Media expert Kate...script and check it for accuracy, make sure this is something a doctor would really say or do, to make...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7059-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7059_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:41:41">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=177336</link><title>Device May Restore Speech to People on Breathing Tubes</title><description>Doctors say 'electrolarynx' eased frustration for patient on mechanical ventilator...Tubes By Brenda GoodmanHealthDay ReporterWEDNESDAY, March 19, 2014 (HealthDay News) -- Doctors in the Netherlands say...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7059-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7059_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:45:11">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=152950</link><title>Did Beethoven's Hearing Loss Shape His Compositions?</title><description>Dutch researchers speculate that he favored notes he could hear better as he became more deaf...deafness may have shaped his musical style.Researchers from the University of Amsterdam in the Netherlands...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7059-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7059_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:46:43">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=159827</link><title>Residents as Good as Fully Trained Docs if Properly Supervised: Study</title><description>Their inexperience is counteracted by teaching from more experienced physicians, researchers say...well supervised provide care that's as good as care provided by fully trained doctors, according to a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7059-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7059_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:51:38">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=88612</link><title>Biomarker May Predict Response to Cancer Therapy</title><description>Dutch researchers identify cell type that is potential target for these agents...medical oncology at VU University Medical Center in Amsterdam, said in a prepared statement.Vroling and her colleagues...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7059-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7059_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:55:40">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=166295</link><title>Asthma Linked to Increased Risk of Dangerous Lung Blockage</title><description>Odds of blood clot in lung artery increase along with severity of the respiratory disease, study...lead author Dr. Christof Majoor, of the Academic Medical Centre in Amsterdam, said in a news...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>