<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7061">startup advisors chicago</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:57:11" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7061-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7061_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:57:12">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=50794</link><title>Money: Too Rich for Your Health?</title><description>They have money, power, and glory. So why are they miserable?...vulnerable you feel -- and the more worries you rack up. University of Chicago researchers divided 800 teenagers into four groups...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7061-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7061_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:01:38">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=54642</link><title>Parenting: How To Be a Positive Parent</title><description>Being a parent can feel like a cross between a prison warden and a traffic cop. We say no and don't to our kids so often, is it...really wanted to know was, whether he came from Chicago or Wichita.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7061-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7061_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:05:29">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=174271</link><title>Parents' Feeding Choices May Raise Baby's Risk for Celiac Disease</title><description>Study links late introduction of gluten, breast-feeding beyond 1 year to development of the...months of age," he added. Lara Field, a pediatric dietitian and nutrition advisor at the University of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7061-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7061_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:09:41">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=101385</link><title>Health-Care Reform Could Be Obama's Toughest Challenge</title><description>But experts say time might be right to succeed where others have failed...last week while addressing the American Medical Association (AMA) annual meeting in Chicago. "It is a ticking time bomb for...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7061-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7061_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:10:32">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=86190</link><title>Many Doctors Use Placebos on Patients</title><description>Many Doctors Use Placebos on Patients Chicago Survey: Nearly Half of Doctors Have Given Patients Dummy Pills or Other...I think it's unethical," says John Kusek, PhD, a senior scientific advisor at...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7061-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7061_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:14:24">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=148982</link><title>Are Signs of Old Age Really Something More Serious?</title><description>...an associate professor of neurological sciences at Rush University Medical School in Chicago.Researchers examined 1,100 older nuns and priests every year starting in...disease is different than...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7061-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7061_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:17:48">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=89197</link><title>Report: Polluted Air Puts Millions at Risk</title><description>...March when it set a more lax ozone pollution standard than scientific advisors said was necessary to protect human health. A report issued last week...22. Birmingham-Hoover-Cullman, AL 23. Las...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>