<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7062">marquette university news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:20:17" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7062-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7062_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:20:18">http://www.medicinenet.com/happiness_quiz/quiz.htm</link><title>Happiness Quiz: Test Your Emotional Intelligence Quotient (EQ)</title><description>Take the Happiness Quiz! Plenty of people live in pleasant, fulfilling satisfaction. Is it sex or...do badly in the happiness ranking. From researcher Andrew Oswald of the University of Warwick in...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7062-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7062_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:22:31">http://www.medicinenet.com/15_ways_to_stay_on_your_game_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Men's Health Pictures Slideshow: 15 Ways to Stay On Top of Your Game</title><description>Watch this Men's Health slideshow on 15 Ways to Stay On Top of Your Game. See how first impressions, staying active, good hygiene...of Personality and Social Psychology, 1998. Marquette University:...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7062-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7062_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:26:54">http://www.medicinenet.com/diabetic_peripheral_neuropathy_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Diabetic Peripheral Neuropathy Slideshow: Exercises to Improve Diabetes Nerve Pain</title><description>Watch this slideshow on Diabetic Peripheral Neuropathy. Learn how to improve your balance and see ideas for exercises that help...director of the Diabetes Care Center, University of Washington Medical...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7062-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7062_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:31:23">http://www.medicinenet.com/plastic/article.htm</link><title>Plastic</title><description>Plastics are in most everything, from the jars, cups and containers that hold our foods and beverages to the construction...Fredrick S. vom Saal, a professor of biology at the University of Missouri,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7062-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7062_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:35:16">http://www.medicinenet.com/jobs_that_wreck_your_sleep_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Sleep Pictures Slideshow: Jobs That Wreck Your Sleep</title><description>Did you know that some jobs can wreck your sleep. From network administrators to nurses, see a variety of jobs that affect...complete gallery of slideshows. Air Traffic Controller News of air traffic...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7062-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7062_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:38:02">http://www.medicinenet.com/habits_that_wreck_your_teeth_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Dental Health Pictures Slideshow: 19 Habits That Wreck Your Teeth</title><description>See 19 Habits That Wreck Your Teeth from this slideshow. Learn how chewing ice, eating snacks,...Dental Association. Consumer Guide to Dentistry National Public Radio. News release, New York University.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7062-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7062_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:38:51">http://www.medicinenet.com/sleep_and_sleep_disorders_in_children_and_teens/article.htm</link><title>Sleep and Sleep Disorders in Children and Teenagers</title><description>Sleep needs in children and teenagers depends on the age of the child. Sleep disorders in children such as sleep apnea,...age continue to require 14 to 15 hours of sleep daily. Good news for parents,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7062-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7062_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:41:43">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=163089</link><title>Hantavirus</title><description>Second Source article from Government...Colorado and Utah, the Indian Health Service, the Navajo Nation, and the University of New Mexico all joined together to confront the outbreak. During the...the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7062-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7062_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:46:52">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=79343</link><title>Infertility Q&amp;A</title><description>Second Source article from Government...and Heather and Anthony felt crushed each time. They finally got good news after the sixth try. In February 2004, they found out that Heather...M.D., Ph.D.,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7062-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7062_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:48:04">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=12065</link><title>Heart Attacks - Midwinter Hazard</title><description>HEALTH FEATURE ARCHIVEMidwinter Hazard - Heart Attacks Medical researchers at the University of Southern California (USC) in Los Angeles may win the "Grinch" contest...by stress, there's the chance...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>