<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7065">disney easter dessert recipes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:54:48" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7065-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7065_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:54:49">http://www.medicinenet.com/calcium_rich_dishes_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Food &amp; Recipes Pictures Slideshow: 15 Delicious Calcium-Rich Dishes</title><description>Watch this slideshow on 15 Delicious Calcium-Rich Dishes. Tender stuffed chicken, Spanish cheese,...Food &amp; Recipes Pictures Slideshow: 15 Delicious Calcium-Rich Dishes Reviewed by Laura J. Martin.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7065-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7065_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:57:18">http://www.medicinenet.com/food_combos_for_big_flavor_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Food &amp; Recipes Pictures Slideshow: Surprising Food Combos for Big Flavor</title><description>...See how the right mix of salty, sweet, sour, and spicy flavors can come together in your recipes with these creative cooking ideas...Food &amp; Recipes Pictures Slideshow: Surprising Food Combos...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7065-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7065_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:00:27">http://www.medicinenet.com/super_bowl_party_recipes/article.htm</link><title>Super Bowl Party Recipes (Healthy and Easy)</title><description>Healthy Super Bowl Party recipes, special diet recipes for vegetarians, vegans, people with diabetes, celiac disease and other...Healthy, Easy Super Bowl Party Recipes Did you know that Super Bowl...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7065-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7065_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:02:33">http://www.medicinenet.com/diet_plans_and_programs/article.htm</link><title>Diet Plans &amp; Programs</title><description>Popular weight loss and diet plans include the Atkins diet, Jenny Craig, Zone diet, Weight Watchers,...and weight. These phases promote consistent meal times, healthy snacks and desserts, and water. The...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7065-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7065_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:03:24">http://www.medicinenet.com/10_skinny_cocktails_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Skinny Cocktails Pictures Slideshow: 10 Low-Calorie Alcoholic Drink Recipes</title><description>...on Skinny Cocktails. See how to put your drink on a diet with these low-calorie mixed-drink recipes including mojitos, margaritas,...10 Low-Calorie Alcoholic Drink Recipes Reviewed by Kathleen Zelman,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7065-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7065_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:08:10">http://www.medicinenet.com/10_worst_foods_in_your_fridge_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Healthy Eating Pictures Slideshow: The 10 Worst Foods in Your Fridge</title><description>What are the 10 worst foods in your fridge? From mayonnaise to ice cream and butter to processed lunch meats, watch this slideshow...shrimp for frankfurters and sausage in meals and recipes. Even...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7065-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7065_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:09:36">http://www.medicinenet.com/vegetarian_and_vegan_diet/article.htm</link><title>Vegetarian and Vegan Diet</title><description>There are many types of vegetarians: vegans, lacto-vegetarians, lacto-ovo vegetarians, and flexitarians. Vegans eat only...for myself? What are sources for vegetarian and vegan recipes? What is...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7065-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7065_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:11:01">http://www.medicinenet.com/alcohol_and_nutrition/article.htm</link><title>Alcohol and Nutrition</title><description>Alcohol has a big nutritional impact. Therefore, it is important to understand how alcohol is processed by your body in order to...5 oz. 105 Wine spritzer, 4 oz. 49 Wine, dessert, sweet, 4 oz. 180 The...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7065-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7065_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:11:56">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=14549</link><title>Heart Healthy Guidelines</title><description>...whole milk versions. Use low fat or nonfat yogurt; try it in recipes or as a topping. Try low fat or nonfat sour cream or...low in total fat. Preparation tips: Use fruits as a snack or dessert.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7065-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7065_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:14:13">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=22753</link><title>Nutrition Low Cholesterol: Daily Food Guide, Milk, Yogurt, Cheese</title><description>...sodium cheeses. Read the label to compare the sodium content. Frozen Dairy Desserts Buy frozen desserts that are lower in saturated fat, like ice milk...Eat lowfat or nonfat yogurt alone or as a...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>