<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7068">Speech and Language Processing: An Introduction to Natural Language Processing, Computational Linguistics, and Speech Recognition</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:19:16" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7068-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7068_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:19:17">http://www.medicinenet.com/auditory_processing_disorder_in_children/article.htm</link><title>Auditory Processing Disorder in Children</title><description>Children with auditory processing disorders often do not recognize subtle differences between sounds in words, even though the...Auditory Processing Disorder in Children Introduction to auditory...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7068-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7068_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:21:22">http://www.medicinenet.com/sign_language/article.htm</link><title>Sign Language</title><description>American Sign Language (ASL) is a complete, complex language that employs signs made with the hands and other movements, including...American Sign Language What is American Sign...own forms of local,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7068-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7068_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:22:54">http://www.medicinenet.com/dementia_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Dementia Pictures Slideshow: Disorders of the Brain</title><description>...Vascular (multi-infarct) dementia (MID), Creutzfeldt-Jakob Disease (CJD), Pick disease and more. Learn about causes, diagnosis,...she stressed the words in an unusual way. She sometimes became..</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7068-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7068_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:26:38">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=80625</link><title>Early Red Flags and Warning Signs of Autism</title><description>Autism signs and symptoms at an early age include lack of gestures, smiles and unusual posture. Learn more about the early signs...and founder of First Signs, an organization dedicated to educating...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7068-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7068_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:28:00">http://www.medicinenet.com/chronic_pain/article.htm</link><title>Chronic Pain</title><description>Chronic pain is pain (an unpleasant sense of discomfort) that persists or progresses over a long period of time. In contrast to...Chronic Pain Chronic pain facts* Introduction to chronic pain The A..</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7068-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7068_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:32:53">http://www.medicinenet.com/fragile_x_syndrome/article.htm</link><title>Fragile X Syndrome</title><description>...on the X chromosome. People with Fragile X syndrome suffer from physical, social, emotional, speech, language, sensory,...Physical Social and emotional Speech and language Sensory Is there a...is...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7068-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7068_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:35:46">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=50348</link><title>Help for Sensory Integration Disorder in Kids</title><description>...disorder can throw kids off balance but there is help available to get them back on track...researched the issue of sensory processing and motor planning problems in...one's self Delays in speech,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7068-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7068_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:37:22">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=53894</link><title>Fibromyalgia and the Mind-Body-Spirit Connection</title><description>Join our discussion with authors William B. Salt II, MD, and Edwin H. Season, MD, about treating the pain and fatigue associated...1972, where he currently holds an appointment as Clinical...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7068-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7068_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:37:53">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=161314</link><title>Dyslexia May Be Caused by Signal Processing Problem in Brain</title><description>Researchers hope study findings will lead to more treatment options...Be Caused by Signal Processing Problem in BrainFRIDAY, Aug...with signal processing involving speech recognition in the brain,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7068-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7068_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:41:04">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=163458</link><title>New Treatments May Help Restore Speech Lost to Aphasia</title><description>Loss of language skills can stem from stroke or other brain damage...New Treatments May Help Restore Speech Lost to AphasiaBy Maureen SalamonHealthDay...that passing nuisance can be an everyday...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>