<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7070">compact flash memory card</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:44:54" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7070-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7070_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:44:55">http://www.medicinenet.com/low_testosterone_quiz/quiz.htm</link><title>Low Testosterone (Low T) Quiz: Test Your IQ of Men's Conditions</title><description>What are symptoms of low testosterone (low T)? Take this quiz to learn more about causes of low...symptom of low-T is common in both men and women? AHot flashes BLoss of sexual desire CChanges in...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7070-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7070_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:46:04">http://www.medicinenet.com/sleep_disorders_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Sleep Disorders Pictures Slideshow: A Visual Guide to Sleeping Disorders</title><description>See a visual guide on the different types of sleep disorders and learn about their symptoms, causes,...relationship troubles, poor job performance, job-related injuries, memory problems, and mood...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7070-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7070_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:48:55">http://www.medicinenet.com/depression_triggers_as_you_age_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Depression Pictures Slideshow: Sneaky Depression Triggers as You Age</title><description>Watch this slideshow on Sneaky Depression Triggers as You Age. From too little vitamin B12 to too much time alone, look at these...and Menopause Hormone fluctuations, hot flashes, and life changes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7070-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7070_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:50:44">http://www.medicinenet.com/menopause/article.htm</link><title>Menopause</title><description>...periods permanently stop, also called the "change of life." Menopause symptoms include hot flashes, night sweats, irregular...menopause can include abnormal vaginal bleeding, hot flashes, vaginal...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7070-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7070_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:54:24">http://www.medicinenet.com/alzheimers_disease_causes_stages_and_symptoms/article.htm</link><title>Alzheimer's Disease</title><description>...disease is a common cause of dementia. Symptoms and warning signs of Alzheimer's disease include memory loss, difficulty...of the brain that is characterized by impairment of memory and eventually...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7070-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7070_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:57:38">http://www.medicinenet.com/huntington_disease/article.htm</link><title>Huntington's Disease</title><description>...mood swings, apathy, depression, and anger uncharacteristic of the individual. Judgement, memory, and other cognitive functions...The disease may affect a person's judgment, memory, and other...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7070-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7070_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:58:08">http://www.medicinenet.com/vaginal_dryness_and_vaginal_atrophy/article.htm</link><title>Vaginal Dryness</title><description>Vaginal dryness and vaginal atrophy occurs in women during perimenopause, menopause, and postmenopause. With vaginal atrophy, the...other symptoms of the menopausal transition. Hot flashes, night...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7070-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7070_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:01:50">http://www.medicinenet.com/vegetarian_and_vegan_diet/article.htm</link><title>Vegetarian and Vegan Diet</title><description>There are many types of vegetarians: vegans, lacto-vegetarians, lacto-ovo vegetarians, and flexitarians. Vegans eat only...loss of appetite, weight loss, poor memory, dementia, depression, problems...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7070-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7070_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:04:51">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=10288</link><title>Memory Exercises That Work</title><description>...Memory Exercises That Work Memory strategies are known to everyone who has ever...way to remember your PIN number (personal identification number) for your bank card, your credit card, and your...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7070-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7070_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:05:28">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=225</link><title>First Aid For Floods And Flash Floods</title><description>Floods And Flash Floods Emergency Information What is a flood? What is a flash flood...food and water, non-electric can opener, essential medicines, cash and credit cards, sturdy shoes Develop an...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>