<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7082">The raven</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:09:50" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7082-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7082_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:09:51">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=152189</link><title>Ravens Gesture With Beaks Just Like Humans Use Hands</title><description>Birds are every bit as smart, communicative as apes, researchers say...Ravens Gesture With Beaks Just Like Humans Use HandsTHURSDAY, Dec. 1 (HealthDay News) -- A new study says ravens use their beaks to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7082-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7082_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:11:09">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=51294</link><title>Looking Good, Feeling Rotten</title><description>...even a friend, to take your complaints seriously. But do your homework, be persistent, and find the help and support you need to...Feature Reviewed By Gary Vogin Nov. 19, 2001 -- Raven Erebus lived...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7082-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7082_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:12:24">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=101354</link><title>Standard IQ Test May Undervalue People With Autism</title><description>Study shows they could solve problems faster than non-autistics on a different test...Wechsler Adult Intelligence Scale, the test most often used to measure IQ, researchers said.But when given another...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7082-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7082_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:15:02">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=172506</link><title>Quarterback's Death, NFL Study Split Over Brain Disorder</title><description>Autopsy shows former Michigan college player had CTE; Loyola study finds no evidence that NFL...later cleared for play in a subsequent game," the college said, according to The Grand Rapids Press.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7082-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7082_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:17:53">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=105542</link><title>3 NFL Stars to Donate Brain Tissue for Trauma Research</title><description>Program studies affects of repeated blows to the head...scientists learn more about the link between brain trauma suffered by athletes and dementia later in life.The players -- Matt Birk of the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7082-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7082_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:20:17">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=168623</link><title>Plans to Penalize Non-Emergency Use of ERs Flawed: Study</title><description>Common symptoms are difficult to diagnose as mild or serious at first, researchers explain...it's unreasonable to expect the average person to know what those symptoms mean before heading to the ER,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7082-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7082_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:21:30">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=175612</link><title>Study Challenges Myths About Frequent ER Users</title><description>They're likely to have chronic health conditions, rather than mental illness or substance abuse,...addition, ER use accounts for a small portion of these patients' total Medicaid costs, found...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>