<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7083">I'm on the road again</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:22:44" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7083-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7083_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:22:46">http://www.medicinenet.com/tattoo_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Before You Tattoo Pictures Slideshow: Tattoo Types, Safety, Removal</title><description>Want to tattoo? Get the scoop on tattoo safety, tattoo risks, tattoo care, and what to expect from tattoo removal through this...Safety, Removal Reviewed by Andrew Seibert, MD on Thursday, October...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7083-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7083_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:24:54">http://www.medicinenet.com/sugar_addiction_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Healthy Eating Pictures Slideshow: The Truth About Sugar Addiction</title><description>Watch this slideshow on Sugar Addiction to see why we often crave sweets and binge on carbs. Learn how sugar affects the brain and...Reviewed by Kathleen Zelman, MPH, RD, LD on Wednesday, October...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7083-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7083_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:26:04">http://www.medicinenet.com/cycling_biking_or_bicycling/article.htm</link><title>Cycling</title><description>Bicycling is a low-impact form of cardiovascular exercise that builds endurance and tones the hips, thighs, and glutes while...a tiller. This didn't exactly catch on, and so in 1817, von Drais...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7083-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7083_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:27:25">http://www.medicinenet.com/yaws/article.htm</link><title>Yaws</title><description>Yaws is an infectious disease that mainly occurs in the tropical areas of South and Central America, Asia, Africa, and the Pacific...usually features lesions that appear as bumps on the skin of the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7083-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7083_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:30:34">http://www.medicinenet.com/concussions_brain_injuries_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Concussions &amp; Brain Injuries Pictures Slideshow: Symptoms, Tests &amp; Treatment</title><description>...head faces a harsh blow, you can experience fractures, bleeding, memory loss and more. Learn how the brain reacts and recovers...Reviewed by Charles Patrick Davis, MD, PhD on Monday, September...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7083-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7083_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:31:25">http://www.medicinenet.com/feeding_a_picky_eater_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Children's Health Pictures Slideshow: Quick Tips for Feeding a Picky Eater</title><description>Discover these Quick Tips for Feeding a Picky Eater with this slideshow. See the problems found with picky eaters and learn...Reviewed by Kathleen Zelman, MPH, RD, LD on Tuesday, December 20, 2011...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7083-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7083_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:33:28">http://www.medicinenet.com/colostomy_a_patients_perspective/article.htm</link><title>Colostomy: A Patient's Perspective</title><description>Colostomy surgery is commonly performed by severing the colon to attach the end leading to the stomach to the skin through the...possibly my fate would have been different. On October 3, 1995 I...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7083-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7083_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:34:43">http://www.medicinenet.com/anabolic_steroid_abuse/article.htm</link><title>Steroid Abuse</title><description>Anabolic steroids are synthetic substances that are related to testosterone and promote skeletal muscle growth and the development...prevented? Where can I get more information on anabolic steroid...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7083-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7083_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:36:34">http://www.onhealth.com/skin_cancer/article.htm</link><title>Skin Cancer</title><description>Skin cancer is the most common form of cancer in humans. There are three main types of skin cancer; basal cell carcinoma and...state. Treatment of nonmelanoma skin cancer depends on the type and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7083-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7083_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:39:10">http://www.medicinenet.com/running/article.htm</link><title>Running</title><description>Running is the sixth most popular exercise in the U.S. The health benefits of running include increases in HDL cholesterol and...I have? What are some other tips on buying running shoes? What type...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>