<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7085">Adam rogers music</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:07:53" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7085-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7085_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:07:54">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=51463</link><title>Mental Health: Are Kids Good for Your Health?</title><description>For a group of residents at a home for the aged, the pitter-patter of little feet does more than...seemed to improve right before our eyes. "As long as I have music, I can keep going," she said,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7085-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7085_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:08:36">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=51485</link><title>Death: Talk About Death</title><description>When a loved one is dying, how do you find the right words?...hospice workers; touch and silence become more meaningful. For Roberta's family, music remained vital. Sheldon had tried to talk to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7085-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7085_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:09:16">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=153112</link><title>Study: Music Can Ease Pain</title><description>Study: Music Can Ease Pain Music May Have the Most Benefits for the Anxiety...for years, commonly using it as a way to distract worried patients.Roger Fillingim, PhD, says the study shows it may be...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7085-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7085_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:11:18">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=170439</link><title>Designated Drivers Often Drink Themselves, Study Finds</title><description>While most abstained, 35 percent had alcohol in bloodstreams and some were legally drunk...a drink or two. But the message is clear, said study author Adam Barry, an assistant professor at the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7085-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7085_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:14:53">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=51150</link><title>Age: She's Older, He's Not</title><description>Can an older woman find love with a younger man? And can they make it last?...see a woman who was interested in buying his Arabian horse. Olivia Rogers (not her real name) was a successful doctor,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7085-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7085_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:15:34">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=51498</link><title>Gardening for Health</title><description>Can the simple pleasure of gazing on a landscape improve your health? Perhaps. A growing number of...on your wall. The Proven Power of Nature A landmark study by Roger S. Ulrich, published in the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7085-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7085_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:16:28">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=51144</link><title>Sexual Health: And Now for Something Completely Different</title><description>Cobwebs forming in your love nest? Been there, done that \-- but years ago? Don't assume sexual...is an inevitable consequence of a long-term relationship. By Jane Meredith Adams \--&gt; Their bedroom...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7085-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7085_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:19:22">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=51882</link><title>Is TV Really So Bad for Kids?</title><description>Is TV Really So Bad for Kids? Experts say it depends on what they're watching, and how much. And the...send shock waves through parents raised on Captain Kangaroo and Mr. Rogers. Violence and sexual...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7085-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7085_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:22:54">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=52032</link><title>Fitness: Few Minutes a Day Increase Fitness Level</title><description>Working out just a few minutes a day may make a difference in your fitness level. ...Power of 10: The Once-a-Week Slow Motion Fitness Revolution by Adam Zickerman and Bill Schley, and Flip the Switch:...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7085-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7085_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:26:33">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=53888</link><title>Young Adults: Relationships and Health</title><description>In this special audiocast event, Dr. Drew Pinsky, co-host of the radio show 'Loveline,' will be...a private clinical medicine practice. Dr. Drew and his Loveline partner, Adam Carolla, published their...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>