<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7095">iron in water supply</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:46:31" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7095-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7095_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:46:33">http://www.medicinenet.com/childrens_abdominal_pain_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Abdominal Pain in Children Pictures Slideshow: A 'Tummy Ache,' or Something Serious?</title><description>Watch this slideshow on Abdominal Pain in Children. See the causes and symptoms of your child's abdominal region discomfort and...soap, to more serious issues like swallowing iron pills or an...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7095-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7095_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:48:20">http://www.medicinenet.com/sources_of_indoor_air_pollution_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Home Health Pictures Slideshow: Surprising Sources of Indoor Air Pollution</title><description>Watch this slideshow on Surprising Sources of Indoor Air Pollution. Air pollution is likely worse inside your home than out. See...an exhaust fan. Instead, consider using cast iron or stainless...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7095-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7095_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:50:20">http://www.onhealth.com/congestive_heart_failure/article.htm</link><title>Congestive Heart Failure</title><description>Congestive heart failure (CHF) is a condition in which the heart's function as a pump is inadequate to meet the body's needs. A...called diastole. Diseases such as hemochromatosis (iron overload) or...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7095-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7095_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:52:02">http://www.medicinenet.com/infant_formulas/article.htm</link><title>Infant Formulas</title><description>...preferred feeding for infants, parents may consider formula-feeding if there is an inadequate supply of breast milk, the baby...have received a four- to six-month supply of these antibodies...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7095-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7095_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:56:14">http://www.medicinenet.com/liver_disease/article.htm</link><title>Liver Disease</title><description>Liver disease can be cause by a variety of things including infection (hepatitis), diseases such as gallstones, high cholesterol...and blood clotting to cholesterol, glucose and iron metabolism. A...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7095-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7095_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:59:25">http://www.medicinenet.com/breastfeeding/article.htm</link><title>Breastfeeding and Formula Feeding</title><description>It's important to know whether you will breastfeed or bottle-feed your baby prior to delivery, as the breasts' ability to produce...supplements or medications increase a low milk supply? Is it...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7095-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7095_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:00:12">http://www.medicinenet.com/blood_transfusion/article.htm</link><title>Blood Transfusion</title><description>...and donor blood (someone else's blood). There are four blood types: 1) A; 2) B; 3) C; 4) O. In addition, each person's blood is...of viruses and infectious diseases, fever, iron overload, lung...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7095-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7095_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:02:02">http://www.medicinenet.com/cycling_biking_or_bicycling/article.htm</link><title>Cycling</title><description>Bicycling is a low-impact form of cardiovascular exercise that builds endurance and tones the hips,...almost entirely of wood except for the iron tires which were positioned in a straight...up with...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7095-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7095_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:02:42">http://www.medterms.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=38692</link><title>Breastfeeding practices</title><description>...iron stores or anemia). Fluoride should not be administered to infants during the first 6 months after birth, whether they are breast- or formula-fed. During the period from 6 months to 3 years of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7095-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7095_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:05:22">http://www.medterms.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=12468</link><title>Vitamin B2</title><description>...B2 is riboflavin. Vitamin B2 is a water-soluble vitamin, one that cannot be stored...body. Its role in maintaining an energy supply for the body is crucial, for it...and antibodies. 2. Absorption...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>