<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7105">dark knight rises dvd</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:27:46" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7105-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7105_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:27:48">http://www.medicinenet.com/bad_bugs_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Bad Bugs Pictures Slideshow: Identify Bugs and Their Bites</title><description>Through this slideshow of bad bugs and insect pictures, learn how to identify bug bites from mosquitos, bees, spiders, bed bugs,...and spasms, abdominal pain, tremors, weakness, or a rise in blood...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7105-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7105_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:30:57">http://www.medicinenet.com/kidney_stone_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Kidney Stone Pictures Slideshow</title><description>Kidney stones? Learn to recognize the symptoms and signs of kidney stones through pictures and find...and they occur more frequently in men. The prevalence of kidney stones rises dramatically as men...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7105-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7105_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:33:00">http://www.medicinenet.com/uveitis/article.htm</link><title>Uveitis</title><description>...eye redness, photophobia, and floaters. Treatment may involve prescription eyedrops, antibiotics, and wearing dark glasses...colored ring of tissue you can see in the mirror. The dark hole in the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7105-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7105_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:33:56">http://www.onhealth.com/primary_biliary_cirrhosis/article.htm</link><title>Primary Biliary Cirrhosis</title><description>Primary Biliary Cirrhosis is a chronic disease characterized by progressive inflammation and destruction of small bile ducts...tend not to occur until the serum cholesterol rises to very high levels,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7105-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7105_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:37:24">http://www.medicinenet.com/summer_skin_hazards_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Skin Pictures Slideshow: Summer Skin Hazards</title><description>Don't let spider bites, sunburn, poison ivy, chigger bites, and jellyfish stings sabotage your...a nodule at the bite site. Muscle cramps, nausea, vomiting, seizure, and rise in blood pressure may...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7105-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7105_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:42:14">http://www.medicinenet.com/diabetic_peripheral_neuropathy_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Diabetic Peripheral Neuropathy Slideshow: Exercises to Improve Diabetes Nerve Pain</title><description>Watch this slideshow on Diabetic Peripheral Neuropathy. Learn how to improve your balance and see ideas for exercises that help...or other object for support. Slowly rise up onto the balls of both...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7105-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7105_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:43:44">http://www.medicinenet.com/mucormycosis/article.htm</link><title>Mucormycosis</title><description>Mucormycosis (zygomycosis) is a fungal infection caused by Zygomycetes. Symptoms and signs include fever, headache, coughing,...reddish and swollen skin over nose and sinuses, dark scabbing in nose by...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7105-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7105_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:45:13">http://www.onhealth.com/jaundice/article.htm</link><title>Jaundice</title><description>Jaundice is a yellowish staining of the skin and whites of the eyes (sclerae) with bilirubin, the pigment found in bile. Jaundice...gives stool its brown color. The urine may turn dark or brownish in...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7105-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7105_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:46:30">http://www.medicinenet.com/swimming/article.htm</link><title>Swimming</title><description>Swimming is a low-impact form of exercise that's easy on the joints, builds cardiorespiratory fitness and muscle mass, and is an...also reports that swimming was required of knights and that Romans...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7105-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7105_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:49:04">http://www.medicinenet.com/diet_plans_and_programs/article.htm</link><title>Diet Plans &amp; Programs</title><description>Popular weight loss and diet plans include the Atkins diet, Jenny Craig, Zone diet, Weight Watchers,...carbohydrates than we did 10 years ago, and obesity is on the rise. This is half true. We consume...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>