<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7108">renting car seattle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:25:24" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7108-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7108_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:25:25">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=50579</link><title>The BTK Killer: Portrait of a Psychopath</title><description>Experts say the dispassionate confession of serial killer Dennis Rader is typical of psychopaths...says Jacqueline Helfgott, an associate professor of criminal justice at Seattle University in...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7108-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7108_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:27:20">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=54698</link><title>Rip Currents: Danger at the Beach</title><description>Headed to the beach this summer? Did you know that according to the U.S. Lifesaving Association, rip currents along the beach...For example, you might have to pay $8 to park your car near the beach in...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7108-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7108_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:30:09">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=166060</link><title>Texting While Walking May Be as Dangerous as Texting While Driving</title><description>Study found many use cell phones when crossing streets, which puts them at risk for accidents...busy streets, which could increase their chances of being hit by a car, a new study says.Distracted...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7108-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7108_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:33:44">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=169886</link><title>Cancer Patients May Face Higher Bankruptcy Odds</title><description>Washington state study found a nearly tripled risk, with younger adults most vulnerable...and technical project coordinator at the Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center, in Seattle. Whether people...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7108-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7108_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:34:39">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=52515</link><title>How to Avoid the Pitfalls of Memorial Day</title><description>With Memorial Day serving as the unofficial start to the celebrated season of sun, you want to make...by summer weekend," says Lola O'Rourke, a registered dietitian in Seattle. "If you're grilling,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7108-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7108_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:35:24">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=51068</link><title>Mental Illness: When Cops Confront Mental Illness</title><description>A trend away from institutionalization means more emotionally disturbed people are on the streets...a suspect who is emotionally disturbed. "The typical robber or car thief wants to live to see...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7108-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7108_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:38:47">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=176822</link><title>Too Much Sitting After 60 May Lead to Disability, Study Says</title><description>For each extra sedentary hour per day, researchers found a 50 percent increased risk...also an affiliate investigator at the Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center, in Seattle.The take-home message,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7108-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7108_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:39:42">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=177252</link><title>Timing Is Key to Massage's Benefits for Neck Pain: Study</title><description>Two or three one-hour sessions a week reduced pain, improved functioning...researcher Karen Sherman, senior scientific investigator at Group Health Research Institute in Seattle."In the short term, 60...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7108-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7108_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:41:51">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=51999</link><title>Men in Love</title><description>What do men need to keep the relationship strong? Learn the secrets to success from the Love Doc. ...and clinical director of The Gottman Institute, a Seattle-based couples-counseling center, discussed...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7108-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7108_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:46:12">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=50843</link><title>Exhausted? Stressed-Out?</title><description>Then simplify. More and more Americans are finding that scaling back may be the key to better health...the badges of success: the Jeep Cherokee, the Nissan 300 ZX sports car, the Cadillac...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>