<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7109">best place to eat pho in new york</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:47:16" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7109-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7109_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:47:18">http://www.medicinenet.com/foods_for_healthy_skin_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Skin and Beauty Pictures Slideshow: Best Foods for Healthy Skin</title><description>Foods for Healthy Skin Picture Slideshow. Eat your way to healthy, vibrant skin with super foods that contain Vitamin A,...and Beauty Pictures Slideshow: Best Foods for Healthy Skin...skin diet.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7109-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7109_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:50:51">http://www.medicinenet.com/easy_tasty_grilled_foods_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Healthy Eating Pictures Slideshow: Easy, Tasty Grilled Foods for Dinner Tonight</title><description>Watch this slideshow to see Easy and Tasty Grilled Foods. When your rushed to get dinner on the table, fire up the grill and use...the fish firmly in place, so they're easy...chunks for kebabs. The...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7109-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7109_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:53:24">http://www.medicinenet.com/alzheimers_disease_causes_stages_and_symptoms/article.htm</link><title>Alzheimer's Disease</title><description>Alzheimer's disease is a common cause of dementia. Symptoms and warning signs of Alzheimer's disease include memory loss,...problems with language, disorientation to time and place, poor or decreased...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7109-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7109_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:58:25">http://www.medicinenet.com/jet_lag/article.htm</link><title>Jet Lag</title><description>Jet lag (desynchonosis) is a temporary disorder that results from travel across time zones. Symptoms include anxiety,...last? What are the best ways to cope with...zone. Thus, when a New Yorker...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7109-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7109_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:02:39">http://www.medicinenet.com/depression/article.htm</link><title>Depression</title><description>Depression is an illness that involves the body, mood, and thoughts and affects the way a person eats and sleeps, the way one...interfere with the ability to work, sleep, eat, and enjoy...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7109-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7109_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:04:43">http://www.medicinenet.com/huntington_disease/article.htm</link><title>Huntington's Disease</title><description>Huntington's disease is the result of degeneration of neurons in areas of the brain. Huntington's disease is an inherited disorder...of the disorder. These cases are thought to be caused by a new...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7109-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7109_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:06:09">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=46692</link><title>Exercise For Seniors</title><description>...doing? What should I eat? Target heart rate Exercise...exercise in a public place or use expensive equipment...until recently. Today a new picture is emerging from...you can. It's best to increase...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7109-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7109_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:06:57">http://www.medicinenet.com/mistakes_new_parents_make_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Parenting Pictures Slideshow: 10 Mistakes New Parents Make</title><description>Watch this slideshow on 10 Mistakes New Parents Make. Learn how to prevent these common parenting mistakes dealing with...Parenting Pictures Slideshow: 10 Mistakes New Parents Make Reviewed by...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7109-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7109_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:08:55">http://www.medicinenet.com/exercise_during_pregnancy_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Pregnancy Pictures Slideshow: Exercise During Pregnancy</title><description>Should you exercise during pregnancy. Watch this slideshow to learn about which prenatal workouts and health tips can help you...stay healthy and feel your best. Regular exercise during pregnancy...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7109-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7109_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:11:43">http://www.medicinenet.com/skin_cancer_melanoma_quiz/quiz.htm</link><title>Skin Cancer (Melanoma) Quiz: Test Your Skin IQ</title><description>What causes skin cancer? Take our Skin Cancer Quiz to learn about the risks, symptoms, causes, and treatments for this common skin...many melanomas. About 50,000 new cases of melanoma are diagnosed...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>