<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7119">chocolate photo</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:58:47" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7119-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7119_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:58:48">http://www.medicinenet.com/brain_foods_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Food Pictures Slideshow: Brain Foods That Help You Concentrate</title><description>Learn how to increase concentration and boost memory by watching this photo slideshow on brain foods such as fish (omega 3 fatty...you and help you concentrate. Found in coffee, chocolate, energy...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7119-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7119_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:01:35">http://www.medicinenet.com/healthy_eating_pictures_slideshow_portion_control/article.htm</link><title>Healthy Eating Pictures Slideshow: Secrets of Portion Control</title><description>Practicing portion control which can help you lose weight and eat a healthy diet. But how much is...fruit or milk with one cookie instead of several cookies. Choose dark chocolate to satisfy a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7119-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7119_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:04:34">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=77555</link><title>Stress: How to Sleep When Stressed</title><description>...or comforter in a soothing color. Create a welcoming environment with flowers, photos, pictures, candles-whatever makes you feel content and relaxed. Avoid use of...Finally, don't consume...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7119-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7119_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:08:18">http://www.onhealth.com/canker_sores_health/article.htm</link><title>Canker Sores</title><description>Canker sores (aphthous stomatitis) are among the most common causes of sores in the mouth. Causes of canker sores include...as atenolol [Tenormin]) food allergies or sensitivities (chocolate,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7119-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7119_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:11:18">http://www.medicinenet.com/adult_acne_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Acne Pictures Slideshow: Causes, Solutions and Treatments for Adults</title><description>Watch this slideshow on Adult Acne. See popular questions and answers on treatment, causes and...pimples. This always produces a poor result. What's the Truth About Chocolate and Acne? There is no...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7119-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7119_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:14:56">http://www.medicinenet.com/migraine_headaches_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Headache Pictures Slideshow: A Visual Guide to Migraine Headaches</title><description>Do you suffer from migraine headaches? Watch this slideshow to learn about the many different symptoms, triggers, and treatments...cited by patients are red wine, cheese, chocolate, soy sauce,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7119-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7119_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:17:06">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=77427</link><title>At a Loss for Words</title><description>...time to time, I take out our family photo album and flip through the pages, looking for some sort of sign that we missed at the time. But, all I see is a smiling boy digging his hands in a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7119-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7119_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:20:34">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=50648</link><title>Lighten Up</title><description>Did you hear the one about the scientists who said laughter is good for your heart?...improve your sense of humor on your own, Miller says: Place a photo of a family event that makes you smile or...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7119-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7119_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:21:49">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=76866</link><title>Fast Food: A Nighttime Trend?</title><description>Dietitians say late-night trips to the local drive-through may have an impact on our waistlines...night run per week for a small hamburger, medium fries, and a chocolate shake, you've boosted your...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7119-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7119_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:23:17">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=54021</link><title>Pilates Body Conditioning Techniques</title><description>Personal trainer, fitness instructor and author Brooke Siler will discuss her views on the Pilates...biggest proponent of learning from a magazine. The positions are what a photo editor has chosen.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>