<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7126">alicia keys brand new me lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:21:33" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7126-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7126_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:21:34">http://www.medicinenet.com/skin_and_beauty_antiaging_tips_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Skin and Beauty Pictures Slideshow: Antiaging Tips &amp; Secrets to Look Younger</title><description>...See before and after pictures of how real women can take years off their looks with new tricks, artful makeup, and the right skin...actual eye. Eyeliner is the key. Apply it in a thin..</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7126-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7126_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:23:58">http://www.medicinenet.com/flu_vaccination/article.htm</link><title>Flu Vaccine (Flu Shot)</title><description>Every year in the United States, on average; 5% to 20% of the population gets the flu, more than 200,000 people are hospitalized...Can the flu vaccine give me the flu? What should I...of the genes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7126-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7126_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:26:31">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=53748</link><title>Parenting: Welcome to Parenthood</title><description>Welcome to the New Parent club! Now what? Ann Douglas, author of The Mother of All Baby Books, answered that little question when...Events Transcript Welcome to the New Parent club! Now what? Ann..</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7126-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7126_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:29:11">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=50454</link><title>Cereal: Restaurant Serves Cereal All Day</title><description>New cafe featuring flakes and O's could be latest healthy fast-food fare...New Restaurant Serves Cereal All Day...choose from more than 30 brand-name cereals and a multitude...ways include the Devil...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7126-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7126_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:30:39">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=54512</link><title>Breast Cancer, Metastatic: Treatment Goals and Therapy Options -- Harold J. Burstein, MD</title><description>...will best allow you to reach your goals? We covered these issues and more when WebMD and the Y-ME National Breast Cancer...when WebMD and the Y-ME National Breast Cancer Organization presented..</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7126-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7126_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:33:36">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=54444</link><title>Exercise: Get Going and Keep Going -- Meg Jordan, PhD, RN. -- 01/21/03</title><description>With another new year comes another chance to create a new you. But if gyms and the buff people who go there intimidate you, or...Live Events Transcript With another new year comes another chance...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7126-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7126_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:37:38">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=56127</link><title>IBS: What Can I Eat?</title><description>...learn to eat well with WebMD's "Recipe Doctor," Elaine Magee, MPH, RD, author of Tell Me What to Eat If I Have IBS. She joined us...MPH, RD, author of Tell Me What to Eat If I...grains, beans,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7126-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7126_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:39:00">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=55787</link><title>Menopause: Change of Life, Change of Diet</title><description>...says you should include how and what you eat in those changes. She's written about it in her new book, The Change of Life Diet and...written about it in her new book, The Change of Life..</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7126-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7126_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:42:38">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=154640</link><title>More People Need Training in Lifesaving Epinephrine Use, Advocates Say</title><description>Parents, educators, caregivers, friends can respond to severe food allergies...a severe peanut allergy, the New Albany, Ohio, mother got trained...carry a 'trainer pen' with me and have them practice...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7126-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7126_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:45:46">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=165476</link><title>Harmful Bacteria Found in Samples of U.S. Pork</title><description>...Consumer Reports study shows. The new report also found traces of...came from many major store brands. Some carried misleading and unapproved...animals is one of the key drivers of antibiotic...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>