<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7128">where to donate clothes in nyc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:13:02" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7128-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7128_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:13:03">http://www.medicinenet.com/breastfeeding_common_breastfeeding_challenges/article.htm</link><title>Breastfeeding: Common Breastfeeding Challenges</title><description>Breastfeeding an infant can cause common challenges both for the mother an infant. Some challenges include sore nipples, low milk...you are thinking about using creams, hydrogel pads, or a nipple...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7128-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7128_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:16:59">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=77931</link><title>Trans Fats Banned in NYC</title><description>NYC Bans Trans FatsMedical Author: Melissa Conrad Stöppler, MD Medical Editor: William C. Shiel, JR, MD, FACP, FACR On December 5, 2006, the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7128-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7128_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:18:04">http://www.medicinenet.com/staph_infection_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Staph Infection Pictures Slideshow: Symptoms, Causes, Treatment and Prevention Tips</title><description>Learn about staph infections (Staphylococcus aureus) and learn about causes, symptoms and treatment on how this group of bacteria...for example, towels, washcloth, razor, clothing, or uniforms)...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7128-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7128_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:20:44">http://www.medicinenet.com/skin_pictures_child_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Skin Pictures Slideshow: Childhood Skin Problems</title><description>Watch and learn about skin conditions often seen in babies and children. Read how to recognize these common childhood conditions...scaly and bumpy red patch to form on the infected area. It is...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7128-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7128_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:25:15">http://www.medicinenet.com/heat_rash_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Heat Rash Pictures Slideshow: Symptoms, Causes &amp; Treatments</title><description>...on Heat Rash (prickly heat) which develops when the skin sweat ducts become blocked causing symptoms of red bumps often leading to...made by physical examination. Knowing that the rash appears...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7128-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7128_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:26:04">http://www.medicinenet.com/smoking_quiz/quiz.htm</link><title>Smoking Quiz: Test Your Medical IQ</title><description>...and facts about quitting smoking with the Smoking Quiz. When it comes to smoking, quitters always...Once you've smoked your last cigarette, toss all of your ashtrays and lighters. Wash any clothes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7128-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7128_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:28:53">http://www.medicinenet.com/image-collection/crabs_pubic_lice_picture/picture.htm</link><title>Picture of Crabs (Pubic Lice)</title><description>Parasitic insects found in the genital area of humans. See a picture of Crabs (Pubic Lice) and learn...spread through contact with an infested person's bed linens, towels, or clothes. A common...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7128-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7128_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:31:18">http://www.medicinenet.com/7_tips_less_holiday_travel_stress_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Holiday Travel Pictures Slideshow: 7 Tips to Make it Less Stressful</title><description>...and post-holiday travel dates compound the stress. Watch this slideshow for tips on how to reduce holiday travel stress...You can also dress in layers which can be removed if necessary. If you...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7128-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7128_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:35:04">http://www.medicinenet.com/heat_rash/article.htm</link><title>Heat Rash</title><description>Heat rash is a skin irritation caused by excessive sweating. It can occur at any age and it appears as a rash that itches or feels...humid conditions, wearing lose fitting clothes and using air...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7128-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7128_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:36:40">http://www.medicinenet.com/heat_stroke/article.htm</link><title>Heat Stroke</title><description>...stroke is a true medical emergency that can be fatal if not promptly and properly treated. Symptoms of heat stroke include: high...excessively or perform vigorous activity in the sunlight for...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>