<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7129">avg home edition</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:39:46" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7129-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7129_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:39:47">http://www.medicinenet.com/childhood_illness_symptoms_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Children's Health Pictures Slideshow: Symptoms of Common Infant and Childhood Illnesses</title><description>Watch this slideshow to see common symptoms and home treatment for infant and childhood illnesses...drinking too much fruit juice. Until diarrhea stops, keep your child at home and hydrated. If...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7129-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7129_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:40:58">http://www.medicinenet.com/shingles_picture_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Shingles Pictures Slideshow: A Collection of Photos on Shingles</title><description>Shingles (herpes zoster virus) is a painful, contagious rash caused by the Varicella zoster virus. Watch this slideshow to see...take a look at both conventional medicine and home self-care remedies...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7129-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7129_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:42:04">http://www.medicinenet.com/schizoaffective_disorder/article.htm</link><title>Schizoaffective Disorder</title><description>Schizoaffective disorder is a mental illness that features schizophrenia and a mood disorder, either major depression or bipolar...and Statistical Manual of Mental Disorders, fifth edition (DSM-V), in...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7129-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7129_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:43:34">http://www.medicinenet.com/munchausen_syndrome_by_proxy/article.htm</link><title>Munchausen Syndrome by Proxy</title><description>Munchausen syndrome by proxy (MSBP) is a mental illness (factitious disorder) in which a caregiver secretly abuses a child by...and Statistical Manual of Mental Disorders, fourth edition, treatment...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7129-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7129_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:44:27">http://www.medicinenet.com/childrens_health_illnesses_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Slideshow: Children's Health - Childhood Illnesses Every Parent Should Know</title><description>View this slideshow on 24 childhood illnesses that parents be aware of. Know what to look for and when to call the doctor for...Most children with croup can be treated at home, but occasionally, when...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7129-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7129_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:47:49">http://www.medicinenet.com/hyperhidrosis_sweating_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Hyperhidrosis (Sweating) Pictures Slideshow: What Makes You Sweat</title><description>Watch this slideshow on Hyperhidrosis (sweating). From exercise to fever, see the reasons you...Lippincott Williams &amp; Wilkins, 2006.Medscape Medical News.Merck Manual Home Edition.Murphy, S. Run...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7129-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7129_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:48:20">http://www.medicinenet.com/attention_deficit_hyperactivity_disorder_in_teens/article.htm</link><title>Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD) in Teens</title><description>Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) in teens is a disruption of neurocognitive functioning. Genetics contribute to...found in the Diagnostic and Statistical Manual 4th Edition (DSM-IV).</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7129-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7129_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:51:01">http://www.medicinenet.com/borderline_personality_disorder/article.htm</link><title>Borderline Personality Disorder</title><description>Borderline personality disorder is a serious mental illness characterized by pervasive instability in moods, interpersonal...a safe environment, while allowing the sufferer to go home each evening.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7129-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7129_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:53:11">http://www.medterms.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=24405</link><title>Substance abuse</title><description>...abuse that is frequently cited is that in DSM-IV, the fourth edition of the Diagnostic and Statistical Manual of Mental Disorders (DSM) issued by...in a failure to fulfill major role obligations at...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7129-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7129_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:57:55">http://www.medicinenet.com/head_injury_symptoms/views.htm</link><title>Head Injury Symptoms</title><description>...CT scan to look for brain bleeding or injury. The February 2009 edition of the Annals of Emergency Medicine contained an article that compared six...was safe to reassure the patient and family and...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>