<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7131">golf games</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:01:17" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7131-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7131_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:01:18">http://www.medicinenet.com/parenting_pictures_slideshow_fitness_and_exercise/article.htm</link><title>Parenting Pictures Slideshow: Fitness and Exercise</title><description>Parenting your child's fitness and exercise habits. Take steps towards encouraging a healthy level...Look for water aerobics classes at local swimming pools and golf lessons at golf courses. Get the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7131-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7131_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:02:04">http://www.medicinenet.com/osteoarthritis_active_with_kids_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Osteoarthritis Pictures Slideshow: Stay Active With Kids and Don't Let Arthritis Stop You</title><description>Watch this slideshow on how to have fun with children while having arthritis. See ways to spend time with your kids or grandkids...or share an active hobby, such as swimming, golf, dancing, or...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7131-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7131_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:06:08">http://www.medicinenet.com/parenting/article.htm</link><title>Parenting</title><description>Good parenting helps foster empathy, honesty, self-reliance, self-control, kindness, cooperation, and cheerfulness, says...game of Frisbee. Make use of community resources. When it comes to finding...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7131-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7131_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:08:28">http://www.medicinenet.com/pilates/article.htm</link><title>Pilates</title><description>Pilates was created in the 1920s by Joseph Pilates for the purpose of rehabilitation. It improves flexibility, strength, and body...Claim #11. Improves performance in sports (golf, skiing, skating,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7131-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7131_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:12:10">http://www.medicinenet.com/eyewear_guide_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Eye Health Pictures Slideshow: Your Eyewear Guide for Vision, Sport &amp; Fashion</title><description>Watch this slideshow on eye health. Learn about your eye care needs and fashion wishes \-- with eye...gradual shift in strength -- invisible to your younger co-workers. Risky Games: Polycarbonate...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7131-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7131_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:14:27">http://www.medicinenet.com/18_secrets_men_want_you_to_know_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Healthy Relationships Pictures Slideshow: 18 Secrets Men Want You to Know</title><description>Watch this slideshow on 18 secrets men want you to know from sex to love to marriage...are important, men also need time for themselves. Whether your guy enjoys golf, gardening, or working out at the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7131-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7131_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:17:21">http://www.medicinenet.com/tween_child_development/article.htm</link><title>Tween: Child Development</title><description>Developmental milestones for tweens 9-11 years of age include the ability to use deductive reasoning to anticipate consequences,...encouragement and exploring nontraditional sports (golf, martial arts,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7131-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7131_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:21:08">http://www.medicinenet.com/asthma_complexities/article.htm</link><title>Asthma Complexities</title><description>There are many unusual symptoms of asthma, including sighing, difficulty sleeping, anxiety, chronic cough, recurrent walking...becomes breathless shortly after her soccer games and coughs on a cold...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7131-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7131_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:24:43">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=90064</link><title>Wii Exercise Games: Can You Really Get Fit?</title><description>...at everyone, says Nintendo. The company created the video exercise game to go with its original Wii console, which boasts virtual games of tennis, bowling, baseball, boxing, and golf. You need to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7131-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7131_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:27:17">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=50457</link><title>Exergaming: Exercise, Lose Weight, With Video Game</title><description>As the beeps and whistles emanate from the family room, are you afraid Junior is going to develop...Golf Launchpad In this one, back off, kiddies, you use your own golf clubs to play 800 of the...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>