<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7133">museum of natural history</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:49:42" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7133-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7133_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:49:43">http://www.medterms.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=40332</link><title>Mead, Margaret</title><description>...for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) and taught at a number of institutions, but her long term professional base was at the American Museum of Natural History in New York City</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7133-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7133_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:51:01">http://www.medicinenet.com/anthrax_-_from_russia_with_love/views.htm</link><title>Anthrax - From Russia with Love</title><description>...the deadliest outbreak of anthrax in recorded history. Anthrax is a bacterium (germ) that can...patient with anthrax on display in a museum at her medical school. The Cover-upAlthough...nature of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7133-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7133_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:53:12">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=50974</link><title>Safety: Snakes Not So Charming in the Wild</title><description>The message is simple: When hiking, don't mess with things that slither...on the guest list. King, the curator of herpetology -- the scientific field that studies amphibians and reptiles -- at the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7133-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7133_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:56:26">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=53906</link><title>Poison Prevention: Children Act Fast ... So Do Poisons with Paige Cucchi, MSPH and Robert Geller,</title><description>National Poison Prevention Week: Children act fast ... so do poisons! Talk with the experts from the...age groups and awarded those prizes at a Poison Prevention Week kickoff luncheon, held on Monday...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7133-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7133_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:59:48">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=155202</link><title>Earliest Known Horse Shrank Due to Warming Planet: Report</title><description>Analysis of fossilized teeth reveals new evidence of link between mammals' body size and global temps...temperatures in the near future, according to study leaders Ross Secord of the University of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7133-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7133_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:03:08">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=115660</link><title>Restaurant Sushi May Have More Mercury Than Store-Bought Fare</title><description>Toxin concentrations higher in certain tuna species versus others, study finds...to specific species," Jacob Lowenstein, a graduate student working with the American Museum of Natural History in New York...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7133-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7133_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:04:32">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=92998</link><title>How to Grade the Presidential Debates</title><description>...As the presidential debates get under way, history suggests what the candidates say may not...sound unrehearsed. Rhythm and pacing should be natural, "like they're having a conversation." Speech..</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>