<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7134">history of yoga</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:05:10" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7134-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7134_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:05:11">http://www.medicinenet.com/exercise_during_pregnancy_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Pregnancy Pictures Slideshow: Exercise During Pregnancy</title><description>...which prenatal workouts and health tips can help you stay healthy and feel your best, including aerobics, yoga, kegels and more...recurrent miscarriage Previous premature births or history of early...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7134-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7134_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:07:55">http://www.medicinenet.com/celebrities_with_migraines_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Migraine Headaches Pictures Slideshow: Celebrities With Migraines</title><description>...this slideshow on Celebrities with Migraine Headaches. See how these famous celebs, who have a history with migraines, cope with...75% chance of having migraines if their parents do. Knowing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7134-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7134_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:09:16">http://www.medicinenet.com/yoga/article.htm</link><title>Yoga</title><description>Yoga is an activity that improves muscles strength and flexibility while centering your thoughts and relaxing you. The practice...centers your thoughts, and relaxes and calms you. Yoga does all that...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7134-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7134_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:12:48">http://www.onhealth.com/asthma/article.htm</link><title>Asthma</title><description>...hyperreactive airways constrict and result in symptoms like wheezing, coughing, and shortness of breath. Causes of asthma include...soul and breath as part of the mind, body, and spirit...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7134-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7134_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:13:29">http://www.medicinenet.com/high_blood_pressure_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>High Blood Pressure (Hypertension) Pictures Slideshow: Symptoms, Causes and Treatments</title><description>View a slideshow on high blood pressure (hypertension). See inside the arteries and learn causes,...they are overweight, are African-American, or if they have a family history of the condition.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7134-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7134_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:15:40">http://www.medicinenet.com/endometriosis_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Endometriosis Pictures Slideshow: A Visual Guide to Symptoms, Stages and Treatments</title><description>Learn about the causes, symptoms, stages, tests and treatments of endometriosis including pain,...have short menstrual cycles (shorter than 28 days) Who have a family history (mother or sister) of the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7134-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7134_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:17:52">http://www.medicinenet.com/pilates/article.htm</link><title>Pilates</title><description>Pilates was created in the 1920s by Joseph Pilates for the purpose of rehabilitation. It improves flexibility, strength, and body...and more in this article. What is the origin of Pilates? Admittedly,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7134-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7134_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:19:07">http://www.medicinenet.com/menstrual_cramps_and_pms_medication_guide/article.htm</link><title>Menstrual Cramps and Premenstrual Syndrome (PMS) Medication Guide</title><description>...cramps and premenstrual syndrome (PMS) symptoms include abdominal cramping, bloating, a feeling of fullness, abdominal pain, mood...with heavy menstrual flow. Smoking and a family history of severe...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7134-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7134_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:21:35">http://www.medicinenet.com/tai_chi/article.htm</link><title>Tai Chi</title><description>Tai chi is an ancient Chinese martial art that was designed for self-defense and to promote inner peace. Tai chi has been shown to...and calm. In this article, we will cover the history, philosophy,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7134-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7134_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:24:25">http://www.medicinenet.com/fibromyalgia_facts/article.htm</link><title>Fibromyalgia</title><description>Fibromyalgia is a chronic pain condition characterized by symptoms such as fatigue, sleep disturbances, and tender points. Stress...Because it is in part hereditary, a family history of fibromyalgia...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>