<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7144">can headphones cause hearing loss</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:49:07" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7144-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7144_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:49:08">http://www.medicinenet.com/tinnitus_ringing_ears_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Tinnitus Pictures Slideshow: Why Are My Ears Ringing?</title><description>Learn causes, symptoms, relief remedies, treatments and prevention tips for Tinnitus (ringing in the...resolves. Rarely, however, tinnitus can represent a serious medical...these background sounds...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7144-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7144_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:51:51">http://www.medicinenet.com/mens_embarrassing_body_problem_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Men's Health Pictures Slideshow: Embarrassing Male Body Problems</title><description>See embarrassing body problems for men such as belly fat, back hair, sweating, erectile dysfunction,...removal creams, or shaving can rid you of your...male hormone, is what causes men to have more..</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7144-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7144_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:53:14">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=117412</link><title>MP3 Players Might Harm Hearing</title><description>Prolonged listening at loud volume may lead to temporary and later irreversible loss, experts say...to temporary changes in hearing, which over time might...result in permanent hearing loss, Belgian...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7144-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7144_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:56:32">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=175334</link><title>Parents Clueless About Dangers of iPods, Other Noise Hazards: Study</title><description>Hearing loss is up among teens, but Mom and Dad aren't sounding alarms...some degree of preventable hearing loss, but few parents warn...concerts are a common cause of noise overdose, as...and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7144-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7144_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:59:53">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=56186</link><title>Heart Health: Choose to Move for a Healthy Heart</title><description>Heart disease is a leading killer of women. But there are things you can do to reduce your risk. Joan Lunden, an award-winning...Joan Lunden WebMD Weight Loss Clinic - Live Events Transcript..</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7144-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7144_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:03:53">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=78018</link><title>Exercise Music: Tunes to Get Fit By</title><description>Want to have more fun and work out harder? Exercise with music, experts say...Russi Sarnataro WebMD Weight Loss Clinic - Feature Reviewed By...s not that music causes you to lose weight...Capuano...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>