<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7146">why do leaves fall</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:09:34" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7146-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7146_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:09:35">http://www.medicinenet.com/bad_bugs_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Bad Bugs Pictures Slideshow: Identify Bugs and Their Bites</title><description>Through this slideshow of bad bugs and insect pictures, learn how to identify bug bites from mosquitos, bees, spiders, bed bugs,...in the U.S. do not spread disease, but their bites can cause intense...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7146-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7146_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:11:47">http://www.medicinenet.com/ways_to_wreck_your_skin_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Skin and Beauty Pictures Slideshow: 12 Ways to Wreck Your Skin</title><description>See 12 Ways to Wreck Your Skin with this slideshow. Learn how sun damage, smoking, overeating and...The following slides show what not to do." * 1. Get Overexposed "There was a time...to permanent...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7146-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7146_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:13:08">http://www.medicinenet.com/allergies_quiz/quiz.htm</link><title>Allergies Quiz: Test Your Medical IQ</title><description>What are the causes of allergies? This online quiz challenges your knowledge of common food and household allergens, environmental...on the tissue. In other words, antihistamines do not stop the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7146-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7146_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:14:17">http://www.medicinenet.com/summer_skin_hazards_pictures_quiz/quiz.htm</link><title>Summer Skin Hazards: Test Your Visual IQ</title><description>When it comes to summer, there plenty of hazards under the sun! Take the Summer Skin Hazards Quiz...use tick repellant. ', this, event)"&gt; MosquitoesMosquitoes typically do not cause significant...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7146-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7146_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:17:27">http://www.medicinenet.com/7_tips_less_holiday_travel_stress_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Holiday Travel Pictures Slideshow: 7 Tips to Make it Less Stressful</title><description>Travel during the holidays can be a very stressful process. Loaded with gifts, baggage, kids and possible wintry weather, crowded...departing, and have some backup ideas ready (leave earlier, leave...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7146-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7146_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:21:44">http://www.medicinenet.com/autism_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Autism Pictures Slideshow: Symptoms, Diagnosis and Treatment</title><description>Watch this slideshow on Autism. See an overview on this brain disorder found in children that interferes with their ability to...are often screened if they seem to fall behind age-related...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7146-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7146_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:23:36">http://www.onhealth.com/liver_cancer/article.htm</link><title>Liver Cancer</title><description>...are at the greatest risk of developing liver cancer. Many patients with liver cancer do not develop symptoms until the advanced...and HCC. Many patients with liver cancer do not develop...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7146-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7146_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:26:23">http://www.medicinenet.com/broken_finger/article.htm</link><title>Broken Finger</title><description>...are a traumatic injury to the finger or fingers such as playing sports, injury in the workplace, falls, and accidents. Treatment...punching something, falls, or in other accidents. The main...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7146-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7146_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:27:48">http://www.medicinenet.com/low_blood_pressure/article.htm</link><title>Low Blood Pressure</title><description>...enough oxygen and nutrients to vital organs such as the brain, heart, and kidneys; the organs do not function normally and may be...systolic blood pressure for most healthy adults falls between 90...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7146-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7146_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:28:40">http://www.medicinenet.com/indoor_allergens/article.htm</link><title>Indoor Allergens</title><description>Indoor allergens are substances that can cause an allergic reaction in some people. Common sources of indoor allergens include...are most favorable to dust mites? How do dust mites cause allergic...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>