<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7155">ted talk mooc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:32:48" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7155-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7155_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:32:49">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=105070</link><title>Senator Ted Kennedy, a Legend Dies of Brain Cancer</title><description>Senator Ted Kennedy, a Legend Dies of Brain Cancer Medical Author: Benjamin C Wedro...longer speak for themselves. That means that patients and families need to talk about topics that are...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7155-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7155_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:35:36">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=52253</link><title>Motivating the Overweight Child</title><description>Encouraging an overweight child to exercise can be a tricky situation...s school of public health. Age-appropriate Exercise Here are some suggestions Ted Ganley, MD, orthopaedic director of sports...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7155-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7155_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:39:33">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=54315</link><title>Krabbe's Disease</title><description>Jim Kelly, former Buffalo Bills quarterback and current ESPN golf and sailing commentator, will...one so far. The child cannot walk right now, but can smile, talk... a lot of things other children...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7155-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7155_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:40:34">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=89657</link><title>Sen. Ted Kennedy Has Brain Cancer</title><description>Sen. Ted Kennedy Has Brain Cancer Doctors Diagnose Kennedy With Malignant Brain Tumor By...the tumor because it is what we call an infiltrating tumor. We talk about rootlets or tentacles of tumor that...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7155-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7155_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:43:26">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=51566</link><title>When the Diagnosis is Serious</title><description>A serious diagnosis, hard enough to cope with in itself, presents another challenge for families \--...of the lymph system. A few hours later when Harpham's husband Ted returned home from the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7155-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7155_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:46:21">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=54008</link><title>Sibling Rivalry: Truth About the Family Favorite</title><description>Dr. Vera Rabie-Azoory discusses his views on sibling rivalry and parental favoritism...verbal skills. If a girl, for example, has a lot of sweet talk and gentle words to use with us, that's pleasing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7155-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7155_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:47:41">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=163083</link><title>Obesity Surgery Seems to Reduce Heart Risks, Study Says</title><description>Diabetes remission, lower blood pressure and cholesterol levels noted after 6 years...percent, which shows a pretty durable weight loss," said study lead author Ted Adams, an adjunct associate...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>