<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7173"> severed spinal cord</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:50:44" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7173-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7173_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:50:45">http://www.medicinenet.com/chronic_pain/article.htm</link><title>Chronic Pain</title><description>Chronic pain is pain (an unpleasant sense of discomfort) that persists or progresses over a long period of time. In contrast to...Appendix Spine basics: the vertebrae, discs and spinal cord The...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7173-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7173_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:52:58">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=50970</link><title>How 'Perfect' Care Saved an Athlete</title><description>Advances in treatment for spinal injuries offer new hope, and a tantalizing glimpse into the future...recoveries, but the diagnosis of a spinal cord injury usually means life in a wheelchair.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7173-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7173_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:56:07">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=158803</link><title>Re-Routing Spinal Cord Signals Restores Movement in Paralyzed Rats</title><description>But experts note the technique might not work in humans...the brain and spinal cord can often adapt and recover from moderate injury through a quality known as neuroplasticity, severe injuries can...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7173-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7173_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 12:59:06">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=118772</link><title>Health Highlights: Aug. 9, 2010</title><description>Meningitis Risk Influenced By Certain Genes: ResearchersScientists Regrow Spinal Cord Nerve Cells In Mice1 Million Pounds of...did this by deleting a gene called PTEN in mice with severed spinal cords...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7173-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7173_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:02:59">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=109824</link><title>Stem Cells Likely to Help Genetic Disorders First</title><description>Drugs developed without animal testing could be one result, some predict...cells involves cell-based therapy, where stem cells are used to repair damaged heart muscle or severed spinal cords.But the...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>