<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7180">blink reflex</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:14:40" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7180-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7180_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:14:41">http://www.medicinenet.com/trigeminal_neuralgia/article.htm</link><title>Trigeminal Neuralgia</title><description>Pain that originates in the face is referred to as trigeminal neuralgia. This pain may be caused by an injury, and infection in...be no jaw or facial weakness found. The corneal reflex controlled by...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7180-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7180_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:17:22">http://www.medicinenet.com/dry_eyes/article.htm</link><title>Dry Eyes</title><description>Dry eyes are caused by an imbalance in the tear-flow system of the eye, but also can be caused by the drying out of the tear film...close attention with the eyes, a person may not blink as often. This...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7180-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7180_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:21:07">http://www.medicinenet.com/detecting_hearing_loss_in_children/article.htm</link><title>Detecting Hearing Loss in Children</title><description>There are many degrees of hearing, from normal hearing to deafness. Many states mandate the testing of newborns before leaving the...including something as small as an eye blink, can obliterate the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7180-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7180_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:22:02">http://www.medterms.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=5266</link><title>Reflex</title><description>Reflex: An involuntary reaction. For example, the corneal reflex is the blink that occurs upon irritation of the eye</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7180-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7180_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:23:38">http://www.onhealth.com/parkinson_disease_health/article.htm</link><title>Parkinson Disease</title><description>Parkinson's disease (PD) is an age-related deterioration of certain nerve systems, which affects your movement, balance, and...hypomimia (decreased facial expression), decreased blink rate, and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7180-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7180_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:25:56">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=104160</link><title>Third Trimester of Pregnancy</title><description>...of the third trimester, your baby continues to grow and mature: the lungs are nearly fully developed. Your baby's reflexes are coordinated so he or she can blink, close the eyes, turn the head,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7180-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7180_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:27:45">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=173158</link><title>Anxiety Linked to a Need for More Personal Space</title><description>Anxious people perceive threats as closer than others do, and may react defensively, study suggests...stimulus to a nerve in each participants' hand, which caused them to blink. This hand-blink reflex,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7180-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7180_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 14:28:55">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=115733</link><title>Test Spots Potential Organ Donors Among Coma Patients</title><description>It can predict which are most likely to be good candidates upon death, study finds...damage could be a potential organ donor. The four factors are:No corneal reflex. This is tested by touching the...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>