<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7197">contraceptive diaphragm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:55:45" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7197-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7197_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:55:46">http://www.medterms.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=9759</link><title>Contraceptive, diaphragm</title><description>Contraceptive, diaphragm: A barrier method of contraception that is available by prescription only and must be sized by a health professional to achieve a proper fit...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7197-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7197_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 16:58:00">http://www.medterms.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=9758</link><title>Diaphragm (contraceptive)</title><description>Diaphragm (contraceptive): A barrier method of contraception that is available by prescription only and must be sized by a health professional to achieve a proper fit...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7197-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7197_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:01:35">http://www.medicinenet.com/barrier_methods_of_birth_control/article.htm</link><title>Barrier Methods of Birth Control</title><description>Barrier methods of birth control include, spermicides, male condom, female condom, contraceptive sponge, diaphragm, and the...of contraception Spermicides Male condom Female condom Contraceptive...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7197-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7197_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:02:50">http://www.medicinenet.com/birth_control_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Birth Control Pictures Slideshow: Methods, Side Effects and Effectiveness</title><description>See the mechanics, side effects, and effectiveness for common birth control methods. Withdrawal,...Most Effective Methods Although barrier methods, such as the condom or diaphragm, are moderately...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7197-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7197_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:04:48">http://www.medicinenet.com/toxic_shock_syndrome_tss/article.htm</link><title>Toxic Shock Syndrome (TSS)</title><description>Toxic shock syndrome is an infection that causes symptoms such as low blood pressure, fever, and a rash with peeling skin...surgical wounds, history of using a diaphragm or contraceptive sponge, having...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7197-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7197_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:05:59">http://www.medicinenet.com/womens_health/article.htm</link><title>Women's Health</title><description>Women's health is an important topic area to guide a woman through the stages of her life, as well as knowing the conditions and...not rests with the woman. Her choices include oral contraceptives,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7197-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7197_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:08:26">http://www.medicinenet.com/birth_control_methods/article.htm</link><title>Birth Control Methods</title><description>There are a variety of birth control methods to choose from. It varies from person to person and their preferences to either...to fertilize an egg. Examples of physical barrier contraceptives include...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7197-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7197_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:11:00">http://www.onhealth.com/toxic_shock_syndrome/article.htm</link><title>Toxic Shock Syndrome</title><description>Toxic shock syndrome (TSS) is a condition caused by toxins formed by Staphylococcus aureus or group A Streptococcus bacteria...left in place for an extended time period) and barrier contraceptive...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7197-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7197_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:14:13">http://www.medicinenet.com/nafarelin/article.htm</link><title>nafarelin, Synarel</title><description>Nafarelin (Synarel) is a medication prescribed for the management of pain with endometriosis, and decreasing the size of...ovary (ovulation) and result in pregnancy, unless proper contraceptive...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7197-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7197_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:16:09">http://www.medterms.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=9760</link><title>Cervical cap</title><description>...rim designed to fit snugly around the cervix and act as a barrier contraceptive device. A spermicide is applied to the cap before insertion to kill sperm. A cervical cap is basically a small snug...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>