<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7249">largest alligator on record</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:41:33" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7249-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7249_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:41:35">http://www.onhealth.com/attention_deficit_hyperactivity_disorder_adhd/article.htm</link><title>ADHD (Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder in Children)</title><description>Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) is a behavioral disorder characterized by the symptoms hyperactivity, impulsivity,...Is ADHD inherited? Is childhood ADHD on the increase? If so, why? Can...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7249-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7249_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:42:42">http://www.medicinenet.com/parenting_a_child_with_adhd/article.htm</link><title>Parenting a Child With ADHD</title><description>ADHD is a behavioral condition with characteristics that include hyperactivity, inattention, and impulsivity. Parenting a child...for children with ADHD? Is childhood ADHD on the rise? What is the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7249-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7249_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:45:44">http://www.medicinenet.com/west_nile_virus_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>West Nile Virus Pictures Slideshow: Causes, Symptoms, and Treatment</title><description>Watch this slideshow on West Nile Virus (encephalitis). Spread by mosquitoes that feed on infected birds, learn about causes,...and Treatment Reviewed by John P. Cunha, DO, FACOEP on Monday, September...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7249-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7249_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:48:47">http://www.medicinenet.com/human_body_quiz/quiz.htm</link><title>Human Body Quiz: Test Your Medical IQ</title><description>...your little-known body parts! Take this quiz to learn more about your body and what goes on inside...B 300 million Explanation: According to the U.S. population clock on December 1, 2010,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7249-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7249_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:51:24">http://www.onhealth.com/child_abuse/article.htm</link><title>Child Abuse</title><description>Child abuse falls into four categories: neglect, physical abuse, sexual abuse, and emotional abuse. There are certain risk factors...of verbally communicating the harm inflicted on them. Other factors...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7249-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7249_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:52:26">http://www.medicinenet.com/huntington_disease/article.htm</link><title>Huntington's Disease</title><description>Huntington's disease is the result of degeneration of neurons in areas of the brain. Huntington's disease is an inherited disorder...s disease? What research is being done on Huntington's disease?</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7249-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7249_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:54:32">http://www.medicinenet.com/skin_problems_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Skin Pictures Slideshow: Adult Skin Problems</title><description>Through this slideshow of pictures on adult skin problems, learn to spot and treat commonly found skin conditions such as acne,...Skin Problems Reviewed by Gary W. Cole, MD, FAAD on Tuesday, April 30,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7249-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7249_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:56:27">http://www.medicinenet.com/sexual_health_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Sexual Health Pictures Slideshow: Surprising Health Benefits of Sex</title><description>Watch this slideshow on the surprising health benefits of sex, including stress relief, boosting...Health Benefits of Sex Reviewed by Melissa Conrad Stöppler, MD on Monday, October 17,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7249-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7249_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:59:09">http://www.medicinenet.com/type_1_diabetes_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Type 1 Diabetes Pictures Slideshow: Symptoms, Causes and Treatment</title><description>View a picture slideshow on Type 1 Diabetes. See warning signs, causes, treatments and health tips for this potentially...and Treatment Reviewed by Charles Patrick Davis, MD, PhD on Thursday, February...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7249-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7249_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:02:23">http://www.medicinenet.com/feet_facts_quiz/quiz.htm</link><title>Feet Facts Quiz: Test Your Medical IQ</title><description>Did you know that certain shoes and common diseases can wreak havoc on your feet? If you've been...in arch supports can help with these problems. Q:Feet are their largest... AIn the morning BWhen...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>