<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7250">collagen vascular disease</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:03:23" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7250-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7250_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:03:24">http://www.onhealth.com/miscarriage/article.htm</link><title>Miscarriage</title><description>...cannot always be determined. The most common causes of a miscarriage in the first trimester are collagen vascular disease (lupus),...are chromosomal abnormalities, collagen vascular disease (such as...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7250-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7250_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:06:23">http://www.medicinenet.com/skin_conditions_picture_quiz/quiz.htm</link><title>Skin Disease Picture Quiz - Identify These Common Skin Conditions</title><description>Could you identify a scabies infestation? Take the Skin Diseases Pictures Quiz and learn to identify...Lupus Erythematosus Systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE) is a systemic collagen vascular disease...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7250-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7250_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:09:07">http://www.medicinenet.com/nail_health_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Nail Health Pictures Slideshow: What Your Nails Say about Your Health</title><description>Subtle changes in the color or texture of your nails may be a sign of disease elsewhere in the body. Watch this slideshow to find...Damaged capillaries caused by certain autoimmune collagen vascular...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7250-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7250_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:09:46">http://www.medicinenet.com/laser_eye_surgery_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Laser Eye Surgery Pictures Slideshow: Better Vision Through Surgery (LASIK, PRK, LASEK &amp; More)</title><description>Watch this slideshow on Laser Surgery to achieve better vision. See how LASIK works, similar...make you a poor candidate for laser vision correction. Conditions such as collagen vascular diseases,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7250-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7250_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:12:47">http://www.medicinenet.com/connective_tissue_disease/article.htm</link><title>Connective Tissue Disease</title><description>Connective tissue disease is when the body's connective tissues come under attack, possibly becoming injured by inflammation...one's own body tissues (autoimmunity). Diseases in which inflammation or...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7250-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7250_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:15:10">http://www.medicinenet.com/hypersensitivity_pneumonitis/article.htm</link><title>Hypersensitivity Pneumonitis</title><description>...body aches. Examples of hypersensitivity pneumonitis include bagassosis, mushroom worker's disease, sauna taker's disease, pigeon...as a marker for activity seen in diffuse lung disease) may be...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7250-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7250_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:16:46">http://www.medicinenet.com/pulmonary_hypertension/article.htm</link><title>Pulmonary Hypertension</title><description>Pulmonary hypertension is an abnormal elevation of the pressure in the pulmonary circulation caused by the constriction of the...pulmonary artery hypertension associated with collagen vascular...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7250-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7250_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:18:56">http://www.medterms.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=20748</link><title>Roth's spot</title><description>...A hemorrhage in the retina with a white center. Originally associated with bacterial endocarditis, Roth's spots may be seen in leukemia, diabetes, collagen-vascular diseases, and other conditions...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7250-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7250_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:21:05">http://www.medterms.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=4948</link><title>Pleurisy</title><description>...the friction generated by the rubbing of the two inflamed layers of pleurae with each breath. The causes of pleurisy include lung infections, collagen vascular diseases such as lupus and rheumatoid...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7250-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7250_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 02:21:40">http://www.medterms.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=5352</link><title>Rhabdomyolysis</title><description>...muscle damage as, for example, in crush injury or electrical shock. Drugs or toxins may also cause this disorder. Underlying diseases that can also lead to rhabdomyolysis include collagen vascular...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>