<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7299">row row row your boat lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:32:29" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7299-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7299_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:32:31">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=78846</link><title>Exercise Tubing and Bands</title><description>...won't dent the floor or mash your toe if you drop them, and you...them and do upright and bent-over-rows, lateral raises, front raises, overhead presses, and...end up behind you (like rowing a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7299-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7299_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:34:51">http://www.medicinenet.com/allergies_quiz/quiz.htm</link><title>Allergies Quiz: Test Your Medical IQ</title><description>What are the causes of allergies? This online quiz challenges your knowledge of common food and household allergens, environmental...nasal discharge BSneezing more than twice in a row CLack of fever...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7299-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7299_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:36:10">http://www.medicinenet.com/habits_that_wreck_your_teeth_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Dental Health Pictures Slideshow: 19 Habits That Wreck Your Teeth</title><description>See 19 Habits That Wreck Your Teeth from this slideshow. Learn how chewing ice, eating snacks,...Dental Health Pictures Slideshow: 19 Habits That Wreck Your Teeth Reviewed by Brunilda Nazario, MD on...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7299-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7299_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:38:26">http://www.medicinenet.com/childrens_cold_flu_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Cold and Flu Pictures Slideshow: Treating Your Child's Cold or Fever</title><description>Watch this Cold and Flu slideshow on Treating Your Child's Cold or Fever. See helpful tips to safely choose and use...Cold and Flu Pictures Slideshow: Treating Your Child's Cold or Fever Reviewed...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7299-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7299_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:40:37">http://www.medicinenet.com/reasons_your_child_cant_sleep_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Children's Health Pictures Slideshow: Top Reasons Your Child Can't Sleep</title><description>Watch this slideshow on Reasons Your Child Can't Sleep. From snoring and nightmares to sleep apnea and even you, see what reasons...Children's Health Pictures Slideshow: Top Reasons Your Child Can't...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7299-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7299_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:43:30">http://www.medicinenet.com/jobs_that_wreck_your_sleep_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Sleep Pictures Slideshow: Jobs That Wreck Your Sleep</title><description>Did you know that some jobs can wreck your sleep. From network administrators to nurses, see a variety of jobs that affect...Sleep Pictures Slideshow: Jobs That Wreck Your Sleep Reviewed by...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7299-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7299_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:44:43">http://www.medicinenet.com/bronchitis_quiz/quiz.htm</link><title>Bronchitis Quiz</title><description>What happens within the body when a person develops bronchitis? Take this quick quiz to learn the...with sputum production for at least 3 months, 2 years in a row. Chronic bronchitis is a diagnosis...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7299-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7299_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:46:55">http://www.medicinenet.com/diabetes_caring_for_your_diabetes_at_special_time/article.htm</link><title>Diabetes: Caring for Your Diabetes at Special Times</title><description>Taking care of a disease such as diabetes is a life-long process. Learn how to care for yourself or loved one with diabetes in...Diabetes: Caring for Your Diabetes at Special Times Introduction When...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7299-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7299_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:48:34">http://www.medicinenet.com/disease_prevention_in_women/article.htm</link><title>Disease Prevention in Women</title><description>...are a basic part of prevention medicine. All screening tests are commonly available through your general doctor. Some...All screening tests are commonly available through your general doctor.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7299-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7299_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 10:50:59">http://www.medicinenet.com/oral_cancer/article.htm</link><title>Oral Cancer</title><description>...loose teeth, pain upon swallowing, a lump in the neck, earache, and a sore on your lip or in your mouth that won't heal are all...and oropharynx have many parts: Lips Lining of your cheeks Salivary...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>