<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7303">what causes itchy feet</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:01:25" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7303-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7303_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:01:26">http://www.medicinenet.com/what_skin_says_about_health_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Skin &amp; Health Pictures Slideshow: What Your Skin Says About Your Health</title><description>...health problems including diabetes, lupus and lung cancer. Watch this slideshow to learn what skin can tell you about your health...Skin &amp; Health Pictures Slideshow: What Your Skin Says About...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7303-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7303_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:03:38">http://www.medicinenet.com/eczema_atopic_dermatitis_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Eczema (Atopic Dermatitis) Pictures Slideshow: Causes, Symptoms and Treatment</title><description>Watch this slideshow on Eczema (Atopic Dermatitis). Learn about the causes, symptoms and treatment for eczema, as well as the...Eczema (Atopic Dermatitis) Pictures Slideshow: Causes, Symptoms and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7303-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7303_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:04:36">http://www.medicinenet.com/gout_quiz/quiz.htm</link><title>Gout Quiz: Test Your Medical IQ</title><description>Learn what causes those painful crystals to form during a gout flare. Take the Gout Quiz to learn...called gouty arthritis. Gout can cause an attack of sudden burning...caused by the buildup of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7303-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7303_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:05:36">http://www.medicinenet.com/athletes_foot/article.htm</link><title>Athlete's Foot</title><description>Athlete's foot (tinea pedis) is a skin infection caused by the ringworm fungus. Symptoms include itching, burning, cracking,...Athlete's Foot Athlete's foot facts What is athlete's foot? What...s foot...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7303-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7303_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:06:12">http://www.medicinenet.com/what_feet_say_about_your_health_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Foot Health Pictures Slideshow: What Your Feet Say About Your Health</title><description>What do your feet say about your health? Watch this slideshow to learn how cold feet, misshapen nails, swelling, and numbness can...Foot Health Pictures Slideshow: What Your Feet Say About Your..</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7303-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7303_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:07:24">http://www.medicinenet.com/scabies_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Scabies Pictures Slideshow: Stop the Itch Mite</title><description>Get the facts on scabies (itch mite) causes, signs and symptoms. Learn what scabies looks like and how to treat it throught this...the complete gallery of slideshows. What Is Scabies? Scabies is an...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7303-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7303_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:08:15">http://www.medicinenet.com/hives/article.htm</link><title>Hives</title><description>Hives, also called urticaria, is a raised, itchy area of skin that is usually a sign of an allergic reaction. The allergy may be...Hives (Urticaria &amp; Angioedema) Hives facts What are hives...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7303-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7303_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:09:17">http://www.medicinenet.com/jock_itch/article.htm</link><title>Jock Itch</title><description>Jock itch is an itchy red rash that appears in the groin area. The rash may be caused by a bacterial or fungal infection. People...Jock Itch Jock itch facts What is jock itch? What does...jock itch...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7303-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7303_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:10:01">http://www.medicinenet.com/allergy/article.htm</link><title>Allergy</title><description>...contact with certain foreign substances. When these allergens come in contact with the body, it causes the immune system to...to the body and can cause an allergic reaction. IgE is...more about...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7303-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7303_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:11:25">http://www.medicinenet.com/senior_health/article.htm</link><title>Senior Health (Successful Aging)</title><description>Senior health is important for healthy and successful aging. Eating healthy and regular exercise may lower a person's risk for...Charles P. Davis, MD, PhD What are some common facts about...also...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>