<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7307">causes of the cold war</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:40:56" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7307-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7307_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:40:57">http://www.medicinenet.com/generalized_anxiety_disorder_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Generalized Anxiety Disorder (GAD) Pictures Slideshow: Symptoms, Diagnosis &amp; Treatment</title><description>...through this slideshow. See if your worries are normal or something more by look at the symptoms, diagnosis, and treatments of...twice as many women as men. What Causes GAD? The genes passed...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7307-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7307_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:42:01">http://www.medicinenet.com/polio_facts/article.htm</link><title>Polio</title><description>A polio infection causes symptoms and signs such as paralysis, limb deformities, and even death. There is no curative treatment...What is the history of polio? What causes polio? What are risk...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7307-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7307_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:42:36">http://www.medicinenet.com/anaphylaxis/article.htm</link><title>Anaphylaxis</title><description>Anaphylaxis is a serious allergic reaction that affects a number of different areas of the body at one time, and can be fatal...How common is anaphylaxis? What are common causes of anaphylaxis? What...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7307-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7307_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:43:55">http://www.medterms.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=19542</link><title>Infection, adenovirus</title><description>...diseases include a form of the common cold, pneumonia, croup, and bronchitis. Patients with compromised...first recognized among military recruits during World War II, can be caused by adenovirus...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7307-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7307_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:44:43">http://www.medicinenet.com/croup/article.htm</link><title>Croup</title><description>Croup is a contagious viral infection that affects children's respiratory system. Symptoms include a...Croup Croup facts What is croup? What causes croup? Is croup contagious? What are croup..</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7307-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7307_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:46:08">http://www.medicinenet.com/hay_fever/article.htm</link><title>Hay Fever</title><description>Hay fever (allergic rhinitis) is an irritation of the nose caused by pollen and is associated with the following allergic...Why does an allergic reaction occur? What causes allergic rhinitis? When...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7307-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7307_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:48:25">http://www.medterms.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=18884</link><title>Ricin</title><description>...conditions such as very hot or very cold temperatures. Ricin is extremely toxic by several...within 36-72 hours. When ingested, ricin causes severe gastrointestinal symptoms followed by vascular...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7307-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7307_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:49:55">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=26652</link><title>Ricin - Poison at the Capital?</title><description>...conditions such as very hot or very cold temperatures. The signs and symptoms Ricin is...when it is consumed. Once ingested, ricin causes severe gastrointestinal symptoms followed by vascular...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7307-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7307_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:51:28">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=54693</link><title>Allergy: Winning the War Against Allergies</title><description>The official start of spring is right around the corner, but for many allergy sufferers the sneezin' season has already begun...Winning the War Against Allergies-- Paul Enright -- 03/11/04..</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7307-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7307_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:53:03">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=51822</link><title>Depression: Suffering From 'Let-Down Effect?'</title><description>Do you manage to stay healthy through the most stressful of times, only to succumb to colds or flu when you finally have some down...serving in the Persian Gulf War in 1991. "About 80% of these...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>