<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7328">reduce acne redness</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:19:56" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7328-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7328_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:19:57">http://www.medicinenet.com/quick_acne_cover_ups_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Acne Pictures Slideshow: Quick Cover-ups, Do's and Don'ts</title><description>Watch this slideshow on Quick Acne Cover-ups, Do's and Don'ts. See solutions on how to best handle...Acne Pictures Slideshow: Quick Cover-ups, Do's...for touch-ups throughout the day. DO: Reduce...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7328-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7328_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:21:20">http://www.medicinenet.com/acne/article.htm</link><title>Acne (Pimples)</title><description>Acne is a localized skin inflammation as a result of overactivity of oil glands at the base of hair follicles. This inflammation,...Acne(Pimples) What is acne? What causes acne...middle third of the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7328-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7328_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:23:16">http://www.medicinenet.com/rosacea/article.htm</link><title>Rosacea</title><description>Rosacea is a skin disease that causes redness of the forehead, chin, and lower half of the nose. In addition to inflammation of...rosacea? Is rosacea contagious? Is rosacea like acne? What are...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7328-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7328_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:24:53">http://www.medicinenet.com/photodynamic_therapy/article.htm</link><title>Photodynamic Therapy</title><description>...esophageal cancer, and Barrett's esophagus. It's used to treat actinic keratosis, as well as acne, rosacea, skin cancer, sun...light source. PDT is also used for acne, rosacea, skin cancer, sun...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7328-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7328_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:27:00">http://www.medicinenet.com/sapho_syndrome/article.htm</link><title>SAPHO Syndrome</title><description>...the skin, bone, and joints. SAPHO syndrome is an eponym for the combination of synovitis, acne, pustulosis, hyperostosis, and...an acronym for the combination of synovitis, acne, pustulosis,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7328-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7328_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:28:19">http://www.medicinenet.com/blepharitis/article.htm</link><title>Blepharitis</title><description>Blepharitis is inflammation of the eyelids. Acne rosacea, Staphylococcal bacteria, allergies, sensitivities to makeup or contact...or infection. Signs of inflammation are swelling, redness, pain,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7328-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7328_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:30:06">http://www.medicinenet.com/dermabrasion/article.htm</link><title>Dermabrasion</title><description>Dermabrasion involves freezing and then sanding the skin. Dermabrasion improves the appearance of scars and other skin conditions,...to respond best to this approach include acne scarring, keloids,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7328-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7328_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:31:19">http://www.medicinenet.com/plastic_surgery_cosmetic_surgery/article.htm</link><title>Plastic Surgery (Cosmetic Surgery)</title><description>Cosmetic surgery and procedures include interventions to improve one's appearance and fight the effects of aging on the outside...the lips to create fuller lips and reduce wrinkles around the mouth.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7328-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7328_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:32:18">http://www.medterms.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=8037</link><title>Acne rosacea</title><description>Acne rosacea: A chronic skin disease that causes persistent redness over the areas of the face and...right strength may also be used to reduce local inflammation. Avoiding smoking, food and drink...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7328-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7328_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 14:32:50">http://www.medicinenet.com/adapalene/article.htm</link><title>adapalene, Differin</title><description>Adapalene (Differin) is a gel prescribed for the treatment of acne (pimples). Side effects (sun sensitivity, for example), drug...side effects of adapalene are irritation, redness, dryness, and...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>