<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7402">little johnny</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:26:56" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7402-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7402_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:26:56">http://www.medicinenet.com/7_tips_less_holiday_travel_stress_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Holiday Travel Pictures Slideshow: 7 Tips to Make it Less Stressful</title><description>Travel during the holidays can be a very stressful process. Loaded with gifts, baggage, kids and possible wintry weather, crowded...change of clothing for you as well as for the little ones, since...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7402-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7402_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:28:11">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=16696</link><title>Exercise Preventing Asthma?</title><description>...differences during the past 40 years. Let us go back in our minds to the 1960s. It is late afternoon and school is out. Little Johnny and Jane come racing through the back door to find mom greeting...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7402-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7402_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:29:06">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=53946</link><title>Spinning: The Mind &amp; Body Experience with Johnny G</title><description>Fitness expert Johnny G will discuss how to combine cycling with inspirational music, visualization and breathing techniques to...a newly oriented instructor's class may also be a little bit weak,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7402-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7402_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:30:00">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=54304</link><title>AIDS Decade in Review</title><description>It was the decade of protease inhibitors, safe sex, Lazarus, and survivor guilt. Join Larry Kramer, Richard Marlink, MD, and...and most people don't want to believe that because little Johnny and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7402-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7402_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:31:04">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=53926</link><title>Aging: Attitude Toward Aging with Marsha Hunt</title><description>Marsha Hunt, star of stage and screen and a social activist, will discuss attitudes towards aging...from the wheelchair, and she gets great meals together. There's very little out of reach for us if...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7402-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7402_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:32:14">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=51682</link><title>Parenting the Picky Eater</title><description>When you have a child who hardly eats, it seems everyone has an opinion. We asked the experts to...Parenting the Picky Eater Why Johnny won't eat By Michele Bloomquist WebMD Feature Reviewed By...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7402-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7402_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:33:13">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=56666</link><title>Halloween: Trick Kids into Healthy Treats</title><description>Getting your kids to gobble goodies that are good for them!...she can borrow to put in Johnny's lunchbox. The kids like the variety and often end up eating or drinking the nutritious treats while...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7402-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7402_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:34:41">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=167001</link><title>'Xtreme Eating Awards': And the Winner Is?</title><description>...quickly send you up a dress size:The Bacon Cheddar Double from Johnny Rockets has 1,770 calories, more than three McDonald's Quarter Pounders...milligrams of sodium, the Veal Porterhouse with red...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7402-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7402_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:35:23">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=56465</link><title>Eating Habits: Family-Sized Portions</title><description>Does your family have healthy eating habits?...your kids serve themselves at dinnertime? Just keep a watchful eye over little ones when it comes to dishing out sweets.Eating more meals at...family?</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7402-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7402_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:36:49">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=52190</link><title>Metrosexuals: It's a Guy Thing!</title><description>An emerging breed of man, the metrosexual, shows his soft, sensitive, feminine side. ...with male-targeted grooming products, including moisturizers (and perhaps even a little makeup). He may work on his...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>