<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7405">light therapy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:41:13" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7405-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7405_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:41:15">http://www.medicinenet.com/image-collection/low_level_light_therapy_sunetics_device_picture/picture.htm</link><title>Picture of Low Level Light Therapy: Sunetics Device</title><description>Low level light laser therapy (LLLT) has been used to treat a variety of medical disorders from ulcers to musculoskeletal...ICNUM**. Picture of Low Level Light Therapy: Sunetics Device Image...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7405-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7405_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:42:21">http://www.medicinenet.com/image-collection/low_level_light_therapy_lllt_laser_comb_picture/picture.htm</link><title>Picture of Low Level Light Therapy: Laser Comb</title><description>Low level light laser therapy (LLLT) has been used to treat a variety of medical disorders from ulcers to musculoskeletal...ICNUM**. Picture of Low Level Light Therapy: Laser Comb Image Source:...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7405-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7405_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:42:58">http://www.medicinenet.com/photodynamic_therapy/article.htm</link><title>Photodynamic Therapy</title><description>Photodynamic therapy (PDT) is a procedure that treats precancerous cells, in addition to other types of cancer cells. The medical...Photodynamic Therapy (PDT or Blue Light Therapy) What is...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7405-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7405_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:44:40">http://www.medicinenet.com/psoriasis/article.htm</link><title>Psoriasis</title><description>...may include creams, lotions, oral medications, injections and infusions of biologics, and light therapy. There is no cure for...apply. These cases may require ultraviolet light treatments or...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7405-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7405_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:46:22">http://www.medicinenet.com/scalp_psoriasis/article.htm</link><title>Scalp Psoriasis</title><description>...Treatment includes topical medicated shampoos, creams, gels, oils, ointments, and soaps, medications, and light therapy...benefit only lasts about six weeks at best. Ultraviolet light in wavelengths...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7405-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7405_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:47:36">http://www.onhealth.com/migraine_headache/article.htm</link><title>Migraine</title><description>...of the head. These may be accompanied by nausea, vomiting, increased sensitivity of the eyes to light (photophobia), increased...or photophobia (decreased tolerance to light). How are migraine...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7405-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7405_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:49:17">http://www.medicinenet.com/non-drug_migraine_treatments_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Migraine Headaches Pictures Slideshow: 14 Non-Drug Treatments for Migraines</title><description>...this slideshow on 14 Non-Drug Treatments for Migraines. Acupuncture, biofeedback and massage therapy are among this list of...too. Complementary therapies like this generally work best along...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7405-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7405_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:50:01">http://www.medicinenet.com/psoriasis_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Psoriasis Pictures Slideshow: See Moderate to Severe Forms of this Common Skin Condition</title><description>See moderate to severe forms of the common skin condition psoriasis. Learn about the different types...salicylic acid to work effectively. Medical Treatment – Phototherapy (Light Therapy) The...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7405-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7405_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:51:48">http://www.medicinenet.com/depression_overview_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Depression Overview Pictures Slideshow: Symptoms, Types, Tests &amp; Treatment</title><description>What is depression? Get information on symptoms, tests, and treatments for many types of depression...times per week is enough for anyone to reap the benefits of exercise. Light Therapy (Phototherapy)...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7405-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7405_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 02:53:52">http://www.medicinenet.com/hair_loss_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Hair Loss Pictures Slideshow: Causes, Treatments and Solutions for Men &amp; Women</title><description>Experiencing hair loss? Watch and learn about causes, treatments and solutions for conditions such as male\- and female-pattern...such as oral steroids or ultraviolet light therapy, are either toxic or...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>