<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7407">kim kardashian pregnant</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:08:32" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7407-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7407_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:08:33">http://www.medicinenet.com/travel_health_and_vaccines_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Travel Health Pictures Slideshow: Vaccines &amp; Preventing Diseases Abroad</title><description>Some of the world's most spectacular destinations are also home to some of the world's nastiest bugs. Watch this slideshow on...on cloudy days. Precautions During Pregnancy Being pregnant doesn't put...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7407-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7407_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:09:30">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=51715</link><title>Morning Sickness: Doing Battle</title><description>Nothing can blast the euphoria of discovering you're pregnant faster than morning sickness...Bitoun Blecher ---&gt; Nothing can blast the euphoria of discovering you're pregnant faster than morning...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7407-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7407_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:10:56">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=162680</link><title>7 Embarrassing Pregnancy Symptoms</title><description>...So many things happen to a woman's body when she becomes pregnant, and most are shocking: hair growth on your belly, belching and constipation...The majority of the time, it's normal signs of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7407-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7407_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:12:54">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=163671</link><title>BPA Exposure Impacts Pregnant Women's Thyroids, Study Suggests</title><description>Widely used chemical linked to lower levels of hormone in newborn boys, but not girls...BPA Exposure Impacts Pregnant Women's Thyroids, Study SuggestsBy Amanda GardnerHealthDay ReporterTHURSDAY, Oct. 4...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7407-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7407_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:13:45">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=174457</link><title>Buttocks-Enhancing Procedures Please Patients, Small Study Finds</title><description>Technique uses liposuction, fat injections to produce curvier backsides, but not without potential...DohenyHealthDay ReporterFRIDAY, Oct 11 (HealthDay News) -- Beyonce, Kim Kardashian and Jennifer...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7407-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7407_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:14:39">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=150020</link><title>Twitter Tracks Mood Swings</title><description>...Ashton Kutcher are really on the rocks or what reality TV star Kim Kardashian had over for lunch.All of this tweeting may actually give researchers...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7407-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7407_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:15:24">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=115830</link><title>Does This Surgery Make My Butt Look Big?</title><description>...Washington, D.C.) -- First there was J. Lo. Then Beyonce, Rihanna, and Kim Kardashian started strutting their stuff on stage and on screen. As a result...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7407-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7407_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:16:48">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=112734</link><title>Flame Retardant Exposure May Harm Fertility</title><description>...found in some household objects, took about twice as long to become pregnant as women with lower blood levels, according to a new study. "For...the odds of becoming pregnant in any given month,"...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7407-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7407_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:17:37">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=177120</link><title>Overweight Moms May Have Dangerously Big Babies</title><description>Excessive weight gain leads to serious problems for mothers and infants, study suggests...related diabetes all contribute to having big babies," said lead researcher Shin Kim, of the division of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7407-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7407_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:18:56">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=84940</link><title>Pancreas May Be Key to Pregnancy-Linked Diabetes</title><description>The condition can pose dangers to mother, baby, experts note...islet growth, a code we intend to crack," senior author Dr. Seung Kim, associate professor of developmental biology, said in a prepared...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>