<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7412">when queen elisabeth</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:46:03" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7412-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7412_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:46:04">http://www.medterms.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=38649</link><title>Kubler-Ross, Elisabeth</title><description>Kubler-Ross, Elisabeth: (1926-2004) Swiss-born American psychiatrist whose work with and teching about terminally ill patients helped alter attitudes toward death and the care of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7412-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7412_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:47:04">http://www.medicinenet.com/fattest_and_fittest_states_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Healthy Eating Pictures Slideshow: The Fattest and Fittest States in America</title><description>What are The Fattest and Fittest States in America? See if your state is on the list as this...Kentucky is a fast-food capital. There are more Applebee's, Arby's, Dairy Queen, McDonald's, and Papa...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7412-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7412_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:48:52">http://www.medicinenet.com/aids_retrospective_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>AIDS Retrospective Pictures Slideshow: A Pictorial Timeline of the HIV/AIDS Pandemic</title><description>Get a historical overview of the HIV/AIDS pandemic from human contraction to the present through...a symbol of AIDS solidarity. Magic Johnson announces he is HIV positive. Queen singer Freddy Mercury...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7412-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7412_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:49:51">http://www.medicinenet.com/hemophilia/article.htm</link><title>Hemophilia</title><description>Hemophilia is one of a group of inherited bleeding disorders. Hemophilia A and B are inherited in an X-linked recessive genetic...has been called the Royal Disease because Queen Victoria, Queen of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7412-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7412_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:50:34">http://www.onhealth.com/loss_grief_and_bereavement/article.htm</link><title>Grief: Loss of a Loved One</title><description>Grief is the feeling one experiences after a loss (of a friendship, death of loved one, job). Complicated grief refers to grief...model for understanding grief was developed by Elisabeth...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7412-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7412_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:52:17">http://www.medterms.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=3464</link><title>Fire ants</title><description>...poultry and the young of ground-nesting wild birds. Fire ants can kill newborn domestic and wild animals. Each colony is composed of a queen, winged males and females and 3 kinds of workers. A nest...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7412-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7412_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:52:52">http://www.medterms.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=38657</link><title>Elizabeth Kubler-Ross</title><description>Elizabeth Kübler-Ross: See: Kübler-Ross, Elisabeth</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7412-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7412_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:53:44">http://www.medterms.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=25269</link><title>Montgomery, William W.</title><description>...American otolaryngologist who developed many techniques used in surgery on the throat and the vocal cords. Dr. Montgomery operated on kings and queens, celebrities and the less-celebrated at the Mass.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7412-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7412_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:54:22">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=2058</link><title>Tobacco's -Healing Properties Were Discovered By Jean Nicot</title><description>...medicinal properties. He described tobacco as a panacea and sent tobacco plants to the French court. Nicot sent snuff to Catherine de Medici, the Queen of France, in 1560 to treat her migraine...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7412-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7412_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 03:56:03">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=24628</link><title>Cancer: New Drug Deters Breast Cancer Relapses</title><description>...With Canadian Cancer Society funding, the clinical trial was coordinated by the National Cancer Institute of Canada Clinical Trials Group at Queen's University, in partnership with the U.S. National...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>