<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7416">release date bioshock infinite</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:05:20" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7416-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7416_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:05:22">http://www.onhealth.com/primary_biliary_cirrhosis/article.htm</link><title>Primary Biliary Cirrhosis</title><description>Primary Biliary Cirrhosis is a chronic disease characterized by progressive inflammation and destruction of small bile ducts...immune system is capable of recognizing a nearly infinite number of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7416-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7416_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:06:51">http://www.medicinenet.com/rocky_mountain_spotted_fever_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Rocky Mountain Spotted Fever Pictures Slideshow: Causes, Symptoms and Treatment</title><description>Watch this slideshow on Rocky Mountain Spotted Fever. Learn about causes, symptoms, treatments and...container or plastic bag and put it in your freezer. Write the date of the bite on a piece of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7416-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7416_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:07:45">http://www.medicinenet.com/reasons_for_blood_sugar_swings_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Diabetes Pictures Slideshow: 20 Reasons for Blood Sugar Swings</title><description>Watch this slideshow on 20 Reasons for Blood Sugar Swings. See symptoms and get helpful tips to balance jumps and dips in blood...Job Stress Stress may cause your body to release hormones that can...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7416-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7416_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:08:57">http://www.medicinenet.com/bioterrorism/article.htm</link><title>Bioterrorism</title><description>Bioterrorism is a form of terrorism where there is the intentional release of biological agents such as viruses, germs, or...is a form of terrorism where there is the intentional release of biological...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7416-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7416_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:09:59">http://www.medicinenet.com/adhd_in_adults_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>ADHD in Adults Pictures Slideshow: Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder</title><description>Most people think of children when they hear the term attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD). But 30%-70% of kids with...in adults than in children, but the research to date is promising.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7416-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7416_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:11:12">http://www.medicinenet.com/tattoo_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Before You Tattoo Pictures Slideshow: Tattoo Types, Safety, Removal</title><description>Want to tattoo? Get the scoop on tattoo safety, tattoo risks, tattoo care, and what to expect from...the artist's business license to make sure it's up to date. And check the tattoo area: Look for...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7416-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7416_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:12:18">http://www.medicinenet.com/premenstrual_syndrome/article.htm</link><title>Premenstrual Syndrome (PMS)</title><description>Premenstrual syndrome (PMS) is a combination of physical and emotional disturbances that occur after a woman ovulates and ends...symptoms of PMS and may have some benefit. To date, studies have been...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7416-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7416_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:14:04">http://www.medicinenet.com/trichinosis/article.htm</link><title>Trichinosis</title><description>Trichinosis is a food-borne disease caused by ingesting parasites (roundworms) in undercooked pork or wild-game meat. Symptoms of...have not been reported to infect humans to date. There are other...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7416-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7416_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:15:10">http://www.medicinenet.com/labor_and_delivery/article.htm</link><title>Labor and Delivery</title><description>Labor signs can be very distinct for pregnant women. It is not possible to know what causes labor to start or when exactly it will...labor can begin a few weeks prior to the due date or up to 2 weeks...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7416-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7416_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 04:16:58">http://www.medicinenet.com/natural_methods_of_birth_control/article.htm</link><title>Natural Methods of Birth Control</title><description>Natural methods of contraception are considered "natural" because they are non-mechanical and non-hormonal. Natural methods of...mucous than usual (like raw egg white) just before release of an egg...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>