<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7426">game bmx boy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 05:30:39" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7426-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7426_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 05:30:40">http://www.medicinenet.com/teen_boys_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Teen Boys Pictures Slideshow: Sports, Gym and Locker Room Gross-Outs</title><description>...the only thing that grows in locker rooms. Watch this slideshow on sports health for teen boys. From yellow toenails and itchy...Teen Boys Pictures Slideshow: Sports, Gym and Locker Room...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7426-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7426_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 05:32:13">http://www.medicinenet.com/autism_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Autism Pictures Slideshow: Symptoms, Diagnosis and Treatment</title><description>Watch this slideshow on Autism. See an overview on this brain disorder found in children that interferes with their ability to...Autism occurs about four to five times more often in boys than girls.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7426-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7426_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 05:33:41">http://www.medicinenet.com/tween_child_development/article.htm</link><title>Tween: Child Development</title><description>Developmental milestones for tweens 9-11 years of age include the ability to use deductive reasoning to anticipate consequences,...8 years of age in girls and 9 years of age in boys. While this early...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7426-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7426_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 05:35:21">http://www.medicinenet.com/dyslexia/article.htm</link><title>Dyslexia</title><description>Dyslexia affects a person's ability to spell, read, write, or even speak. It's considered the most common learning disability in...genes (hereditary). It is found more often in boys than in girls. A...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7426-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7426_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 05:36:41">http://www.medicinenet.com/celebrities_with_migraines_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Migraine Headaches Pictures Slideshow: Celebrities With Migraines</title><description>Watch this slideshow on Celebrities with Migraine Headaches. See how these famous celebs, who have a...of Fame quarterback Troy Aikman started having headaches when he was a boy. "When you make a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7426-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7426_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 05:38:18">http://www.medicinenet.com/celebrities_with_diabetes_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Celebrities With Diabetes Pictures Slideshow: Nick Jonas, Salma Hayek and More</title><description>See pictures of celebrities that have been diagnosed with type 1 or type 2 diabetes including Halle...his high school weight of 96 pounds. "I was a very skinny boy!" Halle Berry Actress Halle Berry...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7426-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7426_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 05:38:55">http://www.medicinenet.com/anabolic_steroid_abuse/article.htm</link><title>Steroid Abuse</title><description>Anabolic steroids are synthetic substances that are related to testosterone and promote skeletal muscle growth and the development...who use anabolic steroids, a cat and mouse game exists. They try to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7426-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7426_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 05:40:00">http://www.medicinenet.com/attention_deficit_hyperactivity_disorder_in_teens/article.htm</link><title>Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD) in Teens</title><description>Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) in teens is a disruption of neurocognitive functioning. Genetics contribute to...cell phone usage, and video games. What stimulant medications are...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7426-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7426_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 05:40:59">http://www.medicinenet.com/autism_and_communication/article.htm</link><title>Autism Spectrum Disorder (In Children and Adults)</title><description>Autism in children and adults is a developmental disorder, characterized by impaired development in communication, social...and their families. It tends to affect about five boys to every one girl.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7426-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7426_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 05:41:50">http://www.medicinenet.com/teen_child_development/article.htm</link><title>Teen: Child Development</title><description>During the high school years, teens are developing the intellectual skills necessary for college or the work force. Teenagers are...of age? Puberty is the time at which a growing boy or girl begins...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>