<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7438">facebook privacy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:48:54" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7438-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7438_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:48:55">http://www.medicinenet.com/teen_girls_tricky_situations_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Teen Girls Pictures Slideshow: Mean Girls, Cyberbullying, Dating, Periods &amp; More</title><description>Watch this slideshow on tricky situations faced by teen girls. See how to deal with dating, sexting, cyberbullying, mean girls,...to do: Narrow your online social circle. Limit your Facebook page to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7438-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7438_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:50:00">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=120449</link><title>Bullying, Harassment of Gay/Lesbian Teens: Expert Q&amp;A</title><description>...What happened to the student in New Jersey is an invasion of privacy, and that is illegal. Certainly teenagers should report illegal acts to the...of a wide audience. If you post something on your...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7438-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7438_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:51:46">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=175911</link><title>Facebook Faux Pas: Awkward! Or Maybe Not</title><description>Survey found those intent on putting best face forward were likelier to feel bad about online miscues...he said.On the other hand, people who reported more sophisticated Facebook skills were less...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7438-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7438_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:53:11">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=163330</link><title>Can Facebook Prolong Post-Breakup Pain?</title><description>Those who 'stalk' their ex electronically show more longing, less personal growth, study says...on an individual's privacy settings, even an "unfriended" ex may be able to glean information from...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7438-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7438_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:53:53">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=168444</link><title>Facebook 'Likes' Leave a Personal Trail, Study Warns</title><description>...beliefs and even intelligence can be gathered by others, raising privacy concerns, researchers report...Facebook seems casual and relatively unimportant to the user. What's surprising is that...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7438-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7438_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:54:34">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=174787</link><title>Beware of Affordable Care Act Scammers</title><description>...insulted if you say you want to check out their web site and organization.Check the privacy settings if you use social media. Thieves are good at pulling information off sites such as Facebook.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7438-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7438_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:55:19">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=156166</link><title>Physician Misconduct Showing Up on the Internet: Survey</title><description>New poll of medical boards reports online professional violations by doctors...and patients need to be aware of medical misconduct on blogs, Twitter, Facebook and other social media and online venues...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>