<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7439">make crown</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:56:55" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7439-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7439_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:56:56">http://www.medicinenet.com/cosmetic_dentistry_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Cosmetic Dentistry Pictures Slideshow: Before and After</title><description>...can improve your smile? See before &amp; after pictures of what braces, dental implants, crowns, veneers, teeth whitening,...Cosmetic dental procedures, including bridges, crowns, whitening,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7439-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7439_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:58:38">http://www.medicinenet.com/image-collection/dental_makeover_picture/picture.htm</link><title>Picture of Dental Makeover</title><description>A combination of dental techniques can be used to achieve a great smile. See a picture of Dental...techniques can be used to achieve a great smile. Porcelain veneers and crowns can correct crooked...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7439-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7439_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 06:59:59">http://www.medicinenet.com/hair_loss_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Hair Loss Pictures Slideshow: Causes, Treatments and Solutions for Men &amp; Women</title><description>Experiencing hair loss? Watch and learn about causes, treatments and solutions for conditions such as male\- and female-pattern...and ponytails can pull hard enough on hairs to make them fall out. If...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7439-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7439_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:01:23">http://www.medicinenet.com/dental_crowns/article.htm</link><title>Dental Crowns</title><description>Dental crowns are caps that encase the tooth with the purpose of restoring the size, shape, strength or appearance of the tooth...the tooth for very long. Occasionally, a temporary crown will purposely...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7439-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7439_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:02:32">http://www.medicinenet.com/hair_and_scalp_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Hair and Scalp Pictures Slideshow: What They Say About Your Health</title><description>Is your hair trying to tell you something about your health? Some medications and conditions affect your hair as well as your body...involving the temples, frontal hairline, and crown of the scalp,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7439-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7439_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:03:30">http://www.medicinenet.com/brighter_whiter_teeth_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Dental Health: 10 Secrets to Brighter, Whiter Teeth Pictures Slideshow</title><description>Want brighter, whiter teeth? Watch this slideshow to find out which teeth whitening strategies perk...whiteners if you have had some types of dental work such as crowns, bonding, veneers, fillings,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7439-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7439_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:04:16">http://www.medicinenet.com/root_canal/article.htm</link><title>Root Canal</title><description>A root canal is a dental procedure that's used to save an infected tooth. Treatment involves removing the tooth's nerve and pulp...The dentist may choose to do the crown immediately, or may wait a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7439-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7439_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:06:07">http://www.medicinenet.com/gum_problems/article.htm</link><title>Gum Problems</title><description>Gum problems may be caused by improper brushing and flossing, gum disease, canker sores, treatments and hormonal changes. Symptoms...with dental braces and dental work such as dental crowns because...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7439-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7439_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:08:26">http://www.medicinenet.com/dental_implants/article.htm</link><title>Dental Implants</title><description>Dental implants are replacement tooth roots that are anchored into the jawbone in order to secure and provide a foundation for...the area to be considered for the dental implant and makes an...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7439-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7439_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:10:50">http://www.medicinenet.com/cavities/article.htm</link><title>Cavities</title><description>Learn more about cavities including symptoms, treatment, and prevention. See how tooth decay, plaque, and bacteria contribute to...is known as tooth remineralization. Fluoride makes the enamel more...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>