<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7445">marathon training</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:50:41" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7445-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7445_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:50:42">http://www.medicinenet.com/adhd_pictures_slideshow_parenting_tips/article.htm</link><title>ADHD Pictures Slideshow: Tips for Parenting a Child With ADHD</title><description>Get tips for parenting a child with ADHD (attention deficit hyperactivity disorder). Parents can learn tips and techniques in this...your child's less positive behaviors like training for a marathon.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7445-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7445_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:51:34">http://www.medicinenet.com/depression_tips_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Depression Pictures Slideshow: Tips for Exercise, Diet and Stress Reduction</title><description>The right exercise, diet, and activities \-- even playing with a pet \--can help you recover from...Choose an Exercise You Enjoy If you don’t like to run, you won't last long training for a marathon.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7445-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7445_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:52:14">http://www.onhealth.com/tips_for_parenting_a_child_with_adhd/article.htm</link><title>Tips for Parenting a Child with ADHD</title><description>Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) can be challenging for a parent or caregiver with a child with this disorder...of changing your child's less positive behaviors like training for a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7445-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7445_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:53:19">http://www.medicinenet.com/running/article.htm</link><title>Running</title><description>Running is the sixth most popular exercise in the U.S. The health benefits of running include increases in HDL cholesterol and...millions of Americans. Thousands of road races and marathons occur each...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7445-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7445_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:55:24">http://www.medicinenet.com/senior_exercise/article.htm</link><title>Senior Exercise</title><description>Since muscle mass decreases as people age, it's important for older adults to exercise, as it keeps seniors strong, helps to burn...just that it isn't clear how much flexibility training older adults...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7445-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7445_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:56:32">http://www.medicinenet.com/pilates/article.htm</link><title>Pilates</title><description>Pilates was created in the 1920s by Joseph Pilates for the purpose of rehabilitation. It improves flexibility, strength, and body...of 24 females who did either traditional weight training or the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7445-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7445_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:58:14">http://www.medicinenet.com/swimming/article.htm</link><title>Swimming</title><description>Swimming is a low-impact form of exercise that's easy on the joints, builds cardiorespiratory fitness and muscle mass, and is an...can work your upper body. Pull buoys are excellent training devices...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7445-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7445_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 07:59:06">http://www.onhealth.com/osteoporosis/article.htm</link><title>Osteoporosis</title><description>Learn about osteoporosis, a condition characterized by the loss of bone density, which leads to an increased risk of bone fracture...in women who undergo extremely vigorous exercise training and in...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7445-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7445_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:01:15">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=78814</link><title>Fitness: Changing Up Your Workout Routine</title><description>...is true that in the first few weeks or months of a training program there is a learning curve where the body becomes biomechanically more...rate remain the same for the same level of exertion. Take...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7445-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7445_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:02:14">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=80625</link><title>Early Red Flags and Warning Signs of Autism</title><description>Autism signs and symptoms at an early age include lack of gestures, smiles and unusual posture...place, because this is more than a race and bigger than a marathon. It's a series of marathons...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>