<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7446">cycling on the mont ventoux</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:03:08" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7446-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7446_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:03:10">http://www.medicinenet.com/osteoarthritis_active_living_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Osteoarthritis Pictures Slideshow: Active Living From Day to Night</title><description>Check out this slideshow on Active Living From Day to Night with Osteoarthritis. Even with arthritis you can keep your active...Day to Night Reviewed by Varnada Karriem-Norwood, MD on Friday, June 29,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7446-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7446_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:03:59">http://www.medicinenet.com/exercises_for_copd_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>COPD Pictures Slideshow: 10 Smart Exercises for People With COPD</title><description>Watch this slideshow on 10 Smart Exercises for People With Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease (COPD). If you have COPD, give...People With COPD Reviewed by Brunilda Nazario, MD on Monday, September...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7446-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7446_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:05:44">http://www.medicinenet.com/exercise_and_fitness_quiz/quiz.htm</link><title>Exercise and Fitness Quiz: Test Your IQ</title><description>Take our Exercise and Fitness Quiz and learn to maximize your fitness level with simple exercises...re healthy and you know it, you can start exercising, but err on the side of being too slow than...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7446-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7446_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:06:52">http://www.medicinenet.com/cycling_biking_or_bicycling/article.htm</link><title>Cycling</title><description>Bicycling is a low-impact form of cardiovascular exercise that builds endurance and tones the hips, thighs, and glutes while...Cycling (Biking or Bicycling) What is the history of biking? What are the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7446-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7446_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:08:14">http://www.medicinenet.com/teen_boys_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Teen Boys Pictures Slideshow: Sports, Gym and Locker Room Gross-Outs</title><description>Team spirit isn't the only thing that grows in locker rooms. Watch this slideshow on sports health for teen boys. From yellow...Room Gross-Outs Reviewed by Renee A. Alli, MD, FAAP on Friday, March 02,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7446-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7446_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:09:31">http://www.medicinenet.com/fibromyalgia_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Fibromyalgia Pictures Slideshow: Photos of Causes, Diagnosis, Symptoms &amp; Treatment</title><description>...fibromyalgia (fibrositis) with pictures, a chronic condition that causes pain and stiffness of the tendons, muscles, and joints...Reviewed by William C. Shiel Jr., MD, FACP, FACR on Monday, June 18,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7446-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7446_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:10:41">http://www.onhealth.com/weight_loss/article.htm</link><title>Weight Loss</title><description>Successful weight loss and healthy weight management depend on sensible goals and expectations. Most people should lose weight...You can achieve this either by cutting back on your food intake, by...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7446-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7446_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:12:14">http://www.medicinenet.com/swimming/article.htm</link><title>Swimming</title><description>Swimming is a low-impact form of exercise that's easy on the joints, builds cardiorespiratory fitness and muscle mass, and is an...an activity that burns lots of calories, is easy on the joints,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7446-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7446_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:13:53">http://www.medicinenet.com/interval_training/article.htm</link><title>Interval Training</title><description>Interval training is thought to have originated in Sweden, where it's called fartlek training. Interval training is a method of...say you usually train comfortably at 6 mph on the treadmill. So, after...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7446-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7446_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:15:32">http://www.medicinenet.com/bipolar_disorder/article.htm</link><title>Bipolar Disorder</title><description>Bipolar disorder (or manic depression) is a mental illness characterized by depression, mania, and severe mood swings. Treatment...bipolar type I and bipolar type II disorder based on the severity of...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>