<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7447">running shoes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:16:35" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7447-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7447_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:16:37">http://www.medicinenet.com/feet_facts_quiz/quiz.htm</link><title>Feet Facts Quiz: Test Your Medical IQ</title><description>Did you know that certain shoes and common diseases can wreak havoc on your feet? If you've been...prolonged walking or running. The correct answer is: • True Explanation:...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7447-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7447_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:17:21">http://www.medicinenet.com/slideshow_pictures_budget_friendly_exercise_gadget/article.htm</link><title>Exercise and Fitness Pictures Slideshow: 10 Budget-Friendly Exercise Gadgets</title><description>There are plenty of inexpensive and free ways to exercise. Watch this slideshow about budget-friendly exercise gadgets and learn...Stability ball: $10-$20." * Walking or Running Shoes ($40-$120) "If...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7447-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7447_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:18:00">http://www.medicinenet.com/diabetes_foot_problems_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Diabetes and Foot Problems Pictures Slideshow</title><description>Watch this slideshow on diabetes related foot problems. For people with diabetes, too much glucose in the blood can cause serious...common cause of ingrown toenails is pressure from shoes. Other...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7447-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7447_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:18:35">http://www.medicinenet.com/running/article.htm</link><title>Running</title><description>Running is the sixth most popular exercise in the U.S. The health benefits of running include increases in HDL cholesterol and...running outdoors vs. a treadmill? What about the risk of running...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7447-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7447_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:20:11">http://www.medicinenet.com/teen_boys_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Teen Boys Pictures Slideshow: Sports, Gym and Locker Room Gross-Outs</title><description>Team spirit isn't the only thing that grows in locker rooms. Watch this slideshow on sports health for teen boys. From yellow...very painful and may even interfere with walking or running.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7447-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7447_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:20:49">http://www.medicinenet.com/broken_foot/article.htm</link><title>Broken Foot</title><description>...of ways. Falling from heights, dropping heavy objects on the foot, or stress fractures from running or walking. Treatment of a...a daily basis, absorbing the pounding of walking, running, and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7447-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7447_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:21:49">http://www.medicinenet.com/foot_pain/article.htm</link><title>Foot Pain</title><description>Foot pain may be caused by injuries (sprains, strains, bruises, and fractures), diseases (diabetes, Hansen disease, and gout),...Microtrauma injuries can be caused by running on uneven surfaces or...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7447-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7447_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:23:04">http://www.medicinenet.com/patellofemoral_syndrome/article.htm</link><title>Chondromalacia Patella (Patellofemoral Syndrome)</title><description>Chondromalacia patella (housemaid's knee or secretary's knee) results from misalignment of the kneecap as it slides over the lower...resistance but high rpms), pool running, or swimming (flutter...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7447-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7447_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:24:55">http://www.medicinenet.com/heel_spurs/article.htm</link><title>Heel Spurs</title><description>Heel spurs, pointed, bony outgrowths of the heel, are caused by localized soft tissue inflammation and can be located at the back...cortisone, are often helpful. Orthotic devices or shoe inserts are...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7447-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7447_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:25:52">http://www.medicinenet.com/walking/article.htm</link><title>Walking</title><description>Walking has numerous health benefits. Learn how walking can help you, how much you need to do to...of walking is that you don't need lots of fancy equipment, but shoes can make a difference. There...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>