<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7452">arizona game and fish homepage</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:54:41" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7452-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7452_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:54:42">http://www.medicinenet.com/pictures_slideshow_foods_to_boost_male_health/article.htm</link><title>Men's Health Pictures Slideshow: Foods to Boost Male Health</title><description>Watch and learn about foods that boost male health including oysters, cherries, and ginger which keep men on top of their game;...calories from fat. Olive oil and nuts also contain good fats. Fatty...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7452-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7452_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:56:22">http://www.medicinenet.com/healthy_eating_at_restaurants_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Healthy Eating at Restaurants Pictures Slideshow: Don't Abandon Your Diet</title><description>See how to recognize the dangers and stay on your healthy diet when eating out. Watch this slideshow to learn about healthy eating...An upscale bistro. Pizza after the ball game. Fast food with the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7452-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7452_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:57:26">http://www.medicinenet.com/mercury_poisoning/article.htm</link><title>Mercury Poisoning</title><description>Mercury is a naturally occurring element found in water, soil, and the air. Mercury is also contained in some fish, some of the...mercury in dental amalgam? What about mercury in fish? What about...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7452-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7452_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:58:21">http://www.medicinenet.com/dry_skin/article.htm</link><title>Dry Skin</title><description>...may be caused by external factors, like cold temperatures, low humidity, harsh soaps, and certain medications, or internal...foods include flax, walnuts, safflower oil, and cold-water fish such as...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7452-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7452_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 08:59:07">http://www.medicinenet.com/beach_body_essentials_for_men_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Exercise and Fitness Pictures Slideshow: Beach Body Essentials for Men</title><description>...this slideshow on Beach Body Essentials for Men. Get yourself beach ready before you hit the sand with our visual guide to...can last through a 40-80 minute beach volleyball game. Gels work well...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7452-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7452_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:00:20">http://www.medicinenet.com/toddler_food_guidelines/article.htm</link><title>Toddler Food Guidelines</title><description>With all the temper tantrums, picky eating, and food throwing you may wonder if your toddler is getting enough to eat. Children...grains, vegetables, and fruits. Protein sources include meats...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7452-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7452_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:01:28">http://www.medicinenet.com/food_poisoning/article.htm</link><title>Food Poisoning</title><description>...but can also be life threatening. The most common form of food poisoning is caused by bacteria and include symptoms such as fever,...to a large release of histamine chemical from the fish when it is...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7452-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7452_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:02:24">http://www.medicinenet.com/hurricane_preparedness/article.htm</link><title>Hurricane Preparedness</title><description>Natural diasters such as a hurricane can take a toll on family, friends, and neighbors. Both physiological and psychological...storm Keys to the home, vehicles, sheds Toys, books, and games for...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7452-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7452_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:03:46">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=14549</link><title>Heart Healthy Guidelines</title><description>...eating plan. Choose heart-healthy foods from different food groups--meat, poultry, fish, and shellfish; dairy foods; eggs; fruits and vegetables; breads, cereals, pasta, rice...hiking, swimming, or...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7452-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7452_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:04:24">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=23373</link><title>Fast Food Salads High in Fat</title><description>...Salad: Tuna salad's biggest downfall is the high-fat combination o fish and mayonnaise -- and a mighty downfall it caused. Containing 25 Grams of...want. Stick with fresh vegetables, the rare gems...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>