<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7453">pc 2 games reviews</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:05:39" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7453-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7453_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:05:42">http://www.medicinenet.com/beach_body_essentials_for_men_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Exercise and Fitness Pictures Slideshow: Beach Body Essentials for Men</title><description>Watch this slideshow on Beach Body Essentials for Men. Get yourself beach ready before you hit the sand with our visual guide to...the elbows to push back up. Do 2-3 sets of as many reps as..</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7453-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7453_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:06:31">http://www.medicinenet.com/swimming/article.htm</link><title>Swimming</title><description>Swimming is a low-impact form of exercise that's easy on the joints, builds cardiorespiratory fitness and muscle mass, and is an...old age. In this article, I'll review the history of swimming, the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7453-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7453_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:07:47">http://www.medicinenet.com/food_poisoning/article.htm</link><title>Food Poisoning</title><description>Food poisoning is common, but can also be life threatening. The most common form of food poisoning is caused by bacteria and...breath, and difficulty swallowing within 1 to 2 hour of eating.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7453-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7453_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:08:47">http://www.medicinenet.com/attention_deficit_hyperactivity_disorder_in_teens/article.htm</link><title>Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD) in Teens</title><description>Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) in teens is a disruption of neurocognitive functioning. Genetics contribute to...with males being diagnosed with this disorder 2.5 times more often...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7453-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7453_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:09:54">http://www.medicinenet.com/running/article.htm</link><title>Running</title><description>Running is the sixth most popular exercise in the U.S. The health benefits of running include increases in HDL cholesterol and...all the fuss is about. I'll review the history of running, how to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7453-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7453_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:11:39">http://www.onhealth.com/attention_deficit_hyperactivity_disorder_adhd/article.htm</link><title>ADHD (Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder in Children)</title><description>Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) is a behavioral disorder characterized by the symptoms hyperactivity, impulsivity,...1 for the predominantly hyperactive type vs. 2:1 for the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7453-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7453_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:12:58">http://www.medicinenet.com/pilates/article.htm</link><title>Pilates</title><description>Pilates was created in the 1920s by Joseph Pilates for the purpose of rehabilitation. It improves flexibility, strength, and body...an alternative or complement to weight lifting, (2) might need...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7453-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7453_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:14:01">http://www.medicinenet.com/exercise_and_activity/article.htm</link><title>Fitness</title><description>Regular physical activity can reduce the risk of disease. Regular exercise can also reduce the...of developing coronary heart disease, stroke, non-insulin-dependent (type 2) diabetes mellitus, high...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7453-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7453_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:15:31">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=222</link><title>First Aid Disaster Kit For Your Family</title><description>...recommendations. How do I prepare my kit? Review the checklists in this document. Gather the...include: Sterile adhesive bandages in assorted sizes 2-inch sterile gauze pads (4-6) 4...lenses and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7453-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7453_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:16:32">http://www.medicinenet.com/2008_airport_food_review_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>2008 Airport Food Review Pictures Slideshow: Ranking of the Nation's 15 Busiest Airports</title><description>Where can a hungry air travelers find a healthful meal? Watch this slideshow as nutrionists from the Physicians Committee for...2008 Airport Food Review Pictures Slideshow: Ranking of the Nation's...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>