<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7456">gps reviews</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:27:42" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7456-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7456_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:27:43">http://www.medicinenet.com/pedometers/article.htm</link><title>Pedometers</title><description>Pedometers objectively measure physical activity by keeping track of how many steps you've taken...activity recall. They can also be fun! In this article, I'll review how pedometers work, how to use...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7456-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7456_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:28:41">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=170222</link><title>Smartphone Apps Can Make Workouts More Fun</title><description>Latest technology lets you jog along with zombies, bulls and race cars...you can use the supplies you picked up during your run to fortify your community. The GPS statistics from your run are uploaded...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7456-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7456_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:29:54">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=150872</link><title>Restore Your Near Vision -- Without Reading Glasses</title><description>...taking a quick look at a menu, at the GPS in the car, and so on," he says.These findings were presented at a medical conference. They should be considered preliminary as they have not yet undergone...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7456-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7456_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:31:18">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=147960</link><title>'Cyberstalking': Worse Than in-Person Harassment?</title><description>...Among them: Installing spyware on a target's computer or via email; GPS (global positioning system) surveillance of the movement of victims; posting personal or...should be considered preliminary...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7456-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7456_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:32:13">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=175726</link><title>The Challenge of Tracking What People Eat</title><description>...says, scientists would be able to hook research subjects up to a GPS device to track their movement, monitor what they eat and how much...should be considered preliminary as they have not yet...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>