<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7457">the music man lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:34:07" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7457-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7457_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:34:09">http://www.medicinenet.com/unzip_your_sex_life_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Sexual Health Pictures Slideshow: Men \- Tips to Unzip Your Sex Life and Make it Great</title><description>Men: How to unzip your sex life and make it great? Watch this slideshow to get tips for more sexual pleasure such as better...Sexual Health Pictures Slideshow: Men \- Tips to Unzip Your Sex Life and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7457-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7457_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:35:54">http://www.medicinenet.com/mens_embarrassing_body_problem_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Men's Health Pictures Slideshow: Embarrassing Male Body Problems</title><description>See embarrassing body problems for men such as belly fat, back hair, sweating, erectile dysfunction, gas, body odor, and bad...Men's Health Pictures Slideshow: Embarrassing Male Body Problems...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7457-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7457_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:37:04">http://www.medicinenet.com/tween_child_development/article.htm</link><title>Tween: Child Development</title><description>Developmental milestones for tweens 9-11 years of age include the ability to use deductive reasoning to anticipate consequences,...fantasy fears (such as witches, monsters, boogie man). The development...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7457-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7457_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:38:13">http://www.medicinenet.com/high_blood_pressure_treatment/article.htm</link><title>High Blood Pressure Treatment</title><description>High blood pressure (hypertension) means high pressure (tension) in the arteries. Treatment for high blood pressure include...body mass index (BMI), a measure of overall obesity. Men should strive for...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7457-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7457_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:39:33">http://www.medicinenet.com/20_hottest_fitness_trends_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Exercise &amp; Fitness Pictures Slideshow: 20 Hottest Fitness Trends for Men and Women</title><description>What are the 20 hottest fitness trends for men and women this year? Watch this slideshow to see the latest exercise crazes such as...Pictures Slideshow: 20 Hottest Fitness Trends for Men and Women...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7457-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7457_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:40:42">http://www.medicinenet.com/quit_smoking_tips_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Quit-Smoking Pictures Slideshow: 13 Tips to End Your Addiction</title><description>...and find practical tips to help you break your nicotine addiction and kick the cigarette habit for...when quitting smoking. Helpful methods can include yoga, tai chi, music, massage, and exercise.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7457-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7457_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:42:18">http://www.medicinenet.com/teen_depression/article.htm</link><title>Teen Depression</title><description>Depression in teenagers may be caused by many factors. Symptoms of teen depression include apathy, irresponsible behavior,...are encouraged to interpret their environment and respond to it compared to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7457-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7457_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:43:37">http://www.medicinenet.com/bullying/article.htm</link><title>Bullying</title><description>...physical or verbal aggression that involves an imbalance of power. The four types of bullying...who engage in these behaviors are males 60% of the time. While men who bully tend to direct their...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7457-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7457_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:44:32">http://www.medicinenet.com/aerobic_exercise/article.htm</link><title>Aerobic Exercise</title><description>Aerobic exercise is any form of exercise that can be sustained for more than a few minutes while your heart, lungs, and muscles...more. Here's a partial list of the documented health benefits of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7457-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7457_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:46:08">http://www.medicinenet.com/dementia/article.htm</link><title>Dementia</title><description>...for dementias such as cortical, subcortical, progressive, primary, and secondary dementias. Other conditions and medication...In many cases, it may coexist with AD. The incidence of vascular...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>