<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7461">navalni trial latest news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:14:07" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7461-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7461_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:14:08">http://www.medicinenet.com/aids_retrospective_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>AIDS Retrospective Pictures Slideshow: A Pictorial Timeline of the HIV/AIDS Pandemic</title><description>Get a historical overview of the HIV/AIDS pandemic from human contraction to the present through...access to lifesaving drugs still in clinical trials. The first World AIDS day is held...HIV...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7461-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7461_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:15:26">http://www.medicinenet.com/new_hepatitis_c_treatments/views.htm</link><title>New Hepatitis C Treatments</title><description>There are several clinical drug trials currently underway that suggests soon they may be able to eradicate the hepatitis C virus...of Liver Disease in Boston, the results of many trials of new drugs...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7461-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7461_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:16:07">http://www.medicinenet.com/health_news_2009_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Health News Pictures Slideshow: Top 10 Stories of 2009</title><description>Watch this slideshow to see photos that capture the top 10 health news stories of 2009 from lost...Health News Pictures Slideshow: Top 10 Stories of 2009 Reviewed by Louise Chang, MD...eight...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7461-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7461_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:17:56">http://www.medicinenet.com/autism_and_communication/article.htm</link><title>Autism Spectrum Disorder (In Children and Adults)</title><description>Autism in children and adults is a developmental disorder, characterized by impaired development in communication, social...managing autism in closely controlled clinical trials. In the past, a piece...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7461-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7461_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:18:56">http://www.medicinenet.com/eye_diseases_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Eye Diseases Pictures Slideshow: Recognize These Common Eye Conditions</title><description>Eye diseases can cause damage and blindness if not detected and treated soon enough. Watch this slideshow to learn the warning...none of these have been proven effective in clinical trials.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7461-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7461_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:19:36">http://www.medicinenet.com/caregiver_burnout_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Senior Health Pictures Slideshow: 23 Ways to Avoid Caregiver Burnout</title><description>Watch this slideshow on 23 Ways to Avoid Caregiver Burnout. Pets, music, pill organizers, and...speaker phone or online video chat. Have an agenda to discuss the latest medical news, daily...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7461-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7461_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:21:01">http://www.medicinenet.com/pulmonary_fibrosis/article.htm</link><title>Pulmonary Fibrosis</title><description>Pulmonary fibrosis is scarring throughout the lungs. Pulmonary fibrosis can be caused by many conditions including chronic...with specific experience in this field. Research trials using different...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7461-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7461_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:22:26">http://www.medicinenet.com/hyperhidrosis/article.htm</link><title>Excessive Sweating (Hyperhidrosis)</title><description>Hyperhidrosis is excessive sweating of the underarms, palms, or soles of the feet. Treatment may involve over-the-counter...Botulinum toxin (Botox), a muscle poison much in the news as a cosmetic...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7461-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7461_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:24:04">http://www.medicinenet.com/fiber/article.htm</link><title>Fiber</title><description>Fiber is a nondigestible carbohydrate that's known to have beneficial physiological effects in humans. Fiber falls into two...of a high soluble fiber supplement. A German clinical trial reported that...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7461-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7461_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:25:24">http://www.medicinenet.com/sarcoidosis/article.htm</link><title>Sarcoidosis</title><description>Sarcoidosis, a disease resulting from chronic inflammation, causes small lumps (granulomas) to develop in a great range of body...None have been evaluated in controlled clinical trials, and the risk...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>