<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7463">hollywood actress</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:27:54" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7463-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7463_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:27:55">http://www.medicinenet.com/perfect_brows_and_lashes_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Skin and Beauty Pictures Slideshow: How to Get Perfect Eyebrows and Eyelashes</title><description>Watch this slideshow on How to Get Better Eyebrows and Eyelashes. See how to maintain perfectly...your brows to instantly go darker or lighter. Get The Natural Look Actress Camilla Belle proves you...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7463-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7463_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:29:32">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=50581</link><title>Inner Beauty</title><description>...her health and beauty - without resorting to the cosmetic surgery that is sometimes used by her Hollywood peers. The actress spoke...Inner Beauty Susan Sarandon Defies Hollywood by Aging Gracefully...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7463-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7463_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:31:21">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=50357</link><title>Fad Diets: Revisiting Fad Diets of the Past</title><description>...the cabbage soup diet, the Beverly Hills diet, the grapefruit diet, the Scarsdale diet, the Hollywood juice diet, to name just a...in two weeks; the Beverly Hills diet, created by actress Judy...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7463-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7463_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:32:18">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=125827</link><title>Stroke Takes a Toll on Hollywood Stars</title><description>...have in common, besides being Hollywood stars of course?Answer: All are Oscar nominees or winners who suffered a stroke, an event that took a tremendous toll on their and other stars' careers.Of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7463-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7463_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:32:59">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=54358</link><title>Health Makeover: Week Two with Marilu Hennner</title><description>Join actress Marilu Henner, star of stage and screen, for a four-week special WEBCAST series based...leading men and worked with some of the best directors in Hollywood and on Broadway. She...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7463-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7463_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:34:19">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=54361</link><title>THealth Makeover with Marilu Henner: Week Three</title><description>Join actress Marilu Henner, star of stage and screen, for a four-week special WEBCAST series based...leading men and worked with some of the best directors in Hollywood and on Broadway. She...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7463-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7463_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:35:03">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=169836</link><title>Angelina Jolie Has Preventative Double Mastectomy</title><description>Testing revealed she carries a genetic mutation that left her susceptible to breast cancer...By Steven ReinbergHealthDay ReporterTUESDAY, May 14 (HealthDay News) -- Hollywood film star Angelina Jolie...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7463-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7463_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:35:42">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=175887</link><title>Only High-Risk Women Need Breast Cancer Gene Test: Experts</title><description>Even those with family history of BRCA mutations should talk with professionals first, panel says...in genetic testing for breast cancer has greatly increased, partially due to Hollywood film star...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7463-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7463_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:37:12">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=141116</link><title>Elizabeth Taylor Dies of Heart Failure</title><description>Elizabeth Taylor Dies of Heart Failure Legendary Actress, 79, Had Been Diagnosed With Congestive Heart Failure in 2004 By Matt...she was cast in nearly 60 films. Several of them are among Hollywood's...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7463-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7463_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:37:42">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=54357</link><title>Eating on the Road Is a Piece of Cake: How the Stars Keep It Off with Nikki Haskell</title><description>Former Hollywood starlet Nikki Haskell is the author of numerous books and articles who has her own beauty line. She will be...chefs wherever they go. You could run an ad in the Hollywood Reporter or...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>