<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7466">interconnects skin effect</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:41:44" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7466-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7466_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:41:46">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=21735</link><title>Cancer Treatment Side Effects: Skin and Nails</title><description>Cancer Treatment Side Effects: Skin and Nails You may have minor skin problems while you are having...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7466-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7466_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:43:25">http://www.medicinenet.com/smoking_effects_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Smoking Effects Pictures Slideshow: How Smoking Affects Your Looks and Life</title><description>See how the effects of smoking dramatically speed up wrinkles and aging, causes early menopause, hair loss, cataracts, sagging...Smoking Effects Pictures Slideshow: How Smoking Affects Your Looks...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7466-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7466_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:44:48">http://www.medicinenet.com/image-collection/portuguese_man_of_war_sting_picture/picture.htm</link><title>Picture of Portuguese Man of War Sting</title><description>One of the most painful effects on skin is the consequence of attack by oceanic hydrozoans known as Portuguese men-of-war, which...the Portuguese man-of-war. One of the most painful effects on skin is...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7466-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7466_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:45:34">http://www.medicinenet.com/sun_damaged_skin_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Sun-Damaged Skin Pictures Slideshow</title><description>See how the effects of sun damage to your skin can cause conditions of wrinkles, moles, melanoma (skin cancer) and more through...Sun-Damaged Skin Pictures Slideshow Reviewed by John P. Cunha, DO,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7466-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7466_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:46:51">http://www.medicinenet.com/dermabrasion/article.htm</link><title>Dermabrasion</title><description>Dermabrasion involves freezing and then sanding the skin. Dermabrasion improves the appearance of scars and other skin conditions,...and microdermabrasion? Are there any adverse side effects with...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7466-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7466_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:47:51">http://www.medicinenet.com/lyme_disease/article.htm</link><title>Lyme Disease</title><description>Lyme disease is a bacterial illness, which is spread by ticks when they bite the skin. Initially the disease affects the skin...is spread by tick bites. Lyme disease can affect the skin, joints,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7466-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7466_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:49:27">http://www.medicinenet.com/microdermabrasion/article.htm</link><title>Microdermabrasion</title><description>Microdermabrasion is a skin-exfoliating treatment that may improve the condition of acne scars and fine wrinkles. Skin should feel...with keratosis pilaris? What are possible side effects of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7466-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7466_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:50:53">http://www.medicinenet.com/radiation_therapy/article.htm</link><title>Radiation Therapy</title><description>...to kill cancer cells. Depending on the dose and the part of the body that is being treated, side effects of radiation may include...types of radiation therapy? What are the side effects of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7466-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7466_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:51:46">http://www.medicinenet.com/percutaneous_ethanol_injection_of_liver/article.htm</link><title>Percutaneous Ethanol (Alcohol) Injection of Liver</title><description>During percutaneous ethanol injection of the liver, pure alcohol is injected through the skin into liver cancers to kill the...percutaneous alcohol injection? What are the side effects of percutaneous...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7466-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7466_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:52:44">http://www.medicinenet.com/dry_mouth/article.htm</link><title>Dry Mouth (Xerostomia)</title><description>Dry mouth is a common side effect of many prescription and non-prescription drugs and certain medical conditions. Symptoms of dry...the oral tissues against ulcers, sores, and other effects of...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>