<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7473">noise canceling head phones</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:30:52" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7473-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7473_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:30:53">http://www.medicinenet.com/reasons_your_child_cant_sleep_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Children's Health Pictures Slideshow: Top Reasons Your Child Can't Sleep</title><description>Watch this slideshow on Reasons Your Child Can't Sleep. From snoring and nightmares to sleep apnea...even if they're breastfeeding. A white noise machine soothes their ears and hushes sounds..</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7473-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7473_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:31:20">http://www.medicinenet.com/autism_and_communication/article.htm</link><title>Autism Spectrum Disorder (In Children and Adults)</title><description>Autism in children and adults is a developmental disorder, characterized by impaired development in communication, social...may be an extreme intolerance to loud noises or crowds, visual...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7473-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7473_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:32:02">http://www.medicinenet.com/alzheimers_disease_causes_stages_and_symptoms/article.htm</link><title>Alzheimer's Disease</title><description>Alzheimer's disease is a common cause of dementia. Symptoms and warning signs of Alzheimer's disease include memory loss,...more often among people who suffered significant traumatic head injuries...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7473-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7473_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:33:13">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=20432</link><title>Hearing Loss and Aging</title><description>...Have a problem hearing because of background noise, Sense that others seem to mumble, or...or bacterial infections, heart conditions or stroke, head injuries, tumors, certain medicines, and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7473-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7473_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:34:34">http://www.medicinenet.com/fragile_x_syndrome/article.htm</link><title>Fragile X Syndrome</title><description>Fragile X syndrome is the most common inherited form of mental retardation. It's caused by a mutation on the X chromosome. People...children have very soft, velvety skin, a broad forehead, or a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7473-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7473_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:35:17">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=223</link><title>Earthquake Preparedness: Emergency Plan</title><description>...the family knows the name, address, and phone number of the contact person. 6. Help...desk near you, cover your face and head with your arms and crouch in an...smell gas or hear blowing or hissing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7473-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7473_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:36:43">http://www.onhealth.com/tinnitus/article.htm</link><title>Tinnitus</title><description>Tinnitus is a ringing or swishing that seems to originate in the ear or head. Most of the time it is not a serious problem (it is...Tinnitus(Ringing in the Ears and Other Ear Noise) Tinnitus facts...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7473-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7473_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:38:19">http://www.medicinenet.com/vertigo_balance_disorders_quiz/quiz.htm</link><title>Vertigo and Balance Disorders Quiz: Test Your Medical IQ</title><description>Take the quiz and find out the causes, symptoms, treatments, and ways to prevent the confusing...faint. Q:Vertigo is most commonly associated with which body part? AThe head BThe mind CThe inner...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7473-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7473_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:39:04">http://www.medicinenet.com/tinnitus_ringing_ears_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Tinnitus Pictures Slideshow: Why Are My Ears Ringing?</title><description>Learn causes, symptoms, relief remedies, treatments and prevention tips for Tinnitus (ringing in the...What Is Tinnitus? Tinnitus is a ringing, swishing, or other type of noise that seems to...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7473-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7473_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:40:21">http://www.medicinenet.com/fibromyalgia_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Fibromyalgia Pictures Slideshow: Photos of Causes, Diagnosis, Symptoms &amp; Treatment</title><description>Learn about fibromyalgia (fibrositis) with pictures, a chronic condition that causes pain and stiffness of the tendons, muscles,...the elbows, shoulders, knees, hips, back of the head, and the sides of...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>