<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7486">board games teenagers</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 22:04:25" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7486-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7486_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 22:04:27">http://www.onhealth.com/attention_deficit_hyperactivity_disorder_adhd/article.htm</link><title>ADHD (Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder in Children)</title><description>Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) is a behavioral disorder characterized by the symptoms hyperactivity, impulsivity,...others (for example, butts into conversations or games). DSM-IV...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7486-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7486_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 22:05:52">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=53702</link><title>Breast Cancer Husband</title><description>The impact of breast cancer is a tremor felt by every member of the family. Marc Silver felt this emotional earthquake when his...before you go out for a golf game. MEMBER QUESTION: How do I get my...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7486-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7486_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 22:07:25">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=51874</link><title>Parenting: Breaking the Thumb-Sucking Habit</title><description>It's OK for infants and toddlers to soothe themselves by sucking a thumb or finger, experts say. But if that child enters...sucking his finger when he's a teenager," says Sabine Hack, MD, assistant...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7486-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7486_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 22:08:27">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=119232</link><title>When It Comes to the Head, No Hit Is Normal</title><description>After repeated blows in various sports, teen nearly dies...charging through his final high school lacrosse game in San Diego, running full-tilt downfield...also digging after the ball. The two...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7486-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7486_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 22:09:44">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=56186</link><title>Heart Health: Choose to Move for a Healthy Heart</title><description>Heart disease is a leading killer of women. But there are things you can do to reduce your risk. Joan Lunden, an award-winning...walking up steps a few minutes every day, playing a game of tennis, or...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>