<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7496">why IEEE member</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 22:51:40" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7496-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7496_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 22:51:41">http://www.medicinenet.com/smoking_and_quitting_smoking/article.htm</link><title>Smoking (How to Quit Smoking)</title><description>...in the U.S. from smoking related illnesses. Secondhand smoke or "passive smoke" also harm family members, coworkers, and others...the health of children, unborn children, family members, and...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7496-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7496_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 22:53:12">http://www.medicinenet.com/heterochromia_iridis/article.htm</link><title>Heterochromia Iridis</title><description>...often recognized by a parent (in the case of an affected infant) or by the patient or a family member (acquired heterochromia...or in acquired cases, by the patient or a family member. Diagnosis...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7496-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7496_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 22:54:38">http://www.medicinenet.com/alprazolam/article.htm</link><title>alprazolam, Xanax, Xanax XR, Niravam</title><description>Alprazolam is a member of the benzodiazepine family, which are sedatives that cause dose-related depression of the central nervous...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7496-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7496_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 22:56:17">http://www.medicinenet.com/contagious_quiz/quiz.htm</link><title>Is It Contagious? Test Your Medical IQ</title><description>Is it contagious? Take this quiz to learn about contagious diseases, how contagious diseases are...contagious and cannot be passed from person to person, but it can occur in members of the same family...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7496-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7496_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 22:57:06">http://www.medicinenet.com/genetic_counseling/article.htm</link><title>Genetic Counseling</title><description>...to a genetic professional or genetics clinic. Genetic counseling provides patients and family members the tools to make the right...and evaluation? Genetic professionals work as members of health...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7496-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7496_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 22:58:01">http://www.medicinenet.com/phobias_picture_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Phobias Picture Slideshow: What Are You Afraid Of?</title><description>View a slideshow on phobias such as social, agoraphobia claustrophobia, arachnophobia and others...generally develops after a person witnesses a plane crash or loses a family member in a plane crash or...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7496-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7496_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 22:59:11">http://www.medicinenet.com/feet_facts_quiz/quiz.htm</link><title>Feet Facts Quiz: Test Your Medical IQ</title><description>Did you know that certain shoes and common diseases can wreak havoc on your feet? If you've been...Another colorful name for this condition is "jungle rot," often used by members of the armed services...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7496-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7496_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 23:00:04">http://www.medicinenet.com/eczema_atopic_dermatitis_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Eczema (Atopic Dermatitis) Pictures Slideshow: Causes, Symptoms and Treatment</title><description>Watch this slideshow on Eczema (Atopic Dermatitis). Learn about the causes, symptoms and treatment for eczema, as well as the...is seen most commonly in individuals who have family members who have...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7496-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7496_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 23:01:24">http://www.medicinenet.com/pregnancy_myths_and_facts_quiz/quiz.htm</link><title>Pregnancy Myths and Facts Quiz: Test Your Pregnancy IQ</title><description>Being pregnant is a delicate time for both mother and baby. Take this quiz to separate the myths and...correct answer is: • True Explanation: Folic acid, a member of the family of B...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7496-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7496_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 23:02:12">http://www.medicinenet.com/skin_problems_pictures_slideshow/article.htm</link><title>Skin Pictures Slideshow: Adult Skin Problems</title><description>Through this slideshow of pictures on adult skin problems, learn to spot and treat commonly found...of a linear blistering eruption occurs within 24-48 hours of exposure to a member of the poison ivy...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>