<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7499">gold price</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 23:05:08" name="MedicineNet" id="FW14-e071"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e071-7499-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7499_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 23:05:09">http://www.medicinenet.com/dentures/article.htm</link><title>Dentures</title><description>Dentures, removable replacements for missing teeth, come in two types: partial and complete dentures. Dental implants and bridges...tooth to both of the crowns. Bridges are made from gold, porcelain...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7499-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7499_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 23:06:11">http://www.medicinenet.com/diabetes_mellitus/article.htm</link><title>Diabetes (Type 1 and Type 2)</title><description>Diabetes mellitus is a chronic condition characterized by high levels of sugar (glucose) in the blood. The two types of diabetes...the oral glucose tolerance test (OGTT) is a gold standard for making...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7499-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7499_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 23:06:53">http://www.medicinenet.com/running/article.htm</link><title>Running</title><description>Running is the sixth most popular exercise in the U.S. The health benefits of running include increases in HDL cholesterol and...proving the superiority of the Aryan race by winning gold medals in the...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7499-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7499_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 23:07:52">http://www.medicinenet.com/fillings/article.htm</link><title>Fillings</title><description>...cavities and teeth that have been cracked, broken, or worn down. Filling materials include cast gold, silver amalgams, composite...are available. Teeth can be filled with gold; porcelain; silver...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7499-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7499_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 23:08:48">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=51711</link><title>Infertility Tests Every Aspect of a Couple's Life</title><description>Patti Gellman rode a physical and emotional roller coaster for two years trying to get pregnant for...eating a hot fudge sundae. "I think women pay a very high price with some of these infertility...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7499-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7499_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 23:10:19">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=50423</link><title>Medications: What to Avoid When Buying Drugs Online</title><description>Not all online pharmacies are equal. Here's what to look for and what to avoid when buying drugs...AIDS drug, came packaged in an aluminum can inside a box of "Gold Dye &amp; Stain Remover Wax."...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7499-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7499_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 23:11:41">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=62308</link><title>Chefs' Tips and Recipes for Healthier Cooking</title><description>4 top chefs share tips and recipes for lighter dishes that don't scrimp on taste and style...buy local, you not only get the most nutrients and the best prices, but you add a natural variety to your...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7499-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7499_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 23:12:44">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=173910</link><title>Report: Health-Reform Plans Seem to Have Lower-Than-Expected Premiums</title><description>But consumers need to weigh other factors, too, experts say...definitely have good prices," said Cristine Vogel, associate director in the Chicago health care office of Navigant Consulting Inc., a...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7499-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7499_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 23:13:59">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=172271</link><title>Maryland Releases Health Insurance Rates</title><description>...through its Marketplace, the Maryland Health Connection, starting Oct. 1.The prices vary depending upon your age, geographic location, whether you're a smoker, and the level of plan you choose. Of...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e071-7499-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e071/7499_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 23:15:22">http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=163735</link><title>Weight Watchers Gets Thumbs Up in Study</title><description>...group behavioral therapy delivered by a clinically trained professional is considered the "gold standard" in weight loss treatment.But these professionally led programs are typically..</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>