<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7057">web of science</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:15:17" name="KidsClicks!" id="FW14-e089"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e089-7057-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7057_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:15:18">http://science.howstuffworks.com/science-vs-myth/extrasensory-perceptions/hypnosis.htm</link><title>How Hypnosis Works</title><description>This website tells about the history and uses of hypnosis, and separates the facts from the myths about hypnosis.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7057-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7057_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:18:17">http://www.jsworldwide.com/</link><title>Jon Scieszka Worldwide</title><description>Welcome to the JSWorldwide website. Welcome to the place where folks from all over the world will find more than anyone needs to know about men made of stinky cheese, kids who act like squids, math curses, science verses, time warping, and random details about Jon Scieszka.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7057-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7057_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:20:02">http://www.dfat.gov.au/geo/australia/</link><title>Australia Country Information-Dept of Foreign Affairs and Trade</title><description>This section of the website goes into detail on various topics about Australia. Great for finding information for school reports. General topics include: people, culture, symbols, anthem, coat of arms, currency, kangaroos, education, health care, plants, and animals. There are also more detailed topics on: Australian people, Indigenous Australians, multicultural Australia, government, international relations, trade, economy, arts and sports, science, transportation, environment, and detailed government documents are available for viewing.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7057-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7057_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:22:19">http://www.emedicinehealth.com/abortion/article_em.htm</link><title>Abortion-Types, Preparation, and Procedure Information</title><description>eMedicineHealth.com provides an extensive web site full of facts about abortion. Learn about the legal history, the debate today, and the science and psychology of abortion.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7057-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7057_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:24:52">http://www.exploratorium.edu/cooking/</link><title>Science of Cooking</title><description>Discover how a pinch of curiosity can improve your cooking! Explore recipes, activities, and Webcasts that will enhance your understanding of the science behind food and cooking.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7057-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7057_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:26:16">http://www.mathpuzzle.com/</link><title>Mathpuzzle.com</title><description>Martin Gardner celebrated math puzzles and Mathematical Recreations. This site aims to do the same. The webmaster, Ed Pegg Jr, is a twenty year member of the National Puzzler's League, and frequently contributes to the New York Times crossword, Games, and National Public Radio's Sunday Puzzler.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7057-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7057_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:29:00">http://www.ontariosciencecentre.ca/</link><title>Ontario Science Center</title><description>This is the web site of the Ontario Science Center in Toronto Canada. It contains some interactive activities for children along with information about the center itself.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7057-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7057_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:29:48">https://www.cmnh.org/</link><title>The Cleveland Museum of Natural History</title><description>The searchable website of the Natural History Museum of Cleveland features current exhibits, research and collections information, classes and programs, and conservation information.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7057-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7057_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:32:34">http://www.scientology.org/</link><title>Scientology Home Page</title><description>The official Scientology website. Scientology is an applied religious philosophy. It holds in common many of the beliefs of other religions and philosophies, and considers man to be a spiritual being, with more to him than flesh and blood. It was founded by L. Ron Hubbard, who was also known for his self-help Dianetics program and science fiction novels.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7057-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7057_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:34:03">http://education.usgs.gov/</link><title>The US Geographical Survey</title><description>Visit often and explore things on, in, around, and about the Earth such as plants and animals, land, water, and maps. Learn how Biology, Geology, Hydrology, and Geography can help us understand our changing world.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>