<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7133">museum of natural history</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:55:39" name="KidsClicks!" id="FW14-e089"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e089-7133-01"><link>http://www.amnh.org/exhibitions/butterflies/</link><title>The Butterfly Conservatory-American Museum of Natural History</title><description>The Butterfly Conservatory is a beautiful and detailed informative website featuring detailed full size pictures of butterflies and full motion video of butterflies in action. You can also do numerous activities such as learn how to grow a butterfly garden or download backgrounds for your desktop.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7133-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7133_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:56:09">http://www.mnh.si.edu/earth/text/2_0_0.html</link><title>Dynamic Earth Gems and Minerals</title><description>Find out the difference between gems and minerals, read stories of famous gems, and learn about the building blocks of the universe. From the National Museum of Natural History.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7133-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7133_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:58:31">http://www.amnh.org/</link><title>American Museum of Natural History</title><description>Home to many of the nation's leading scientists, the American Museum of Natural History continues to build on a distinguished tradition of advanced research, seeking to identify and describe the earth and its myriad life forms, and to share the results of this work with a broad public. View their online exhibits.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7133-04"><link>http://www.amnh.org/ology/index.php?channel=marinebiology#channel</link><title>Ology-American Museum of Natural History</title><description>There are many different sections of this website to explore. You can learn all about the field of marine biology, how to make a coral reef, how you can help the ocean, take a journey to the bottom of the sea in a fun game, make your own ocean stationary, and a whole lot more.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7133-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7133_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:01:15">http://www.flmnh.ufl.edu/index.php/exhibits/always-on-display/butterfly-rainforest/visitor-info/</link><title>Butterfly Rainforest-Florida Museum of Natural History</title><description>If you are living or traveling anywhere near The University of Florida in Gainesville you might like to visit the Butterfly Rainforest. Learn all about the the Butterfly Rainforest and all the other exhibits dedicated to butterflies that the museum has to offer.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7133-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7133_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:02:09">http://www.carnegiemnh.org/</link><title>Carnegie Museum of Natural History</title><description>Welcome to the Carnegie Museum of Natural History, one of the six largest natural history museums in the nation. Through its explorations, collections, research, exhibitions, and educational programs, the Carnegie Museum of Natural History advances knowledge of the Earth, its life and cultures, and acts as a steward of our natural world; this is our mission.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7133-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7133_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:06:55">https://www.museumofwesternco.com/</link><title>Museum of Western Colorado</title><description>The Museum of Western Colorado's interests range from natural history and paleontology  dinosaurs!  to cultural and social history, Native American pottery, and western firearms. We hope that our Web site, like our Museum sites here in western Colorado, will be a learning experience that is fun!</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7133-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7133_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:08:12">http://www.flmnh.ufl.edu/</link><title>Florida Museum of Natural History</title><description>Welcome to the Florida Museum of Natural History, the largest natural history museum in the southern United States, holding more than 16,000,000 specimens of mammals, birds, reptiles, amphibians, fishes, mollusks, butterflies, vertebrate and invertebrate fossils, Recent and fossil plants, and associated databases and libraries in the main museum research facility, J.C. Dickinson Hall on the University of Florida Campus, Gainesville, and in the Allyn Museum of Entomology in Sarasota.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7133-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7133_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:11:20">http://www.nhm.org/site/</link><title>Natural History Museum</title><description>The Natural History Museum of Los Angeles County exists to advance knowledge and to enable people of all ages, backgrounds, and interests to appreciate their natural and cultural heritage. The Museum assembles, conserves, interprets, and holds in trust collections of irreplaceable objects from nature and human history. These collections reveal the history of the Earth and the evolution and diversity of life and culture. They sustain programs of research, exhibits, education, and publication.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7133-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7133_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:16:12">http://www.sbnature.org/</link><title>Santa Barbara Museum of Natural History</title><description>The Museum offers a close look at the story of the region's birth, geology and minerals, native wildlife, rich marine life and the culture of the Chumash Indians . Features include a 72-foot blue whale skeleton, the region's only public planetarium and observatory , a creek-side setting and a multi-cultural and science gift shop.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>