<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7348">map of the united states</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:03:59" name="KidsClicks!" id="FW14-e089"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e089-7348-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7348_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:04:00">http://www.learner.org/biographyofamerica/index.html</link><title>Annenberg Media - A Biography of America</title><description>Includes key events, maps, and transcripts for a living narrative of United States history. A companion to the video series.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7348-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7348_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:07:39">https://www.cia.gov/library/publications/the-world-factbook/geos/us.html</link><title>United States-CIA Factbook</title><description>This site includes an introduction to the country. You can see photos, the flag, and maps of the country. You can also click on the following topics to learn more: geography, people, government, economy, communications, transportation, military, and transnational issues.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7348-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7348_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:10:50">http://kids.nationalgeographic.com/kids/places/find/united-states-of-america/</link><title>United States of America-NatGeo Kids</title><description>This is a fun site for kids to learn and explore to learn about the U.S.A. You can read interesting facts and view pictures taken in the United States. There are videos about the train system in America, maps, cards, and links to many famous landmarks of the United States such as the Statue of Liberty.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7348-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7348_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:14:30">http://www.enchantedlearning.com/school/USA/</link><title>Zoom School-U.S.A.</title><description>This site is a fun way to learn interesting facts about the United States. You can do the following: learn about dinosaurs who lived in the area, read about the bald eagle, view and print flags, maps, and various symbols of the United States, read about imagined and real heroes such as Johnny Appleseed and Martin Luther King Jr, explore the presidency, and much more.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7348-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7348_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:18:43">http://www.ipl.org/div/stateknow/</link><title>Stately Knowledge-Internet Public Library</title><description>This site includes a map of the United States. You can click on individual states to learn more about them. There are also charts comparing the states to each other.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7348-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7348_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:20:25">http://pubs.er.usgs.gov/</link><title>USGS Maps Booklet</title><description>This booklet gives a brief overview of the types of maps sold and distributed by the USGS through its Earth Science Information Centers (ESIC) and also available from business partners located in most States. The USGS provides a wide variety of maps, from topographic maps showing the geographic relief and thematic maps displaying the geology and water resources of the United States, to special studies of the moon and planets.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7348-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7348_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:22:54">http://msrmaps.com/default.aspx</link><title>Microsoft Research Maps</title><description>The Microsoft Research Maps Web site is one of the world's largest online databases, providing free public access to a vast data store of maps and aerial photographs of the United States. Microsoft Research Maps is designed to work with commonly available computer systems and Web browsers over slow speed communications links.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7348-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7348_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:26:46">http://www.weather.gov/</link><title>National Weather Service</title><description>The National Weather Service provides an interactive map of the United States that is always updated to show where there are any weather or hazard warnings such as lake effect snow advisories, flash flood watches, high surf advisories, and many more.You can also view different observations and forecasts as well.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7348-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7348_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:30:09">http://www.americaslibrary.gov/es/index.php</link><title>Explore the States</title><description>This site provides a map of the United States. Click on the state you are interested in and you will be taken to a page about that state. A short introduction to that state is given, along with photos of the state map, state flag, and other state related photos. You can also click on several other stories about the state to learn some interesting facts about the state.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7348-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7348_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:32:37">http://www.ushmm.org/learn/students/the-holocaust-a-learning-site-for-students/</link><title>The Holocaust: A Learning site for Students</title><description>Organized by theme, this site uses text, historical photographs, maps, images of artifacts, and audio clips to provide an overview of the Holocaust. From the United States Holocaust Memorial Museum.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>