<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7484">earthquake</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:41:25" name="KidsClicks!" id="FW14-e089"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e089-7484-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7484_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:41:26">http://www.harpercollins.com/authors/12366/Patricia_Lauber/index.aspx</link><title>Patricia Lauber from HarperCollins Publishing</title><description>Patricia Lauber is the author of more than sixty-five books for young readers. Many of them are in the field of science, and their range reflects the diversity of her own interests-bats, dolphins, dogs, volcanoes, earthquakes, the ice ages, the Everglades, the planets, earthworms.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7484-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7484_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:42:30">https://gitso-outage.oracle.com/thinkquest</link><title>Natural Disasters Without Warning</title><description>Throughout this site you will find interesting facts about twisters, earthquakes, and volcanoes. This page is not only for the young people, but also for the older viewer. In this web site you will not only find information, you will also find fun quizzes and tough tongue twisters.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7484-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7484_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:45:56">http://www.ready.gov/tsunamis</link><title>FEMA for Kids-Tsunami</title><description>A tsunami is a series of huge waves that happen after an undersea disturbance, such as an earthquake or volcano eruption. Learn about the biggest ones that have happened and see which areas of the world are at the greatest risk of being struck.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7484-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7484_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:48:03">http://www.exploratorium.edu/faultline/index.html</link><title>Faultline, Seismic Science at the Epicenter</title><description>The Exploratorium presents a prolific website that has live data on earthquakes around the world, in depth statistics and stories about the greatest earthquakes in history, the basics of earthquakes, stories about how scientists and architects are preparing for the next big quake, and many more activities.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7484-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7484_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:48:53">http://walrus.wr.usgs.gov/tsunami/</link><title>Tsunami and Earthquake Research at the USGS</title><description>Here you will find general information on how local tsunamis are generated by earthquakes as well as animations, virtual reality models of tsunamis, and summaries of past research studies.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7484-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7484_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:51:17">http://www.planetseed.com/node/15228</link><title>SEED-Tsunami</title><description>An excellent website with in depth exploration of tsunamis including visualizations of tsunamis, earthquakes, geologic history and tons more. A must visit for anyone interested in tsunamis.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7484-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7484_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:55:30">http://www.fi.edu/earth/earth.html</link><title>EARTHFORCE</title><description>If you've ever felt the rumble of an earthquake or seen the eruption of a volcano, you've witnessed EARTHFORCE. EARTHFORCE is the pushing and pulling in the core, crust, or water of the Earth that causes motion like eruptions, quakes, or floods.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7484-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7484_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:58:03">http://www.nationalgeographic.com/eye/tornadoes/tornadoes.html</link><title>National Geographic-Eye in the Sky</title><description>National Geographic presents 'Eye in the Sky,' which is a look at natural disasters such as tornadoes, volcanoes, hurricanes, wild fires, and earthquakes around the world. Check out video clips and tons of fun facts about these phenomenons.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7484-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7484_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:02:10">http://www.pbs.org/wnet/savageearth/</link><title>Savage Earth</title><description>In this Web companion piece to the PBS series, original articles by journalists Daniel Pendick and Kathy Svitil explain the science behind volcanoes, earthquakes, and tsunamis, and feature original animations that illustrate the action of these natural phenomena. You can also Ask the Experts your questions, and explore other Savage Sites on the Web.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e089-7484-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e089/7484_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:04:56">http://nctr.pmel.noaa.gov/</link><title>Tsunami Research Program</title><description>Here you will learn how tsunamis are caused by underwater earthquakes.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>