<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7484">earthquake</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:25:08" name="LinkedIn Jobs" id="FW14-e079"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e079-7484-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e079/7484_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:25:09">http://www.linkedin.com/jobs2/view/13429055</link><title>Senior Build Engineer (MS Build, Batch scripting, Linux)</title><description>At RMS, we have big ideas around big data. We seek candidates that rise to challenges with the curiosity and mental dexterity to analyze and solve complex... more...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e079-7484-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e079/7484_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:27:43">http://www.linkedin.com/jobs2/view/11685962</link><title>Actuary - Commercial Insurance Product - Property Pricing Manager</title><description>Description Advance your actuarial career at Liberty Mutual Insurance - A Fortune 100 Company! Commercial Insurance Product Management has an exciting... more...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e079-7484-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e079/7484_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:28:36">http://www.linkedin.com/jobs2/view/13429011</link><title>Manager, Model Development (CAT Modeling, Insurance industry exp.)</title><description>RMS is the world's leading provider of analytics and decision science solutions for the quantification and management of catastrophic risks throughout the... more...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e079-7484-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e079/7484_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:30:15">http://www.linkedin.com/jobs2/view/13427663</link><title>Senior Software Engineer (GIS, Python)</title><description>Play a key role in a team developing the next generation RMS mapping platform and providing highly sophisticated, seamless integration of RMS GIS platform with... more...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e079-7484-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e079/7484_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:32:56">http://www.linkedin.com/jobs2/view/12948191</link><title>Senior Consultant (Informatica Developer), Client Integration Solutions</title><description>Senior Consultant (Informatica Developer), Client Integration Solutions Newark, CA   RMS is building an iPaaS integration layer to seamlessly integrate... more...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e079-7484-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e079/7484_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:33:52">http://www.linkedin.com/jobs2/view/13371105</link><title>Risk Management Leader</title><description>The Risk Management Services Strategic Leader designs, develops and executes on the strategy for providing exceptional nationwide risk management services... more...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e079-7484-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e079/7484_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:37:13">http://www.linkedin.com/jobs2/view/13249689</link><title>Desktop Engineer Lead</title><description>Job Description Desktop Engineer Lead:   Outline of Role: The Desktop Engineer Lead is responsible for technical leadership (evaluation, recommendation, and... more...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e079-7484-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e079/7484_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:39:50">http://www.linkedin.com/jobs2/view/13213817</link><title>Analytics Engineering Manager: data structures, algorithms, efficient data transformations</title><description>Reporting to the Senior Director of Analytical Development, you will lead a team of software engineers responsible for designing and developing the analytics,... more...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e079-7484-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e079/7484_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:42:14">http://www.linkedin.com/jobs2/view/13194448</link><title>Principal Software Engineer, Analytical Development (C#/.NET)</title><description>We want you to bring your ideas and software engineering skills to our dynamic, growing team!    Team Description RMS is currently building RMS(one), our... more...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e079-7484-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e079/7484_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 13:43:28">http://www.linkedin.com/jobs2/view/11494655</link><title>Senior Business Insight &amp; Analytics Manager</title><description>RMS is the world leader in catastrophe risk modeling. From earthquakes and hurricanes to terrorism and infectious disease, our models provide critical risk... more...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>