<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7001">LHC collision publications</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:50:44" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7001-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7001_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:50:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/front-end-collision-injury-1986</link><title>I was in a front-end collision and had a bad neck injury.</title><description>... I was in a front-end collision and had a bad neck injury. The MRI showed a torn ligament along the back of my neck. I wasn't even hit that hard by the other driver. Was this ligament defective and just ready to break? Research studies on frontal impact car collisions aren't very common. Based on data collected by insurance companies soft tissue injuries are more common with low-speed frontal collisions than we think. In fact up to 70 percent of the people in frontal impacts have neck injuries. Now a new study from the Biomechanics Research Lab at Yale University has some information to offer. They studied the effect of frontal impacts on soft tissues in the cervical spine. They found even low impact collisions can cause enough strain on a ligament to snap it. This occurs when the force of the impact is greater than the physiologic strength of the ligament. So it's possible there was nothing wrong with your ligament before the accident. Any past accidents, injuries, or strains could incre... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7001-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7001_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:51:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/76410/41234/led-permanent</link><title>Rear end collision led to rotator cuff surgery and neck,shoulder,back pain leading to permanent dis</title><description>...  I a 29 years old and was in a rear end collision in December of 2007, I have had rotator cuff surgery,numerous injections,mri's,xrays and just cant see why I have such pain in my back and neck, i do have a bulged disc in my neck but why my back pain and why for so long with everything? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7001-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7001_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:52:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/105638/collision-depression</link><title>Worlds in Collision - Mixed Depression, Mixed Mania</title><description>... Two recent shareposts, “The Depression-Mania Two Step” ( Part I and Part II ), zeroed in on a crucial fact that tends to be overlooked by clinicians, namely: Despite the fact that depression and mania present as polar opposites, the two can hardly be viewed as unrelated. For our own health and safety, they need to be seen together as part of the same cycling phenomenon. Today’s depression is tomorrow’s mania, but there is another twist: Too often, depression fails to clear the room. Too often, mania doesn’t wait to be invited in. The two show up at once. The dance is over. A free-for-all breaks out. The experts refer to the condition as a “mixed” episode or state. Sweet mania turns sour. Vegetative depression becomes animated. Those who have been through either describe the experience as akin to wanting to crawl out of your skin, of feeling the urge to grab the world by the throat and wring it. I used to joke: “I get road rage a lot - ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7001-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7001_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:53:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/128667/understanding</link><title>Public Agenda Report Gauges Public's Understanding of Research on Aging</title><description>... So what were the researchers’ findings? Here goes: ... ... Length of life vs. living healthier longer. Researchers believe that people think that aging researching focuses on living longer as opposed to living healthier longer, and credit the popular... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7001-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7001_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:54:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/93268/public-socially</link><title>Depression and Public Speaking: Quelling Anxiety with Public Speaking</title><description>...   ... The last time I spoke in "public" was for a poetry class when I was an undergraduate in college.  I had to give an informal talk about the poet, Sylvia Plath.  I am sure Sylvia was rolling around in her grave when I failed to get through my speech.  I stopped about a third of the way through because I froze up.  And this was for a small class while sitting in a circle of chairs.  I still remember the looks my classmates gave to me, sort of a mixture of shock and pity.  My face was red with shame as the teacher gently nudged the next person to talk.  Of... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7001-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7001_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:55:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/610558/163536</link><title>I am allergic to the chlorine in public pools but I am fine when I am in someone's backyard pool. Why is that? Also, what can I do or take to be able to swim in public pools?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7001-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7001_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:58:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/relationships-256886-5.html</link><title>Public Displays of Affection</title><description>... They're everywhere: the couples out in public with their tongues down each other's throats and a serious case of wandering hands. It's enough to make you shout, "Get a room!" "America has become a nation of sexual exhibitionism," says Carole Altman, Ph.D., author of 101 Ways to Make Love Happen (Casper Publishing, 1999). "People feel the need to demonstrate their sexuality to others, and public displays of affection (PDA) are the perfect way to prove that our private lives are truly sexual," she says. All couples have to find their own comfort level when it comes to public displays of affection. Many couples find themselves in a situation in which one partner is totally into PDA, while the other prefers a more "hands off" approach. Take Tom and Anna, both 21, seniors at the University of Virginia in Charlottesville, VA, who started dating during their freshmen year. They weren't always in sync in terms of PDA. "I saw it a... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7001-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7001_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:00:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/129542/153306/ms</link><title>Dealing with Public Insensitivity Towards MS</title><description>...   ... You know the kind where if something can go wrong, it will. Or a morning where you are running late for your something or other, and you’re not sure why. Or if you try to use your hands to hold something, and it continues to slip out of your stupid MS-numbed fingers . ...   ... Those mornings are so frustrating! Sadly earlier this week, I was having one of those mornings — several days in a row. It was making me so upset. So much so that I even exclaimed, “I need therapy!” ...   ... Yes, I probably would benefit from speaking with a trained professional, but that was not the kind of therapy I needed. Neither was a visit with Jaren, my physical therapist, or a session with Mike, an occupational therapist who’s been treating me. ...   ... I wanted some retail therapy. ...   ... I was certain that getting out of the house and looking at cute clothes was just what the doctor would have ordered. ... &amp;n... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7001-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7001_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:03:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/4852/14428/ann-ms</link><title>Ann Romney, a New Public Face of MS</title><description>... Ann Romney, wife of Republican presidential hopeful Mitt Romney, has gone national with her battle against MS. On her wife-of-the-candidate website , and she offers significant detail about her story .   Much of it will be familiar to anybody who has battled the disease or helped a friend or family member cope. An excerpt:   When I was first diagnosed, it was probably the most difficult time for me. I was having difficulty with my physical balance, but I would soon realize I was having just as much difficulty with my emotional balance. I was overwhelmed and had so many questions. I had always been an independent person, strong and able. I saw the disease as an invading pac man - eating away at the myelin that was protecting my nerves. It was chewing me up, but I didn't know when or how it would spit me out.   Some details of her treatment are unusual:   My personal treatment has consisted of both traditional and alternative practices such as equine therapy, refle... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7001-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7001_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:05:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/121/9340/helps-public</link><title>A Soprano on Lexapro Helps Educate the Public About Mental Illness</title><description>... Some years ago, I was making videos for an organization with a huge campaign about end-of-life care (palliation, hospice, Living Wills, etc.) They made a large contribution to the field by getting a Los Angeles film professional to serve as liaison with the television and motion picture industry. This man made certain that producers knew to come to him to get correct information about end-of-life care. When AJ Soprano revealed his battle with depression on television, I wasn’t there to watch, but I applaud the notion that we’re no longer afraid to show mental illness on TV, and that – occasionally – whether through advisory groups or other media, we can get it “right.” If Soprano takes his Lexapro, and Joe and Jane Doe take their Prozac or other anti-depressants, we may have a chance to both educate the public and help palliate depression. On a related note, those who were watching HOUSE on Fox Network last night would have noticed that they seemed to have been working in tandem with T... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>