<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7002">exhaled NO IBS papers</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:08:14" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7002-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7002_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:08:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/53858/39291/fibroyalfia</link><title>I have had Fibroyalfia for 19 years and sliped disks in my neck also Ibs and acid reflux .heart prpo</title><description>... I didn't know what was wrong with me because I was a very active moving person.  Weight lifting and racing were my best times in life plus making the money to help poeple who needed yearly.  Then one sad day my doctor told me I needed to slow down I was over doing it.  I had Fibromyalgia.  Well I had never hard of it so there must not be such a thing.  Well during my dance classes I had fore young girls during the day I would sometimes not feel my fingers or just felt like I needed a rest time for a nap.  This just wasn't me at all. My doctor advised me to go to a locat Doctor library and he gave me information on how to recieve a card and I went.  I remember reading the works and walking may become at a point where you may have to use a wheel chair!  I looked at those words and cried and didn't care who saw me.  How could this happen I was alway very healthy and my kids eat healthy too.  I would just let this pass in my mind and keep ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7002-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7002_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:11:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/30255/40443</link><title>exhaling</title><description>... my 8 yr. old son is having difficulty exhaling. The doctors have told me its nothing to worry about, but he is miserable. He really is not in pain, most of the time. He just makes this high pitched sighing sound when he exhales. Has anyone else gone through this, and what did you do to stop it??? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7002-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7002_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:15:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/sleep-disorders/c/question/602714/60056</link><title>When i sleep i make noises as i exhale and they wake me up, how do i stop this?</title><description>... When i go to sleep i tend to wake up many times during the night and people tell me that i make these loud throat noises when i exhale and i wake myself up from it. I am wondering if you no what this is and how it can be treated. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7002-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7002_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:18:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/question/907259/97669</link><title>What is Exhaled Nitric oxide (eNO) test? Is it helpful to monitor asthma?</title><description>... Recently I came across many articles which states that Exhaled nitric oxide is an effective way to monitor asthma. I have come across medical journals, which states that Measuring Nitric Oxide (NO) from the breath (during exhalation) has proven to be a useful tool for some asthma specialists in the U.S. and other parts of the world. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7002-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7002_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:21:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/115309/85759</link><title>makes noise in throat (like grunting) when exhaling while doing tasks, concentrating, etc.</title><description>... When my friend is doing anything besides sleeping, reading a book or watching T.V. he inhales through his nose and exhales through the mouth making a sound in the back of his throat-like grunting or groaning.  It is pronounced if he is doing a task, playing a hand of bridge or anything that takes some concentration or effort.  He is on medication for bi-polar and anxiety/up-tighness.  He is not aware of making this noise.  He has been checked thoroughly for physical conditions that might be a cause for this noise and there is nothing physically wrong with him.  He us 80 years old. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7002-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7002_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:26:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/907259/97668/exhaled-treatment</link><title>Exhaled Nitric Oxide and its role in the treatment of Asthma Part I</title><description>... In the first part of the series, we discuss the findings from the reputed New England Journal of Medicine on Use of Exhaled Nitric Oxide Measurements to Guide Treatment in Chronic Asthma. ...   ... In medicine, exhaled nitric oxide (eNO) can be measured in a breath test for asthma which is characterized by airway inflammation. Nitric oxide (NO) is a gaseous molecule produced by certain cell types in an inflammatory response. Exhaled NO (also referred to as FENO) is a promising biomarker as a guide to therapy in adults and children with asthma. The breath test has recently become available in many well-equipped hospitals in developed countries. Clinical trials have looked at whether tailoring asthma therapy based on eNO values is better than conventional care, in which therapy... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7002-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7002_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:31:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/846640/89966/exhale</link><title>Waiting to exhale!</title><description>...   ... I really ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7002-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7002_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:35:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/399759/85920</link><title>when I exhale Ihear a faint cracking/popping sound in my throat. Is air leaking in my abdomen?</title><description>... Also my abdomen is so blotted. Is air leaking in my abdomen somehow?  What is that poppoing sound?  And my throat is sore. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7002-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7002_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:36:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/cold-flu/c/question/205596/71974</link><title>I exhale gasp for air slumping oftentimes and then inhale getting insufficient air.</title><description>... This episode generate heart palpatations, racing thoughts, feeling out of control, increase body warmth. Can this be associated with a heart condition reflecting SR-St sinus arrhythmia and sinus tachycardia abnormality. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7002-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7002_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:40:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/question/312064/127567</link><title>My husband recently started wheezing on exhale breathing while he sleeps. He had a Stint put in a few years ago. He won't see a doctor because he says it's just a cold. What should I do?</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>