<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7004">z-machine</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:11:01" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7004-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7004_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:11:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/sleep-disorders/c/question/294407/143857</link><title>I have OSA, been on CPAP 3 months, still fatigued. CPAP machine data reveals that I'm doing well with the machine. I still am very fatigued. I have changed masks several times, and still nothing...</title><description>... I find myself fighting the machine at times to breathe normally, and wake up with a stomach full of air.....suggestions...Although I have OSA my doctor doesn't think sleep apnea is the reason I am not sleeping and are still fatigued ... Any other disorders I should be ruling out? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7004-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7004_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:12:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/341271/118608</link><title>i live in Kenya n i have been diabetic for 10yrs..my challenge is to find a machine for monitoring my progress all the times without the test strips running out of stock.is there a digital machine?</title><description>... A digital machine that i can use to eases my time of looking for the test strips and some times they are out of stock.Also is there a machine that can be used at home to test sensitivity of the legs? ... thanks ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7004-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7004_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:12:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/sleep-disorders/c/question/992613/147645</link><title>I have been on an auto-pap machine for about 5 wks now. I have morning grogginess that I didn't have before the APAP machine.Is this normal, when does it go away, and could it be an adjustment setting</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7004-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7004_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:16:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/sleep-disorders/c/5954/9148/res-med</link><title>Res Med Recalls CPAP Machines</title><description>... Res Med, one of the world's largest suppliers of CPAP (Continuous Positive Airway Pressure} machines, used in the treatment of sleep apnea, today announced a worldwide voluntary recall of approximately 300,000 of its early production S8 flow generators. The recall was prompted by the remote possibility of a short circuit in the power supply connector.   Res Med states: Patients may continue to use their S8 flow generators until they receive a replacement device. As with any electrical device, patients should make sure that it is placed on a hard clean surface and that the area around the device is clear during use. Patients should discontinue use of the device if there are any signs of electrical failure such as intermittent power, cracking sounds, sparking or charred smell. Patients should not use supplemental oxygen with an affected device; patients using supplemental oxygen should immediately contact their home healthcare provider for a replacement.   In only seven... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7004-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7004_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:20:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/175833/61717</link><title>Where can I rent a TENS machine in the Tacoma area?</title><description>... Need info on how and where to rent the machine.... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7004-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7004_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:22:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/35035/147725</link><title>When I use my CPAP machine I have allergic symptoms:nasal congestion, frequent sneezing and irritability in my nose. Can I be allergic to the mask or tubing? Antihistamines do help much.</title><description>... Allergies from CPAP machine? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7004-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7004_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:24:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/3232/11753/vending-machines</link><title>Vending Machines</title><description>... My husband and I do Prison Ministry. We go into the prisons and we are spiritual advisors to many inmates one on one. Here is my dilemma - lunchtime is from a vending machine.   I have tired to be selective in my choices of eating. The food is high carb and high fat. I have selected Pizza on several occasions. I have also had Chicken Salad Sandwich. The majority of the food is Chicken Wings, Hamburgers, Cheeseburgers, Hoagie Sandwiches, no salads or vegetables.   And there is a junk food machine. So do you all have any thoughts? No I cannot pack my own lunch and take it into the prison.   I conquered the breakfast issue because we leave our house so early we eat enroute on our travel. We eat either at Burger King or McDonalds on the turnpike, I just asked for the nutrition information and was able to make wise choices.   Egg McMuffin 30 carb and coffee or tea If I want juice I just eat half of the english muffin and drink half of the juice.    ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7004-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7004_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:25:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/23153/151904/elliptical</link><title>Questions to Ask Before Buying (or trying) an Elliptical Machine</title><description>...   ... Although, the low impact nature of this machine is an alternative to pounding on a treadmill. Because the pedals glide and land softly, some people do really well with an elliptical machine. With less impact to the feet, ankles, knees, hips and spine, these popular exercise devices are often the most popular and hard to snag items at the gym. All the while, the lowly stationary bicycle which also offers a low impact ride sits dusty and unwanted in the corner. ...   ... But before you go out and purchase an elliptical machine to call your own, you need to try one for at least a week at a local gym because it may not be right for your body. Here are s... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7004-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7004_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:29:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/698243/147057</link><title>Is ONSTIM andTMS the same as the TENS stimulator machines of old?</title><description>... The TENS machines did not help me much so I would like to know how these differ, and how they may be better. I am a chronic migraneur - quite intractable and have had this problem for 43 years going from bad to much much worse. I am looking for other tx that might make my life more bearable. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7004-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7004_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:30:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/question/82587/30869</link><title>Albuterol Inhaler ran through washing machine</title><description>... As the summary says, I accidentally ran my inhaler through the washing machine in a pair of pants.  It doesn't seem like any water got inside of the canister, and it still dispenses the medication like normal without any blockage or other problems, but I'm not sure if it would be safe to continue to use it.  I would really appreciate any answers that might help me with this. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>