<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7007">Allen Ginsberg Howl review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:24:11" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7007-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7007_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:24:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/84/12950/dr-barry-icon</link><title>Dr. Barry Ginsberg: A Diabetes Icon Explains... Everything</title><description>... Republished by permission of Amy Tenderich of diabetesmine.com .   Well OK, maybe not everything , but it was pretty inspiring interviewing the endo who led the research team for the landmark DCCT (Diabetes Control and Complications Trial)!   Dr. Barry Ginsberg is internationally recognized as an "iconic figure" in diabetes, blood glucose monitoring technology and implantable sensors. He's published over 100 articles in peer-reviewed journals and has received over 5 million dollars in research grants. He recently retired from 15 years as vice president for worldwide medical affairs at BD Medical's Diabetes Care unit. And very lucky for us, he was generous enough last week to share some of his accumulated wisdom with our community via DiabetesMine.com . He's so refreshingly down-to-Earth -- you just have to read this! DM) You've seen a lot of changes in diabetes care over the years. What do you think is the most important new development underway righ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7007-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7007_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:25:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/120/157274/review-asylum</link><title>Book Review: Asylum</title><description>...   ... Forty years worth of data from Sweden's health registry anonymously covering almost 1.2 million patients and their relatives were researched. ...   ... Bipolar disorder was more common among artists and scientists, from dancers and photographers to researchers and authors. ...   ... Writers were more likely to be diagnosed with schizophrenia, depression, anxiety and substance abuse.  They were almost 50 percent more likely to commit suicide than the general population, according to the study. ...   ... Could this have implications for how schizophrenia symptoms are treated?  ...   ... Study researcher Simon Kyaga, a Karolinska Institutet doctoral student, wonders if it opens the way for a new approach to treatment where you ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7007-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7007_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:27:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/120/165754/review-saving-normal</link><title>Book Review: Saving Normal</title><description>... He's the psychiatrist that was the chair of the DSM-IV Task Force. As you might know the DSM is the bible of psychiatric diagnoses: the Diagnostic and Statistical Manual of disorders. ...   ... Allen Frances was compelled to write this book after witnessing how proud his colleagues were to publish the DSM-V. Allen Frances wrote Saving Normal as "an insider's revolt against out-of-control psychiatric diagnosis, DSM-5, big pharma, and the medicalization of ordinary life." ...   ... I read the section on the perils of diagnosis inflation that caused stigma and hardship for people with mild distress or ordinary feelings. I read the section on how psychiatry got it right for people with severe psychiatric symptoms. ...   ... Allen Frances is not against the judicious use of psychiatric intervention for people who need it like those of us with schizophrenia and bipolar. Rather, he is against the runaway train of big pharma gr... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7007-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7007_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:29:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/727598/160646/exercise-air-reviewed</link><title>As We Begin to Head Outside to Exercise, Nation's Air Quality Reviewed</title><description>... And just in time for the great exodus to the outdoors, the American Lung Association has released its “State of the Air 2013” report . This report looks at the levels of ozone and particle pollution across the United States during 2009, 2010 and 2011. This report used data collected by states, tribes and federal agencies. ... Key findings in the report include the following: ... ... Approximately 42 percent of the U.S. population (131.8 million people) live in counties that have unhealthy levels of either ozone or particle pollution. ... Almost 40 percent of the U.S. population lived in areas that had unhealthy levels of ozone in 2009-2011. ... Over 44.3 million people lived in areas that had unhealthy levels o... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7007-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7007_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:29:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/8689/153195/preventing-summer</link><title>Preventing Summer Brain Drain in Your ADHD Child</title><description>... Summer vacation is almost upon us. You can tell because the number of field trips are increasing - teachers know that even students without Attention Deficit Disorder lose the ability to focus in the last couple of weeks of school, so why fight it? For kids with ADHD, especially those who struggle with academics, summer vacation is a welcome relief from the grind of lessons. For parents, it’s a relief to be free of the need to nag the kids about homework . But that’s also a bad thing. Summer vacation will not only let everything your child learned dribble out his ears, but he’ll also get out of the learning mode. The first couple of weeks back to school is always hard for children, but especially for children with ADHD, and it will be here before you know it. Staying in learning mode all summer not only keeps your child’s brain active, but the continued familiarity with the learning process will make back to school less of a shock. However, it is summer, after all... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7007-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7007_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:30:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/sleep-disorders/c/68/12568/sleep</link><title>Non-Medicinal Treatments for Sleep Disorders</title><description>... So far I have spent a lot of time reviewing the different medicines available for the treatment of insomnia . Today, we will touch on some non-pharmacologic (non-medicine) treatments. It is important to point out that the effects of different medications for insomnia are evident only when you are taking the medicines, not when you stop taking them. The non-medicinal treatment, however, "teaches" patients with insomnia how to get a good night's sleep. The effects of this instruction stay with the patient long after the actual treatment sessions have ended.   These non-pharmacologic treatments are usually performed by a psychologist who uses various methods to retrain the patient on their approaches to sleep. I will analyze a few of the more common methods below. (Much of this blog is adapted from a very good review article by Dr. Becker, Neurologic Clinics, November 2005.)   Stimulus control, or ‘‘the 10-minute rule'' - Studies have shown that whe... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7007-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7007_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:33:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/sleep-disorders/c/68/21865/sleep-apnea</link><title>Obstructive Sleep Apnea: Surgical Treatments</title><description>... In our most recent blog, we were talking about positive airway pressure (PAP) therapy, which usually takes the for of continuous positive airway pressure or CPAP. Though PAP is the "gold standard" and the most effective therapy for obstructive sleep apnea (OSA), we noted that many patients have difficulty maintaining its use over the long term. We also discussed some of the techniques a good sleep center will utilize to improve the long term compliance to CPAP. In this blog, I wanted to review some other options in the treatment of OSA, particularly surgical treatments.   Surgical Treatment   In most children, the primary treatment for OSA is surgery to remove the tonsils and adenoid tissue. This generally improves the sleep apnea and returns their sleep to normal. Unfortunately with the rapidly expanding epidemic (pun intended) of childhood obesity, sleep centers are beginning to see more "adult-like" sleep apnea, where this surgery alone may not help. &amp;nbsp... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7007-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7007_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:34:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/sleep-disorders/c/68/56428/relieving</link><title>Relieving Those Restless Legs</title><description>...   ... We reviewed some of the symptoms, causes, and adverse effects of restless legs syndrome in the past two blogs, now let’s talk about how RLS is diagnosed.   Due to the unusual sensations that patients with RLS complain of, it is sometimes difficult for a healthcare provider to determine if these complaints are actually related to RLS.   Contrary to popular belief, a sleep study is not needed to diagnose RLS and treatment decisions can be based on a sufferer’s response to 4 simple questions.   If the answer to all 4 questions is yes, then a diagnosis of RLS is likely.   These questions are: ...   ... ·          Do you feel an urge to move your legs, usually accompanied or caused by an uncomfortable and unpleasant sensation in your legs? ... ·          Does this urge to move begin or worsen when you lie do... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7007-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7007_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:36:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/guides/000031_9.html</link><title>Stress - References</title><description>... References Allen J, Annells M. A literature review of the application of the Geriatric Depression Scale, Depression Anxiety Stress Scales and Post-traumatic Stress Disorder Checklist to community nursing cohorts. Database of Abstracts of Reviews of Effects (DARE). 2010. Bisson J. Post-traumatic stress disorder. Clinical Evidence (British Medical Journal Publishing Group). 2009. Review. Available online. Block JP, He Y, Zaslavsky AM, Ding L, Avanian JZ. Psychosocial stress and change in weight among US adults. Am J Epidemiol . 2009;170(2):181-192. Bradt J, Dileo C. Music for stress and anxiety reduction in coronary heart disease patients. Cochrane Database Syst Rev . 2009 Apr 15;(2):CD006577. Chiesa A. Serretti A. Mindfulness-based stress reduction for stress management in healthy people: a review and meta-analysis. Database of Abstracts of Reviews of Effects (DARE). 2010. Ginsburg KR and the Committee on Communications and Committee on Psychosocial Aspects of Child and Family Health. Clinical... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7007-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7007_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:38:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/sleep-disorders/c/68/2832/you-sleep</link><title>How Do You Know If You Have a Sleep Disorder?</title><description>... ... Typically, a sign that you have a sleep disorder is if you have trouble going to sleep or staying asleep, problems staying awake (“I don’t have a sleep problem, I can fall asleep anywhere!), unusual behaviors during sleep (e.g., sleep walking), very loud, disruptive snoring, or episodes where people see you stop breathing during sleep. If any of these issues are present, they should be discussed with your doctor and may even require a visit to a sleep specialist. ... ... Each of these issues would require a separate blog, but I would at least like to give some insight about what your doctor may ask you so that you can be prepared. The main areas that your doctor will key in on are: ... ... How is your sleep at night? Note if... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>