<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7008">jesse van ruller solo transcriptions</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:42:11" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7008-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7008_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:42:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/23153/37307/music-therapy</link><title>Treating Chronic Pain with Music Therapy</title><description>...   ...   ... ... ... ... ... ... ...   ... Pain does take away dreams of careers, vacations, and living life. When you are in pain, it is easy to feel "stripped, drawn, and cheated." But, do not feel defeated. "Nooo, sir!"  You can hold onto your fate "from a string" and regain control by "looking for direction." Another direction is all you need to find another dream because "this dream is over, dream another dream." When you are in pain and your dreams are smashed, you just need to keep reaching, keep "reachin' out for anything," and keep reaching for another dream. Just "dream another dream"! ...   ... Thank you for the music selections! Keep them coming in ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7008-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7008_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:45:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/40574/ultimate-experience</link><title>My Ultimate Mahler Experience</title><description>... Mahler? You gotta be kidding? Okay! I admit it. I'm a Gustav Mahler fan. The other day, I boarded AMTRAK from San Diego to LA for no reason other than to hear a performance of his Eighth Symphony, known as "Symphony of a Thousand." "Mahler's Symphony of a Thousand!" I burbled to my LA buddy "Jane" two months ago. "Do you realize how rarely this is performed?" These days, they get by with a bare bones complement of merely 400 singers and musicians, but that's enough to bust the budget of any symphony orchestra. Moreover, Mahler is an acquired taste. Who is going to turn out to hear Mahler? Okay, maybe nine or ten thousand at the Hollywood Bowl on a week night. Jane had the tickets and a picnic. Her friend brought some more goodies. I brought the wine and the good weather. Mahler's Symphony of a Thousand premiered in Munich in 1910, with an 850-strong chorus and an orchestra of 171. The composer himself conducted. The performance brought down the house. Wild clapping and stomping went on for ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7008-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7008_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:45:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/35788/123913/totalmente</link><title>DEPRESION??'SOCIEDAD TOTALMENTE ENFERMA, MULTIPLES FACTORES</title><description>... EN LA REPUBLICA ARGENTINA, vivimos en una sociedad enferma, enferma de ODIO IRRECONCILIABLE CON LA VERDAD HISTORICA, sometida por los ORGANISMOS DEL ESTADO, EXTORSIONADOS, POR LA AFIP-DGI-PAMI-ANSES-ONCCA-MINISTERIOS DEL TRABAJO, NACIONAL Y PROVINCIALES.-CATASTROS,TIERRAS Y CONTRIBUCIONES DE MEJORAS PROVINCIALES, ES NECESARIO Y URGENTE UNIFICAR TODOE EN UN SOLO ORGANISMO, O TRATARLO POR REGIONES DEL PAIS, CON DIGITALIZACION TOTAL DE LA REPUBLICA, PARA LLEVAR AL CIUDADANO DE LA MANO, CON NUEVA GENTE, DECENTE, QUE AYUDEN AL CONTRIBUYENTE A PAGAR SUS IMPUESTOS, CON MORATORIAAS A DIEZ AÑOS, Y SIN INTERÉS ALGUNO, TERMINAR CON LAS INDUSTRIAS CRIMINALES DEL JUICIO MONTADAS EN MUNICIPIOS Y COMUNAS PARA DESTRUIR EL TRABAJO DEL HOMBRE, SE TRABAJA A DESTAJO, SIN GANAS, BRAZOS CAIDOS, EN FORMA INFORMAL, EN NEGRO, Y CLARO, SE LLEVAN TODO, LOS DELINCUENTES QUE ESTAN EN ESTOS LUGARES CON LA COMPLICIDAD DE MUCHISIMOS FUNCIONARIOS PUBLICOS QUE SE PRESTAN AL JUEGO.-OTRO FACTOR: ATENCION A... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>