<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7009">linkedin engineering</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:46:38" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7009-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7009_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:46:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002432rec.html</link><title>Genetically engineered foods</title><description>... Alternative Names Bioengineered foods Recommendations Genetically engineered foods are generally regarded as safe. There has been no adequate testing, however, to ensure complete safety. There are no reports of illness or injury due to genetically engineered foods. Each new genetically engineered food will have to be judged individually. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7009-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7009_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:49:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002432fod.html</link><title>Genetically engineered foods</title><description>... Alternative Names Bioengineered foods Food Sources Tomatoes, potatoes, squash, corn, and soybeans have been genetically altered through biotechnology. Many more foods have engineered ingredients and more are being developed. Check with the Food and Drug Administration (FDA) for more information. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7009-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7009_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:50:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002432sid.html</link><title>Genetically engineered foods</title><description>... Alternative Names Bioengineered foods Side Effects The Food and Drug Administration (FDA) regulates production and labeling of genetically engineered foods. Some people have raised concerns that the genes from one food that are inserted into another food may cause an allergic reaction . For instance, if peanut genes are in tomatoes, could someone with a peanut allergy react to tomatoes? In January 2001, the FDA's Center for Food Safety and Applied Nutrition proposed that developers of bioengineered food submit scientific and safety information to the FDA at least 120 days before the food is marketed. Further details on these foods may be found on the FDA website. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7009-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7009_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:53:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002432.html</link><title>Genetically engineered foods overview</title><description>... Definition Genetically engineered foods have had foreign genes (genes from other plants or animals) inserted into their genetic codes. Genetic engineering can be done with plants, animals, or microorganisms. Historically, farmers bred plants and animals for thousands of years to produce the desired traits. For example, they produced dogs ranging from poodles to Great Danes, and roses from sweet-smelling miniatures to today's long-lasting, but scent-free reds. Selective breeding over time created these wide variations, but the process depended on nature to produce the desired gene. Humans then chose to mate individual animals or plants that carried the particular gene in order to make the desired characteristics more common or more pronounced. Genetic engineering allows scientists to speed this process up by moving desired genes from one plant into another -- or even from an animal to a plant or vice versa. Alternative Names Bioengineered foods Function Potential benefits of genetically engine... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7009-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7009_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:54:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/tissue-engineering-1746</link><title>What is tissue engineering?</title><description>... What is tissue engineering? Tissue engineering is a new area of science. It includes growing living human tissue for transplantation and other uses. Tissue engineering combines biology and engineering. It looks for ways to restore, maintain, or improve tissue function. One example of this is the use of cartilage cells to replace damaged or destroyed cartilage. Normal, healthy cartilage cells called chondrocytes are removed from the knee. These are grown and multiplied in a lab and then reinjected into the knee. The new cells are injected into the area of damaged cartilage. This allows the patient to regrow a smooth joint surface. The new, smooth weight-bearing surface is less likely to become arthritic. Many different types of tissue can be grown this way. This includes skin, bone, ligaments, and tendons. In the future, labs may be able to make donor tissue and organs for anyone who needs them. Living tissue and electronics may be combined to form new joints. These are only a few of the ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7009-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7009_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:57:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/146513/141156</link><title>I have been at a steel mill for 2 months working 50-60 hrs per week as a materials engineer and I feel like I cannot go in. I am homesick and depressed and I don't know why? Can you help me?</title><description>... I am a new graduate with a masters degree in Materials Engineering. My work and internships with the exception of 1 internship has been in nanotechnology. I left graduate school because I did not like the long hours of research and working on 1 project for 2 years. I have tried something new and I am working at a steel mill as a metallurgist (a professional) if you will and I am salaried. Its been nearly 2 months and I thought I was used to this job, but lately I have been feeling like I don't know why I am here; I am always anxious in the morning and though I get sleep; I dont want to go to work in the morning and I feel sad and depressed. My parents came to visit over the July 4th weekend and that made me homesick for the first time in my life. What is wrong with me? Also, I am working between 50-60 hrs per week which is normal at this job and I feel like I just made a mistake. Help me? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7009-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7009_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:01:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/5068/11670/diabetic</link><title>Diabetic Engineers</title><description>... Back in the 1960s, when I was in graduate school, progress in the then-new discipline of molecular biology was going on at a rapid pace. This was partly because the time was right. When the time for some scientific advance is right, you'll often see different labs making the same discoveries at just about the same time.   But another reason was that the new science of molecular biology was attracting researchers who weren't biologists -- they had been trained in chemistry, physics, or mathematics instead. They brought to the study of molecular biology new ways of looking at problems, and new techniques that traditionally trained biologists had not yet learned.   They also brought creativity. Sometimes, when you're too familiar with a problem, you tend to see it the way everyone else sees it. You tend to accept the dogmas that your professors taught you.   You might even have been taught that some problem is too complicated to understand. So why bother try... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7009-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7009_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:04:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002432prv.html</link><title>Genetically engineered foods prevention</title><description>... Alternative Names Bioengineered foods ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7009-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7009_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:07:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/194/14038/pink-engine</link><title>Pink Search Engine</title><description>... Please visit Pinkgle , my pink Google search engine at http://www.pinkgle.com. I am setting it up so the "Pinkgle" part of the search will be editable by others, which means it can be a breast cancer-related search engine. The Google portion returns the same results as regular Google searches. 20% of proceeds will go to the Susan G. Komen Foundation. Best wishes! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7009-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7009_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:08:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/news/the-latest-in-acl-tissue-engineering</link><title>The Latest in ACL Tissue Engineering</title><description>... In this report doctors review the latest developments with tissue engineering for ligaments. The anterior cruciate ligament (ACL) of the knee is the main target. They also describe a new three-dimensional (3-D) model they are using at the University of California (Los Angeles) to study ligament engineering. ACL repair has come a long way in the last 30 years. There's a 90 percent success rate now. Athletes are even able to return to their former level of competitive play. But problems persist. For some patients, knee pain, weakness, and loss of motion leave them unhappy with the results. So scientists keep working on finding a good synthetic graft ACL substitute. The first step is to study and understand how normal ligaments heal when injured. The authors describe what is currently known about this process. The hope is to find a way to provide a pathway for ligament healing instead of using a synthetic replacement. Ligament engineering may depend on finding repair cells that can build a ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>