<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7010">manchester united FC football</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:10:49" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7010-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7010_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:10:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/7540/nfls-88-plan</link><title>NFL's 88 Plan: Must-Read Article on football and dementia</title><description>... Here's a must-read article on dementia in former professional football players. In today's New York Times : Wives United by Husbands' Post-N.F.L. Trauma ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7010-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7010_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:11:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/bum-knee-football-injury-2333</link><title>I have a bum knee from an old football injury.</title><description>... I have a bum knee from an old football injury. The ACL and medial meniscus are gone. And now I have arthritis pretty bad. A friend of mine just had half of his knee joint replaced. He said it was a some kind of English joint. He's had wonderful results. Could I qualify for this kind of treatment, too? Your friend may have received the Oxford unicompartmental knee replacement surgery. The implant is actually manufactured in England (where Oxford is located) but distributed in the United States by the Biomet Company in Indiana. This implant works very well when used in the right patient. There is a long list of patients who should not be given this implant. The four most important factors include: You must have healthy, normal knee ligaments Bone and cartilage damage must only be on the medial side of the knee (side closest to the other knee) The ligament on the medial side of the knee cannot be so short that the knee can't be aligned normally Minimal joint contracture (must be able to be... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7010-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7010_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:15:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/499724/129213</link><title>Any Football Fans Here? What Is Your Favorite Football Food?</title><description>... A few times a year, I ignore all the diet rules, and cook some "no no" munchies. Yesterday I fried chicken wings while we were watching the Green Bay game. Then we had chocolate chip ice cream for dessert. Yum!!! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7010-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7010_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:16:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/215658/155728/concussions-cte</link><title>Football, Concussions, CTE and Suicide: The Truth Behind the Hysteria</title><description>...   ... And with the return of football – from the NFL and high-level college football all the way down through Pop Warner levels – concussions return to the national consciousness. ...   ... In recent years, the plight of NFL players has made headlines, particularly the debilitating injuries suffered by former players, now struggling in retirement with physical disabilities, such as bad hips and deformed fingers, but also mental and emotional ones, such as dementia and severe depression.  In fact, the psychological effects of the game outweigh any physical problems; several players have even committed suicide after retirement, most attributed to depression or other mental disorders.  ...   ... The media has used these tragedies as an opportunity to speak out about concussions.  Chris Nowinski, co-founder and executive director of the Sports Legacy Institute, appears on television throughout the football season to speak about ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7010-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7010_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:17:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/202/134171/motherhood</link><title>Concussions, Youth Football and Migraines</title><description>...   ... My son, a sophomore in high school, grew up without playing youth football. This made me very happy. I feel strongly that football is a dangerous sport and can leave some players with long lasting injuries. Can I tell you... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7010-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7010_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:20:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/806316/142327/brain</link><title>Professional Football and Traumatic Brain Injury Changing the Way We Think of MS</title><description>...   ... 75 former NFL players are now suing the league for concealing the long-term risks of the concussions that often happen in pro football. ...   ... These NFL players say that, over time, these mild concussions lead to long-term health problems associated with more dramatic forms of traumatic brain injury. No, they didn't have bleeding head wounds, nor did they spend days in a coma after a hard hit. But, they have symptoms like they could have have experienced these more violent scenarios. ...   ... So, what are the symptoms of mild brain injury, and what does this have to do with how we think about multiple sclerosis? ...   ... Let's answer the first question first. ... &amp;nb... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7010-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7010_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:23:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/football-practice-crutches-2733</link><title>Please help! Our son just came home from football practice on crutches.</title><description>... Please help! Our son just came home from football practice on crutches. He has a lump behind the knee and can't bend or straighten the leg all the way. The coach told him to ice it and just rest. We're wondering if he needs to go to the emergency department now. Is this something that can wait until morning when the clinic is open and his regular doctor is available? Conservative care with rest, elevation, ice, and antiinflammatory medication is the standard first-line treatment for muscular problems like this one. It does not sound like there is an undisplaced fracture since you didn't mention any open wounds or bone sticking out of the skin. The suspicion of a bone fracture might be grounds for a visit to the emergency department. If the lump you described does not go down (or go away) with conservative care, there may be more going on than just some swelling in response to an injury. An MRI may be needed to identify the tendon or muscle involved and to show the extent of the damage. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7010-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7010_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:25:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/896502/122988/revisions</link><title>Football Needs Revisions to Make Sport Safe for Players</title><description>... Honestly, I’m very thankful that the National Football League is cracking down on banned hits to the head and neck. And I’m hopeful that the NFL’s competition committee will change the rules to ban all hits using the helmet when they meet in the off-season. ... Why do I feel strongly enough to blog about this for the diet/exercise site? Well, let’s start with my 13-year-old next door neighbor, Ben. He’s just started playing football this year at his middle school, being tabbed to play tight end and kicker. (His parents and I are secretly happy that about the kicker position since it could keep him out of the line of fire if he continues playing.) But I’m still worried the massive hits by NFL players, like Ben’s beloved Houston Texans, will influence his and his peers’ style of play if they continue to play at the high school and college level. You might suggest that I’m naïve in considering this influence, but that’s not the... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7010-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7010_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:30:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/ligaments-injured-football-1617</link><title>One of the ligaments inside my knee was injured in a recent football game.</title><description>... One of the ligaments inside my knee was injured in a recent football game. I'm wondering about the knee bones. My biology teacher said ligaments are attached to bones. Do the bones get hurt, too? Good job thinking it through! In fact, bones are often bruised when the ligaments that attach to them get torn. These "bruises" can't be seen on an X-ray. They can be seen with MRI scans. A bone bruise is like a small fracture of the bone. Most bruises will go away completely. But it's still unclear what the bone injury will mean in the long term. Scientists are concerned that the initial bone injury eventually causes the bone to become less resilient--less "bouncy." With the shock absorbers down, the cartilage that covers the knee joint ends up taking more force. This can take a toll on the joint surfaces, and may lead to arthritic changes in the knee joint. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7010-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7010_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:33:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/57548/100203/football</link><title>Football Injuries Linked to Dementia</title><description>...   ... An autopsy following Mike Webster's death in 2002 was carried out by Barnet Omalu, a forensic pathologist, who suspected repetitive head injuries sustained while playing football, were the cause of his erratic behaviour. Although Webster's brain looked normal when the pathologist examined it, cross section slides of brain tissue showed abnormal tau protein commonly seen at levels in people 80 and 90 year olds with dementia. ...   ... A diagnosis of repetitive brain injury, later refined and called chronic traumatic encephalopathy (CTE), was given to the condition. The recognition of the dangers of repeated blows to the head during the sport has now led to a judicial committee in the House... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>