<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7019">Alek Wek</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:05:35" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7019-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7019_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:05:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/question/698650/90294</link><title>My 10 wek old grandson has sings of sinus infection what can we do to help him breath better</title><description>... His nose is stuffy,&amp;he has problems breathing. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7019-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7019_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:06:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/question/44243/38086</link><title>amelogenesis imperfecta,and bone wekness</title><description>... i'm youg female, i have an amelogenesis imperfecta prolem, in the same time my doctor said that my jaws are weak as well!!!  i have done 3 orthognathic surgery!! another prolbem is associated with my hip, i have another problem with it, some time the pain is so sever!! ...   ... my doctor also, told me that there is a relation between the hip problem, but i don't know what is that relation  can you help me!!!! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7019-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7019_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:07:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/310621/133312</link><title>Anyone help For the past few weks i have been gettng sudden debilitating stabbing pains in my head</title><description>... Please anyone have any ideas at all? They come on all of a sudden lasting from just a few min's too hours they are a pain i have never felt before. I have 4 children youngest 7 months and have never suffered migranes or headaches. They are on both sides, but say one time on right  second on the left at the front usually above my brow, so intense i have too stop what im doing, and hold my head, my eye also waters too.Any ideas what they maybe please. thankyou  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7019-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7019_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:07:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/270181/101083</link><title>look below</title><description>... i signed up for the newsletter but it said when diagnosed it only went 07 i was just diagnosed last wek how do i change that or can you change it ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7019-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7019_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:08:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/776640/80683</link><title>leftside is weak,Bruising on left-knee &amp;thigh with pain of &amp; on left-side</title><description>... Two weeks ago my lower part from the hip on down was very stiff like I had been working out all day and had done nothing.Last wek i noticed bruising on the outer of my left knee and up on my thigh on the left-side.The pain is off &amp; on on my left- side only.Could you give me a idea on what this may be,i am worried.please!!!  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7019-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7019_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:09:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/80784/36586</link><title>have invasive ductal carcinoma stage 1 grade 3.her2 not final yet-</title><description>... the first regiment was supported by 2 oncologists ... cant decide ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7019-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7019_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:10:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/c/485/12898/caretak</link><title>caretakerofolds</title><description>... When I dont take drugs avarge BP is read 13.5 over 9.0 after taking pills for some weeks it changes to average 11.5 over 7.5 which causes geneal wekness and ED. My question is how dangerous might be 13.5 over 9.0 without drug . ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7019-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7019_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:10:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/736569/135292</link><title>vaginal discharge</title><description>... since the birth of my daughter 11 weks ago ive had a white sticky vaginal discharge smear test normal . j=have cervical entropian 1 x swab said canf=didas no tx worked . labour episiotomy 3rd degree tear and vontouse ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7019-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7019_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:11:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/75659/28097</link><title>What Genetics test would tell me if Tamoxifen will help prevent recurrence or not?</title><description>... I was detected with HER2+, ER+, PR- Breast Cancer in Apr '05. IT was poorly different. and was nearly 5cm in longest dimension. I was a stage IIB by one set of Standards and a III,III,IV by another .... took the Adriamycin/Cytoxin, 6weekly dose-dense of Taxol out of 12 alone, until HERCEPTIN was approved, then I took 6 more Taxols + 6 herceptinsIV. Then I had 6 More weekly doses of Herceptins, followed by a year every 3 weeks of HERCEptin full Strength.. I hardly weigh 100 lbs.  AT the end of that year my ONC added Zometa every 2 or 3 months.. and before or after the HERCEPTIN.. i had 6 weks of radiation on my the site where I once had a Breast.. had surgery to remove in Apr.), Now i am only taking TAMOXIFEN =pill 20mg/day. What does ?(forgot name) indicate or put me..it was  the III,III.IV one ?? What is the name of the Gehetic TEST that tells if Tamoxifen is beneficial or not? and please help my ChemoedBrain on What does the Oncotype DX indicate.. ?? and if the CTC is good... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7019-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7019_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:12:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/707937/81918</link><title>A question for Dr Davis about Lipids/vasospsm/ treatments</title><description>...   ... 1) sharp quick pain in chest lasts 1-2 seconds- followed by sweating or increased heart rate sometimes weakness- maybe hard to walk/wekness- goes away 5-10 minutes ...   ... 2) sharp pain or tighness in upper kneck-  anxiety weakness need to lie down ...   ... 3) today- was an example of exercise- playing tennis after an hor- slow tighntess in kneck- jaw.mild chest but weak and ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>