<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7020">synovial joint</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:12:49" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7020-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7020_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:12:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/578989/120876</link><title>What Causes Synovial Joint Stiffness</title><description>... my son has suffered extreme pain in all his joints for over 2 years, the pain has now extended to his head.  He has recently been diagnosed with synovial arthritis.  What causes this and how can it be treated.  He is most of the time immobilised by the pain making work difficult as he is truck driver.  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7020-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7020_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:13:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/003629prv.html</link><title>Synovial fluid analysis prevention</title><description>... Alternative Names Joint fluid analysis; Joint fluid aspiration References El-Gabalawy HS. Synovial fluid analysis, synovial biopsy, and synovial pathology. In: Firestein GS, Budd RC, Harris ED Jr, et al, eds. Kelley's Textbook of Rheumatology . 8th ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Saunders Elsevier; 2008:chap 48. Parrillo SJ, Marrison DS, Panacek EA. Arthrocentesis. In: Roberts JR, Hedges JR, eds. Clinical Procedures in Emergency Medicine . 5th ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Saunders Elsevier; 2009:chap 53. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7020-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7020_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:14:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/003629.html</link><title>Synovial fluid analysis overview</title><description>... Definition Synovial fluid analysis is a group of tests that examine your joint (synovial) fluid. The tests help diagnose and treat joint-related problems. Alternative Names Joint fluid analysis; Joint fluid aspiration How the test is performed A sample of synovial fluid is needed for this test. Synovial fluid is normally a thick, straw-colored liquid found in small amounts in joints, bursae (fluid-filled sacs in the joints), and tendon sheaths. After the area is cleaned, the health care provider will insert a sterile needle through the skin and into the joint space. Once the needle is in the joint, fluid is drawn through it into a sterile syringe. The fluid sample is sent to the laboratory. The laboratory technician will: Check the sample's color and clarity Place it under a microscope, count the number of red and white blood cells, and then look for crystals (in the case of gout) or bacteria Measure glucose, proteins, uric acid, and lactic dehydrogenase (LDH) Culture the fluid to see if any bac... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7020-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7020_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:15:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/19698-146.html</link><title>Synovial fluid</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7020-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7020_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:15:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/003629res.html</link><title>Synovial fluid analysis results</title><description>... Alternative Names Joint fluid analysis; Joint fluid aspiration Normal Values What abnormal results mean Abnormal joint fluid may look cloudy or abnormally thick. Blood in the joint fluid may be a sign of injury inside the joint or a body-wide bleeding problem. An excess amount of normal synovial fluid can also be a sign of osteoarthritis. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7020-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7020_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:16:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/003922.html</link><title>Synovial biopsy overview</title><description>... Definition A synovial biopsy is the removal of a piece of tissue lining a joint. The tissue is called the synovial membrane. Alternative Names Biopsy - synovial membrane How the test is performed The test is usually done in the operating room with the use of arthroscopy . The health care provider will inject a numbing medicine (local anesthetic) into the area. An instrument called a trocar is inserted into the joint space. This tool helps push fluid in and out of the area. A biopsy grasper is inserted through the trocar and turned to cut out a tissue segment. The tools are removed. The biopsy site is cleaned. Pressure and a bandage are applied. How to prepare for the test Tell your health care provider: If you are pregnant If you have any drug allergies If you have bleeding problems What medications you are taking (including any herbal medicines and supplements) How the test will feel With the local anesthetic, you will feel a prick and a burning sensation. As the trocar is inserted, there will be so... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7020-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7020_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:17:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/003629ris.html</link><title>Synovial fluid analysis risks</title><description>... Alternative Names Joint fluid analysis; Joint fluid aspiration What the risks are Infection of the joint -- unusual but more common with repeated aspirations ... Bleeding into the joint space Special considerations Ice or cold packs may be applied to the joint for 24 to 36 hours after the test to reduce the swelling and joint pain . Depending on the exact problem, you can probably resume your normal activities after the procedure. Talk to your health care provider to determine what activity is most appropriate for you. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7020-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7020_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:17:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/003922prv.html</link><title>Synovial biopsy prevention</title><description>... Alternative Names Biopsy - synovial membrane References El-Gabalawy HS. Synovial fluid analysis, synovial biopsy, and synovial pathology. In: Firestein GS, Budd RC, Harris ED Jr., et al, eds. Kelley's Textbook of Rheumatology . 8th ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Saunders Elsevier;2008:chap 48. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7020-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7020_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:18:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/encyclopedia/408/70.html</link><title>Synovial Sarcoma</title><description>... A soft tissue tumor in membranes and often in the joints. Sarcomas are uncommon malignant tumors that begin either in bones or in soft tissues such as muscles, cartilage, fat or connective tissue. Sarcomas make up about 1 percent of all cancers in adults and 15 percent of all cancers in children. There are at least 56 different types of soft tissue sarcomas named according to the normal tissue from which the tumor is derived. In this manner, they are classified histologically according to the soft tissue cell of origin. Some soft tissue sarcomas arise in connective tissue (fibrosarcoma); nerve structures (neurofibrosarcoma); smooth muscles ( leiomyosarcoma ); fat (liposarcoma) and in membranes lining joints (synovial sarcoma). As with many forms of malignancy , the cause of sarcomas is not known. Because of the rarity of soft tissue sarcomas (non- rhabdomyosarcoma ) in children and young adults, all patients should have their treatment planned by a multidisciplinary team of cancer specialists ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7020-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7020_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:19:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/242100/156965</link><title>L3-4 synovial cyst, L4-5 retrolithiasis and disc herniations with daily leg pain</title><description>... My neurosurgeon recommends spinal fusion, and claims no other treatment will help with synovial cyst and retrolithiasis. I describe my pain as moderate (level 4-7), but everyday for a year and a half. If I had severe pain, I'd have the surgery in a minute. While I would love to be pain-free (or at least reduced), I'm not sure that I want to go through with fusion. I'm 52, and love hiking and being active. Should I have the surgery or just keep dealing with the pain? ...   ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>