<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7022">hermitian conjugate</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:27:43" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7022-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7022_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:27:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/r/medications/conjugated-estrogens-oral-2378/uses</link><title>Conjugated Estrogens Oral Uses and How to Use</title><description>... Generic Name: ESTROGENS - ORAL Pronounced: (ES-troe-jenz) Conjugated Estrogens Oral Uses ... This medication is a female hormone. It is used by women ... to help reduce symptoms of menopause (such as hot flashes, vaginal dryness). ... These symptoms are caused by the body making less estrogen. If you are using ... this medication to treat symptoms only in and around the vagina, products ... applied directly inside the vagina should be considered before medications that ... are taken by mouth, absorbed through the skin, or injected. ... Certain estrogen products may also be used by women after ... menopause to prevent bone loss (osteoporosis). However, there are other ... medications (such as raloxifene, bisphosphonates including alendronate) that ... are also effective in preventing bone loss and may be safer. These medications ... should be considered for use before estrogen treatment. ... Certain estrogen products may also be used by men and ... women to treat cancers (certain type... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7022-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7022_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:28:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/r/medications/conjugated-estrogens-oral-2378/images</link><title>Conjugated Estrogens Oral Medication Images</title><description>... Conjugated Estrogens Oral ESTRACE 0.5 MG TABLET ... Conjugated Estrogens Oral ESTRADIOL 0.5 MG TABLET ... Conjugated Estrogens Oral ESTRADIOL 0.5 MG TABLET ... Conjugated Estrogens Oral ESTRACE 0.5 MG TABLET ... Conjugated Estrogens Oral ESTRADIOL 1 MG TABLET ... Conjugated Estrogens Oral ESTRACE 1 MG TABLET ... Conjugated Estrogens Oral ESTRADIOL 1 MG TABLET ... Conjugated Estrogens Oral ESTRADIOL 1 MG TABLET ... Conjugated Estrogens Oral ESTRACE 1 MG TABLET ... Conjugated Estrogens Oral ESTRADIOL 2 MG TABLET ... Conjugated Estrogens Oral ESTRACE 2 MG TABLET ... Conjugated Estrogens Oral ESTRADIOL 2 MG TABLET ... Conjugated Estrogens Oral ESTRADIOL 2 MG TABLET ... Conjugated Estrogens Oral ESTRACE 2 MG TABLET ... Conjugated Estrogens Oral PREMARIN 0.3 MG TABLET ... Conjugated Estrogens Oral PREMARIN 0.625 MG TABLET ... Conjugated Estrogens Oral PREMARIN 0.9 MG TABLET ... Conjugated Estrogens Oral PREMARIN 0.9 MG TABLET ... Conjugated Estrogens Oral P... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7022-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7022_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:29:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/question/663913/77961</link><title>Can I use Conjugated Linoleic acic while on Prednisone thrapy for MS?</title><description>...   ... I am about 15kg overweight, and nothing I try seem to work.  I started taking conjugated Linoleid acid (CLA), and to my amazement I started losing centimeters.  I have been on Cortisone therapy both intravenously and oraly for 3 weeks now, course nearly complete, what I would like to know is:- can I take CLA while on therapy and if not how soon after therapy can I start taking it again? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7022-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7022_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:30:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/forms-high-blood-pressure-412792-1.html</link><title>Pneumococcal conjugate vaccine</title><description>... Definition ... ... The pneumococcal conjugate vaccine helps protect against mild and severe infections due to the bacteria Streptococcus pneumoniae. This bacteria frequently causes ear infections, meningitis, and pneumonia in children. ... See also: Pneumococcal polysaccharide vaccine ... ... Information ... ... The pneumococcal conjugate vaccine is a killed (or inactivated) vaccine. This means it uses a protein or other small pieces taken from the bacteria to teach the immune system to recognize and fight active bacteria. ... This vaccine effectively prevents childhood illnesses caused by Streptococcus pneumoniae . ... WHO SHOULD GET THIS VACCINE ... Children should receive four doses of the vaccine, one dose at each of the following ages: ... ... 2 months ... 4 months ... 6 months ... 12 - 15 months ... ... Pneumococcal conjugate vaccine is not the same as the pneumococcal polysaccharide vaccine, which is used in children over age 2 and in adults. For information on that vaccine, see: Pneumococcal pol... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7022-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7022_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:30:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/r/medications/conjugated-estrogens-vagl-78022/images</link><title>Conjugated Estrogens Vagl Medication Images</title><description>... Generic Name: ESTROGENS CREAM - VAGINAL Pronounced: (ES-troe-jenz) Conjugated Estrogens Vagl ESTRACE 0.01% CREAM ... Conjugated Estrogens Vagl PREMARIN VAGINAL CREAM-APPL ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7022-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7022_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:31:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/r/medications/conjugated-estrogens-vagl-78022/dosage</link><title>Conjugated Estrogens Vagl Dosage and Storage</title><description>... Generic Name: ESTROGENS CREAM - VAGINAL Pronounced: (ES-troe-jenz) Conjugated Estrogens Vagl Overdose ... This medicine may be harmful if swallowed. If swallowing ... or overdose is suspected, contact a poison control center or emergency room ... immediately. US residents can call the US National Poison Hotline at ... 1-800-222-1222. Canada residents can call a provincial poison control center. ... Symptoms of overdose may include: severe nausea/vomiting, unusual vaginal ... bleeding. ... Conjugated Estrogens Vagl Missed Dose ... If you miss a dose, use it as soon as you remember. If it ... is near the time of the next dose, skip the missed dose and resume your usual ... dosing schedule. Do not double the dose to catch up. ... Conjugated Estrogens Vagl Notes ... Do not share this medication with others. ... Keep all regular medical and laboratory appointments. You ... should have regular complete physical exams (for example, once a year) which ... include laboratory and medical tests (such a... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7022-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7022_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:32:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/r/medications/conjugated-estrogens-vagl-78022/uses</link><title>Conjugated Estrogens Vagl Uses and How to Use</title><description>... Generic Name: ESTROGENS CREAM - VAGINAL Pronounced: (ES-troe-jenz) Conjugated Estrogens Vagl Uses ... This medication is a female hormone. It is used by women ... to help reduce vaginal symptoms of menopause (such as vaginal ... dryness/burning/itching). These symptoms are caused by the body making less ... estrogen. When treating only vaginal symptoms of menopause, products applied ... directly inside the vagina (such as this medication) should be used first. ... Estrogens that are taken by mouth, absorbed through the skin, or injected may ... have greater risks of side effects due to more estrogen being ... absorbed. ... How To Use Conjugated Estrogens Vagl ... Read the Patient Information Leaflet if available from ... your pharmacist before you start using this medication and each time you get a ... refill. If you have any questions, ask your doctor or ... pharmacist. ... Use this medication as directed by your doctor. Fill the ... applicator with the medication according to the direct... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7022-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7022_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:32:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/r/medications/conjugated-estrogens-oral-2378/dosage</link><title>Conjugated Estrogens Oral Dosage and Storage</title><description>... Generic Name: ESTROGENS - ORAL Pronounced: (ES-troe-jenz) Conjugated Estrogens Oral Overdose ... If overdose is suspected, contact a poison control center ... or emergency room immediately. US residents can call the US National Poison ... Hotline at 1-800-222-1222. Canada residents can call a provincial poison ... control center. Symptoms of overdose may include: severe nausea/vomiting, ... unusual vaginal bleeding. ... Conjugated Estrogens Oral Missed Dose ... If you miss a dose, take it as soon as you remember. If it ... is near the time of the next dose, skip the missed dose and resume your usual ... dosing schedule. Do not double the dose to catch up. ... Conjugated Estrogens Oral Notes ... Do not share this medication with others. ... Keep all regular medical and laboratory appointments. You ... should have regular complete physical exams (for example, once a year) which ... include laboratory and medical tests (such as blood pressure, breast ... exam/mammogram, pelvic exam, pap smear) ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7022-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7022_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:33:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/r/medications/conjugated-estrogens-vagl-78022/interactions</link><title>Conjugated Estrogens Vagl Medication Interactions</title><description>... Generic Name: ESTROGENS CREAM - VAGINAL Pronounced: (ES-troe-jenz) Conjugated Estrogens Vagl Interactions ... Drug interactions may change how your medications work or ... increase your risk for serious side effects. This document does not contain all ... possible drug interactions. Keep a list of all the products you use (including ... prescription/nonprescription drugs and herbal products) and share it with your ... doctor and pharmacist. Do not start, stop, or change the dosage of any ... medicines without your doctor's approval. ... Some products that may interact with this drug ... include: ... ... aromatase inhibitors (such as anastrozole, exemestane, ... letrozole) ... fulvestrant ... raloxifene ... tamoxifen ... toremifene ... ... This medication may interfere with certain laboratory ... tests (including metyrapone test), possibly causing false test results. Make ... sure laboratory personnel and all your doctors know you use this ... drug. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7022-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7022_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:34:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/r/medications/conjugated-estrogens-oral-2378/interactions</link><title>Conjugated Estrogens Oral Medication Interactions</title><description>... Generic Name: ESTROGENS - ORAL Pronounced: (ES-troe-jenz) Conjugated Estrogens Oral Interactions ... Drug interactions may change how your medications work or ... increase your risk for serious side effects. This document does not contain all ... possible drug interactions. Keep a list of all the products you use (including ... prescription/nonprescription drugs and herbal products) and share it with your ... doctor and pharmacist. Do not start, stop, or change the dosage of any ... medicines without your doctor's approval. ... Some products that may interact with this drug ... include: ... ... aromatase inhibitors (such as anastrozole, exemestane, ... letrozole) ... fulvestrant ... raloxifene ... tamoxifen ... toremifene ... ... This medication may interfere with certain laboratory ... tests (including metyrapone test), possibly causing false test results. Make ... sure laboratory personnel and all your doctors know you use this ... drug. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>