<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7024">reinforcement learning</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:42:44" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7024-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7024_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:42:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/copd/withdrawal-203625-5.html</link><title>Stop Smoking Tips- Use Positive Reinforcement Lists</title><description>... When I was struggling to quit smoking, I found it helpful to write down all the reasons I wanted to stay smoke-free and carry that list with me. These statements were little nuggets of positive reinforcement that served to remind me of why quitting was so important to me. Whenever I was in the grip of a craving, I would be tempted to throw all caution to the wind and just go have that darn cigarette. But if I could give myself time to take a few deep breaths and refer back to my list, I would uncover the calm resolve I needed to make it through the moment. I soon found that nothing was ever as bad as it seemed - time always made the cravings go away. The trick was to give myself enough time to get past the craving and make it through to the other side. I needed to learn how to deal with these moments without returning to my old habits. The reasons I wrote down were meaningful to me and they will be different for everyone. I share my list here with the hope that it might inspire someon... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7024-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7024_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:43:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/eorthopod/faq/isn-counseling-reinforcing-3687</link><title>Isn't the talk of counseling and stuff for chronic pain just reinforcing that the pain is all in my head?</title><description>... Isn't the talk of counseling and stuff for chronic pain just reinforcing that the pain is all in my head? When a patient with chronic pain is referred for counseling or participates in group sessions, this is in no way a sign that the pain is not real. In fact, the sessions are helping people learn how to cope with their pain and perhaps find ways to lessen the pain. For example, someone who is very stressed and under a lot of pressure may feel more pain than someone who has learned to manage the stress so that it doesn't affect the body physically. If your back is painful and lack of exercise is contributing to the pain, counseling may help you learn how to overcome the fear of exercising. More and more, counseling is becoming an integral part of pain management. Reference: Thomas P. Guck, PhD, et al. Attributions Regarding Unmet Treatment Goals After Interdisciplinary Chronic Pain Rehabilitation. In Clinical Journal of Pain . June 2008. Vol. 24. No. 5. Pp. 415-420.' ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7024-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7024_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:43:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/copd/c/88905/20257/stay-quit</link><title>Use Positive Reinforcement Lists to Help Stay Quit</title><description>... When I was struggling to quit smoking, I found it helpful to write down all the reasons I wanted to stay smoke-free and carry that list with me. These statements were little nuggets of positive reinforcement that served to remind me of why quitting was so important to me. Whenever I was in the grip of a craving, I would be tempted to throw all caution to the wind and just go have that darn cigarette. But if I could give myself time to take a few deep breaths and refer back to my list, I would uncover the calm resolve I needed to make it through the moment. I soon found that nothing was ever as bad as it seemed - time always made the cravings go away. The trick was to give myself enough time to get past the craving and make it through to the other side. I needed to learn how to deal with these moments without returning to my old habits. The reasons I wrote down were meaningful to me and they will be different for everyone. I share my list here with the hope that it might inspire someon... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7024-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7024_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:44:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/c/727598/147540/individual</link><title>Mixed Research Findings Reinforce Need for Individual Decision on Removal of Ovaries</title><description>... First of all, let’s learn more about this surgery. According to Medicinenet.com , surgical menopause “occurs when a premenopausal women has her ovaries surgically removed in a procedure called a bilateral oophorectomy. This causes an abrupt menopause, with women often experiencing more severe menopausal symptoms than if they were to experience menopause naturally.” Doctors often recommend a bilateral oophorectomy due to cervical cancer, uterine cancer and ovarian cancer, although it can be performed as a treatment for other conditions such as uterine fibroids, endometriosis or infections. ... While a bilateral ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7024-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7024_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:45:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/57548/124948/reinforcing</link><title>Tips for Reinforcing Identity in People with Alzheimer's</title><description>... Caregivers have many roles and one of the most valuable is to support the skills of people with Alzheimer's and to help maintain their sense of identity and self worth. People with dementia are, in many ways, no different to any other people. In their life history they have lived their lives, had jobs, families, made choices, influenced others and been influenced themselves. A person's identity reminds us that memories of life experiences very much contribute to their identity in the present. ...   ... The problem for people with Alzheimer's is that recall is more severely affected than recognition. This means that people with dementias such as Alzheimer's   are often able to retain the ability to recognize their own story when they can only recall small fragments of it or have difficulty communicating what they remember about it. ... ... Caregiver Tip: ... ... Caregivers to people with mid-to-late stage Alzheimer's can help by collecting and recording their stories. They, or nursing and nu... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7024-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7024_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:45:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/5949/117679/reinforces</link><title>Newsweek Article Reinforces Stigma of Pain Meds</title><description>...   ... APF was particularly concerned with several biased and unfounded comments in the article, including a quote from a doctor who works at an addiction treatment center who stated: 'Opioids are really dangerous…Boomers, of course are entering their 60... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7024-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7024_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:46:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/41/5888/compliance-positive</link><title>When it Comes to Encouraging Compliance, Try Positive Reinforcement</title><description>... ... Let’s face it, there are very few people out there who will voluntarily undertake a long-term, and sometimes difficult, medication regime of their own accord. That’s the nature of mental disorders - the treatment is often perceived by the patient to be more difficult than the alternative. ... ... ... In my case, it’s my family that keeps me on track. That’s the overriding reason for my med compliance, the happiness and well-being of those that depend on me. Un-medicated, my family paid the price. When manic I was loud, explosive, confrontational, with a terrible temper, and very easily triggered. To make... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7024-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7024_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:47:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/283233/125864</link><title>what is preferance or reinforcer assessment and why is it important in behavioral treatment?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7024-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7024_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:48:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/727598/160013/reinforces-alzheimer</link><title>Report Reinforces that Alzheimer's Can Be Cause of Death</title><description>...   ... Now I have new data to back up this statement. And I can use my mom’s case as a way of explaining it much better. Let’s see how my extra-long elevator speech sounds…. ...   ... The Alzheimer’s Association’s 2013 Alzheimer’s Facts and Figures points out that Alzheimer’s disease is the sixth-leading cause of death in our country as well as the fifth-leading cause of death in people who are 65 and older. ...   ... While that seems bad enough, those numbers may in actuality be worse. That’s because the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention’s National Center for Health Statistics only considers Alzheimer’s as the cause of death if the condition is listed on the death certificate. However, other conditions often are listed as the primary cause of deat... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7024-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7024_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:49:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/c/727598/160133/reinforces-hormone-breast</link><title>Study Reinforces Link Between Hormone Therapy, Breast Cancer</title><description>...   ... This new study involved 41,449 postmenopausal women who had not experienced a hysterectomy and did not have a mammogram negative within two years of the study’s start. Of these, 25,328 were not using hormones while 16,121 used hormone therapy (estrogen and progestin). None of the women in this study participated in estrogen-only therapy, which is used by women who have had a hysterectomy. ... The researchers checked back in with these women after an average of 11 years and found 2,236 diagnoses of breast cancer. Their analysis found that the incidence of breast cancer was higher in women who used both estrogen and progestin than in women who didn’t use hormones. Furthermore, women who started using hormone therapy close... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>