<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7025">M/G/1 queue</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:50:24" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7025-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7025_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:50:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/366241/84934/documentary</link><title>Award-winning Documentary on Paranoid Schizophrenic Artist Now Available on Netflix</title><description>...   ... http://mynameisalan.com/ ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7025-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7025_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:50:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/9347/20803/silliness</link><title>Silliness, but what is your......</title><description>... I was listening to music this afternoon and I have several songs that remind me of being bipolar in my music queue.  I know this sounds schmaltzy, but what is your favorite song that represents you as yourself with bipolar disorder?  My favorite song representing my manic periods is Drops of Jupitor by train, among several others.  40 feet remain by Franz Ferdinand is also another favorite for my depressive episodes.  Any takers? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7025-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7025_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:51:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/question/374073/89136</link><title>when does GERD end?</title><description>... my baby is 11 months old and things are just getting worse with time -medication has not worked. She has not eaten full solid meals since she was 8 months old-only a few teaspoons or a rusk a day. I have become very depressed especially when her poor weight is emphasised by strangers when i'm stuck in a shopping queue! she only drinks 16 oz of Infatrini per day. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7025-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7025_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:52:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/100/41772/things-count</link><title>It's the Little Things that Count</title><description>... This week I'm resuming the series of Blogs called Choices in Recovery . ...   ... Like every other discipline of interest to mankind [at least in the English speaking world] that deals with specific issues of long standing, the field of mental illness and mental health, develop their own arcane terminology.  Schizophrenia, schizoaffective disorder, four point constraints, palming (one's medicine), cognitive behavioral therapy, catatonia are all examples of this phenomena.  To make matters even more difficult for the uninitiated, anagrams such as WRAP, ADHD, and IOOV abound. ...   ... For providers these are helpful.  Communications among them becomes much more succinct and efficient (assuming all providers define these shorthand devices to mean the same thing). ...   ... As a consumer, I get rather tired of all the words with special meanings and all the anagrams that I'm unable to decode.  I tend to become confused, thinking that "Wrap" is the cold, wet blanket used ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7025-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7025_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:53:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/240285/132881/life</link><title>is this life?</title><description>... hello.actually ,i am kind of late in almost everything than normal girls should do.im 25 ,single,unemployed and student.at this age ,many of my friends have a career ,married and mom.is this life? is this wat is expected from us? lately i also got the urge of getting married knowing fully well im not independent and don't knw if im ready for kids and for living with a total stranger.my parents don't talk to me abt marriage and well,i cant blame them,im not independent enough.but still,im getting old and when i look at others,its as if im a failure.do good girls get the guys ? and do bad girls remain single? as a punishment? i made mistakes and i can b clasified in the depressed/bad girl part? but does that mean i  will remain single.i went on a dating site and look at all the boys whom i can date and if they r saying the truth abt their profile,well,they r potential husbands but i don't knw.when will my turn come? it seems im the last one in the queue or i will be left with the o... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7025-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7025_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:53:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/635479/101294/today-cigarette</link><title>Today's rant against cigarette smoke</title><description>...   ... One of my triggers is smoke.  Cigarette smoke will trigger a migraine but cigar smoke is absolutely the worst.   My headache specialist calls it "odor induced migraine".   He also says it is tied to my other chemical sensitivities that are triggers - like perfumes, and strong chemical reactions.  Some of the triggers have to be ingested, but a small amount of smoke is guaranteed to cause a migraine with only one sniff.  While it is in my power to avoid many of the triggers, I haven't figured out how to avoid smoke without becoming a recluse. ...   ... Many smokers claim to have the right to smoke.  I do not disagree.  Just know that non-smokers usually desire breathing smoke free air.  They cannot... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7025-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7025_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:54:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/932594/140100/procrastinit</link><title>Procrastinitis</title><description>...   ... It's a funny thing but lately I've found that I've become rather good at procrastinating. I didn't really think it was that large a part of my personality before now, in fact I was the kid who did her homework as soon as she got home from school and the adult who washes up straight after dinner just so it's out of the way. I don't like putting things off because I figure the more you do it the harder it becomes to muster up the energy needed to complete the task. ...   ... And yet... ...   ... I haven't worked in years, but I'm feeling better now and being around my boyfriend who works very hard I feel like I really should step up to the plate... but then I come up with all sorts of excuses like the fact that I haven't worked in years means I have no references. So I think 'well if I do some volunteer work I can get references from that' and still I come up with excuses... the weather is too cold and wet for me to go and... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7025-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7025_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:55:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/</link><title>Living With Quiggles: Don't Let the Stigmatrizer Win</title><description>... Stigma: 1) the recognition of difference based on some distinguishing characteristic or mark; 2) a consequent devaluation of the person Quiggles: a made-up term (by the famous sociologist, Erving Goffman) to identify all of the variations and difference of the human body which occur either from birth, daily wear and tear, accident, or illness which can be, and will be, stigmatized.   It is just days after the failed July physician-terrorist attempts on London and I've just hung up the phone from talking to one of my all-time favorite colleagues in Britain. Of course the conversation eventually turned to the recent events. I asked him how he and others were coping since they travel into Central London each day. Over the last few years I've noticed how different our two cultures are when it comes to recovering psychologically from events such as this, and true to form his reaction was different from what I expected. He pointed out that his fellow countrymen had carried on admirab... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7025-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7025_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:55:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/38190/caregiving-lessons</link><title>"The Diving Bell and the Butterfly" Provides Caregiving Lessons</title><description>... A friend suggested that I rent the movie, The Diving Bell and the Butterfly . I had heard about the movie last year when it was up for four Oscars, so I placed it first in my Netflix queue. I expected to be engrossed by the way that director Julian Schnabel portrayed the true story of Elle editor Jean-Dominique Bauby who suffered a stroke and had to live with an almost totally paralyzed body; only his left eye wasn't paralyzed. However, I wasn't expecting to see such a good portrayal of caregiving and to find several lessons emerging. I think that these lessons can be helpful for any caregiver , but especially those who help a loved one with Alzheimer 's . ...   ... Lesson 1: It's about the loved one, not about you. I found myself mesmerized in watching the two therapists who are trying to help Bauby regain physical function. One of the therapists discovered a system to help Bauby communicate in which she would call out different letters to Bauby and he would blink when the correct le... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7025-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7025_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:56:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/1950/111371/bright-side</link><title>Looking on the Bright Side</title><description>...   ...             ‘Here I am facing my fears, doing CBT and slowly convincing myself that the car will not break down every time I drive and my family will not be struck down by fatal illnesses and in the last two weeks both these things have happened. Why don't I just save myself the money and give in to my chronic anxiety!' ( looking on the bright side ) ...   ... At one level we can appreciate the irony of the situation but at another it's all too common. Life isn't static, so whilst it may be convenient to focus on certain central concerns there are always unforeseen issues that take priority. ...   ... From what Lillykitten has written it seems she is wrestling to accommodate a new way of thinking. At the outset these processes may be viewed by ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>