<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7026">keanu reeves films</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:57:13" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7026-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7026_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:57:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/157571/146974/film-portrayal</link><title>Take Shelter: Best Film Portrayal of Anxiety</title><description>...   ... If you see one movie before the end of the year, you have to see Take Shelter , an independent film written and directed by Jeff Nichols. It has been described as the best drama of the year so far and was also proclaimed the winner of the Critics Week Grand Prize at the Cannes Film Festival. I saw this film at an independent theater on the weekend and I was blown away. I fully agree with movie critic Clem Bastow of The Vine who described this movie as a portrait of anxiety: “Those who've never understood [anxiety] could do to see Take Shelter as a total immersion virtual reality experience.” It is difficult to pinpoint all the themes explored in this movie. They include: Anxiety, fear, schizophrenia, the frustration of seeking mental health treatment, and the strength of family to pull through these challenges. ...   ... Special Note: Our Christina Bru... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7026-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7026_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:57:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/003815ris.html</link><title>Abdominal film risks</title><description>... Alternative Names Abdominal film; X-ray - abdomen; Flat plate; KUB x-ray What the risks are There is low radiation exposure. X-rays are monitored and regulated to provide the minimum amount of radiation exposure needed to produce the image. Most experts feel that the risk is low compared with the benefits. Pregnant women and children are more sensitive to the risks of the x-ray. Women should tell the health care providerif they are, or may be,pregnant. Special considerations The test is not usually recommended for pregnant women. The ovaries and uterus cannot be shielded during the abdominal x-ray because of their location. Men should have a lead shield placed over the testes to protect against the radiation. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7026-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7026_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:58:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/129542/155770/women</link><title>Where Are the Disabled Women in Film?</title><description>...   ... After all, according to a May 2002 statistic from the Disability Statistics Center, an estimated 1.6 million Americans who live outside of a health-care facility use wheelchairs to aid in mobility , and of those, women comprise a nearly 58% majority (ucsf.org, 2012). ...   ... In part it is because women live longer than men and are more likely to be affected by chronic disabling conditions such as diabetes, rheumatoid arthritis, osteoporosis, autoimmune disease, and Alzheimer’s disease. The Pharmaceutical Research and Manufacturers of America (PhRMA) report that autoimmunity targets women seventy-five percent of the time, and autoimmune diseases affect women three times more than men (phrma.org, 2012). ...   ... Also, almost two-thirds of all Americans living with Alzh... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7026-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7026_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:58:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/003815res.html</link><title>Abdominal film results</title><description>... Alternative Names Abdominal film; X-ray - abdomen; Flat plate; KUB x-ray Normal Values The x-ray will show normal structures for a person your age. What abnormal results mean Abnormal findings include: Abdominal masses Build-up of fluid in the abdomen Certain types of gallstones Foreign object in the intestines Hole in the stomach or intestines Injury to the abdominal tissue Intestinal blockage Kidney stones The test may be performed for: Abdominal aortic aneurysm Acute appendicitis Acute cholecystitis Acute kidney failure Addison's disease Adenomyosis Annular pancreas Ascariasis Atheroembolic renal disease Biliary atresia Blind loop syndrome Cholangitis Chronic renal failure Cirrhosis Echinococcus Encopresis Hirschsprung's disease Idiopathic aplastic anemia Injury of the kidney and ureter Intussusception (children) Necrotizing enterocolitis Nephrocalcinosis Peritonitis; dialysis associated Peritonitis, spontaneous Primary or idiopathic intestinal pseudo-obstruction Renal artery stenosis Renal cell carcinoma Secondary aplasti... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7026-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7026_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 14:59:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/003815.html</link><title>Abdominal film overview</title><description>... Definition An abdominal x-ray is an imaging test to look at organs and structures in the belly area, including the spleen, stomach, and intestines. When the test is done to look at the bladder and kidney structures, it's called a KUB (kidneys, ureters, bladder) x-ray. See: X-ray Alternative Names Abdominal film; X-ray - abdomen; Flat plate; KUB x-ray How the test is performed The test is performed in a hospital radiology department or in the health care provider's office by an x-ray technologist. You lie on your back on the x-ray table. The x-ray machine is positioned over your abdominal area. You hold your breath as the picture is taken so that the picture will not be blurry. You may be asked to change position to the side or to stand up for additional pictures. How to prepare for the test Inform the health care provider if you are pregnant, have an IUD inserted, or have had a barium contrast media x-ray in the last 4 days. If you have taken any medications such as Pepto Bismol (which contains ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7026-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7026_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:00:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/62126/43410/festival</link><title>Breast Fest Film Festival 2008</title><description>...   ... Their website states, "BREAST FEST is the world's first film festival dedicated to breast cancer awareness. This annual festival includes short films, documentaries, animation, dramatic features and experimental works which span the emotional spectrum. Through the use of film and new media, BREAST FEST is dedicated to showcasing the many issues surrounding breast cancer in significant and interesting ways, and ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7026-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7026_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:00:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/44/7357/dear-film</link><title>Dear Talula: A Breast Cancer Film</title><description>... ... I was the one who suggested that my book club take in Lunafest   last week at our beautifully restored Bay City State Theatre. All I knew of the eight short films on the program was that they were directed by women.  So after a convivial dinner in front of a warm fire in a nearby restaurant, four of us settled in our padded seats and prepared to be dazzled. For the most part, we were. Most of the films were very short and international: A couple in China had to decide the fate of a fifth daughter; a young woman in India became a spirited bus driver; a very pregnant Mexican woman struggled to ensure her infant would be born on U.S. soil;  a Japanese tourist entertained fantasies of the London underground; and an adopted Chinese girl displayed all-American charm. Then we were hit with Dear Talula , a 33-minute breast cancer journal directed by a 37-year-old diagnosed fourteen months after the birth of her first child. Poignantly filmed by friends and her documentary-photogr... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7026-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7026_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:01:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/849319/66648/interview-advocate</link><title>Autism Interview: Robert Parish, award winning film maker, author, and autism advocate</title><description>... ... In honor of Autism Awareness month I have the privilege of interviewing my friend, editor, and fellow parent of a child on the autism spectrum.  I first heard of Robert when someone on an on-line support group for parents told me about his documentary entitled, Come Back Jack.   I remember having a cathartic cry when I saw it because Jack was so much like my son.  It made me feel as though I were not alone in experiencing both the joys and struggles of parenting a child who has autism.  I wrote about my reaction to his film to my support group.  My written "review" of Come Back Jack was read by a member who just happened to be Robert's neighbor!  She hand delivered a copy of my post to him and then he contacted me soon after.  My initial mortification turned to gratitude when Robert invited my son and me to be part of an upcoming film he was creating about autism.  And more than several years after our documentary debut, Robert had graciou... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7026-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7026_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:02:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/3308/13927/pain-film</link><title>Pain: A Personal Short Film Essay</title><description>...   A short film on my personal experience of pain. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7026-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7026_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:03:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/104637/departures-film</link><title>Learning About Departures From a Film and a Book</title><description>... Lately, I’ve been thinking a lot about departures. Part of this is due to my Netflix choices, and part due to my reading list. ...                 ... First, let me tell you about “ Departures ”, which was the Academy Award winner for best foreign language film in 2008. The movie follows the life of lead character, Daigo Kobayashi, who is left without a job when the symphony orchestra that he works for disbands. Daigo moves back to his hometown and looks for a job. He ends up answering a classified ad for “departures,” thinking that he can find a career in the travel industry. Instead, he finds that the job focuses on the Japanese ceremonial rituals that prepare corpses for cremation. Overcoming his initial queasiness, Kobayashi learns the proper way of respectfully preparing the dead body. This film does a great job of capturing the varied responses of families and friends who have lost... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>