<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7027">prefered or preferred</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:03:29" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7027-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7027_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:03:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabeteens/c/question/550036/71532</link><title>Do you prefer to be called "diabetic" or someone who has diabetes?</title><description>...   ... When peole acknowledge your diabets - ...   ... Do you (A) Prefer to be called "Diabetic". ...           (B) Prefer to b call "a person (insert your name here) who has Diabetes". ...           (C) Prefer noone says anything about you and diabetes. ...           (D) Don't Care one way or another. ...   ... Thanks for your response! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7027-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7027_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:04:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/news/total-hip-replacement-what-do-patients-prefer</link><title>Total Hip Replacement: What Do Patients Prefer?</title><description>... In the last five years, surgery for total hip replacement (THR) has changed with smaller incisions and minimally invasive surgery (MIS). In this study a direct comparison was made of the two-incision THR and the mini-posterior THR. The same surgeon did all surgeries. The same anesthesia and rehab program were used with all patients. Twenty-six (26) patients were included. They had the two-incision method done on one hip. Then later they had the mini-posterior approach. Having both hips replaced one after the other is called a staged-bilateral procedure. After each operation, the patients kept a diary to keep track of their progress. They reported how long they used an assistive device (cane, walker) when walking. They also wrote down when they started driving again and when they went back to work. Other milestones included walking up and down stairs and walking half a mile. After six months they filled out a survey. They told the researchers which operation they preferred and why. Two-t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7027-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7027_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:04:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/just-diagnosed-3508-143.html</link><title>Treatment Options for Osteoporosis</title><description>... The most common bones affected are the hip, wrist and vertebrae. ... Approximately 10 million people in the US currently have ... osteoporosis. Estimates are that fifty percent of women and 25% of ... men will have it in their lifetime and the population with ... osteoporosis will increase as the population ages. Post-menopausal ... women; people taking steroids to threat arthritis, asthma, and ... other diseases; and people who are inactive are at risk for ... developing osteoporosis. Osteoporosis is diagnosed generally by ... results of a type of x-ray called a bone density test. Fractures ... due to osteoporosis can result in decreased mobility, increased ... functional impairment, decreased quality of life and increased ... likelihood of mortality. Simple, common steps to reducing bone loss ... are participating in weight-bearing exercise on a regular basis ... (such as walking and lifting light weights), taking calcium and ... vitamin D supplements, and avoiding tobacco ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7027-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7027_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:05:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/59238/154675/shaping-flavor</link><title>Shaping Baby's Taste Preferences</title><description>...   ... According to this research, the fact that I ate super healthy during my pregnancy might also have contributed substantially to their palate preferences.  In fact, it had occurred to me before I got pregnant, because of my health training, that what I was eating before and during pregnancy would clearly impact the health and well being of my... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7027-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7027_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:06:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/question/45251/43523</link><title>Need to change from Copaxone to another MS med. Any preferences??</title><description>... I have been on Copaxone since January of this year and now need to change.  The idea of an interferon scares the heck out of me.  Does anyone have a preference for the other remaining MS meds? ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7027-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7027_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:06:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-cancer/c/question/50290/66954</link><title>which is the preferred method for removing one AK just above the lip? Freezing or cream?</title><description>...   ... Thank you. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7027-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7027_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:07:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/question/91871/87938</link><title>Have MS, would like dental implants (preferably immediate load). Bad idea or not?</title><description>... I have MS and would like dental implants. I am getting conflicting stories from every dentist... about 7 so far. Some say I may not have dental implants, some say I can do immediate load implants, some say traditional. I prefer the immediate load but I am absolutely unable to find any information on MS and implants. Need advice or direction of who to ask. I am relatively healthy, no issues with MS. Are implants safe, will they be rejected? Any advice will be appreciated. Thank You. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7027-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7027_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:08:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/78028/22228/mlt-price-good</link><title>Maxalt (or preferably Maxalt MLT which melts in your mouth at same price) is very good</title><description>... Maxalt (or preferably Maxalt MLT which melts in your mouth at same price) is very good.  It is in triptan family of drugs. You get only 9 to a Rx but since one makes me sleep, I break it in half and it works well, and I get 18 that way.    Bad news it is very expensive, but my insurance covers all but $30. Good news is that I read a reliable source that said it probably would be generic in December.   Lately however there are sometimes it doesn't get rid of all the headache, and I have had to take something else like Fioricet or Fiorinal or Ibuprophen in an hour or 2.  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7027-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7027_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:09:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/588063/144020</link><title>Respected Incharge, I'm Devang Chauhan from INDIA, SURAT. Only, I want to know about that "If inside heart 2 artery is blocked than what is preferable? surgery or angioplasty??" My dad had been pass</title><description>... Please give me right direction because i have no more time.... ... Thanks. ... Devang Chauhan. ... my add: b-3,amit apt., dhobi street, nanpura, Surat 395001. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7027-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7027_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:09:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/76423/167607</link><title>Looking for your suggestions on preferred onset meds...</title><description>... Hi. New to group, first post. Chronic migraine sufferer, has grown over last 20+ years. In the middle of a 4 or 5 week blast right now-lost track. Currently taking for prevention: Cymbalta 60mg in AM, Topomax 100mg in AM and 100mg in PM along with my second round of Botox injections recently. I did really well after my 2nd round of Botox but that was when I was on Trokendi XR 150mg at night instead of Topomax. I learned after 1st of year ins making me pay 80% which was $350 after discount card so I had to go back to Topomax and Dr upped the dose. Unfortunately it's not working and my head hurts non-stop. ... I am currently on Prednisone, 7th day, tomorrow is the last. I've done this once before and it worked on the 8th day. I have to take way more onset meds now to try and get close to getting rid of a headache than ever before (sometimes two of each spread out-Imitrex oral and Vicoden and Rx pain cream). I've also gone in for anesthesia shots which do nothing except make you f... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>