<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7030">Lyrics Bangarang</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:25:04" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7030-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7030_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:25:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/86453</link><title>Put on a Happy Face (lyrics)</title><description>... I'm not sure which forum this post belongs to, so someone can move it if there is one where it fits better.  What is wrong with me?  I wish I could understand.  No, I'm not looking for another diagnosis or label, I have enough of those. ...   ... In any one day, I go from feeling fabulous to suicidal, and everything in between.  It makes me feel sick.  Nausea.  Headache.  Insomnia.  Irritable.  If it just happened once in a while, that would be normal.  (I think.)  I could cope.  But every day? ...   ... I understand that being in therapy means there are going to be some uncomfortable moments, things maybe I don't really want to own up to, along with the impulse to jump in my car and drive to Arizona where I can take on a new identity.  Right?  Unfortunately, I don't have enough money for the fuel to get to Arizona, much less start a new life.  ...   ... Is it worth it?  Is the pain worth it to try to get to some ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7030-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7030_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:25:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/7358/143414</link><title>I take both Tridural and Lyric but will have to stop as my husband turns 65 in sept and the senior health plan doesno't have it on the Canada government medication list, it is to costly .</title><description>... The Blue cross medication list for senior does't cover these drugs and I cannot afford them to purchase totally on our own. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7030-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7030_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:26:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/147331/58787</link><title>hi,everybody first time here.,after years of pain,my doc told me ave cps,my meds r duro pats ,lyric</title><description>... diazs,trams,sleepers,in stephen ffom n.ireland,bless ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7030-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7030_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:27:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/444306/150069/dreamed-dream</link><title>I dreamed a dream lyrics</title><description>... There was a time, when men were kind And their voices were soft And their words were inviting There was a time, when love was blind And the world was a song And the song was exciting There was a time it all went wrong I dreamed a dream in time gone by When hope was high and life worth living I dreamed that love would never die I dreamed that God would be forgiving Then I was young and unafraid And dreams were made and used and wasted There was no ransom to be paid No song unsung, no wine untasted But the tigers come at night With their voices soft as thunder As they turn your hope apart As they turn your dreams to shame He slept a summer by my side He filled my dreams with endless wonder He took my childhood in his stride But he was gone when autumn came And still I dream he'd come to me That we would live the years together But there are dreams that cannot be And there are storms we cannot weather I had a dream my life would be So different from the hell I'm living So different... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7030-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7030_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:28:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/922587/119279/floyd-lyric</link><title>I feel like a Pink Floyd lyric</title><description>...   ... I wrote them a letter Friday listing all the things I do for Mom an... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7030-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7030_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:28:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/139270/life-eliminate</link><title>Which Life Stressors Would You Like to Eliminate?</title><description>...   ... Due to Memorial Day weekend we are a little behind in our question of the week. ...   ... Are there certain things you turn to when you are feeling depressed or soul searching? One thing that helps me when I am feeling down is music and especially song lyrics. ...   ... Woke up with a Foo Fighters song in my head this morning called " All My Life ." ...   ... The tense agitation of the guitar at the beginning of the song makes you feel the words all the more. ...   ... "All my life I've been searching for somethin' Somethin' never comes, never leads to nuthin' Nothin' satisfies, but I'm gettin' close Closer to the prize at the end of the rope" ... The wonderful thing about song lyrics is that they can speak to you regardless of the original meaning of the songwriter. Some think that this song was written by Foo Fighter's lead singer, David Grohl, as he was trying to deal with divorce. Yet to me the first stanza speaks to anyone wondering, "Is this all there is?" ... As I was listening to mu... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7030-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7030_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:29:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/148381/depression</link><title>The Twelve Days of Christmas: Anxiety and Depression Free</title><description>...   ... On the first day of Christmas I gave a gift to me: A stress free holidayeee! (A poet I am not so forgive my attempt to rhyme). How you ask? Let us help with a couple of articles on how to take the stress and anxiety out of your holiday plans. ...   ... • Coping with Social Anxiety and Depression During the Holidays ... • 10 Tips to Reduce Holiday Stress ...   ...   ... On the second day of Christmas I gave a gift to me: Two (potentially) Mood Enhancing Supplements (Please note that you should always ask your doctor about any supplements or herbal remedies you wish to take to avoid adv... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7030-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7030_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:30:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/315799/65207</link><title>I USE LYRICA FOR MY RSD WITH GREAT RESULTS, DO OTHERS???????????</title><description>... I TAKE LYRICE75mgBID FOR MY RSD IT WORKS GREAT! DO OTHER RSD PATIENTS USE IT AS WELL? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7030-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7030_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:31:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/5741/101044/thoughts</link><title>Circles of thoughts</title><description>...   ... The good thing about hearing lyrics is that I think in circles. If I forget a thought that I want to remember I wait for the lyric to repeat and when it gets to where the thought was thought ..I remember it. That's why I say I remember in circles. I also think backwards. I'll let my mind think 5 or 6 things then retrace all of em. Mind excercises. ...   ... I started a "challenger" Suduko puzzle. My Lord its hard. ...   ... I have to work on the book. ...   ... Have a good day! ...   ... Keep this day special for everyday is a blessing. Choose wisely how you will spend it. ...   ... Dave ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7030-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7030_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:31:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/147331/58833/robinson</link><title>s robinson</title><description>... ive lived with cps 4 years now,my doc just told me a week ago,im 39,with a family,been a strugle,meds, r lyric,duro pats,trams,diazs,sleeps,wud like 2 make friends 4 chat ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>