<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7031">Thomas test</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:33:00" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7031-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7031_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:33:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/12995/47043/thomas-moore</link><title>Care of the Soul--Thomas Moore</title><description>... The ordinary acts we practice every day at home are of more importance to the soul than their simplicity might suggest. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7031-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7031_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:33:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/respiratory-therapist-comics-275996-5.html</link><title>Adult Asthmatics Dismissing their Asthma Symptoms: Doubting Thomas Comic</title><description>... Read the full text of The Doubting Thomas Asthmatic and leave a comment!   Read all of Rick Frea's Posts   Visit Respiratory Therapist Cave , Rick Frea's personal blog ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7031-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7031_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:34:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/849319/69238/interview-advocate</link><title>My Interview with Thomas McKean, author and advocate for those on the Autism Spectrum</title><description>... ...   ... I first met Thomas many years ago when my now teen-age son was diagnosed with autism.  Thomas is an incredible individual who has overcome so many of the challenges associated with having an autism spectrum disorder.  Thomas is a published writer, lecturer, poet, and has even been on Oprah.  Always candid, always forthright, Thomas is a tremendous advocate for parents and caregivers as well as for those who are on the autism spectrum.  Every time I talk to Thomas I gain a greater insight as to the struggles associated with autism as well as the great potential of each individual given this diagnosis.  I am honored to be granted this interview with Thomas.  I hope that you will gain as much enlightenment as I have from his shared experiences and words.  ...   ... I now introduce to you, Thomas McKean. ...   ... Blog sites :  Thomas Mckean                 &amp;n... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7031-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7031_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:34:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/27819/columnist-dementia</link><title>Columnist Thomas Friedman's Tribute to His Mother, Who Had Dementia</title><description>...   ... As Mr. Friedman notes, his mother had dementia for the past 10 years. However, his column doesn't tell about her struggles with this disease. Instead, it's a tribute to his mother's remarkable life and her influence on him. Obviously, his message is meaningful for someone like me who has already lost a mother. I'd also encourage those whose mothers (or fathers, for that matter) are in the grips of dementia to read the column and take some time to reflect on the totality of a parent's life. ...   ... And I agree totally with Friedman's last message. "So on this Mother's Day, if you take away one thing from this column, take this: Call your mother. I sure wish I could call min... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7031-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7031_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:35:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/325197/111912/award-announced</link><title>Thomas E. Heftler Migraine Research Award Winner Announced</title><description>...   ... Dr. Andreou is the second recipient of the Heftler award, which was created and funded by the Migraine Research Foundation in memory of Mr. Heftler who was a founding member of the MRF Board of Directors. The $10,000 award recognizes the most innovative research proposal in migraine by a neurology resident or headache medicine fellow in an accredited U.S. program. ...   ... Dr. Andreou will conduct her research at the Headache Group in the Department of Neurology at the University of California, San Francisco. She will work in collaboration with Dr. Peter J. Goadsby, Professor of Neurology and Principal Investigator at th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7031-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7031_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:36:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/160816/understanding-mental-illness</link><title>Beyond the DSM: Thomas Insel and Understanding Mental Illness</title><description>...   ... He went on to say that: “We will be supporting research projects that look across current categories – or sub-divide current categories – to begin to develop a better system.” ...   ... Thus: “Studies of biomarkers for ‘depression’ might begin by looking across many disorders with anhedonia or emotional appraisal bias or psychomotor retardation to understand the circuitry underlying these symptoms.” ...   ... Dr Insel’s announcement comes three weeks prior to the publication of the DSM-5, which will supersede the DSM-IV. Dr Insel is no fan of the DSM. In his blog, he refers to how people describe the manual as a “bible in its field,” but at best, he says, it is a “dictionary, creating a set of labels and ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7031-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7031_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:37:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/52325/46467/doubting-asthmatics</link><title>The Doubting Thomas Asthmatics</title><description>...   ... Thomas was the apostle who did not believe Jesus had been resurrected. According to the Bible, ( John 20:24-29 ) he was not convinced until he actually saw and felt the scars of Jesus. ...   ... Since then, anyone who refuses to believe something without direct physical proof is called a Doubting Thomas. And, therefore, an asthmatic that refuses to believe he has asthma is rightfully dubbed a Doubting Thomas . ...   ... Believe it or not, I've seen my fair share of these folks in my 11 years as an RT. It's neat, because they will come into the ER for an unrelated reason, the doctor will listen to them and order a breathing treatment, and then I enter the patient's room thinking I'm going to do another breathing treatment just because the doctor didn't know what else to do. ...   ... Just recently I had a pudgy, balding male named Carl, mid 30s, lying supine on the ER bed. He appeared to be breathing normally. I gave him my usual line, "H... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7031-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7031_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:38:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/87455/25732/barquee-depression</link><title>Thomas Barquee's "Missa" helps me snap out of lethargy and depression.</title><description>... I'm bipolar and often slip into lethargy and depression. But every time, without fail, Thomas Barquee's album, "Missa" helps me snap out of it, energizing and cheering me. "Dona Nobis Pacem" floats me, like ocean waves, as I ride on its powerful currents of sound. "Gloria" lifts me, makes me feel alive and awake, riding in God's hands, feeling the pulse of creation. "Kyrie" makes me feel small and light, like a dove flying on the breeze, far above the ground. I've listened to Missa countless times, yet this magnificent symphony continues to awaken me and feed my soul. Happy listening, from Renee Marie ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7031-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7031_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:38:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/202/64293/migraineurs-thomas</link><title>Famous Migraineurs: Thomas Jefferson</title><description>...   ... Thomas Jefferson, third President of the United States, was born in Albernarle County, Virginia, on April 13, 1743. He graduated from William and Mary College with a degree in law and was a brilliant politician and the primary author of the Declaration of Independence. ...   ... Did you also know he suffered from what some theorize to have been Migraines , tension-type headaches or even cluster headaches , throughout his prolific career? Most Jefferson biographers including Dumas Malone, Fawn Brodie, and Merrill Peterson have called his "headaches" Migraines. ...   ... Jefferson may have had his first Migraine attack in his early twenties. He had laid out an arduous plan to court Miss Rebecca Burwell at a ball. Unfortunately, Miss Burwell did not share romantic feelings for Jefferson and became engaged to ano... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7031-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7031_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:39:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/9707/162801/antipsychotics-thomas-weighs</link><title>Antipsychotics in the Long Term: Thomas Insel Weighs In</title><description>...   ... This is the view shared by a good many in “the recovery movement,” but it flies in the face of conventional psychiatric wisdom. The American Psychiatric Association’s 2004 Practice Guideline for treating schizophrenia does suggest the possibility of weaning off an antipsychotic for patients who have displayed at least a year of “symptom-remission or optimal response,” but the same Guideline also notes: “Without maintenance treatment, 60%–70% of patients relapse within 1 year, and almost 90% relapse within 2 years... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>