<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7033">Porto</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:46:54" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7033-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7033_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:46:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/treatment-1217-108.html</link><title>Portacaval shunt</title><description>... Definition ... ... A portacaval shunt is a treatment for high blood pressure in the liver. A connection is made between the portal vein, which supplies 75% of the liver's blood, and the inferior vena cava, the vein that drains blood from the lower two-thirds of the body. ... ... Causes, incidence, and risk factors ... ... The most common causes of liver disease resulting in portal hypertension are cirrhosis caused by alcohol abuse and viral hepatitis (hepatitis B and C). Less common causes include diseases such as hemochromatosis, primary biliary cirrhosis, (PBC), and portal vein thrombosis. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7033-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7033_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:47:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/treatment-11425-1.html</link><title>Portacaval shunt</title><description>... Prevention ... ... Cessation of alcohol intake is important for all patients with liver disease, regardless of the cause. Avoiding blood product contamination (transfusion, intravenous drug use with shared needles, high-risk sexual behavior) can prevent the spread of viral hepatitis. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7033-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7033_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:47:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/treatment-11424-1.html</link><title>Portacaval shunt</title><description>... Treatment ... ... Portacaval shunting is a major operation, requiring an abdominal incision. ... Blood flow is diverted around the liver, usually by creating a connection between the portal vein and the inferior vena cava. This reduces pressure in the veins draining the liver, decreasing the dilation of variceal veins in the esophagus, which otherwise are prone to rupture and bleeding. ... Portocaval shunting has largely been abandoned since the advent of TIPS (transjugular intrahepatic portosystemic shunting). This procedure does not involve an incision; rather, a catheter is placed into a large vein in the neck through which a shunt is deployed in the veins draining the liver, thus diverting blood flow around the diseased liver. ... Portacaval shunting is generally reserved for patients who have failed TIPS. ... ... Support Groups ... ... ... ... Expectations (prognosis) ... ... Patients with liver disease have a greatly increased risk of complications after surgery, including bleeding, encephalopat... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7033-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7033_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:48:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/treatment-11423-1.html</link><title>Portacaval shunt</title><description>... Symptoms ... ... Patients with portal hypertension will have varices, which are swellings of veins near the esophagus and rectum caused by backup of blood in the diseased liver. Varices may bleed, leading to the vomiting of blood or blood discharge from the rectum. Patients may also have enlarged veins on the surface of the abdominal wall. ... Liver diseases involving portal hypertension often also cause jaundice (a yellow tinge to the skin and eyeballs), ascites (accumulation of fluid in the abdomen), and difficulty with stopping bleeding, due to an inability of the diseased liver to make clotting factors. As the liver fails to clear toxins from the body, patients may also suffer from hepatic encephalopathy, a disorder where concentration, mental status, and memory are affected; in extreme cases, encephalopathy can lead to coma. ... ... Signs and tests ... ... Many different laboratory tests are used to determine the presence and causes of liver disease. ... ... ... Liver function tests ... ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7033-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7033_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:49:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/867590/95436/surgeon</link><title>First surgeon visit...</title><description>...   ... Feelings n thoughts check: ... 1. Strangly enuff my stress levels have gone down since the day I found out I had cancer. Infact I was more stressed before the biopsy, I remember not being able to talk without bursting out into tears...now I can crack jokes about the situation..atleast once in a while. ... 2. I still feel guilty about putting my hubby through all this, he does not deserve all this atleast not in his early 30s...:(..I didnt even have time to be a good wifey ...u know what I mean...like if it happened 15 years into our marriage, I would be like...look I have been such a goo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7033-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7033_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:49:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/137741/exercise-control</link><title>Exercise to Control A1C</title><description>... For years the experts have been telling us that exercise is important for us to control our diabetes. But they never told us how important it is. Even the experts didn’t know. Until now. Tomorrow, the American Medical Association’s professional journal, JAMA, will publish a systematic review and meta-analysis of previously published studies. Each of those studies was at least 12 weeks long and randomized and controlled clinical trials. Meeting these criteria were 47 trials that included 8,538 people. Daniel Umpierre of the Hospital de Clinicas de Porto Alegre, Brazil, and eight colleagues call their meta-analysis “Physical Activity Advice Only or Structured Exercise Training and Association With HBA1c Levels in Type 2 Diabetes.” JAMA made the full-text of the meta-analysis available to me under embargo until this afternoon, and the abstract is online . As the title of the meta-analysis indicates, the researchers compared structured exercise with a control group of p... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7033-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7033_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:50:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/330514/153766/appetite</link><title>Bright Lights, Big Appetite</title><description>...   ... My step mother is seriously one of the sweetest people on earth, and she is most definitely a nurturer. And by nurturer, I mean she loves to feed me. Every morning of m... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>