<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7034">sony vaio laptop</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:50:52" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7034-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7034_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:50:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/149044/123005/computers-skin</link><title>Laptop Computers and Toasted Skin Syndrome</title><description>...   ... Toasted skin syndrome usually results from a work injury where a worker experiences prolonged exposure to a heat or infrared source. Typical occupations in which this might happen include bakers, boiler operators or glass blowers. There have been other cases where heating pad use or prolonged exposure to a car heater has been k... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7034-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7034_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:51:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/common/images/image.html</link><title>laptop, computer, woman, internet, promo</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7034-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7034_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:51:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/question/908577/146941</link><title>what should i do after knowing that my husband was cheating on me several times, and now i find some porn vids and pics on his laptop apparently he has been doing it for a while?</title><description>... he dosent know that i know all about his infidelity,or that he is watching porn, we have been married for five years and have three kids, he was cheating when we were apart, and i don't know if he is doing anything now or not, i dont trust him anymore, im trying to leave him but im in a different country and don know anyone here yet but before i do that i really want to teach him a lesson and make him see how much pain he has caused me, if anyone has ideas i appreciate it ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7034-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7034_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:52:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/583245/141355</link><title>I hate my life...the only reason I exist is for my son...I don't want to be here.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7034-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7034_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:52:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/question/635061/137698</link><title>Abilify (5mg) was percsribed for my 5 1/2 year old son..is this okay for his age?</title><description>... He has been taking Risperdal (1mg) but there were nont any changes so they changed his perscription and uped the dosage ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7034-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7034_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:53:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/question/31166/62599</link><title>I am 37 and i have a ten almost elven year old son.I had a C section with my son.</title><description>... PLEASE what is the best and fastest way to acheive my goal of weight loss  some kind of muscle tonning and flattened tummy.[does not have to be a six pack]. ...   ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7034-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7034_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:54:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/100271/61156</link><title>which foods should i avoid giving my 9 yrs old son..i beleive he has adhd</title><description>... what should i give him to eat, im struggling with fresh vegg and fruit.. i give him brown bread and fresh orange juice and cheese.. he doesn't like eating meat.. so i need help ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7034-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7034_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:55:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/32873/118450/week</link><title>How Does Your Smart Phone Make a Difference Living with Multiple Sclerosis?</title><description>... ... It seems t he whole world uses hand-held devices. Which ones do you use, how do you use them, and what difference do they make in your life? Are there some you would like to use? ... ... What about your cell phone? How do you use it? Calls only, texting, storing addresses, Internet surfing, listening to music, playing games, tracking family members? ... ... What about laptops, ipods, mp3s, Blackberries, language translaters, Kindles, or other techie devices?  Some devices have very specific purposes, and some can do almost everything. ... ... Many hand held devices are taking advantage of technologies that may be helpful for people with disabilities. There are speech and voice recognition, the ability to synchronize the phone or PDA to a computer, and connect to a wireless network almost anywhere. Of course there are touch screens to make selections easy. ... ... What do you use, a... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7034-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7034_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:55:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/9924/10503/061807-5</link><title>06/18/07 #5 - Hydrocodone for headaches &amp; Migraines while breastfeeding?</title><description>... Full Question: I take hydrocodone for stress/migraine headaches. I am currently breastfeeding my 6 week old son. My doctor told me to go ahead and breastfeed, and then take one or two tablets depending on how bad the pain is. I am wondering how long the medicine stays in my system? I don’t want my baby to get any of it but I know that whatever I eat or drink goes through my breast milk. They reassure me that it is safe to take these but does my baby also get it?   Courtney.   Answer: Dear Courtney; You didn't mention how often your headaches come; assuming they are only once a week or so hydrocodone with acetaminophen might be all right since they both have short half lives, which means that they leave the body pretty quickly.   Therefore, if you just breast-fed (at least four to six hours after the last dose), that would mean there was very little medication left in your milk. The same would be true for migraine specific medications like triptans, especially... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7034-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7034_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:56:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/12741/138176/5-wks</link><title>Gilenya 5.5 wks later</title><description>... I apologize for being lax in posting over the past few weeks. I let my son, Justin, borrow the laptop and I've just had no interest in getting on my desktop. ... I went back to my neuro yesterday and had a good report from my labs. My lymphocyte count is down but not worrisome to him and liver functioning is fine. I go back in 3 months to see him, go for another eye exam in July and start physical therapy on my neck this Friday. I have two bulging disc in my cervical that was discovered during my lst MRI and they've started giving me problems. ... I did switch to taking my Gilenya at night with some of my other meds, just to see if I'd still have the nausea. If I do, I don't know about it. ... So far I'm very pleased with Gilenya. I've noticed subtle changes, such as energy and my husband has noticed slight changes n me as well. ... Gilenya isn't a cure for MS but it sure as heck beats sticking yourself everyday and you can tell a difference using it or at least I can. ... That's it fo... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>