<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7036">holiday houses ardennes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:04:02" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7036-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7036_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:04:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/499724/157858/ra</link><title>RA &amp; Holiday Stress: Enjoying The Holidays In Spite Of RA</title><description>... Every year I see stories in the newspaper and magazines about the stress of the holidays. It seems that many people have a hard time emotionally and physically this time of year. ...   ... Add RA to the mix, and many of us have a tough time trying to enjoy the traditions of our culture and families. I am a great believer in plans. If I have a “plan”, I feel as though I have just a bit of control, and that makes me feel much better. ...   ... Do you have a plan for the holidays? For instance, have you decided how your time will be spent? How much time will you spend with your family, your friends, your co-workers? ...   ... Many of us have financial stress to deal with, especially this time of year. I have a budget I try to adhere to, but I am not always successful. Still, once again, it is a plan, a guideline of sorts. ...   ... I have found over the years, that sometimes the most simple present is the most appreciated. Something made by the giver often has special significance... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7036-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7036_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:05:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/coping-196314-5.html</link><title>Surviving the Holidays with Chronic Pain</title><description>... Does the thought of another holiday season fill you with joyful anticipation or overwhelm you with fear and dread?  The average person considers the holidays at least somewhat stressful.  For people with fibromyalgia , who are already struggling to cope with daily life in general, the added demands and stresses of the holidays can trigger a flare of fibromyalgia symptoms .  While you may not be able to totally avoid all stress, you can reduce your stress level significantly by giving yourself a G.I.F.T. G – Guilt must go. Guilt is born when you fail to live up to your own expectations for yourself.  Year after year you are bombarded with a “magical mythical model” of the idyllic holiday scene – complete with family, friends, food and festivities, encompassed in a spirit of peace and goodwill for all.  If this is the holiday image you are trying to achieve, it is time for a reality check.  The fact is, you have a chronic pain illness t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7036-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7036_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:05:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/18/96785/holidays</link><title>Depression During the Holidays: 9 Tips to Prevent Loneliness During the Holidays</title><description>...   ... ... If you're alone because someone close to you has died, or because your marriage or relationship has ended, realize that it's normal to feel sadness and grief. It's OK to take time to cry or express your feelings. You can't force yourself to be happy just because it's the holiday season. ... ...   ... ... Ask yourself - are you actually okay with being alone during the holidays, but feel that you should be spending it with other people? We're all bombarded with images of happy families spending time together during the holidays. Remember that as wonderful as it can be to be with family, it's also very stressful. ... ...   ... ... Sometimes it's better to be on yo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7036-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7036_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:06:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/92/2833/holiday-101</link><title>Holiday Survival 101: Protecting Your Waistline During the Holidays</title><description>... ... However, you can avoid putting on those extra holiday pounds and still enjoy the tidings of the season. With a little planning ahead, compromise and healthy choices, you can wake up January 2nd without a bigger credit card bill and a bigger waistline. Below are some tips to help you eat healthy during the holiday season. ... ... Holiday Healthy Eating ... ... ... 1. Be a picky eater. You don’t have to indulge every tim... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7036-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7036_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:06:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/ibd/c/2623/163629/holidays-holidays-coming-coming</link><title>The Holidays Are Coming! the holidays are coming!</title><description>...   ... I see the holiday's beginning with Halloween, which I LOVE!!! My husband and I live in a perfect neighborhood for this holiday. Sidewalks everywhere, houses with front porches and friendly inhabitants, and kids, kids, kids. It's a day of decorating and an evening of helping the kids to celebrate this fun and festive holiday. ...   ... Then comes Thanksgiving. I'm funny, I always loved going to my grandmother's house to help her make Thanksgiving dinner, but I never liked eating it. Every year afterward dinner I always felt awful. My parents chalked it up to eating too much, but I never ate near as much as everybody else. But every year it happened - the bloat, the headache, swollen thumb joints, and extreme malaise. And then a few years ago I had some extensive food allergy testing done and found out that I am allergic to turkey! Well, that explains it. If I had only though... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7036-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7036_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:07:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/157995/4-alternatives</link><title>Avoiding Holiday Weight Gain: Strategy 4 Alternatives to Eating Your Way Through the Holidays</title><description>... Alternatives to Eating Your Way Through the Holidays In the many years since my gastric bypass surgery and the weight loss that has followed, I have come to the understanding that gorging my way through holidays is not a requirement. Christmas parties do not have to be affairs testing the limits of food and alcohol consumption although I imagine there is much to be said in some circles for waking up five pounds heavier with a lampshade on your head. Most people do not engage in such behaviors despite debate potential that a photocopied replication of an exposed rear end might someday be as traditional as mistletoe or Jack Frost. These things do not have the pull on me that they once did. The point is that old behaviors need not be current behaviors. Former traditions can be displaced by new ones. I understand that the holidays can involve eating, and then more eating, and then more eating. Eating most certainly can be a social experience, but it is only one of many ways to share compan... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7036-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7036_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:08:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/19065/53413/peace</link><title>A Holiday Poem: Surviving the Holidays with Multiple Sclerosis</title><description>... THE DAY AFTER CHRISTMAS 'It’s the day after Christmas, I still have M.S., Not a dish is unused, the house is a mess; The breakfast was de-lish and made with great care, Sausage balls, monkey bread, fruit was all there. * The guests were my mother, my boyfriend, his Mom, The food brought back memories of Granny who’s gone; I vacuumed and cleaned, which threw dust in the air, I exhausted reserves, but I did not despair. * P.T. has strengthened my legs, I am sure, But it would be nice, if there were a cure; Multiple sclerosis is the name of the beast, It zaps all my energy and is a challenge, at least. * I don’t know ‘bout you, but I will not wait, For the researchers who are trying to make A way for our myelin to regrow and protect The nerves which help signal through our brain and our back. * So in the meantime, I plan to cautiously be Aware of my limitations and abilities, you see, “I may have M.S., but it doesn’t have me,” I live life in full and find comfort in The... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7036-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7036_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:08:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/157863/avoiding-holiday</link><title>Avoiding Holiday Weight Gain: Strategy 2 Holiday Party Smarts</title><description>... As I see it, we have three choices for how we will handle holiday food: ... 1. Eat it all with the intention to make a New Year’s Resolution to lose the pounds we packed on. ... 2. Take a vow of abstinence from all things tasty. ... 3. Plan ahead: Indulge in menus that are extravagant yet still part of our bariatric life (or Paleo, Primal, or whatever healthy plan of eating you follow). Allow yourself some le... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7036-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7036_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:09:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/question/822672/50984</link><title>I'm 61 yrs of age, single living at my exe's house with one of my sons; the other is autistic and</title><description>...   ... Graham ...   ... PS: Thank you very much and I hope you can haver a nice holiday. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7036-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7036_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:09:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/97/16907/ra</link><title>Managing RA During the Holidays</title><description>... Most people have heard about the holiday blues , but not many have heard of the holiday flares. For those of us with rheumatoid arthritis this time of year can be the beginning of very painful season. There are many contributing factors to why you may experience a flare during the holidays; bad eating, stress and depression , just to name a few. Your RA symptoms may increase due to these factors and can make what should be a great holiday into a flare to remember. The fact is we can not always control our symptoms, but we can make choice s to help avoid the pitfalls of pain. The most important tip that I can give you is to slow down . There are a million things to do and not enough time to do them. So, keep it simple. Your house doesn't have to look like a Christmas museum in order to feel festive!   If you want to decorate your home invite some friends over for an afternoon of decorating and tree trimming. Listen to music and enjoy some healthy food and drinks while spending... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>