<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7037">how to write journalistic review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:10:20" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7037-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7037_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:10:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/community-1620-142.html</link><title>Debra Gordon, Medical Journalist</title><description>... Debra Gordon is an award-winning journalist who has been writing about health and healthcare for more than 15 years. She cut her teeth on the medical beat while a reporter at the Virginian Pilot newspaper in Norfolk, Va., then carried her expertise across the country as the medical reporter at the Orange County Register, in Southern California. She has been a full-time freelance health and medical writer and editor since 2000, and has authored or co-authored numerous consumer health books, including Cut Your Cholesterol!, Asthma and Allergy Relief, Eat to Beat High Blood Pressure, 7 Nights to a Perfect Night’s Sleep, Maximum Food Power for Women, and Stealth Health. Her first Idiot’s Guide book, The Complete Idiot’s Guide to Type 2 Diabetes, will be published in the fall. Her work has also appeared in Health, Family Circle, Better Homes &amp; Gardens, Good Housekeeping, Reader’s Digest, and Diabetes Today magazines. She also writes for a variety of corporat... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7037-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7037_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:10:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/community-604-143.html</link><title>Meet David Mendosa</title><description>... California, Riverside, and an M.A. from Claremont Graduate ... University, David became a Foreign Service officer, working 11 ... years in Washington and four years in Africa for the U.S. foreign ... aid program. ... Subsequently, David became a journalist, initially specializing ... Hispanic Business magazine for about four years. ... However, when David was diagnosed with type 2 diabetes in ... February 1994, he began to write entirely about that condition. His ... articles and columns have appeared in many of the major diabetes ... magazines and Web sites. ... David ... Mendosa's Diabetes Directory , was one of the first and is now ... one of the largest Web sites focusing on diabetes. The Web site ... includes about 500 of Davids articles about diabetes and an ... annotated directory to more than 1,400 Web sites about diabetes, ... which are described and linked in th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7037-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7037_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:11:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/1443/147827/performance-review</link><title>Performance Review Anxiety: Tips to Help You Cope with an Upcoming Performance Review</title><description>...   ... The following tips can help you cope with an upcoming review: ...   ... Think about the purpose of the review. While many managers, unfortunately, focus on what the employee has done wrong throughout the year, a performance review is meant to provide you, the employee, with information to help you do your job better. While you are not able to control how your supervisor or manager acts during the review, you can control how you react to the information. For example, imagine your supervisor begins to discuss an error you made on a report you recently completed. Instead of becoming defensive and argumentative, thank the superv... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7037-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7037_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:12:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/269205/109628</link><title>Has anyone had any problems with getting their doctor to write a letter for a handicap tag?</title><description>... Or SS disability reviews? I have both, but they were issued for me because of herniated discs in my lower back. I have not seen my specialist for my back since I was diagnosed with RA. Seems the meds for RA have helped to decrease my back pain episodes. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7037-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7037_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:12:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/reviews-161469-5.html</link><title>Heal Your Headache - Review</title><description>... Ranking 2 stars out of 5 A positive note about "Heal Your Headaches" is that Dr. Buchholz does make one stop and think, partly because he challenges so much of what is now considered to be basic headache and Migraine knowledge backed by significant bodies of verified and published research. In the introduction to the book, he states, "In scientific terms, my beliefs are hypotheses; potential explanations of certain cause and effect relationships." This is a good, honest statement; one I'm glad he included in this book that has resulted in a few raised eyebrows. Dr. Buchholz has developed a "1·2·3 Program for Taking Charge of Your Pain. It consists of three steps: "Avoiding the 'Quick Fix.' Put painkillers in their proper place: infrequent use only." "Reducing Your Triggers. Eliminate headache triggers that you can readily control - mai... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7037-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7037_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:13:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/5949/139106/therapain</link><title>Therapain Plus – Natural Pain Relief Spray: A Product Review</title><description>... A couple of months ago a supplement company that I do some writing for sent me a bottle of Therapain Plus® to try because they wanted me to research and write about it.  I was happy to try it but skeptical about how well it might work.  In my experience, most topical pain relievers have three negatives: they are stinky and/or sticky, their effectiveness doesn't last very long, and they're not practical for the all-over body pain of fibromyalgia.  My Personal Therapain Plus Experience ... In addition to the body-wide aching, which is a daily occurrence with FM, more severe pain sometimes develops somewhere in my body – it may be my arm, hip, shoulder – you never know where it might crop up.  So I set the bottle of Therapain Plus aside to wait for one of those migrating pains to rear its ugly head.  Two weeks later, it made its appearance.  I had been working at my computer for several hours when a sharp, burning pain – located just ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7037-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7037_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:15:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/35144/diary-beneficial</link><title>Take Time to Write A Diary (or a Sharepost) About Caregiving Can Be Beneficial</title><description>...   ... The reason that I bring this word up is that I just was reading the August 4 issue of Time Magazine . The article "Dear (Food) Diary" shares a study published in the August issue of American Journal of Preventative Medicine that found that dieters who kept a food diary lost twice as much weight as dieters who did. So why bring up this study when writing a sharepost about Alzheimer's? I would suggest that having a diary (or journal) about your caregiving journey may provide equally important benefits to both you (the caregiver) and to the loved one. ...   ... For over a two-year period, I've been closely following a case study - me. Having been trained in journalism, I have always focused on the who, what, wher... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7037-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7037_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:15:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/80106/162021/creakyjoints</link><title>Writing to Heal: CreakyJoints Memoir Course</title><description>...   ... GHLF is a nonprofit organization dedicated to helping people "with all forms of chronic conditions through education, support andcommunity, research and advocacy," CreakyJoints cofounder Seth Ginsberg says. CreakyJoints is the arthritis community that is part of GHLF and is very active, with over 55,000 members. Seth explains that "our philosophy is to maintain a positive environment, for education, community, advocacy and research." ...   ... D.Z. Stone is a New York-based writer and journalist who has written for Newsday and The New York Times. She is helping CreakyJoints with their biweekly blogs and newsletter and had noticed that "a lot of the people living with arthritis are older... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7037-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7037_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:16:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/150623/letter-bariatric</link><title>Writing An Appeal Letter For Bariatric Surgery - My Bariatric Life</title><description>...   ... If you have ever had been on the telephone with an insurance representative for a ridiculous length of time, then you know how difficult the process can be: periods of silence while information is fished from a resistant computer program, an abyss of repetitive questions, explanations that only a Harvard grad can understand. When you finally return the phone to the cradle after what seems like eons, you do so without satisfaction. There has been no resolution. Your claim for gastric bypass is denied. Causes for Denial by an Insurance Company ...   ... Insurance companies say no. It is part of who they are. Decisions are based on profit motive, and denials are common place. Your request for gastric bypass can be denied if you provide information that is not accurate or if gastric bypass surgery is not covered under your plan. In addition, your request for gastric bypass surgery can be denied if you have  a pre-exis... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7037-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7037_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:17:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/646074/55332/mismanaged</link><title>FDA Scientists Write Letter to Obama: "Help! The FDA is Mismanaged!"</title><description>...   ... Among their concerns is the assertion that FDA employees have been threatened and told to ignore FDA guidelines. The letter goes on to say "the scientific review process for medical devices at FDA has been corrupted and distorted by current FDA managers, thereby placing the American people at risk." ...   ... The letter came from scientists working in the FDA's Center for Devices and Radiological Health (CDRH). A similar letter from FDA employees went out to members of Congress in October 2008. You can read that letter here . ...   ... The FDA is responsible for the safety and regulation of most foods, medications, dietary supplements, vaccines, medical devices, cosmetics and radition-emitting devices. The agency operates under the United States Department of Health and Human Services (HHS). ...   ... Read the full sto... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>