<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7039">import .csv excel</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:24:40" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7039-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7039_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:24:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/872851/123162/excellent</link><title>Excellent, Excellent Book</title><description>...   ... Amazon web page is: ...   ... http://www.amazon.com/Center-Cannot-Hold-Journey-Through/dp/1401309445/ref=sr_1_1?s=books&amp;ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1288277479&amp;sr=1-1 ...   ... Moonlight ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7039-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7039_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:25:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/copd/c/question/131957/57759</link><title>I was diagnosed with COPD. My breathing tests were "excellent". I've smoked for almost 40 years.</title><description>... How can I have COPD but have "excellent" test results?  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7039-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7039_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:26:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/5153/3587/excel-trigger</link><title>Gridlines in Excel trigger migraines</title><description>... I do a lot of work in Excel (blame my bosses, LOL!) Staring at spreadsheets for a long time, especially with the gridlines showing, seems to trigger migraines -- especially on days that are grey outside, or where ambient light is low. So, the first thing I do when I open or create a spreadsheet is get rid of the gridlines (in MS Excel, click Tools, Options, then unclick the box next to the word "Gridlines" at the bottom left of the options box, then click OK). ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7039-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7039_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:27:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/558587/125186</link><title>Should I have an excisional biopsy after receiving an MRI that shows no tumor, no DCIS, and only benign findings? The MRI was done at Stanford as part of a research study -- an excellent team.</title><description>... I was diagnosed with ADH after finding minor microcalcifications in my left breast. While on my way to an excisional biopsy, I was offered an MRI by a Stanford research team. While DCIS doesn't always show up on MRI, I was told that the images the doctor got were excellent (with contrast too) and that nothing was found other than benign findings. Since I have to pay almost $20k for this surgery, I am wondering whether it is really necessary? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7039-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7039_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:28:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/question/968980/113670</link><title>EXCELS Study for Xolair</title><description>... I have just read several articles concerning the FDA' warning about Xolair and heart attacks etc. I am wondering if there is any additional information from Jan 2010 to present about the EXCELS Study being conducted concerning these accusations. ... My wife will begin treatment with this drug next week and we are gathering information on it now in order to make our decision. She has had asthma for 34 years. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7039-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7039_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:29:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/excellent-osteoarthritis-1862</link><title>I'm 66 years old and in excellent health but I do have osteoarthritis of my right knee.</title><description>... I'm 66 years old and in excellent health but I do have osteoarthritis of my right knee. I'm thinking about having a total knee replacement. I expect I'll have a good result but I've heard of people who end up worse off after surgery. Is there any way to predict these things? Excellent health is probably the biggest and best predictor of results after total knee replacement (TKR). Numerous studies show a direct link between health before an operation and results after the surgery. Patients who rate their health as "poor" are four to five times more likely to die. This is true despite differences in background, disease severity, and other psychologic or social issues. A recent study at the University of Kansas in Wichita confirmed these findings for TKR patients. Those who rated their health as "good" to "excellent" had the best outcomes. Their health status improved dramatically from before to after the operation. Joint stiffness, pain, and function were used to measure health status. The ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7039-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7039_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:30:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/soccer-seasoned-excellent-1672</link><title>Having played soccer since I was eight, I'm a seasoned player in excellent shape.</title><description>... Having played soccer since I was eight, I'm a seasoned player in excellent shape. But last month, I tore the anterior cruciate ligament in my knee during my last high school game. I still don't know what happened. One minute I was after the ball, the next minute I was down on the field and unable to get up. How do these injuries happen? Most ACL injuries occur when the knee is perfectly straight or slightly bent. This type of injury can happen when a player is running, jumping, or standing still. In soccer, the ACL is most likely to be injured when a player is running and changing directions quickly, stopping suddenly, or twisting the body over the foot. Jumping and landing on the foot with the knee twisted can also cause problems. New technology has allowed researchers to measure the strain placed on the ACL. One important discovery has been that stopping suddenly (rapid deceleration) puts a high level of strain on the ACL. This occurs when the foot makes contact with the ground and th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7039-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7039_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:31:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/19065/117260/ms</link><title>Pediatric MS Centers of Excellence: Making Strides</title><description>...   ... But MS is not the only central nervous system demyelinating disease which is seen in children.  In fact, other diagnoses usually come first, just as adults with MS are often given a diagnosis of clinically isolated syndrome before definite MS. ...   ... It can be frightening if your child has unexplained symptoms and the local doctors are unsure how to diagnose or treat your child for his/her condition.  If that disease is suspected of being a demyelinating disease such as multiple sclerosis, acute disseminated encephalomyelitis, or other related diseases, then there is good news. ...   ... In 2006, a nationwide network of Pediatric MS Centers of Excellence was established in the United States through the National MS Society’s Promise 20... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7039-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7039_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:32:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/122498/video-caregivers</link><title>Video Showcases Excellent Training for Alzheimer's Caregivers</title><description>... And honestly, family and friends who are placed in caregiving positions also need to understand how to interact with a person with dementia. That means getting past preconceptions of how the  loved one used to be and identifying ways to interact in a loving and supportive manner. ... But while caregiving, who has time to go to training? And how do you find good training? Well, the Pines of Sarasota has provided a concise and well-conceived answer to my questions. They have developed a DVD (which they sent to me to review) entitled “It’s All In Your Approach. The DVD focuses on a presen... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7039-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7039_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:33:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/102396/offers-excellent</link><title>Book Offers Excellent Advice for Siblings at War Over Parent Care</title><description>...   ... In her book, Russo examines the whole family issue in detail, from why it's such a big issue now through how to make peace with your siblings. ...   ... What Russo calls the "Twilight Transition" has become common for families. She says, in descr... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>