<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7040">vom fass gent</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:34:30" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7040-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7040_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:34:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/prostate/c/question/937254/146200</link><title>signs:abdominal pain above the left pelvic bene,painful urination somtimes,recently i have been observing discharges like sperms from the penis somties when i visit the gent.can abstanance cause this</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7040-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7040_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:35:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/tests-35270-1.html</link><title>Bernstein test</title><description>... Alternative Names Acid perfusion test References Fass R. Evaluation and diagnosis of noncardiac chest pain. Dis Mon . 2008;54:627-641. Kahrilas PJ, Pandolfino JE. Esophageal neuromuscular function and motility disorders. In: Feldman M, Friedman LS, Brandt LJ, eds. Sleisenger and Fordtran's Gastrointestinal and Liver Disease . 9th ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Saunders Elsevier; 2010:chap 42. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7040-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7040_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:37:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/872190/158314</link><title>What is the mid to distal inferior wall and mid inferoseptal?</title><description>... Cardiac Angiogram scheduled for concerning Coronary Artery disesas. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7040-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7040_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:37:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/39/14996/study-acid-sleep</link><title>New Study: Acid Reflux Can Impact Sleep</title><description>...   By using a national survey, researchers have provided scientific evidence that nighttime acid reflux , along with some of the less typical symptoms of gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD), are associated with significant sleep impairment.   The research team (Dean &amp; Fass, 2007) found that sleep impairment was more common among people with GERD (41.9 percent) than those without GERD (19.4 percent). Researchers also found that 49.5 percent of the study respondents with nighttime GERD reported sleeping poorly often or most of the time, compared to 36.7 percent of people with daytime GERD.   Additionally, the researchers found that many of the GERD patients surveyed experience atypical manifestations of GERD such as coughing, sore throat, snoring, wheezing, choking, and chest pain. Of the GERD patients surveyed in this study, 74 percent had at least one nighttime atypical symptom.   These research results were presented at this year's Annual Scienti... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7040-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7040_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:38:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/157655/treat-alzheimer</link><title>Existing Psoriasis Drug May Treat Alzheimer’s</title><description>...   ... According to an article in the LA Times, Johannes vom Berg and his colleagues think that clinical trials of the drug ustekinumab should be launched to see if the drug will help fight Alzheimer’s in humans. These researchers referred to medications tested in psoriasis and other auto-immune diseases such as Crohn’s disease and multiple sclerosis as the “ideal candidate for the initiation of clinical trials for Alzheimer's.” The new study was published in a recent edition of the journal Nature Medicine. ... ... Dr. Lon Schneider, director of pharmacological research at USC's Alzheimer's Disease Resea... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7040-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7040_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:39:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/prostate/c/2091/9830/gentamicine</link><title>gentamicine</title><description>... Hello i have a question regaurding prostate meds in oct of 06 i was diagnosed with enlarged prostate, after what seemed like a ton of meds my gp put me on iv gent witch messed up my vestibular, and my inner ear {tintinitis} question is gentamicine an indicated drug for prostate problems thanks jim ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7040-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7040_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:41:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/8312/12816/14-days</link><title>14 days to go</title><description>... Yes ladies and gents, I have hit my "14 days to DR Young" mark.  Still in the grips of an awful depressive mood,and this is one of the few things keeping me going . I just keep thinking " i cant give up, i see Dr Young in 2 weeks" thank God for this upcoming appointment and of course, thank God for friends :-)   love to you all bim  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7040-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7040_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:42:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/33843/137982</link><title>can't finish during sex?</title><description>... i've just started having sex with my girlfriend, and so far i can't climax while we have sex, she can but it doesn't happen for me. I've realised lately I have a slightly tight foreskin so i've started doing stretches as advised by many websites, gentely doesn't hurt and i know it will take time to allow the foreskin to fully retract over the head and glands, but i was wondering what else can i do? my girlfriend is getting worried and upset it's her fault, it's not obviously, and i want to finish obviously as well, any advice? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7040-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7040_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:43:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/erectile-dysfunction/c/450102/90577/dont</link><title>Dont' Need Drugs!</title><description>...   ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7040-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7040_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:44:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/35788/123913/totalmente</link><title>DEPRESION??'SOCIEDAD TOTALMENTE ENFERMA, MULTIPLES FACTORES</title><description>... EN LA REPUBLICA ARGENTINA, vivimos en una sociedad enferma, enferma de ODIO IRRECONCILIABLE CON LA VERDAD HISTORICA, sometida por los ORGANISMOS DEL ESTADO, EXTORSIONADOS, POR LA AFIP-DGI-PAMI-ANSES-ONCCA-MINISTERIOS DEL TRABAJO, NACIONAL Y PROVINCIALES.-CATASTROS,TIERRAS Y CONTRIBUCIONES DE MEJORAS PROVINCIALES, ES NECESARIO Y URGENTE UNIFICAR TODOE EN UN SOLO ORGANISMO, O TRATARLO POR REGIONES DEL PAIS, CON DIGITALIZACION TOTAL DE LA REPUBLICA, PARA LLEVAR AL CIUDADANO DE LA MANO, CON NUEVA GENTE, DECENTE, QUE AYUDEN AL CONTRIBUYENTE A PAGAR SUS IMPUESTOS, CON MORATORIAAS A DIEZ AÑOS, Y SIN INTERÉS ALGUNO, TERMINAR CON LAS INDUSTRIAS CRIMINALES DEL JUICIO MONTADAS EN MUNICIPIOS Y COMUNAS PARA DESTRUIR EL TRABAJO DEL HOMBRE, SE TRABAJA A DESTAJO, SIN GANAS, BRAZOS CAIDOS, EN FORMA INFORMAL, EN NEGRO, Y CLARO, SE LLEVAN TODO, LOS DELINCUENTES QUE ESTAN EN ESTOS LUGARES CON LA COMPLICIDAD DE MUCHISIMOS FUNCIONARIOS PUBLICOS QUE SE PRESTAN AL JUEGO.-OTRO FACTOR: ATENCION A... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>