<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7042">bmw c1</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:46:31" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7042-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7042_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:46:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/question/941826/92813</link><title>Hugh decline in short timeframe</title><description>... We knew this would happen, but wonder if this very sudden decline is normal. ... Any comments? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7042-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7042_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:47:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/question/941826/86655</link><title>My dad is not on any ALZ meds....</title><description>... My dad is not on any ALZ meds....only blood pressure meds.  He is in late stages and lives at home with my mom and sister.  He sees people, animals, "things" frequently.  We just tell him "No, there's no one/nothing there.  Is that the right thing to tell him?  Would any kind of medicine  help him? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7042-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7042_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:47:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/question/941826/93024</link><title>I'm wondering about AD patients and crying</title><description>... My Dad cried......he sobbed and shed very many real tears this morning when my son and I said goodbye.  He lives with my Mum and my sister (who were home), so he is never alone.  We were all stumped by the sudden uncontrollable sobbing.  It is so heart-wrenching.  Because none of us know what he is remembering or thinking to make him so sad.  Has this happened to any of your loved ones? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7042-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7042_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:49:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/question/941826/87338</link><title>My Dad always loses his balance. He especially wants to pitch backwards.</title><description>... ... The balance thing has us stumped.  All his labs are okay, so there's not an infection anywhere.  I guess the alz is just eating that part of the brain??  Any ideas?  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7042-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7042_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:50:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/86453</link><title>Would I trade it?</title><description>...   ... I would like to be more outgoing, extroverted.  I would like to try out being less fearful of doing new things.  I would like to be able to sit through a whole movie without having to go out and walk off my anxiety after sitting there for the first 20 minutes.  How many movies have I walked out of just because I can't sit still?  Is it me?  Is it medication side effects? ...   ... Some things, you can go into that fittin... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7042-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7042_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:51:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/927520/98450/start</link><title>Where do I start</title><description>...      I am a woman of 64 and I am depressed.  It seems that every December I go into a depression but this year seems to be worse.  I have had so many blessings in my life and my friends tell me to draw closer to God.  I am close to God but I find  myself not wanting to do daily things like reading my bible, or even praying, doing house work, paying bills,or so many things. My children are here for me but I seem to fall in and out of this awful feeling that I cannot describe.   ...      I guess I will start back Dec 24 1998, my husband, three daughters and myself were headed out to families to have a wonderful Christmas Eve as we always did for 25 years and a young man driving his new B.M.W. ran a stop sign doing 84 mph and T boned our car.  We rolled 40 feet off of the road and into a field.  My life was changed in just a second when I lost my husband and my 15 year old daughter.  My husband on impact and my d... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7042-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7042_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:51:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/78660/17532/lyme-disease</link><title>Lyme disease in Connecticut</title><description>... It's December 8, 2007 and I'm beginning my second month of antibiotic treatments. I think that I developed the disease in late May or early June but, because a bulls-eye rash never showed up, I can only guess at when it really hit me.   Additionally, because I've 'normally' got arthritis and I've had aches and pains for 20 years anyway, I took the gradual increase in pain as simply a part of having arthritis.   My symptoms sort of snuck up on me: I found that, because my shoulders were so stiff, I couldn't reach my back in order to wash it while I was in the shower. I chalked it up to the fact that I'd dislocated one of my shoulders in an accident in my early 2o's and never had it looked at by a doctor. (It still 'dislocates' spontaneously from time-to-time and makes me wince a bit.)   I used to get into my car by first putting my legs in and then simply sitting down. Early this summer my hips began to bother me and I had ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7042-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7042_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:52:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/850274/134476/frustration</link><title>sadness, anger, frustration, confusion</title><description>... I am torn up inside. My father sent me an email, several. My uncle is deteriorating he told me. ... I am sad, scared. I sent my father flowers and a book, Chicken Soup for the Grieving Soul. He seemed very happy about this and said the book was helping. ... Then I sent flowers, a letter, a stuffed dalmation dog, and 2 Bibles to my uncle. ... My family is so messed up. My uncle has told me he does not love my father. This hurts as my father is over there all the time and very very sad and tells me he loves his brother and does not want him to die. ... I sent an email to my father and it said thank you to my uncle for being a second role model for my brother and I while we were growing up in addition to our father. I thanked him for discussing my 'bizarre' father with me and his family to understand him although, I said I loved my father very much as I was sure he does too. ... I do not ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>