<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7043">rhapsody in blue sheet piano</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:53:45" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7043-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7043_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:53:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/18/16879/ten-tips-holidays</link><title>Ten Tips for Surviving the Holidays with Depression</title><description>... I just got back from shopping on Black Friday, the day after Christmas. It's called Black Friday because it's the first day of the year that retailers (potentially) start seeing black ink on the balance sheet instead of red. For almost anyone else, unless you're suffering from the holiday blues , Black Friday is the beginning of the the holiday season, full of gift-giving, parties, lots of yummy food and family togetherness. For anyone with depression, however, Black Friday might be thought of as the official start of one of the worst times of the year. Not only are there so many more demands on your time, energy and finances (often an issue for anyone with depression), but there's also an increase in potential irritants like holiday music, crowds and commercialism (which is depressing to everyone). But never fear. Santa Deborah is here to give you a gift: my tips for making it through the holiday season with depression. I figure, conservatively, that I dragged myself th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7043-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7043_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:54:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/88543/depression</link><title>Do You Have Morning Depression?</title><description>... ... In fact I did find many references in the literature for morning depression by its formal name of diurnal mood variation .   Diurnal mood variation is described as a symptom of generally more severe depression where one's mood is worse at certain times of day.  For many people this time of day is the morning hours where one feels the worst and then they may feel better as the day goes on.  It is unclear what causes diurnal mood variation but some think it has to do with a disruption to biological circadian rhythms or our body's natural body clock.  For some people it may be biologically easier to feel... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7043-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7043_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:55:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/93829/29204/seclusion</link><title>Seclusion</title><description>...   ... Confined ...   ... Cranberry ... cocktail is dribbled upon the worn, white sheet, ... Stretched ... over the hard blue mattress ... That ... lies upon the concrete floor, ... In ... the corner of this cracker-box room. ... My ... left arm bandaged in stark white tape, ... Both ... arms, strapped in leather. ... Eyes, ... like revolving planets ... Cast ... themselves around this peach colored room. ... This ... color is supposed to calm me; ... I ... can only hear the screaming, ... The ... blood curdling voices, ... Self-infliction, ... The ... slamming of the door, ... And ... the turning of the lock- ... Seclusion… ... ...                                                 Claudia Krizay ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7043-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7043_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:56:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/779949/65563/migraine-parts</link><title>Migraine: A Symphony in Four Parts</title><description>...   ... He kicks his legs over ... the edge of the piano seat, ... his feet dangling in time ... to the notes he plunks ... out. Slow to play, he ... does not fear your threats. ...   ... You've already shut ... the lights off, draped ... the cool cloth over your ... eyes, and removed the safety ... cap from the bottle of aspirin. ... He clunks through the intro, ...   ... gains speed as the crescendo ... burns into your skin.  ... He pulses and twists ... while you swing ... from the hand ... of a metronome. The notes ...   ... thump drilling holes ... in to your skull. ... This is a song he can play ... without sheet music. ... After eight hours, ... you still can't name that tune.  ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7043-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7043_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:57:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/15/161111/music-depression-oppression</link><title>Music, Depression, Oppression, Salvation</title><description>...   ... A few days ago, the young Korean violinist, Ji-Hae Park, gave a TED Talk, entitled, The Violin and My Long Dark Night of the Soul . Ms Park began with an exuberant rendition of Vivaldi. Then she put down her violin and revealed that she had once suffered from severe depression and had been in total despair. ...   ... Depressives, of course, are drawn to music and the arts and literature. The condition informs their work. Writing in the Opinionator blog on the NY Times earlier this year, composer Keeril Makan disclosed that “the act of composing is in a dynamic relationship with my emotional life.” ...   ... But something else seemed to be going on with Ms Park. “The violin,” she related, “which meant everything to me, became a grave burden to me.” Ms Park did not elaborate, but we can take an educated guess that the musical prodigy career path that she had been pushed into had taken her to the breaki... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7043-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7043_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:58:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/2299/live-tom-woottons</link><title>Reporting Live from Tom Wootton's Conference</title><description>... ... Very few people I talk to or communicate with see bipolar as an advantage, I know that a large chunk of my personality that I cherish – my creativity, my vision, my sensitivity, my mild craziness – can be attributed to some “good” bipolar genes, but this is a hard sell to people still struggling to find the right meds who are looking to pick up the pieces to their shattered lives. ... ... ... “There is no good or all bad,” Tom opened with, or words to that effect. Then he ran through the short version of the all-day or two-day seminar he gives. He started out by having us name all the bad things about mania. Well, that was easy. The list filled... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7043-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7043_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 16:59:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/132903/59470</link><title>Help with adhd</title><description>... Hi I am a mother of 3 and my son has adhd odd ocd and a sleeping disorder. He has been on Ritalin for the past 4 years. The last 6-8 months have been a total nightmare the doctors have changed his medication to see if this will improve his behaviour. He is on Concerta xl now but I think they are making him worse. He was sent home from school yesterday as he had a very bad violent outburst where he broke 2 windows a piano 2 doors all the equipment in the art room as well as throwing paint all over the teacher. He has also been refused his sna for the classroom. There is a school in my area that deals with kids who have adhd but as my sons case is so severe they will not accept him there. I am really at my wits end with it at this stage. I cannot let him out playing as he hits all the other kids and also shows violent behaviour towards other parents too. He does not sleep either even though he is using Melatonin to aid his sleep. I am awake around the clock looking after him even when h... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7043-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7043_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:00:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/38988/39261/prone</link><title>THE PRONE</title><description>...   ... PRONE 7/13/05 ... I am a good patient ... dutifully take off clothes ... place them in bags ... marked patients belongings ... put on blue johnny gown ... matching shower cap ... non slip soled socks ... plastic ID bracelet ... without adornment ... reduced to flesh and bone ... lie on gurney ... covered with sheets ... sign above says NPO ... nothing by mouth ... I am good at ignoring ... thirsts of the body ... hold my arm out ... Nurse says make a fist ... look away at this point ... wait for the pinch ... she inserts a catheter ... into my hands best vein ... IV drips slowly ... I am taken ... give myself ... over to the O.R. ... prepped and ready ... for the MDeity ... he pushes godly drugs ... into my sea blue vein ... Via Con Dios ... I am ready to be reborn ... under anesthesia's baptism ... for a few seconds ... I struggle to stay conscious ... (this is the best part) ... for a brief moment ... I fall like Alice into a rabbit hole ... fast drops straight down ... into a sea of darkness ... ride to a place where nothing is ... memorable and what is left ... behind vanishes in my wake ... all too soon ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7043-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7043_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:01:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/109856/midweek-glory</link><title>Overcoming your Morning Depression</title><description>...        A little inspiration to get you over the hump... ...   ... ...   ... For this week's Midweek Muse we are going to be expressing how we feel about the morning. ...   ... I know for many of us who suffer from depression, the mornings can be a bad time of day, eliciting a sense of dread and even panic about what the day will bring.  Many of you have responded to my post about morning depression saying that your feelings of depression can be especially intense in these early hours. ...   ... But it doesn't have to be this way.  Mornings can also be a peaceful respite, a time of inspiration, and a point of entry for light and hope. ...   ... Here are some of my personal memories, thoughts, and inspirations about the morning: ...   ... One of my fondest sensory memories of my childhood was my grandmother's home.  It was small and quaint with blue morning glories which wrapped around the porch rails.  If you look through the center you... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7043-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7043_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:01:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/38988/39254/ll-swimmingly</link><title>The Last Thing the Doctor Said Before Surgery was, "You'll do swimmingly."</title><description>...   ... THE LAST THING THE DOCTOR SAID BEFORE SURGERY WAS, ... "YOU'LL DO SWIMMINGLY." ... 1. ... Room 428, 5:00 a.m. ... The nurse wakes you up to take blood and vitals. ... It's breakfast time, but the sign over the bed says NPO. ... Take a long shower, brush your teeth a few times. Swish ... and spit, a sneaky way to wet your mouth. Swish again. ... It's a long ride, swooshed down silent corridors, gurney ... wheels clatter on steel floored elevators to the O.R. suite. ... 2. ... Pre-Op ... First to arrive, you're parked in a waiting dock for hours ... in front of automatic doors. Each time the doors slide open, ... watch anesthesiologists line up in light blue caps, ready ... Doors open and close, each time, different staff pace around. ... Some amble with Blackberries, some chat in groups. ... More patients wheeled in, curtains drawn around my stall. ... Surgeons arrive at 8:00. ... Meet green gowned angels who voice orders from ... behind masks. Watch their eyes for any sign of distress ... as they adjust charts, tubing, and lines, with furtive ... touches. Last mi... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>