<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7044">song of ice and fire</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:02:49" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7044-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7044_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:02:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/262730/164931</link><title>the skin and muscle around my leg burn like it is being roasted on fire.if i place my leg on ice before i feel a little relieve.i don't feel any pain in the bones</title><description>... the skin and muscle around my leg burn like it is being roasted on fire. this continues for a long time usually at night when i'm trying to sleep. hence, the burning sensation makes me restless and sleepless. if i place my leg in ice water or on ice before i feel a little relieve.i don't feel any pain in the bones or inside but only the burning sensation in the skin and muscle. please what is the cause of this and how do i treated it. pls recommend some useful medicines for me because i'm suffering and i been to a different health centres and hospitals but the situation persist. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7044-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7044_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:03:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/331225</link><title>Sometimes only the songs by Supertramp can get you through a mixed episode</title><description>...   ... So, just saying, even when wer'e in  the mixed mood variety of bi-polar symtoms we can be useful.  Even if our spelling does go to ths shits.  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7044-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7044_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:04:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/915283/154027/heat-pain</link><title>When to Use HEAT or ICE for Pain</title><description>...   ... During your episode of pain after doing something that you might regret doing, you may wonder what works best, heat or ice? Actually, both have been shown to effectively reduce pain. Ice lollies reduce the pain after tonsillectomies . 1 Ice relieves the pain after knee replacement surgery . 2 The coldness constricts blood vessels, reduces swel... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7044-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7044_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:05:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/89/64263/wheelchairs</link><title>Wheelchairs &amp; Ice Packs: An Arthritis Survivor’s Guide to Orthopedic Surgeries</title><description>...   ...   ... This has made my life a touch challenging.  I love to cook and tried to grocery shop and prepare as much as possible before the siege began.  I made a variety of small meatloaves, chicken noodle and vegetable soups, etc. to freeze in individual portions since I live alone.  I also froze bagels, muffins, hamburger patties, and other things individually. ...   ... When I returned home, post-op, I was met with a mountain of stairs (I have many steps outside my house and, since it is a split-foyer, lots more stairs inside).  After trying to discover an easy solution to this, my friend and I ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7044-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7044_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:06:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002843trt.html</link><title>Fire-ant treatment</title><description>... Home Treatment Home treatment depends on the location of, and reaction to, the sting. Wash the exposed area with plenty of soap and water. Do not use alcohol to wash the area. Wash eyes with plenty of water if any toxin gets in them. For mild stings, place ice (wrapped in a washcloth or other suitable covering) on the bite area for 10 minutes and then off for 10 minutes. Repeat this process. If the patient has circulatory problems, decrease the time to prevent possible damage to the skin. Some people are allergic to fire ant venom. If the reaction is severe, seek immediate medical help and call your local emergency number (such as 911) or poison control. Those who have an allergy to insect bites or stings should carry a bee sting kit (which requires a prescription) and become familiar with how to use it in the event of an emergency. Before Calling Emergency Determine the following information: Patient's age, weight, and condition Identification of the insect, if possible Time of the bite Poison ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7044-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7044_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:07:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/5067/17095/great-close-fired</link><title>Great- can't see, can't think and am close to being fired</title><description>... I have not been fired from a job since I was eighteen years old and I would rather not get fired now... however, I cannot concieve how anyone would want an employee who only shows up to work three days out of the week.  Even when I am at work, I am working with a migraine, which is rather like swimming in pudding... and while I am used to the troubles with writing, the computer typos and such, it is rather hard to explain to others.  My eyes have been shot lately, the whole visual aura thing is going crazy, and I can't really see very far and what I do see if all very warpy.  The hormonal migraines have been torture, because since I am only on the arthrotec, I cannot take the voltaren for bad PMS cramps and the one pill does not cut it for either... which means a lot of pain and very sick to the stomach.   So I miss one more day and I am fired.  I have tried to establish a sort of compramise in work and hours and maybe that will work... really depends on my ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7044-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7044_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:08:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/c/96140/56974/mad-hell</link><title>Mad As Hell - Can You Get Fired Because of Menopause?</title><description>...   ... Bad enough that we have to go through hot flashes, weight gain and mood swings, now we have to fear for our jobs, too? I know what it's like to lose your job because of age discrimination. Ladies and friends: This has got to stop! ...   ... The woman in the Midwest said she was caught crying a few times. I don't know the details of this woman's story but I do know that in my career, I have been hurt, insulted, stepped on, walked over, and treated horribly by both men and women, and I have refused to cry in front of any of them. But I'm lucky that I can control my tear ducts, others may not be able to. Is that any reason to FIRE someone?   ...   ... If a man were having some emotional issues at work, maybe a tendency to slam his office door, come in late a few times or bark at the receptionist once or twice, do you think ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7044-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7044_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:09:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/592998/140948</link><title>i need hindi song the song will come like we are back we are back</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7044-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7044_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:09:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/240911/150720</link><title>Ice pick/Ice cream headche type</title><description>... hi, my sis-in-law is suffering with unknown headche since 3 yrs. according to discussion &amp; study online, this is Ice pick/Ice cream headche type. pl. suggest me the Doctor &amp; usefull medicines for her that is she is in good health as early as possible. - Sushil Mainwal ... Moderator's note: For your security and privacy, please do not post personal contact information such as email addresses and phone numbers. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7044-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7044_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:10:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/452830/84809</link><title>Can you drink Ice water with diabetes, or should you jsut drink water with no ice</title><description>... I have been told that you should not drink cold beverages, just hot or warm ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>