<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7045">Natural Parks America</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:10:51" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7045-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7045_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:10:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/common/images/image.html</link><title>boy, tree, playing, park, nature, promo</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7045-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7045_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:11:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/57718/50962/park-helps-symptoms</link><title>A Walk in the Park Helps ADHD Symptoms</title><description>...   ... Unfortunately, there has been little research to show that nontraditional, alternative treatments are as effective as medications in treating ADHD. However, a recent study gives a bit of optimism for a very simple way to help beat ADHD symptoms: enjoying a bit of green outdoors every day. ... Maybe mother was right when she "shooed" her children out to play each day, knowing fresh air was good for them. ...   ... In a recent issue of the Journal of Attention Disorders, researchers reported that children with ADHD who walked for 20 minutes through a park had an improvement in attention vs those who took a walk through a less "green" area- a neighborhood or downtown area. ...   ... Child environment and behavior researchers Andr... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7045-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7045_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:12:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/caregiver-2081-143.html</link><title>The Alzheimer's Foundation of America- Q&amp;A on Caregiving with founder Eric Hall</title><description>... The Alzheimer’s Foundation of America (AFA) released the findings of their I CAN: Investigating Caregivers' Attitudes and Needs survey. The survey uncovered significant trends among caregivers of Alzheimer’s patients, including a link between the stigma associated with the disease and dramatic delays in Alzheimer’s diagnosis. The AFA found that caregivers are in dire need of support and educational resources, and that despite the burdens of this tragic disease, caregivers often felt they came out stronger and more compassionate as a result of caring for a loved one. Our Alzheimer's spoke with Eric Hall, the president of the AFA, to hear more about the survey, what the AFA learned about caregivers, and what we can do to improve the quality of Alzheimer’s care in this country. A-I: Why did the AFA embark on this project of surveying the caregivers of Alzheimer’s patients? EH: The Alzheimer’s Foundation of America (AFA), as the nation’s l... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7045-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7045_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:13:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/896502/138961/workforce</link><title>New Study Links Changing Nature of U.S. Workforce to Obesity Epidemic</title><description>... OK, I think I’ve had an important “a-ha moment.” I recently wrote a new sharepost entitled, “Regular Movement Critical to Your Health When You Have a Desk Job.” Now a New York Times story by Tara Parker-Pope describes new research that points to another way that a desk job is hurting our health. It turns out that holding a desk job may be one of the key reasons behind the obesity epidemic. ... In this study, researchers reviewed the changing workplace from 1960 until present and found that jobs that requiring physical activity have plunged. In 1960, 50% of jobs required moderate physical activity; now, only 20% of jobs require this level of physical activity, while 80% of American jobs are sedentary or only require light activity. Parker-Pope wrote, “The shift translates to an average decline of 120 to 140 calories a day in physical activity, closely matching the weight gain over the past five decades, according to the report, published Wednesday in the... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7045-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7045_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:13:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/59238/127574/america-stroke</link><title>Obesity and Health Risks in America's Stroke Belt</title><description>...   ... The recent study was actually part of a larger study REGARDS - Reasons for Geographic and Racial Differences in Stroke - based at University of Alabama at Birmingham, with 21,675 participants followed over 4 ½ years, tracking health events.  Of course eating fish is generally a healthy habit, since many fish choic... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7045-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7045_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:14:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/incontinence/c/76594/52857/backs-america</link><title>Cut Backs Across America</title><description>... While we may be facing the worst economic crisis in this country since the Great Depression, as many have decried, it seems illogical to cut the foundation of our country's welfare and the very soil that sustains our well-being, namely education and healthcare. ... As much as we recognize that we cannot tax our way out of this crisis, as Kenneth Adams, chief executive of the Business Council of New York State pronounced, it is also ill-founded thinking that we can allow an avulsion of our very soul and sustenance. ... Something is terribly wrong when we fight foreign wars without a future, ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7045-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7045_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:15:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/140409/bariatric-begin</link><title>Obesity Epidemic in America, How Did it Begin? - My Bariatric Life</title><description>... This article is part of a series on Living Well after Gastric Bypass that covers diet, nutrition, and weight control. Read the first article in the series here . ...   ... I have eliminated processed foods from my life, and just eat real food ...   ... In the more recent years since I had my obesity surgery , I have become educated on healthy eating. It was extremely eye-opening, even shocking, for me to learn where my food really came from and its effects on my health and my life. ...   ... I am so far removed from the relationship with food that I once had. Never more will I stuff my face with processed convenience foods. Instead, I just eat real food (see #JERF on Twitter). What that means is I eat primarily things that can be hunted (meat/fish/fowl) or gathered (produce, nuts, eggs, milk). I supplement my meals with foods that have been minimally-processed such as olive oil, cheese, butter, Greek yogurt, coffee, raw honey, etc. ...   ... I have eliminated refined food... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7045-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7045_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:15:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/59238/161407/america-eating</link><title>What's America Eating?</title><description>...   ... Restaurant sourced pizza, burgers, chicken and French fries actually accounted for less calories in the average diet, compared to store-sourced breads, grain-based desserts, pasta and yes, soft drinks.  Experts agree that in surveys like NHANES, there is some natural “under-reporting” when participants fill out questionnaires.  Taking that into account, the standard fast food fare still supplied less overall calories in the typical American diet compared to these four other identified sources. ...   ... Some interesting statistics: ...   ... Teen... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7045-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7045_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:16:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/647186/142508/abnormal</link><title>Atrial Fibrillation: America's Most Common Abnormal Heart Rhythm</title><description>...   ... So I told myself that I had been under a lot of stress. Earlier in the year, I had been the major caregiver for a family member who had a flare of Crohn's Disease. It took months to resolve the crisis, so naturally, I thought I was still feeling the anxiety. ... But there were other things I began to notice: unusual breathlessness when I was taking my daily walk, and... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7045-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7045_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:17:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/63356/123151/diabetes-america</link><title>The Rising Cost of Diabetes in America</title><description>...   ... What I didn't share with you is how even with health insurance, the rising insurance premiums and co-pays are bankrupting patients like myself who are barely scraping by in this economy. ...   ... Yes, I'm one of the guilty parties who actually (gasp) uses their insurance policies so surely I'm to blame. It's kind of like how I have to pay a higher car insurance rate ever since another driver decided to run a red light and smash into another car that then crunched my car as it idled while waiting at a red light. I'm guilty because I was there. Right place. Wrong time. ...   ... So, too, in childhood. At eleven, I developed "juvenile" or Type 1 diabetes, an auto-immune disease that bankrupted my pancreas of in... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>