<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7046">tuning fork</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:18:00" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7046-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7046_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:18:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/copd/c/55817/43443/stuck-middle</link><title>A Smoker's Tune: Stuck in the Middle Again</title><description>...   ... "Trying to make some sense of it all, But I can see that it makes no sense at all, Is it cool to go to sleep on the floor, 'Cause I don't think that I can take anymore Clowns to the left of me, Jokers to the right, ... Here I am, stuck in the middle with you." ...   ... The clowns to the left of me are the ones who say, "Just have a cigarette. You know you want one. What difference does it make? They could drop the bomb tomorrow and, if you'd quit smoking years before, wouldn't your last thought be, "Well, CRAP...why did I do that? Just THINK of how many cigarettes you could have smoked...and all for nothing!" That's the DEVIL talking, and his pitchfork hurts! ...   ... The Jokers to the right, if you're still a smoker, are those who have convinced you that the evil weed won't affect you. Your cough and sputter are just nature's way of hawking up what needs to come out. Nevermind that peopl... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7046-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7046_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:18:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/56/6819/put-fork</link><title>Put Down the Fork</title><description>... ... Mastication is the scientific word for chewing, which is the beginning of the entire digestive process. Our teeth help us grind food into small pieces. When we chew, the mouth releases saliva which lubricates the food. Saliva also contains the enzyme amylase which helps break down carbohydrates. The food is then ready to be swallowed and passes through the esophagus to the stomach and small intestines where food is further digested. The body absorbs most nutrients from food while it is in the intestines. ... ... Several chemical signals are involved in the digestive process. For example, while you chew, the brain receives signals that allow you to see, smell, and taste your fo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7046-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7046_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:19:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/3511/129552/fork-directs</link><title>As the fork directs</title><description>...   ... I have been writing my memoir on and off for about 9 months. Its coming along nicely. It is my hope that the class will give me some insight and ideas. ...   ... I know a little bit about publishing a book. A friend and I wrote a book. It is in print. It took us a year and half to finish it. He had worked on it a lot before we met. ...   ... Yesterday I ended Mike's chapter. I cried. The anguish I feel is still with me and will be forever. I also got angry when it came to the "family".  That anger will go away. The power to forgive is greater than the power to continue in anger. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7046-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7046_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:19:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/common/images/image.html</link><title>pasta on fork</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7046-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7046_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:20:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/question/991397/127537</link><title>i am 27 and weigh over 400 pds. is there anyone who would help me or should i just eat my to the grave with a fork and spoon</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7046-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7046_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:20:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/27148/132856/physical</link><title>How to Get the Most from a Physical Therapy Tune-Up</title><description>... When a car starts running a little rough, the first thought is to take it in for a tune-up. Check the oil. Check the spark plugs. Check the battery. When the human body starts sputtering, why not get a physical therapy tune-up? Check the muscle strength. Check the balance. Check the body mechanics. Even someone who has had a painful problem for years can benefit from a system-wide check, especially if the pain has been getting worse lately. ...   ... For example, a 41 year old woman with a history of a chronic neck, chest and arm pain started experiencing more frequent flare-ups with activities like playing baseball with her son. She had been through physical therapy before and was doing a home exercises program. But, I thought she could use a physical therapy tune-up. I wrote her a prescription with specific instruction for the physical therapist and sent her to the best one in town. After just a couple of weeks, she was feeling much better. The tune-up improved the mobility in her tho... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7046-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7046_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:21:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/202/20880/fine-tuning</link><title>Fine tuning my Migraine preventive</title><description>... I've been having a hard time with chronic pain and Migraines since the middle of January. Twice in the last four weeks, I have had IV infusion treatments in my doctor's office. The first treatment was not sucessful; however, the second time, my pain was significantly reduced.   Since I am still in pain, my doctor and I have opted to "fine tune" my preventive medication . I began taking Zonegran (an antiseizure medication commonly used for Migraine prevention) again Sunday evening. This is in place of Lamictal , another drug in the same class of drugs as Zonegran. I took Zonegran for a while with some good results, but thought it may have been interferring with some of my depression issues, so I tapered off it and went started Lamictal. In my case, Zonegran and my depression were not related.   I am hopeful I will see a reduction in my Migraine pain with Zonegran. I'll keep you posted. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7046-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7046_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:22:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/224205/156152/co</link><title>Controlling pain sensation by mind body tuning.</title><description>...   ... I had taken the Reiki course second degree when I was not afflicted with RA.   In second degree Reiki we are also taught how to heal others at a distance. You all will get lots of material on Reiki on the net so I will not repeat them. I will just narrate my experience. Unlik... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7046-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7046_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:22:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/8585/14160/time-tune</link><title>Time to Tune In</title><description>... Too many of us sit inside and watch television for hours at a time. It's incredibly detrimental. We are tuning out. We are avoiding. It's time to change that. Find something that changes your attitude, gets you plugged into life again. For me, it's George Harrison's "My Sweet Lord."  That song speaks to my soul, reminds me that I am, no matter what, really alive. Like nothing else, it changes my attitude for the better, no matter what else is going on in my life. We all have that something, even if we have forgotten what it is. It might be as simple as a sunrise or as involved as getting out to a baseball game. We all have it. And it's important to take advantage of it, especially at the worst of times. So take your favorite book, put that favorite song on the iPod and get outside into the sunshine for a bit. Find a way to see an exhibition game or even Little League, maybe soccer or football. Get out and root for the kids. But remind yourse... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7046-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7046_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:23:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/644255/96030/special-day</link><title>Tune in to Kaleidoscope, a women and cancer special, airing Thanksgiving Day on FOX!</title><description>...    ... Kaleidoscope is hosted by a trio of cancer survivors, or "thrivers": The legendary singer and performer, Olivia Newton-John , and Olympic Champions Dorothy Hamill and Scott Hamilton. (who will both be returning to the ice for the first time on the show!) Kaleidoscope also features American Idol favorites David Archuleta and Katharine McPhee and  Olympians Kristi Yamaguchi and Nancy Kerrigan. ...   ... The show will provide information and resources on basic issues surrounding women and cancer...all in a positive and uplifiting way. Please join us for an enchanting evening of Sport, Song and Survivorship! ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>