<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7047">Dewar flask</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:24:13" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7047-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7047_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:24:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/701853/105343/bike</link><title>Garage, bike</title><description>...               Well got the Bike out of the garage with the help of Michelle our scheme manager only to find the front tyre was flat  . Found a pump amongst other things I had forgotten I had........won't throw any of the junk out tho you never know might come in handy one day. Any how still couldn't inflate the tower so enrolled a fellow resident to help and success one inflated tyre ! ...  So yesterday for the 1st time in 3 and 1/2 yrs I cycled to POynton and back (total 8 mile) Then went back into the village later (2mile). You are probably wondering why i hadn't been on my bicycle for 3 and 1/2 yrs. Back then I wasn't very good with balance and a Neurologist told me i was to dangerous and to get rid HA HA ha I didn't. I lent it to my Daughter for a while and then it went into the garage. So yesterday was a RED LETTER DAY ! ... Today I am off down the allotment. Another 1st for this year and a challeng... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7047-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7047_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:24:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/59238/117578/started-cracker</link><title>Junk Food Started with Cracker Jacks</title><description>...   ... Tootsie Rolls came next in 1905 in New York and became the first penny candy to be sold individually wrapped. In 1923, by chance, a fellow left a powdered soda drink out on his porch with a wooden stirring stick still in it and - you guessed it-it froze and was found the next morning. Thus was born a new confection that Unilever now sells to the tune of...2 billion (popsicles) a year. In 1928 came the product that could add fun to a chewing experience - bubble gum. In 1930, pans that were used for strawberry shortcakes stood idle when strawberries were out of season. So a cook decided to experiment with baking mini cakes and he injected them with banana crème... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7047-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7047_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:25:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/1443/167213/fostering-empathy-children-adhd</link><title>Fostering Empathy in Children with ADHD</title><description>... ... Some children with ADHD might get constant attention; parents and teachers pay extra attention to behavior and grades. This sometimes creates a feeling that they are the center of attention. They aren’t used to people paying attention to other children or are simply don’t notice when they do. When a need arises, they expect it to be taken care of immediately and don’t understand when other children’s needs must come first. ... ... Some people are naturally more empathetic. They have the... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7047-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7047_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:26:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/12096/alcohol-elders</link><title>Watching for Alcohol Withdrawal in Elders</title><description>... My post last month, " Is It Dementia or Delirium ?" has kept nagging at me, and I've finally figured out why. There's something else that needs to be considered, when evaluating an elder who is confused or even delirious while in the hospital. We need to consider alcohol.   The first elder who I officially cared for was my next-door neighbor, Joe. Joe was totally deaf from Ménière's disease. He was in his 80s and alcohol had been a large part of his life since Prohibition, when he'd carry a hip flask of moonshine. It wasn't news to me that Joe was alcoholic. When I became his default caregiver, he was in his mid-eighties, and had no desire to change. It was a part of who he was, and we both knew it. We also both knew that, in some way, alcohol would likely have a part in what killed him.   Joe fell often, and much of it was after a number of drinks. One evening he was barbecuing in his garage. I looked out my kitchen window and... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7047-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7047_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:27:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/32873/85977/canes</link><title>Mobility Aids and MS: Canes</title><description>... Walking difficulties are awkward, but people with MS are often hesitant to use a cane .  MS is often a hidden condition and carrying a walking aid simply exposes it to the world.  But why is it so embarrassing?  Canes first came into play when humble shepherds used their staffs to guide and protect their sheep. However, as the years passed, the cane became a symbol of social prestige and privilege. Marie Antoinette made them fashionable and American presidents often carried them. With such a rich history progressing from a lowly tool to a status symbol, a cane is embarrassing no more.  You sway when you walk, you fall down, people think you look drunk and then finally you believe it is time to consider a cane. Karen Zielinski gives advice about trying to walk when it's difficult. She emphasizes that it does not increase your ability to walk, but it does tire you out. Still you think you can maintain your independence if you just try a little harder. Zielinski tell... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7047-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7047_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:27:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/89/36315/chocolate</link><title>Malaria and Chocolate Chips</title><description>... Much to my dismay, my count was Level 8, a rather high count, and began my first of 5 daily shots. With my continuing high fever, the doctor added a strong regimen of Amoxycillin, pain pills, and a prescription for Pectylin-C, an expectorant. It would probably have been a far more interesting experience if I hadn't been so ill!! ...   ... The clinic was a very small place, several miles from my homebase. Each part, i.e. Laboratory, business office, pharmacy, surgery, Xray, etc. was in a separate building. NO medical history was taken, and they didn't even know my name until ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>