<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7048">pictures auvergne</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:28:30" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7048-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7048_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:28:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/750943/138797</link><title>Mom had breast cancer my mammogram shows density in one breast mass in other going in more pictures and possible ultrasound d Should I insist on ultrasound no matter what pictures show thanks</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7048-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7048_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:29:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/c/727598/119470/shortly-middle</link><title>"Someone Will Be With You Shortly" Paints A Funny and Real Picture of Middle-Age Life</title><description>...   ... Hopefully, my aches, pains and meds won’t be a big part of my conversation. Instead, I hope to keep a sense of humor and perspective on the challenges of aging, but to be involved fully in the world. To reach that goal means starting now. ...   ... Which brings me to my book group’s lastest read, “Someone Will Be with You Shortly: Notes From  A Perfectly Imperfect Life” by Lisa Kogan . You may know Lisa from her regular column in O Magazine where she has developed a keen eye and descriptive style that provides a unique take on the world. In one of ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7048-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7048_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:30:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/question/228594/51463</link><title>PICTURE</title><description>... show picture of tramadoll ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7048-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7048_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:30:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/440152/116694/site</link><title>QQuestion on site, can't add picture</title><description>... What file formats will this site take to add a picture? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7048-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7048_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:31:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/284954/55916</link><title>Pill pictures and informatio?</title><description>... I see you have a list of most pain drugs and their pictures-How can I find them on METHADONE? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7048-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7048_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:31:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/question/512837/79345</link><title>question about pictures</title><description>... i put a picture on my sharepost, all that showed up was a box with an x in it. what am i doing wrong ? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7048-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7048_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:32:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/76190/18180/arthr</link><title>Arthritis pictures</title><description>... This section of one of my favorite websites is devoted to providing pictures and images of the deferent types of arthritis. Ankylosing Spondylitis Picture Arthritis hands Bouchard's nodes Bursitis Picture Calcaneal Bursitis Carpal tunnel Dupuytrens contracture Elephantiasis Osteopetrosis Pagets Disease Pelvic Inflammatory Disease ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7048-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7048_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:33:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/9182/7242/farm-show</link><title>Farm Show Pictures</title><description>... Here are pictures of the Farm show we went to. We had fun. It is the Largest Farm show in the world. And peopple from all over the world come by and shop there. Alan loved this big Truck This is Alans Fav. Picture as he loves NASCAR. We had fun. There are none of Michael as he was sleeping through most of it lol. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7048-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7048_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:34:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/question/897869/72209</link><title>profile picture/avatar</title><description>...   ... Maybe this is the wrong place to ask questions of this nature? ...   ... Thanks in advance for your help! ...   ... maryann ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7048-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7048_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:34:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/76190/18184/bone</link><title>Bone disease pictures</title><description>... Here are links to bone related disease pictures.   Bone Cell Bone Marrow Bone Scan Bone tissue Picture Carpal Tunnel Syndrome Clavicle Picture Collar Bone Hip Bone Hyoid Humerus Jaw Mandible Osteochondroma Picture Osteoporosis Bone Pelvic bone Pelvis Pubic Bone Radius Ribs Scapula Sternum Temporomandibular Joint Ulna ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>