<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7051">dinosaur names</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:48:17" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7051-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7051_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:48:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/204/31150/triptan-migraineurs</link><title>FDA Approves New Triptan-Naproxen Compound for Migraineurs!</title><description>...   ... Russell Katz, M.D., Director, Division of Neurology Products, Office of Drug Evaluation I, Center for Drug Evaluation and Research, Department Of Health &amp; Human Service, Public Health Service with the Food and Drug Administration on April 15th issued an approval letter for a ’new’ Migraine compounded drug called Treximet® which should hit the pharmacy shelves any day now! Yes, our government is hard at work watching over the drug industry to protect us from any mistakes in design and production. But yet make sure we Migraineurs continue to have some new treatments, even if they are just minor improvements over an old favorite. It is an impressive system in action to observer as a health advocate, so forgive us for the melodramatic opening credentials for Dr. Katz, but you g... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7051-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7051_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:48:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/141322/scientific-challenge</link><title>Scientific Challenge to the Bipolar Diagnosis: What It Means to Recovery</title><description>... Is the term, bipolar disorder, a diagnostic dinosaur? Should we just light a match to the DSM right now and start over? I just returned from the National NAMI convention in Chicago, where, at one session in particular - Emerging Technologies to Improve Care - I found myself scribbling very fast into my notepad. The reason had less to do with emerging technologies and more to do with how our new understanding of the brain is rendering the bipolar diagnosis obsolete. As one of the presenters - Daniel Hoffman, chief medical officer of CNS Response - noted (quoting head of the NIMH Thomas Insel): “The DSM is 100 percent reliable and zero percent valid.” What this translates to is that even though every psychiatrist in the world may agree on what bipolar disorder (sort of) looks like, it doesn’t mean it’s true. According to Dr Hoffman: “The world wants buckets of symptom clusters and it doesn’t work.” A month ago, I returned from the Ninth Internation... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7051-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7051_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:49:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/5741/81539/yesterday</link><title>Yesterday all my troubles seem so far away</title><description>...   ... Later in the day I was out front weedwhacking, when a woman pulled up front and was looking at a couch and sofa on the curb. She was trying to put it into her truck. I asked if I could help. She asked her teenage daughter if it was alright, after all she was texting and it was important to finish. Anyway I helped put the stuff in the truck. ...   ... I fixed the upstairs potty. So I thought. We went out shopping and when we got home there was water dripping from the ceiling. I turned the water off and the drip stopped. We called a plumber (actually a few before a human called back) he was here maybe 20 minutes. He said it was a simple fix. Simple for him, not me! Anyway its fixed. I have t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7051-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7051_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:50:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/521/33753/i-really-want-more</link><title>I really want more</title><description>... Every two months, I have about 10 days of pain-free time ... (thanks to nerve block injections). ... I have become very possessive of these days!  ... I live every minute of this time with wild joy! ...   ... I try to fit in as many wonderful activities as possible when I am well. ... DH and I go to dinner, to a movie, we watch late-night TV together. ... We talk about his work, about how the kids are growing and what they are learning. ... We remember each other after a long, pain-filled absence from one another. ...   ... The kids and I do science experiments. ... We search for bugs, build dams in the creek, and take the dog for long walks. ... We go to nearby museums, spend time hiking in the park, and read books about dinosaurs and trains. ... We re-connect after weeks of distance.  ... When you have a mom with bad, daily migraines, you learn to get by. ...   ... These pain free times help us all to hold onto our sanity. ... But I really want more.  ... Mo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7051-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7051_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:50:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/5741/83243/music-life</link><title>Music of my life</title><description>...   ... I woke up after having a weird dream about scientists that successfully cloned dinosaurs. They were roaming all over. My grandson loves dinosaurs. We bought him some at the flea market. A vender had some dinos. I asked her how much they were, she said "The big ones are $1.00 and the small ones $.50". I picked out 5 big ones and was ready to pay $5.00, she said "$2.50." I thought okay that's good." I paid and later I said to Margaret, wow I expected to pay $5.00 but I was pleased that I didn't. ...   ... My zucchini bread is very yummy! The first one wasn't done all the way through, though. It is a good recipe. The bread stuck, so I had to bang the pan on the table to get them out. I sprayed the pans, but they stuck anyway. I'm satisfied with it. Life is like that. If you are stuck bang on something to free yourself. (just don't bang to h... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7051-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7051_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:51:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/5741/69527/lemon-country</link><title>Lemon pie and Classic Country</title><description>...   ... Music is good therapy and shuts up the voices. It is required to have music while I cook. ...   ... I wanna go to the flea market. Frappe doesn't have many fleas...HEE HEE! ...   ...   ... Today is lemon meringue pie day. Maybe porkchops. Margaret makes her own and I make my own. I don't like hers. That's about the only meal I don't like of hers. ...   ... Mandy and I cleaned the pool yesterday. Poor Dylan he was sleeping in the chair and fell out. He's okay, he didn't even cry. I had so much fun with him. He loves dinosaurs. You should see that kid eat! He ate his green beans! I admire him for that..I hate green beans. ...   ... The voices weren't too bad today. Thanks Johnny! ...   ... OMG this music is soooooooo good. ...   ... Well I can't think of much else to... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7051-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7051_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:51:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001909.html</link><title>Discussing death with children overview</title><description>... Definition Alternative Names Childhood bereavement Information Death is a concept that is difficult for a child to understand. Grieving adults are often confused and unsure how to respond supportively. Most children require many explanations and have many questions regarding death. "What happens when people die?" and "Where do they go?" are among the most common. Discussing death is extremely difficult for many adults. It requires recognition that death is a natural process for all people. Children may have problems visualizing death. They may develop fears about what happens after death, what death feels like, or what would happen to them if their parents died. Parents should attempt to openly discuss death with their children if they ask about it or if the situation requires. Death should be discussed honestly and in language that children can understand at their stage of development. A child's concept of death varies with age, and this must be taken into consideration. Age 0 - 2 years: See... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7051-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7051_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:52:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/cold-flu/c/82437/18503/ways-kids-habit</link><title>Nag-Free Ways to Get Kids into the Hand-Washing Habit</title><description>...   ... * First make sure your sink area is kid-friendly by having a stepstool; if your toddler or preschooler still can't reach the faucet, consider purchasing a faucet extender at www.sinkpal.com . ...   ... * Squid Soap is "hands down" one of the most fun ways to get your kids to wash properly. The company manufactures a dispenser soap that looks like an orange squid. Kids squirt the "ink," or soap, on their hands and the ink doesn't rub off unless they wash for the recommended twenty seconds.  ...   ... * Since pump dispenser soaps are better than hand soaps for cutting down on germ trans... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7051-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7051_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:53:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/849319/65994/diagnosed-children</link><title>Advice to Parents of Newly Diagnosed Children on the Autism Spectrum</title><description>...   ... I have flashbacks to when he was a toddler with golden curls and an impish grin.  My son's first word was "GO" which he would chant from the confines of his crib in the middle of the night.  It was an appropriate word for him as his body was in constant motion.  He was also a little escape artist.  I remember the first time we lost sight of him in a store.  My husband, my older son, and I split up to find him.  After several minutes (it seemed like hours) of frantic searching, we found Max happy and immersed in playing with the automatic doors at the entrance of the store.  He was oblivious to our worry. ...   ... Then there were the times when he would escape f... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7051-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7051_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:54:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/autism/c/1443/147861/children-spectrum</link><title>Buying Gifts for Children on the Autism Spectrum</title><description>...   ... As the parent of a self-diagnosed teenage Aspie, I understand how confusing it can be to find a present that will be appreciated. My Aspie has, in some ways, always been the most difficult child to buy gifts for, and on the other hand, has been quite easy. His interests have been varied throughout the year but at the same time, narrow. For example, when he was young, he liked cars. Not the big toy trucks, but the small Matchbox cars. There were small cars all over the house. In other years, he was fascinated with dinosaurs, Legos, Pokemon, Naruto, trains, video games and most recently radio controlled planes and helicopters. Sounds easy to buy gifts, right? Not necessarily, although at different ages he was interested in... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>