<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7052">hotel bruges</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:55:02" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7052-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7052_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:55:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/129542/156971/hotel</link><title>Emergency Situations, Hotel Stays and Mobility: Question of the Week</title><description>...   ... And the best part: We had tickets to see Dan’s favorite, Bruce Springsteen and his legendary E Street Band at Wrigley Field. ...   ... Sounds like a perfect trip, right? ...   ... It was, but while we were there, I experienced one of the scariest moments of my life… ...   ... “Wake up Jennifer!” Dan frantically said. ...   ... I tried to shake him off because I do enjoy my sleep, but he kept shaking my shoulder. ...   ... “WAKE UP JENNIFER!” he emphatically stated yet calmly continued, “The fire alarm in the hotel is going off and we need to evacuate.” ...   ... As the seriousness of his words started to sink in, I opened my eyes. It was about 2:30 in the morning and our room’s fire alarm light was flashing and I heard the hotel’s alarm sounding. ...   ... Again Dan told me to get up and ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7052-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7052_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:55:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/380888/85049</link><title>Allergy free hotels...</title><description>... My wife is extremely allergic to mold...is there any resource that would help us find hotels she could stay at that are truly allergy free, including mold?  Or is there a resource that other users can list good hotels for allergy sufferers? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7052-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7052_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:56:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/840771/103272/allergy-friendly</link><title>Allergy friendly hotels AT LAST!</title><description>... Just found this great site www.allergyfriendlyhotels.com which allows people who suffer from allergies to have their needs catered for. Seems to cater for all allergies including food allergies and has hotels in different countries. Think it is worth a look. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7052-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7052_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:56:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/3900/47510/hotel-room-pure</link><title>Is your hotel room "Pure"?</title><description>... I've written often about the challenges traveling with asthma, allergies and food allergies. Pure Solutions has stepped up to the fore to work towards filling in the gap for those of us with allergies and asthma that travel. In conjunction with participating hotels, Pure Solutions aims to bring an allergen-friendly hospitality experiences to those of us with respiratory issues, allergies, or even the frequent traveler who would like a deeper cleaned room for their business stay. ...   ... The Pure Room takes the following steps to ensure a comfortable night's rest (italics from company press materials): ... * Tea Tree Oil, to further maintain the sanitized conditions, a cartridge of tea tree oil is installed. Tea tree oil, a natural product, is known for its antimicrobial and disinfectant properties. The tea tree oil in a particle form is in a canister placed inside the a/c and heating units, where it vaporizes microscopically into the room. The molecules are virtually odorless; howev... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7052-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7052_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:57:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/sleep-disorders/c/86903/31456/hotels</link><title>Hotels Want you to "Sleep Happy"</title><description>... Here are the top five complaints I hear when it comes to sleep issues : ... ... I can't fall asleep - I just keep spinning the problems of the day ... I fall asleep but wake up, really dwelling on something I need to do tomorrow ... I fall asleep, but my kids - the dog - the neighbors - wake me up, and then I can't fall back asleep ... I sleep through the night, but wake up feeling like I didn't sleep for even an hour; I'm still so tired. ... My sleep patterns just seem to be constantly changing - is it aging? Something else that's serious?? ... ...   ... Sleep to me is a chance to re-charge all of my energy engines - physical, mental, emotional; it's a chance to let stress go, let my body relax, dream happy thoughts.  Sure, that's my fantasy script, but usually, the opposite happens.  I experience the common scenario of hit or miss when it comes to a good night's sleep.  So I'm also the perfect person to share what I do know about sleep problems and what we can all do to get a good night's s... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7052-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7052_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:57:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/110/156679/refrigerators</link><title>Insulin and Hotel Refrigerators</title><description>...   ... I had just changed the pump’s reservoir before flying to Chicago, so I knew I had just about enough insulin for the three days I&amp;rsqu... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7052-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7052_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:58:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/145169/70870/conference</link><title>Anyone able to share a hotel room on this coming Sunday after BC Mets conference?</title><description>... Hi, I'm going to be attending the BC Mets conference this weekend at Dana-Farber in Boston. I have a grant for the first two nights, but I'm staying till Mon afternoon, and need to find a place to stay for Sunday night. If anyone is staying on and can share their hotel room, I'd be happy to share the cost. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7052-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7052_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 17:59:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/9993/167470/traveling-ice-hotel-diabetes</link><title>Traveling to the Ice Hotel with Diabetes</title><description>...   ... Like Kris, I’m an avid fan of winter sports. Although I live in Washington, DC, which doesn’t get a lot of snow, my cross country skis and snowshoes lay in-wait all winter for the moment I can jump in the car and make to a snowy trail, or when we have the unusual snow storm that blankets us with enough snow for snowshoeing. ...   ... This year, my winter escape was to Quebec, Canada. While most people head south for warmer weather, we headed north for the Winter Carnival and a stay at the Hotel De Glace , which is a hotel made entirely of i... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7052-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7052_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:00:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/5741/99363/california</link><title>Hotel California hallway</title><description>...   ... I am keeping the Christmas spirit going. I woke with "Oh Christmas tree, oh Christmas tree, how beautiful your branches." Maybe that's why I hear the choir director from my church, in my mind. Funny how stuff ties itself together...the Force is with me. ...   ... I made my list of things I was successful in. Margaret read it and said , it would be a good outline for a book. She said to write a little about each success. I friend also said to write about the failures it took to succeed. Both great suggestions. ...   ... I have too much time on my hands. I work a little on my memoir. I now have an ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7052-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7052_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:00:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/73654/41116/hotels</link><title>Airports, hotels and rental cars - oh my!</title><description>... I'm also dreading these trips because of the toll they will take on me and the unknown situations that could occur. I'm not going to go around announcing I have MS but what if I need to accompany someone to a meeting room two floors up and they lead me to the stairs? (That's a common one - and I usually struggle up, too meek to speak up for myself.) What if they want to take me on a tour of facilities (also common) and there's nowhere to sit down along the way? What if I just have a bad MS day while I'm traveling, meaning fatigue, brain fog and pain - and can't accomplish what I'm supposed to be doing at great company expense? ... There is so much more unpredictability these days,... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>