<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7053">nintendo 3ds hack</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:01:18" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7053-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7053_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:01:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/95808/53881/mii</link><title>Playing Nintendo Wii Games as Multiple Sclerosis Therapy</title><description>... Right after Thanksgiving I wrote a piece titled " Wheeeee!!! " in which I stated that Mandy and I succumbed to Wii madness, purchased one of the video game consoles, and planned to delve into the world of Wii, Miis, and daily fitness tests. We guessed that perhaps, because of the physical nature of Wii gaming, playing Wii would actually prove beneficial to Mandy who, like so many others, suffers from Relapsing-Remitting MS . Now, after a month of playing, we believe that we were correct and that Wii is proving itself well worth the investment. At the risk of being a commercial for Nintendo, I'm going to plow ahead and talk about our experience to date. When you buy Wii it comes with a Sports Games disc. There are five games on the disc from which to choose: Tennis, Bowling, Boxing, Golf, and Baseball. Each game requires a level of physical and mental control over one's limbs. Mandy started slowly and, believe it or not, tired easily after playing just a few of the different games. I could... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7053-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7053_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:02:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/659371/74167/nintendo</link><title>Nintendo Wii approved by AMA??</title><description>...   ... Thank you, ... ag2020 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7053-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7053_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:03:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/908986/129217</link><title>i have apacemaker.will using wii games or nintendo games affect me if so , what will happen to me</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7053-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7053_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:03:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/cold-flu/c/question/180993/51741</link><title>Dry, hacking, bronchial cough, shortness of breath, sneezing, and runny nose. What Do I have?</title><description>...   ... Rose M. Flynn ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7053-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7053_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:04:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/question/730543/63604</link><title>dry hacking cough at night</title><description>... Hi I am 26 yrs old Female Last week I had developed sore throat, and slight cough which felt congested so I treated with Mucinex, no more congested feeling but have dry hacking cough which come back here and there but persistent when I try to go to sleep. I also noticed I breath loud than usual. No history of smoking or asthma or anything. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7053-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7053_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:05:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/question/83134/30357</link><title>my friend told me stories about jealous ex-boyfriend hacking up her cellphone, spying, etc. What is</title><description>... My friend told me stories about jealous ex-boyfriend hacking up her cellphone, spying, etc. What is this symptoms? I got a little confused cause when she call me the other day, I couldn't hear anything in my cellphone after pressing Answer button, but she told me that she could hear my voice, and that the situation was created by her ex-boyfriend. Is this early sign of schizophrenia? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7053-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7053_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:05:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/110/142521/hacking-diabetes</link><title>Hacking Our Diabetes Devices</title><description>...   ... A subsequent flurry of news articles point out that the FDA doesn't have standards in place for wireless data transmission for medical devices, and acknowledged that any medical device with wireless communication components can fall victim to eavesdropping. The problem is that these devices transmitted data unencrypted and can accept commands wirelessly from unauthorized devices. ...   ... BTW, only pumps that accept data wirelessly from other devices would be affected. My present pump doesn't, but I've been looking at switching someday to another brand that does. And my D... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7053-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7053_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:06:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/cold-flu/c/question/393645/151358</link><title>i have adry hacking cough and arunny nose and sneeze alot,am i allergic to something?</title><description>... the cough is so dry i almost vomit when i can't cough any more ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7053-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7053_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:07:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/1440/14925/hard-hack</link><title>HARD HEARTED HANNAH CAN'T HACK IT!</title><description>... Last Tuesday night, having trouble getting to sleep due to chest discomfort, and having taken nitroglycerin twice in 15 minutes without relief, I recalled the cardiologist's words of concern the day before when he urged me to come in and let them do angioplasty - "I don't want you to get too comfortable with that chest pain." "If you use nitro twice without relief, call 911!" So I got up, got dressed, packed an overnight bag, and went out and hailed a cab at 2:30 am in the morning. I went to the emergency room at the VAMC, where I get my primary health care and checked in. They connected me to all the required monitors and at 8 am they admitted me to the hospital, transferring me to the ICU. At 4 pm I underwent an angioplasty - they inserted one stent in my Left Coronary Artery, which was about 50% occluded. The Right Coronary Artery is almost 100% blocked, and they decided to leave it alone for the time being, since there was a collateral artery establishe... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7053-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7053_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:07:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/question/682400/168453</link><title>Deep, hacking cough, canker sores, mucus, but difficult to cough up, no fever. Has been going on for almost two weeks. Need to see a doctor? If not, what are some remediates to get over quickly?</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>