<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7054">yarra valley sightseeing</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:08:36" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7054-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7054_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:08:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002882.html</link><title>Lily-of-the-valley overview</title><description>... Definition Lily of the valley is a flowering plant. Lily of the valley poisoning occurs when someone eats parts of this plant. This is for information only and not for use in the treatment or management of an actual poison exposure. If you have an exposure, you should call your local emergency number (such as 911) or the National Poison Control Center at 1-800-222-1222. Alternative Names Liljekonvall Poisonous Ingredient Convallarin Convallamarin Convallatoxin Note: This list may not include all poisonous ingredients. Where Found The flowers, fruit, and leaves of the lily of the valley plant are poisonous. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7054-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7054_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:09:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002882sym.html</link><title>Lily-of-the-valley symptoms</title><description>... Alternative Names Liljekonvall Symptoms Eyes, ears, nose, mouth, and throat ... Blurred vision Excessive urination at night Halos around objects (yellow, green, white) Gastrointestinal ... Diarrhea Loss of appetite Stomach pain Vomiting or nausea Heart and blood ... Irregular or slow heartbeat Nervous system ... Confusion Depression Disorientation Drowsiness Fainting Headache Lethargy Weakness Skin ... Rash Hives Note: Depression, loss of appetite, and halos are usually only seen in chronic overdose cases. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7054-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7054_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:09:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002882trt.html</link><title>Lily-of-the-valley treatment</title><description>... Alternative Names Liljekonvall Home Treatment Seek immediate medical help. Do NOT make a person throw up unless told to do so by poison control or a health care professional. Before Calling Emergency Determine the following information: Patient's age, weight, and condition Name and part of the plant swallowed, if known Time it was swallowed Amount swallowed Poison Control, or a local emergency number The National Poison Control Center (1-800-222-1222) can be called from anywhere in the United States. This national hotline number will let you talk to experts in poisoning. They will give you further instructions. This is a free and confidential service. All local poison control centers in the United States use this national number. You should call if you have any questions about poisoning or poison prevention. It does NOT need to be an emergency. You can call for any reason, 24 hours a day, 7 days a week. See: Poison control center - emergency number What to expect at the emergency room The health ca... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7054-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7054_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:10:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/670252/86288</link><title>I am looking for a doctor that specializes in adult adhd in Fountain Valley, California.</title><description>... I am looking for a doctor that specializes in adult adhd in Fountain Valley, California.  Does anyone have any recomnedations&gt; ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7054-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7054_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:11:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/question/546424/117051</link><title>how do i find support groups in the san fernando valley california area</title><description>... I am just going thru a really hard time with my bi polar and am about to lose someone who I really care about.  Can you help me find some meetings in the area of san fernando valley california i need some help. ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7054-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7054_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:11:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/34002/36823/valley-girl</link><title>Valley Girl</title><description>... I have Andre Bocelli crooning in my ear.  My ear buds are connected to my ipod;  they are secured tightly and I am filled with the sound. I am heating up the laptop.  Today as always, the music fills where no thought can go for I have battled another spell.  This spell offered to me no magical charm, or desired arousal. It was not a walk in the park, it was void of any enchanted forest, it promised I will struggle to sustain.  But yes, I remember the connotation of my title.  Valley Girls are fashionable and affluent, they are teenage girls living in the San Fernando Valley in California.  I do not live in California and affluent, I am not.  I am a Midwesterner.  I am a middle age woman with a husband and a family, yet I am a valley girl just the same.  For valley in my world is reminiscent of days cluttered with old thoughts of unrest.  My hopeless condition can only worsen; I am four months off and on and off a medication that I... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7054-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7054_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:12:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/368767/119925/plethora</link><title>Peaks, Valleys and Villages – The Plethora</title><description>...   ... Travel in the darkness ... Travel in the sun ... Travel in the light of being ... But, travel. ...   ... I love people. Having fibromyalgia, chronic fatigue syndrome and myofascial pain from unrelenting trigger points in my muscles doesn't change this fact of my life. ...   ... There are valleys, peaks and villages that make getting inside me intriguing. But mostly, it's about growing. Focusing only on setbacks and triumphs can stagnate who I am, like a river with no flow. ...   ... I see the valley as the peep hole that sometimes describes my life; I understand that though the hole is small, the vision is vast. It is a comforting warranty for better times; it is where I sometimes reside until I can identify the lessons. If I embrace that a valley is where animals come to escape the bitter cold of the peaks, where life thrives through a cycle, if I let it be my gathering place and stand still, I will feel the energy rise up through my feet. Then I will I kiss my passion, embrace my... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7054-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7054_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:12:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/326098/125151/journey</link><title>Valley of Darkness</title><description>...   ... The darkness takes over the body to crush life until the last breathe is taken. Even though darkness is trying to destroy what I have, my body stays strong to fight until the end. ...   ... There is a long road for me to travel upon to get to the room of light. There are many trials for me to go through, for my soul to grow and carry on. ...   ... NO matter how long it takes, I will conquer all. NO darkness will take over for there will always be a light in my soul. I will be the one to stand up and shout that I have won the fight. ...   ... I have conquered the pain and depression that has hung over my life. I have pushed onward to be with family and friends. I want to live as long as God shall grant me. ...   ... Death will have to wait on me a while longer, for I carry the torch and it will burn until God takes me home. ...   ... Written By Nancy Latshaw January 2009 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7054-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7054_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:13:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002882prv.html</link><title>Lily of the valley prevention</title><description>... Alternative Names Liljekonvall References Graeme K. Toxic plant ingestions. In: Auerbach PS, ed. Wilderness Medicine . 5th ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Mosby Elsevier; 2007:chap 58. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7054-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7054_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:14:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/5068/10513/peaks-matter</link><title>Do Peaks and Valleys Matter?</title><description>... ... ... One of the most common questions asked by people with diabetes is this: “What are nondiabetic blood glucose (BG) levels?” I discussed that in my recent blog “ Normal Blood Glucose ,” which you can read on this site. But just in case you don’t want to slog through that verbiage, the most important graph in that online lecture is here. ... ...   ... Another question that comes up over and over again is this: “Is it better for me to eat a food that causes a high peak for a very short time or a food that causes a small peak for a longer time?” ...   ... Different people give different answers to that question. Some argue that the only thing that matters is the A1c, so if the area under two curves — one very high but coming down rapidly and the other one lower but lasting a long time —was the same, it wouldn’t matter. ... ...   ... However, a fascinating talk given last fall by endocrinologist Irl Hirsch suggests that there’s more to consider than just the average BG level. As he says... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>