<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7057">web of science</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:23:53" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7057-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7057_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:23:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/872030</link><title>“THE SCIENCE OF POSTURE: WHY SITTING UP STRAIGHT MAKES YOU HAPPIER AND MORE PRODUCTIVE”</title><description>...   ... http://www.fastcompany.com/3021985/work-smart/the-science-of-posture-why-sitting-up-straight-makes-you-happier-and-more-product ...   ... “The way we stand, sit, and walk actually has more long-reaching implications on our mood and happiness than we thought.” ...   ... “Plus, the study used saliva samples to prove that expansive postures actually altered the participants’ hormone levels--decreasing cortisol (C) and increasing testosterone (T):” ...   ... “When we alter our posture and body language, it subconsciously influences our thinking and decision-making.” ...   ... For martial arts students, posture is essential for understanding physical balance, rooting one’s weight into the ground and being able to counter the opposing forces needed to generate power with attacks. ...   ... Posture ties in with body alignment.  Similar to architecture, the body has strengths and weaknesses in certain postures and positions.  From ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7057-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7057_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:24:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/1950/103358/promising-disorder</link><title>'Emotion Ring' Web Trials Look Promising for Panic Disorder</title><description>...   ... There has been an increase in the number of disorders such as panic disorder. The causes may be varied but seem to include our 24 society, increased expectations, the pace of life generally and the digital age in which we live. Whilst the digital age may be partly to blame it may also provide some part of the solution to the problem in the form of online treatments. ...   ... Online therapy in the form of counseling and chat has been around for some time and appears, from what evidence is available, to be reasonably successful. Re... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7057-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7057_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:25:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/38/1741/trials</link><title>Clinical Trial Web Resources for Patients with Rheumatoid Arthritis</title><description>... ... The following is a list of Web sites that maintain information on clinical trials for people with rheumatoid arthritis and rheumatic diseases. ... ... The CenterWatch Clinical Trials Listing Service site contains a comprehensive l... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7057-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7057_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:25:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/c/727598/107096/suggestions</link><title>Time's Issue on "The Science of Living Longer" Has Suggestions to Take to Heart</title><description>... Reaching perimenopause has provided me with some real fodder to think about what I want for the next half of my life. It’s been a time of reflection of where I’ve been, where I am now, and where I want to go. It also has been a time to really acknowledge the limits (especially time) that each of us has in our life and also determining how to push the boundaries to have the fullest and longest life possible. ... Therefore, I found Time ’s special section on “The Science of Living Longer” a good check-up on what the latest research is and what I can do to be proactive as I enter this new phase in life. Here are some of the take-aways from Alice Park’s article, “How to Live 100 Years” : -    The majority of centenarians are mentally alert and relatively free of disability. They also remain active members of their community. -    Genes are an important component of aging; however, they aren’t necessarily the ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7057-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7057_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:26:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/27167/learning-science</link><title>Learning the Latest on Brain Science</title><description>... horizontal in the dark for the past 4 hours, failing miserably to close the ... deal with the gods of sleep.  Two hours ... between 10 and midnight - that was it. Then my racing mind took over. I'm in DC ... at the APA annual meeting, and I'm obviously way overstimulated. ...   ... I have no choice but to turn on the light now and get a few ... things done, but I'm almost certain I will be crashing at my hotel in the ... afternoon. ...   ... I started out the morning listening to Helen Mayberg of Emory ... University talk about deep brain stimulation for depression. This is an ... experimental surgical procedure involving an implant into "Brodman area 25," ... which has numerous connections to various limbic and cortical areas identified ... with depression. In depressed patients, these circuits are over-active. The ... implant works to disrupt the signaling in these circuits. ...   ... Early findings are extremely encouraging. ...   ... I also listened to one of the pioneer... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7057-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7057_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:27:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/367993/98587/science</link><title>Simple Science The Truth About Carbohydrates</title><description>...   ... Carbohydrate (definition) : neutral compounds of carbon, hydrogen and oxygen (such as sugars, starches and celluloses) which make a large portion of animal foods (NASM, 2008). ...   ... Carbohydrates (function) : the chief form of energy for all body functions and muscular exertion.  They also help to regulate digestion and utilization of protein and fat (NASM, 2008). ...   ... The first thing I need to say about Carb... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7057-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7057_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:28:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/951127/91480/people-demanding</link><title>Help people with diabetes by demanding Truth in Science!</title><description>... All you have to do is take 1 minute to sign the Nutrition &amp; Metabolism Society's petition. ... Click here to view . ... Thank you in advance - ... The Metabolism Society is a 501(c)3 nonprofit health organization providing research, information and education in the application of fundamental science to nutrition. The Society is particularly dedicated to the incorporation of biochemical metabolism to problems of obesity, diabetes and cardiovascular disease. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7057-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7057_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:28:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/67813/154088/healthcentral</link><title>The Science of Gossip: A HealthCentral Explainer</title><description>... But, is all gossip necessarily bad? ...   ... A study out of the University of California-Berkeley called “The Virtues of Gossip” published in the May issue of the Journal of Personality and Social Psychology found that gossip can play the role of protecting others from being exploited by passing on information about bad behavior to warn others. They call this “pro-social gossip.” ...   ... Gossip didn’t always have a bad rap ... ... Interestingly enough, the Old English origin of the word “gossip” was “ godsibb ,” meaning “god-sibling” or, what we call today a godparent. It was really used to express a close relationship or friendship. In the 16th century, the meaning took a turn for the worse, and was ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7057-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7057_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:29:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/59238/131875/healthy-science</link><title>14 Healthy Foods with Science Behind Them</title><description>...   ... Grains ... Barley is a grain and according to the IFT there are currently 11 studies to support increased consumption of barley products.  The health benefits associated with eating barley include lowering total cholesterol and LDL, or the bad cholesterol.  Remember that when consuming grains, the less processed the grains, the better. ...   ... Quinoa and buckwheat are two unique whole grains, and according to the IFT review, consumption of seeds and sprouts from these two whole grain choices means you are getting the benefit of polyphenols, compounds associated with health benefits.  If you need to eat "gl... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7057-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7057_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:30:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/athlete-project-injuries-1949</link><title>I am a high school athlete doing a science project on ACL injuries in girls and women.</title><description>... I am a high school athlete doing a science project on ACL injuries in girls and women. So far I've found that females are at greater risk for ACL injury than males. Are they also\rmore likely to reinjure themselves later? Teasing this kind of information out of the literature can be difficult. Other variables must also be considered such as age and level of activity. Treatment of the torn ACL has also changed over the last 20 years, affecting the results for both men and women. In general, more ACL tears are repaired surgically early on. Early ACL repair allows young patients (especially athletes) to return to full activities. Several studies have been done looking at the rate of reinjury in two groups of patients: those who have an ACL repair and those who don't. The consensus at this time is that gender isn't a factor in reinjury. It looks like age is more of a predictive factor. The younger, active patients who don't have ACL repair reinjure the knee later. Meniscus and joint cartilage... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>