<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7059">doctor Amsterdam</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:37:42" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7059-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7059_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:37:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/483906/50201</link><title>My LDR BF says he did not have sex for 2 years if not with me. that is once a year. is this possible</title><description>... HE is 23 and i am 20, he says he loves me and sex does not really matter plus he says I was his first.  he lives in amsterdam and we can only see each other once a year, and then we dont have much time for sex so its like 1 or 2 times. everybody is laughing at me because of this relationship and i get really suspicios of him we had a lot of fights cause i think he is sleeping with woman he knows or his college or drom friends. I wonder is he for real is this possilbe, and is it healthy how long can this go on? or should i set him free? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7059-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7059_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:38:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/question/941647/103967</link><title>Got names of EXPERTS you trust in "white matter brain disease" other than Lucchinetti at MAYO?</title><description>... I am looking for names MD's who are experts in the area of "white matter brain disease" and "autoimmune diseases of the brain" who we may not have yet seen. Our 26 year old son has been looking for answers for nine years. He has been to MAYO twice, seen by Claudia Lucchinetti, MD. His case has been reviewed by experts at the Cleveland Clinic. He has been examined by Fredrick Munchauser (sp?), MD from SUNY, Bruce Hughes, MD at Univ. of Iowa. He is under the care of Rena Zabad, MD at this time and before that, Pierre Fayad, MD, both at Univ. of Nebraska Med. Center in Omaha. His MRI's have also been reviewed by a top specialist in Amsterdam and a pediatric neuro specialist in Canada. None of these experts have ever seen his presentation. He has had complete work-ups at MAYO. He has had 8 spinal taps and every test known to mankind, searching for infectious diseases and other rare possibilities to explain what he has. He has had two brain biopsies, the one done at MAYO bled, crippling hi... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7059-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7059_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:38:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/860247/71616/11-independent</link><title>NYC event, June 11; Remaining Independent- Navigating Health Care for Our Loved Ones</title><description>... ... When: Thursday, June 11 th , 7 PM –9PM ...   ... Title: Remaining Independent: Navigating Health Care for Our Loved Ones and Ourselves ...   ... Sponsored by: Jewish Community Center in Manhattan and Partners in Care ...   ... Start planning now for how you want to live as you or your loved one get older, before “What if….” becomes “Now what?” ...   ... Practical tools and tips to help you physically, emotionally and financially take control of life while dealing with the challenges of growing old. The Jewish Community Center of Manhattan and Partners in Care, the largest licensed home care agency in NYC, will present a panel of experts to discuss methods to help manage the serious challenges that come along with taking care of a loved one suffering from a chronic disease or how you can find the resources you will need.  ...   ... Th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7059-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7059_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:39:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/migraineurs-564687-5.html</link><title>Famous Migraineurs: Anne Frank</title><description>...  Anne Frank's contribution to the history of the Holocaust is well known; but did you also know she may have suffered from Migraines ? Due to the various symptoms she describes in her dairies , Migraine researchers believe that Anne probably had Migraines and tension-type headaches . Anne was born on June 12, 1929, to parents Otto and Edith Frank. Anne and Margot, her older sister, lived in Frankfurt, Germany until Anne was five-years-old.   Otto, being in the banking business, had business connections in Amsterdam. This enabled him to escape there just weeks before the Nazi's began their rise to power in 1933. He went to Amsterdam, leaving behind his wife and two daughters with their grandparents in Aachen, Germany. The Franks were reunited in February, 1934, with Anne being the last family member to arrive in Amsterdam. It wasn't until 1942 that German and Dutch authorities began to concentrate on the Jewish people throughout the Netherlands, tracking ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7059-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7059_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:39:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/003105prv.html</link><title>Facial swelling prevention</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Puffy face; Swelling of the face; Moon face; Facial edema ... ... ... References ... ... Habif TP. Urticaria and angioedema. In: Habif TP. Clinical Dermatology . 5th ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Saunders Elsevier; 2009:chap 6. ... Amsterdam JT. Oral medicine. In: Marx JA, Hockberger RS, Walls RM, et al, eds. Rosens Emergency Medicine: Concepts and Clinical Practice . 7th ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Mosby Elsevier; 2009:chap 68. ... Sharma R, Brunette DD. Ophthalmology. In: Marx JA, Hockberger RS, Walls RM, et al, eds. Rosens Emergency Medicine: Concepts and Clinical Practice . 7th ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Mosby Elsevier; 2009:chap 69. ... Pfaff JA, Moore GP. Otolaryngology. In: Marx JA, Hockberger RS, Walls RM, et al, eds. Rosens Emergency Medicine: Concepts and Clinical Practice . 7th ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Mosby Elsevier; 2009:chap 70. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7059-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7059_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:40:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/63356/149616/shows-bloodsugar</link><title>Study Shows Checking Bloodsugar Rather Pointless for Non-Insulin Dependent Type 2 Diabetics</title><description>... As of 2011, my insurance covers only 4 test strips a day. For a Type 1 diabetic such as myself, this is a ridiculously low number. Like many insulin-dependent diabetics, frequent blood glucose monitoring is essential to my well-being and empowers me to make informed choices that greatly impact not only my day, but my life. I test when ... Like so many of you, my bloodsugar level is always on my mind, whether in the fore or background. I never escape it. I wake up, I test post-prandial numbers at each meal, and often times pre-meal. If I exercise or experience unexplained highs or lows, I test to monitor the situation. If I’m driving, I test before driving to make sure I’m okay. I test before bed, and I test in the middle of night (if I’m with it enough to remember). Don’t get me started on pre-menstrual fluctuations and the need to test even more frequently during this time. So why, why, would an insurance company limit my test strips to four a day, even when my d... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7059-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7059_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:40:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/78/3448/gene-rule-chemo</link><title>The F.D.A. approves MammaPrint® to Detect Chance of Breast Cancer Recurrence</title><description>... An important first step has been taken in possibly cutting down the number of women who have to undergo chemotherapy for breast cancer. The United States Food and Drug Administration Tuesday gave formal approval to MammaPrint®, a product of the Amsterdam-based Agendia company, a recognized world leader in gene analysis diagnostics. MammaPrint analyzes the activity level of 70 different genes found in fresh tumor tissue removed from women experiencing early stage (1 or 2), lymph node-negative breast cancer. That analysis leads to a numerical ranking that assigns women to one of two groups: high risk for recurrence or low risk. Women in the high-risk group have twice the chance of breast cancer recurrence within 10 years as women in the low-risk group. Chemotherapy Prescribed Twice as often as Needed So, if the test says a woman is low-risk, what does that mean? Much less reason for an often debilitating series of injections of powerful chemotherapy drugs. While chemo is commonly recomme... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7059-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7059_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:41:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/89/83429/wildebeests-ve</link><title>Vanity, Arthritis and Wildebeests: I've Become A "Senior Citizen."</title><description>... I'm a well-educated and fairly intelligent person, but once in awhile, an awareness or a thought suddenly hits me that makes me feel very dense (maybe I've spent too much time in the African Bush?). Yesterday, I was running those endless errands, working on my pre-African departure checklist, when suddenly I decided I'd better grab a quick lunch.  I stopped at a local fast food place, something I seldom do, and placed my order at the counter. The girl told me my bill, but then I noticed she was staring carefully at me. She suddenly re-figured my bill and gave me the new lower price.  I love to save money, but asked why she did that and she mumbled something.  I joked "Oh, is it because I'm elderly?" She quickly collected my money and rushed away!  I realize that I have been getting older all of the time, but suddenly (or so it seems), I'm no longer asked if I qualify for the Senior discount (I even saved over $100 on a new stove at Sears this week due to my "wrink... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7059-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7059_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:42:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/157972/loneliness-stroke</link><title>Loneliness May Increase Dementia Risk, Heart Attacks and Stroke</title><description>...   ... The study, headed by Tjalling Jan Holwerda of the VU University Medical Center in Amsterdam, found that participants who reported feeling lonely , no matter how many friends and family surrounded them, were more likely to experience dementia than those who didn’t feel lonely. The team focused on approximately 2,200 older adults living in Amsterdam, ages 65 to 86. None of the participants exhibited signs of dementia and none of them lived in facilities such as nursing homes. The researchers visited the elders two times over the course of three years. About half of them lived alone, with 20 percent reporting feelings of loneliness, even if they were married or lived with family. ...   ... The researchers stress, that solid conclusions can’t be determined at this time because cognitive problems can ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7059-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7059_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:43:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/53/2012/ra</link><title>Research Update: Caffeine, Marijuana and Rheumatoid Arthritis</title><description>... I was in Berkeley, California a couple of weeks ago, and was struck by the prevalence of Starbuck’s coffee and marijuana among the fine citizens of that liberal city. And as luck would have it, there have recently been research findings presented on the topics of caffeine and marijuana and their effects upon patients with rheumatoid arthritis. There have always been concerns that caffeine, found in tea, coffee, colas and chocolate might adversely impact the efficacy of methotrexate. Caffeine is a methylxanthine, which reverses the positive benefits of methotrexate at the cellular level. So the researchers, writing in the Journal of Rheumatology earlier this year, determined the caffeine intake of rheumatoid arthritis patients and assessed its influence on response to methotrexate. The average daily caffeine intake was equivalent to that found in almost two cups of coffee each day; the researchers studied patients who had low, moderate,and high intake of caffeine. The researchers fo... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>