<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7060">jobs IBCN</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:43:34" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7060-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7060_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:43:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/question/199463/153449</link><title>should i go for job? mama ask me to leave my study and go for job 'cause i failed 4 time in 12th. I want to make my study but people and family say that I should go for job,what i have to do?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7060-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7060_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:44:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/693098/118070</link><title>I lost my job due to forgetfullness on the job. Could the forgetfullness have been caused by the Topamax? I take 100 mg. twice a day.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7060-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7060_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:44:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/63137/126167</link><title>My son left job where he was #1 in sales now @ new job,he is not having as much success. He also has no motivation. What can I tell him Help me help him. He gets depressed very easily. Thanks, Robbi</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7060-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7060_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:45:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/334530/132524</link><title>My son is 24, suffers from depression. Heleft his job in Flagstaff to move closer to Mesa. He has no job, and gets anxiety if he even thinks about leaving the house. He has 2 lil boys. What can he do?</title><description>... He has tried several medications, Prozac seemed to help the most, but now he has no insurance, and no resources. He can't leave his little boys as home, or with a sitter, he has no money. I don't know how to help him. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7060-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7060_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:46:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/726000/121262</link><title>my wife is stressed at her job and whenever you advice her she thinks anything is going to happen to her job though without any wrong doing what advice can you give?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7060-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7060_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:47:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/52325/156615/31-jobs-asthmatics</link><title>31 Jobs Asthmatics Should Not Take</title><description>...   ... So, that in mind, each of the following jobs has the potential to expose you to asthma triggers, and you may wish to consider choosing another profession. ... ... Lumberjack (outdoor allergens, sawdust) ... Construction (dust) ... Building destruction/ demolition (dust) ... Roadwork (dust) ... Electrician (dust) ... Factory work/ manufacturing (fumes, dust, chemicals) ... Welding (fumes) ... Auto mechanic/ auto body repair (fumes, chemicals) ... Carpentry (wood dust, house dust) ... Farmer (outdoor and animal allergies) ... Winter athletics (cold air triggers asthma, and may even cause it) ... Cigarette tester (bad for lungs) ... Landscaping/ lawn care (outdoor allergens) ... Door to door salesperson (house pets, wood smoke, cigarette smoke, house dust, etc.) ... Carpet cleaning (dust) ... Janitor (dust) ... Housekeeping (house allergens) ... Mountai... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7060-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7060_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:47:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabeteens/c/22669/20452/worst-jobs</link><title>Worst Jobs for Diabetics</title><description>... Just for fun... I thought I would compile this list.   You know how on aol and other sites they occasionally have random features like "Top 10 worst foods" or "Top 5 highest paying jobs," etc., etc.?   There are some jobs that you actually are not allowed to do if you have diabetes, because of physical demands -- one of those jobs is being an air force pilot. But I was thinking about what would just plain suck, or be really annoying, if you had diabetes.   Here is what i came up with:   1. Professional athlete - we all know why I have this opinion :) Yea, yea it would be fun to be a great sports star, but seriously, having diabetes just makes it sooo complicated... and there are honestly very few successful athletes that I know of with Type 1. There is that olympic skier Kris Freeman, swimmer Gary Hall, and a football player or two, plus others that some of you know. I have to give credit to these guys!   2. Pastry Chef - How on earth coul... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7060-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7060_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:48:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/141334/occupations</link><title>Happy Jobs: Which Occupations Can Boost Your Mood?</title><description>...   ... The Least Stressful Occupations ...   ... Everyone experiences some stress on the job . But excessive stress can le... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7060-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7060_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:49:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/18/108555/job-depressed</link><title>Looking for a Job When You Are Depressed</title><description>...   ... Remember the first rule of a job search: you already have a job. That job is searching for your new job. The energy, skill and creativity you bring to this job every day while you search for your new job will determine both your monetary and psychic income for years to come. You may be depressed right now, but remember that it's your ultimate objective to put depression be... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7060-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7060_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:49:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/100/35219/job-critical</link><title>Finding a Job - Critical Answers</title><description>... The first step in finding and keeping a good job involves a little soul searching.  The best way to do this is to ask and answer a series of questions.  These questions may seem remarkably simple, almost silly.  But don't be mislead.  They're of the utmost importance. ...   ... Before we begin with the questions, however, let's discuss the nature of the answers you must give.  There are at least three reasons why the questions may be difficult to answer: ...   ... 1)  The answers you give must be your answers and your answers alone . . . ...   ... You must tease out and set aside the opinions and expectations of others.  This does not mean that you shouldn't seek the advice of others.  In fact, the advice of others can be very helpful, especially when you start for the first time to measure your functionality in absolute terms.  But, you must remember that their advice represents their opinions.  Their opinions may influence your thinkin... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>