<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7061">startup advisors chicago</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:50:13" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7061-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7061_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:50:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/78118/17505/pain-buy</link><title>Beware of Goji scams and people praying on pain victims to buy the product and startup a "business"</title><description>... Recently I read the posts and after 5 years of dealing with a traumatic spine injury, I decided to look here from support. Unfortunately, I must have reached out to the wrong person, because they were try to sell me some $50 drink and oh yeah, "startup a business".  Sounded like a scam to me. If anyone tries to push off this Goji drink and buy in to it and get rich quick deal, you might want to click on this link and watch the video about that product.  http://www.cbc.ca/marketplace/2007/01/goji.html   Please be careful of people who are on such sites for the wrong reasons. For my first experience, hoping to find someone who could actually understand how I feel for once, I found it to be a negative experience and not what I had hoped for. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7061-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7061_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:50:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/204/50566/military-migraine</link><title>MAGNUM Brings On Board Another Military Migraine Advisor</title><description>... WASHINGTON, DC; August 31th, 2008 - MAGNUM issued our Defending the Military Migraineur (DMM) Report to key members of the United States Senate Arms Committee after spending years trying to assist active duty military personnel and veterans disabled by Migraine disease. Terri Burchfield, our Legislative Director, Susan Denny our Information Services Director, and Michael John Coleman our Executive Director drove to Capitol Hill right after 911. They had to stop the car every other block to be checked by police, some officers armed with machine guns, on their way to the first meeting with then Senate Arms Chairman Senator John Warner (R-VA). ... "I have lived in the Washington, DC area my whole life and it was the first time I recall seeing the police carrying submachine guns on Capitol Hill. It looked like something out of a bad movie, at that point more than any airport screening did the terrorist reach out and touch your soul. Here we are carrying in our suitcase MAGNUM's DMM Migrai... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7061-03"><link>http://www.healthcentral.com/genital-herpes/c/321401/166284/chicago-support</link><title>Herpes dating chicago and herpes support groups in chicago</title><description>...   ... the information is very comprehensive. Provides us the dating sites, the support groups, the std clinics... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7061-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7061_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:51:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/140190/migraine-education</link><title>Migraine and Headache Education Event in Chicago June 25</title><description>...   ... The National Headache Foundation (NHF) is hosting a regional conference at the Chicago Marriott Downtown from 12:30 p.m. to 5:00 p.m. Named Bridging the Gap Between Patient &amp; Clinician , the conference brings together those who cope with the disease and the healthcare professionals who make their lives better. ...   ... This conference is just in time for National Migraine Awareness Month, and the keynote speaker will be Serene Branson, the CBS reporter whose on-air Migraine with severe aphasia fueled speculation that she might have had a stroke. (See my interview with Ms. Branson in Serene Branson on Migraines and Awareness Month .) ...   ... The schedule for the afternoon is: ... ... 12:30PM - 1:30PM ... Registration / Exhibits ...   ... 1:30PM – 1:40PM ... Robert Dalton, Executive Director – NHF ... Welcome and Introductions ... &amp;nbsp... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7061-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7061_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:52:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/974776/105948</link><title>looking to raise money for a local clinic which supplies diabetic equipment-Chicago area</title><description>...   ... Thank you, ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7061-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7061_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:53:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/10196/chicago-society</link><title>Greetings from Chicago - The American Headache Society Conference</title><description>... In order to continue learning about Migraine disease and headaches, Nancy and I are in Chicago to attend the American Headache Society Annual Scientific Meeting. We've been meeting with people today, and the main sessions begin tomorrow. We thought we'd start our reports to you with a bit of fun... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7061-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7061_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:54:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/204/10422/magnum-49th-annual</link><title>MAGNUM Attends 49th Annual Meeting of the American Headache Society In Chicago</title><description>... Follow what's new about Migraine in Chicago with HealthCentral &amp; MAGNUM Please keep track of what is new and exciting regarding Migraine disease and headache disorders at this years 49th Annual Meeting of the American Headache Society In Chicago.  Please visit our very own Teri Robert's reports from MyMigraineConnection every day from Wednesday June 7th through Sunday June 10th! Exciting news will also be breaking as MAGNUM is hand carrying an important Congressional letter concerned about the lack of government funding for Migraine &amp; headache research.... Continue reading on MigraineBlog! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7061-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7061_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:55:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/c/question/57326/33805</link><title>find a doctor heart specialist in chicago</title><description>... I NEED TO FIND A  DOCTOR TOP HEART SPECIALIST IN CHICAGO,IL ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7061-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7061_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:56:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/883600/130299</link><title>I am currently giong to school in Oregon right now, and have been diagnosed for 6 years with RA, I am being sent for graduate studies next year, and the Schools are in Northern Cali, or Chicago</title><description>... Living in Oregon, I have noticed that I get flares often. I am originally from Arizona, and when I am home, I feel better! But I am being sent to graduate school starting in August, and was wondering what people think. My choices are the Bay Area in California, or Chicago. I have never experienced extreme cold weather like in Chicago, and I am more familiar with humid conditions, like in the Bay Area...I guess I just want to see how other people have dealt with extreme cold and how it has affected their RA. Thanks. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7061-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7061_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:56:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/institute-rreplacement-2059</link><title>I saw a news report that the Rehab Institute of Chicago has a new program after knee\rreplacement.</title><description>... I saw a news report that the Rehab Institute of Chicago has a new program after knee\rreplacement. They are using a battery-powered monitoring device to keep tabs on the joint motion. I live in the Chicago area and need a knee replacement. Should I get one of these\rfor myself? A small study was done at the Rehab Institute of Chicago (RIC) using an electric goniometer after total knee replacement (TKA). A goniometer is used to measure joint motion. Most often a physical therapist uses a hand-held goniometer to measure the jointmotion manually. The electric unit was meant to help patients with problems that could delay their recovery. Some had severe rheumatoid arthritis. Others had social or psychologic problems slowing them down. The device is still under investigation and not on the market forgeneral use yet. You may be a good candidate for future studies. To contact RIC call 1-800-354-REHAB (1-312-238-1000) or visit their website on-line at http://www.ric.org . Reference: Todd A. Kuiken,... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>