<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7062">marquette university news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:57:31" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7062-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7062_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:57:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/community-3100-143.html</link><title>Meet Dr. Borigini</title><description>... (now Drexel University) School of Medicine in 1988 and completed a ... residency in Internal Medicine at the University of California, ... Irvine, in 1991. Following that, he spent two years at UCLA, ... completing his rheumatology fellowship in 1993. Between 1993 and ... 1995, he was full-time faculty at UCLA, assisting in the teaching ... of students and housestaff. Dr. Borigini was involved in studying ... novel rheumatoid arthritis treatments and wrote several papers and ... book chapters on that subject. ... After leaving UCLA, he took a position at the VA Medical Center, ... Long Beach, again assisting in the teaching of students and ... housestaff as an Assistant Clinical Professor of Medicine at the ... University of California, Irvine. ... Dr. Borigini has maintained academic ties to the University of ... California (now as an Associate Professor), even after entering ... into private group practice in 1997 as a consulting rheumatologist. ... For the last nine years, he has ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7062-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7062_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:58:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/98860/boston-partnership</link><title>NFL-Boston University Partnership May Be A Great Christmas Present for Dementia</title><description>... Now for a piece of good news this Christmas:   as part of a partnership, the National Football League (NFL) will encourage current and former NFL players to agree to donate their brains to the Boston University Center for the Study of Traumatic Encephalopathy. This Christmas present – the formation of this partnership – is somewhat amazing since the Boston University researchers have consistently been critical on the NFL’s stance concerning player’s concussions. The lead paragraph of a story by New York Times reporter Alan Schwarz puts this announcement into perspective: “After weeks of transforming its approach to concussions and its research into their long-term effects among players, the N.F.L. not only announced suddenly that it would support research by its most vocal critics but also conceded publicly for the first time that concussions can have lasting consequences.” ...             ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7062-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7062_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:58:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/845633/81724</link><title>University Presentation about Diabetes Conversation amps</title><description>... good day. I am from Italy, I'm preparing a presentation about the Diabetes conversations map, for the University.Unlucky in Italy there isn't yet, so please can you send to my email address all news, dates, statistic, studies, phone numbers.....you can? I thank you everybody will help me with my University presentation, and to introduce convarsation map in Italy too. Arianna Capuzzo - email: cinzia.rovida@live.it   - ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7062-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7062_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:59:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/12995/35030/international</link><title>Washington University School of Medicine to lead new international Alzheimer's disease research netw</title><description>...   ... I have met many people suffering from an early stage of dementia in the last several years. Frequently, the problem is going undiagnosed.  Just as often, the children don't know what to do and what actions to take. I believe this is very common. Let's face it, the average person has no idea about what to do. It is common to get overwhelmed and "scared" when Alzheimer's strikes. ...   ... ...   ...   ... "For treatments now in development to be optimally beneficial for patients, we have to find ways of diagnosing Alzheimer's disease as early as possible," says DIAN principal investigator John C. Morris, M.D., the Harvey A. and Dorismae Hacker Friedman Distinguished Professor of Neurology and director of the ADRC.... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7062-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7062_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 18:59:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/120/158973/schizophrenia</link><title>Schizophrenia News: February 2013</title><description>...   ... The experts studied the members of a family with a high rate of mental illness.  An abnormal mutation of NPAS3 was found in a number of the family members.  ... NPAS3 regulates and makes sure healthy neurons are consistently developed. ...   ... The researchers wanted to determine if this observed mutation had any effect on the way NPAS3 should normally function so they grew neurons with mutated and normal versions of the gene in a dish to analyze any significant differences. ...   ... The normal version had long extensions to make good neuronal connections with other cells.  The mutated version had much shorter extensions. ...   ... (Joseph Nordqvist. (2013, January 24... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7062-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7062_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:01:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/1489/support-newsgroup</link><title>News Groups: A Source for Online Diabetes News, Research</title><description>... ... These newsgroups have been around for a lot longer than mailing lists and aren’t technically a part of the Internet at all. While anyone with an Internet account can read these newsgroups, they are the main part of the Usenet. ... ... Dr. Steve Bellovin , now a computer science professor at Columbia University, wrote the first version of software to distribute news within the Unix community in 1979 when he was a graduate student at the University of North Carolina. He worked with two Duke University graduate students, Jim Ellis, who died in 2001, and Tom Truscott, who hooked comp... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7062-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7062_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:01:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/3387/18531/good-news-allergy</link><title>Hookworms... Good News/Bad News for Allergy Sufferers</title><description>... There's a promising new allergy treatment on the horizon, but it's a bit yucky, to be perfectly frank (though not exactly scientific!). It seems that gutworms, or more specifically, hookworms, which are intestinal parasites, may offer protection from allergies, asthma, and other immune system disorders, including diabetes and MS.   I know what you're thinking, I've got to be kidding, right? Well, the truth is, researchers have been looking at why data gathered over the past 30 years shows that people infected with tropical hookworms hardly ever have allergies or asthma.   One theory is that hookworms may cause their host's immune system to be less active. Since overactive immune systems are at play in people with asthma and allergies, this possibility could be significant.   Scientists at the University of Nottingham in the UK are studying whether hookworms offer any kind of protection against immune system disorders. That's the possible good new... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7062-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7062_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:02:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/19065/163535/opinion-reporting</link><title>Opinion: Reporting on the "Not So Much News" News</title><description>... Among various medically-related news sources, I do have a few favorites.  Some of these outfits have experienced medical reporters on staff who are sent to cover big events such as the ECTRIMS conference.  I tend to read these articles first. ... But earlier this week, I was disappointed to read a “news story” - presented by an author whose name I had come to recognize and published on a respected website - which was anything but enlightening.  The reporter seemed to give us the redacted version of a supposedly top secret, classified story in “Striking a Ne... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7062-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7062_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:02:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/15478/78995/health-government</link><title>Please Help Stop Universal Health Care - A Case Against Government Run Universal Health Care</title><description>... The Obama Administration claims that Universal Health Care would provide for those that do not have health care now.  But the facts are that not a single group, class, or economic bracket in the United States of America, including illegal immigrants, can claim that this right has been denied them. The poor in America are already serviced remarkably (though inefficiently) by massive government programs like Medicare and Medicaid. ... Emergency rooms in both public and private hospitals will attend to anyone in urgent need. Most of the  people who do not have health insurance are middle class Americans who have opted out, on their own accord , of purchasing it because of other financial priorities. Is this ideal? No, it's not . But we do not live in an ideal world and the freedom to establish our own financial priorities, as good or bad as they may be, is also a right that must be protected.  In addition, the Universal Healthcare will be forced upon every American citizen - th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7062-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7062_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:03:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/genital-herpes/c/65036/52559/hiv-news</link><title>New HIV News</title><description>...   ... New research shows that the HIV virus can indeed penetrate healthy genital tissue and gain access to its target - immune cells .  The mechanism seems to be the natural shedding that takes place in the vaginal tract, menaing dead cells slough off as new cells replace them and during this process, the "barrier" integrity is less tightly bound, so the virus can penetrate .  The research showed that the virus can move quickly and in 4 hours re... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>