<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7063">Spanish unemployment</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:04:22" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7063-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7063_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:04:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/725645/119509</link><title>I was laid off May of 2009, collected unemployment then diagnosed w/ breast cancer. Had been on short term disability which just ran out and ok to return to work now. Am I eligible for unemployment?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7063-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7063_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:05:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/75/19620/guide-spanish</link><title>Osteoarthritis Guide in Spanish</title><description>... A handbook for osteoarthritis management has been written in Spanish, entitled "Escogiendo Medicamentos Para el Dolor por Osteoarthritis." This document reviews the cost, effectiveness and potential side effects of conventional therapy, including the nonsteroidals, which are used in the management of osteoarthritis. The document is available online, and interested parties should CLICK HERE FOR A COPY . -- Jonathan D. Krant, MD, FACP ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7063-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7063_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:05:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/question/47594/30547</link><title>is there anyone that has squizoprhrenia that speaks spanish</title><description>...   ... but i hope theres somebody that speaks spanish ...   ...   ... thank you ...   ...   ... gisela ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7063-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7063_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:06:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/c/9487/12923/spanish</link><title>Fighting Osteoporosis in Spanish</title><description>... A family friend who lives in Montevideo, Uruguay and knows that I write about osteoporosis just emailed me a Powerpoint presentation about the disease.   It included just the same kinds of points we often talk about here, specifically the incidence of osteoporosis in older women and the public health threat that the risk of fracture poses -- except in Spanish, of course.   Despite the grim statistics, it was heartening to see yet another corner of the world confronting the issue seriously and taking steps to raise awareness. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7063-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7063_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:07:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/question/202119/146427</link><title>do you have people speak spanish</title><description>... tengo asteoarthritis el cual me causa mucho dolor en mis pierdas principalmente la izquierda mis dedos de los pies me hincan como si tuviera agujas la cual me tiene muy deprimida y muchos deceosde llorar ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7063-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7063_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:07:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/484768/145660</link><title>I am 45 years old, currently unemployed and unisured.</title><description>... I am 45 and currently unemployed &amp; unisured. Today my DR found a large mass on my (R) breast and several small one's on the (L), he wrote a script for a mammogram is there anywhere in the FL. panhandle I could have this done at little or no cost? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7063-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7063_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:08:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/13156/65782</link><title>3o-year-old, female, unemployed.</title><description>... I'm now unemployed since end of Jan 2009. I have been trying to look for jobs but failed. Recently, doctor told me I might get disease or stroke due to my bad health condition, and since I have some of the symtoms. I am now living with friends. I dare not inform my parents about my sickness. I don't want them to worry about me. However, I always wish that my housemates could care about me. They don't even ask how am I doing though I told them I had high fever couple days ago. I told them I went to hospital for treatment, but they just don't bother. On last Sunday, I was not feeling well and fainted in my room. My housemate saw me and she woke me up. She knew that I was fainted but she just doesn't bother. I feel very sad and disappointed. Please advise what should I do?  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7063-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7063_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:08:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/762322/103367</link><title>Unemployment and depression</title><description>... Hi everybody it has been awhile since my last question.I am still unemployed i was laid off jan 31,2009.I have done a few positive things.I was in a outpatient group program where i was able to share my feelings and get out of the house.It was 7 days of therapy and group support.I have been to some local depression/anxiety support groups.My goal is to go one time a week.I also have been to my therapist but had to cut back on my visits to one time per month.My copay is 45 dollars that is tough to pay when you are not working.I have met a few people and gone out to supper with them i use a local dating site.I am trying to get myself to go to the gym.Plus meet more people.I am also thinking about either opening a business,going back to school,or moving to a area where the economy is better but i think it is pretty bad still everywhere.I am doing ok with the bills i collect unemployment and my brother pays me rent. HERE IS MY PROBLEM work used to take up my life i worked 60hrs per week fo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7063-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7063_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:09:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/77780/153017/unemployment</link><title>Unemployment, is a twisted blessing</title><description>...   ... Strange thing though... when I've looked back over that year... in the Bipolar/Mental state of things... I was never more "stabilized".  Except for the periods of high anxiety concerning the finances and job hunting, which was pure Generalized Anxiety reaking havoc... my mood cycles, as a whole, were more mild-moderate... not moderate-severe. ...   ... I spent more time outside, could pace my day as I needed, did not have to be somewhere at any specific time someone else dictated, did not have to seek permission to do this or that or go here or there... I didn't have bosses chewing me out, co-workers berating me, ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7063-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7063_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:10:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/</link><title>STUDENT "UNEMPLOYED" WITH NO MEDICAL COVERAGE</title><description>... WHAT IS MY BEST AND SAFEST ALTERNATIVE FOR HEALTH CARE  ... CONCERNED! ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>