<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7064">Korea weather</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:11:04" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7064-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7064_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:11:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/83694/106765/weather</link><title>weather the weather</title><description>... how do you live moment to moment? ... I didn't sleep too well last night ... living in my apartment is nerve wracking. ... Jon ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7064-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7064_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:11:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/122230/strips-meters-south</link><title>Test Strips and Meters from South Korea</title><description>...   ... People from i-SENS Inc ., a company headquartered in Seoul that designs and manufacturers blood glucose monitoring systems, asked me to visit them this fall. In fact, they originally invited me to come last October. But I had to postpone my visit because I had an emergency operation for twisted small intestines at the beginning of that month, and my surgeon said I couldn't travel. ... For the first few days of my trip I am staying on the top floor of a hotel in the Seongbuk district of Seoul, near the company's headquarters. With 24.5 million inhabitants Seoul is the world's second largest metropolitan areas in population (after Tokyo and ahead of Mexico City, New York City, and Mumbai, in that order). Seoul has been Korea's capital for more than 600 years. ... On Fri... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7064-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7064_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:12:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/sara-nash-comics-baltimore-529615-5.html</link><title>Half Way Around the World with RA</title><description>... Read the full text of Half Way Around the World with RA and leave a comment! See All of Sara's Baltimore Comics Visit the Single Gal's Guide to Rheumatoid Arthritis ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7064-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7064_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:13:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/motherlaw-raised-korea-1103</link><title>My mother-in-law was born and raised in Korea.</title><description>... My mother-in-law was born and raised in Korea. She lives with us in the U.S. Most of her work at home and in the garden is done in the squatting position. She’s going to have her hip replaced this month. Will she be able to squat again after the operation? There’s a known relation between hip dislocation and squatting after hip joint replacement. Studies from Korea and other Asian countries report a high rate of revision surgery for this problem. Doctors in these countries are studying the problem. It may be that using a smaller implant will help. The head of the thighbone (femur) is shaped like a round ball. It sits up inside the hip socket. Using an implant with a smaller head may help it stay inside the socket (or cup if the socket is replaced, too). Be sure the doctor is aware of your mother-in-law's habits and your concerns. The type of implant used may be selected based on this information. Reference: Young-Hoo Kim, MD, et al. Contemporary Total Hip Arthroplasty with and without Ceme... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7064-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7064_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:14:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/123246/korean-paradox</link><title>Diabetes in Korea: Less Obesity but Similar Diabetes Rates</title><description>...   ... In some important respects this Asian country is more like America than most of us would think. This country is a democracy with a booming economy.   ...   ... But the differences are great and go beyond Korea's use of a different language and even a different alphabet than Westerners use. The differences go far beyond  history and tradition. The biggest differences that I have seen during my visit this month are in the people themselves.   ...   ... I saw with my own eyes how thin almost all Koreans are. Coming from the United States -- even though I live in the thinnest state -- I have been amazed to see almost no obesity here.   ...   ... So, of course, I expected that almost no one in Korea would have diabetes. After all, didn't the American weight problem lead to the rapid rise of diabetes in our country?   ...   ... We know that some sort of link between being overweight and having diab... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7064-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7064_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:15:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/tv-replacements-countries-1190</link><title>I saw a report on TV showing the high demand for joint replacements in Korea and other countries outside the United States.</title><description>... I saw a report on TV showing the high demand for joint replacements in Korea and other countries outside the United States. Are we the only ones making joint implants? Korea doesn't have any home-based supplier of joint implants. For this reason, they rely on five United States-based firms. There are other suppliers in Europe, but the UnitedStates supplies about 70 percent of the market for hips and 90 percent for the knee. Korea is only one country that relies completely on an imported supply of artificial joints. However this may be changing as these countries are preparing for their own production of joint implants. The demand for joint replacements is expected to go up even more. In Korea knee replacements are at an all time high. This may be because Koreans squat, which puts increased pressure on the knees. Korean women over age 60 with arthritis are a growing group in need of joint replacement. Reference: Jon Antoniou, MD, PhD, et al. In-Hospital Cost of Total Hip Arthroplasty in Ca... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7064-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7064_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:15:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/122879/tiniboy-inventor</link><title>Meeting the tiniBoy Lancet Inventor in Korea</title><description>... Stanley Kim is a practicing physician in Southern California who recently invented the smallest and painless lancets for testing our blood glucose. I wrote about this invention here this August . At that time Dr. Kim and I hadn't met. I interviewed him on the phone from my home office in Colorado. We had to travel all the way to South Korea to meet in person. We are in Busan, Korea's second largest city with about 3.6 million residents. Specifically, we are both attending the International Diabetes Federation's Western Pacific Region Congress along with about 3,000 other people who work with diabetes. This congress is taking place in Busan Exhibition and Convention Center (BEXCO) in the most modern part of the city near Haeundae, the most famous and frequented beach in all of South Korea. As modern as Korea is -- particularly in this part of the country -- it is naturally quite different from what I normally experience in Colorado. But for Dr. Kim, Busan is quite familiar. He grew up in B... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7064-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7064_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:16:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/122336/diabetes-support</link><title>Diabetes Support in Korea</title><description>... When Jeongkwan (Brian) Lee of the i-SENS planning division introduced me to Cheol Jean, Brian called him "the Korean David Mendosa." Brian was being too generous to me. ...   ... Both of us have written about diabetes for years and have organized diabetes support groups. But Cheol Jean, whose business cards reads as Charlie Jean to make it easier for Westerners, has written four books about diabetes -- twice as many as I have -- and founded and leads a much larger diabetes support group. ...   ... ... Charlie Jean and I Meet ...   ... Brian and I arrived in Busan, Korea, on Sunday evening on the bullet train from Seoul. We are here to participate in the Eighth International Congress of the International Diabetes Federation's Western Pacific Region at the Busan Exhibition and Convention Center (BEXCO). ...   ... I will be covering the IDF meeting for HealthCentral from Monday through Wednesday.  About 3,000 people are here for the meeting in Busan, mainly from Korea, Japan, Canada, and Austral... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7064-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7064_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:16:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/24582/115111/half</link><title>My Long Journey to South Korea with RA</title><description>...   ... As an avid and enthusiastic traveler, one thing I was adamant about from the moment I was diagnosed with RA was that I was not going to let it stop me from seeing as much of the world as I could. I knew that traveling would be different with RA, but what can I say- I’m stubborn about giving up the things I love. ... That summer, though I had never done anything so ambitious before developing RA, I set out with two friends to go to South America for three weeks.  The trip included seeing Macchu Piccu, trekking through the Amazon and staying on a tiny island on Lake Titicaca. It took weeks of planning, several doctor visits and all my organization skills to make sure I was prepared for such a trip- and for anything that might happen. Though it was hard on my body, the trip went fantastically, and I victoriously dubbed it my ‘I have RA, but RA doesn’t have me’ trip. ... With that first adventure under my belt, I no longer felt so wo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7064-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7064_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:17:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/706940/132769</link><title>how to treat allergi rhinities in col or winter place like in south korea</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>