<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7065">disney easter dessert recipes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:18:02" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7065-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7065_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:18:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/151519/bariatric-easter</link><title>Easter Dinner Menu Makeover (grain-free, low carb) - My Bariatric Life</title><description>...   ... I have fond early childhood memories of holidays spent around my great grandmother's table, and in later childhood around my grandmother's table, eating wonderful Polish soul food. I don't have Bapshe's or Nana's recipes for babka, cucumber salad, or kielbasa and saurkraut, but I do carry their memories... ...   ... I remember the link kielbasa, coiled and ornamental in the glass enclosure where my brother and I inspected them thoughtfully. Already our stomachs growled in anticipation of the holiday meal my family would make that afternoon. Nana had sent my brother and me down the block and around the corner to Detmer's, the neighborhood Polish deli. The small slip of paper my grandmother had given me was tucked carefully in my pocket, and I took my task as seriously as any of Caesar's messengers must have done. Once inside the tiny market, the aroma of smoked kielbasa enticed and welcomed us. I removed the folded paper from my pocket and hande... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7065-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7065_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:18:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/139543/bariatric-weight</link><title>Grain-free Baked Goods and Dessert Recipes - My Bariatric Life</title><description>...   ... Kelly Brozyna is one of my favorite grain-free bakers. Her recipes produce bakery items so similar to conventional wheat/dairy/sugar versions that no one will feel deprived. Kelly developed these recipes for her family who were suffering from celiac disease, gluten intolerance, ADD and autism, but the recipes are perfect for patients maintaining long-term weight loss from obesity surgery. ...   ... Best-of-all, Kelly Brozyna's grain-free bakery recipes are innovative and easy! Here are a few of my breakfast bakery favorites: ...   ... Who doesn't love ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7065-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7065_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:19:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/221743/99787/healthier</link><title>Healthier Dessert Choices?</title><description>...   ... Thanks for any info!! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7065-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7065_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:20:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/158650/cookies-sweets</link><title>Cakes, Cookies, and Sweets: Grain-free Desserts that Say “I Love You”</title><description>... Grain-free Cakes, Cookies, and Sweets for Your Sweet ...   ... Grains and desserts are not part of the bariatric diet! So, many of us weight-loss surgery patients miss out on sharing Valentine’s confections with our dearly beloved. That or we discredit ourselves and our success by taking in a few sugary starchy treats.  ...   ... There is another option. Baked goods using coconut flour, almond flour, and other grain-free flours offer a delicious bariatric-friendly alternative to wheat. Grain-free flours are high in fiber, low in digestible carbohydrate, and a good source of protein. They can be used to make German Chocolate Cake, Apple Pie, Blueberry Muffins, Chocolate Cranberry Biscotti, and Vanilla Cupcakes with Raspberry Fig Filling – really, just about any traditional baked good can be made grain-free. The recipes are so good that you’ll never know they’re wheat-free.  ...   ... The Best Grain-free Dessert Cookbooks ...   ... Here is my favorite recipe... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7065-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7065_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:20:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/120/22841/happy-easter</link><title>A Happy Easter</title><description>... This year, I spent the holiday at Mom's. She and her sisters are all Easter egg color women, and I'm red-and-black. I was never much for pastels, and even my life hasn't been all bubblegum. It was a bittersweet time as I reflected on how far I've come.   Years ago, I decided I wouldn't have kids, because I didn't want to bring into the world a child who could develop schizophrenia. I'm lucky I have a niece, Rosa, who is three, and a nephew, Christopher, who is six. I saw them on Easter, and when they left to go home, I kissed them and said, "I love you." I always end the day by telling them I love them.   In this lifetime, I won't be a mom, and that is my one true regret because I would've liked that and made a career out of it. Instead, I feel the pull to advocacy as my life's work, because everyone I meet is part of my own healing, and if I could help others heal, that will be my role to play that God gave me. &amp;nbsp... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7065-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7065_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:21:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/c/822/58975/chocolaty-prunes</link><title>Heart Healthy Dessert: Chocolaty Cakes with Prunes in Marsala</title><description>... ... ... Prep time: 20 minutes Cooking time: 15 minutes Serves: 4 ...   ... Ingredients: ... ½ oz cocoa powder, plus a little extra for dusting 3 large eggs 1 level tablespoon granulated sweetener Flavourless oil for greasing ...    ... For the filling: ... 12 ready-to-eat prunes 1½ fl oz Marsala 2 rounded tablespoons low fat fromage frais 1 teaspoon granulated sweetener 1 teaspoon chocolate extract ...   ... You will also need four 1½ inch deep ramekins with a base measurement of 3 inches, very lightly greased, and a small baking tray. ...   ... Method: ... 1.    First of all, place the prunes in a small saucepan with the Marsala. Bring them up to simmering point and leave to cool. Transfer them to a small, lidded plastic box and leave to soak for as long as possible, turning them now and then. ... 2.    When you're ready to make the cakes, pre-heat the oven to gas mark 4, 350°F (180°C). ... 3.    Then separate the eggs, placing the yo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7065-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7065_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:21:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/reviews-294577-5.html</link><title>Recipe: Grape Tarts with Vanilla Pastry Cream</title><description>... Grape Tarts with Vanilla Pastry Cream Serves 6 These tarts look like a fancy restaurant dessert. The tangy grapes contrast well with the smooth pastry cream, creating a unique and satisfying dessert. Crust 12 ounces (about 1 box) vanilla wafers 2 tablespoons unsalted butter, melted Pastry Cream 6 large egg yolks 1/2 cup sugar Pinch salt 1/2 cup all-purpose flour 1 3/4 cups skim milk, heated 1 tablespoon vanilla extract Glaze 1 cup apricot preserves 3 tablespoons sugar 1 tablespoon fresh lemon juice 1 1/2 cups seedless red grapes, stemmed and halved lengthwise 1 1/2 cups seedless purple grapes, stemmed and halved lengthwise Crust : Chop the vanilla wafers into fine crumbs in a food processor. Transfer the crumbs to a small bowl and stir in the butter. Line 6 removable-bottom 3-to-4-inch tart pans with the wafer mixture. Chill in the refrigerator. Pastry cream : Whisk the egg yolks in a medium saucepan, gradually adding the sugar and salt. Whisk until the yolk mixtu... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7065-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7065_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:22:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/5068/96333/cranberry-relish</link><title>A Diabetes Recipe: Cranberry Relish</title><description>... Cranberries. What would Thanksgiving be without them. It's delicious on the day itself, and it's also delicious with the leftover turkey we all eat for the next few days. ...   ... Unfortunately, the easy cranberry sauce, the stuff that comes in cans, is loaded with sugar. So what can we do? ...   ... Use our creativity, of course. If you have a family recipe for cranberry sauce, try making it with a sugar substitute. ...   ... Many people like the combination of cranberries and oranges ground together. So do I, but even whole oranges make my blood glucose go up. So when I make cranberry sauce, I use orange gelatin dessert. ...   ... It's simple: dissolve some sugarfree orange gelatin dessert in boiling water as usual, add some chopped cranberries, let it set, and that's all there is to it. ...   ... If you want to add other stuff, go ahead. Add walnuts. Try a little chopped ginger. Add some chopped onions. Or if you're really courageous, add a little horseradish. ...   ... You could even serve one ve... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7065-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7065_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:23:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/c/3120/9691/bone-month</link><title>More Bone Friendly Recipes for Osteoporosis Awareness Month</title><description>... As we continue to recognize May as Osteoporosis Awareness Month, let us remember that taking preventive measures at an early age is a great way to protect against developing osteoporosis. Between racing to music lessons, waiting for baseball practice or hurrying to art class, kids are busier than ever and need to re-fuel after school. These recipes focus on kid-friendly foods that are high in calcium, which can help prevent the onset of osteoporosis. These recipes are great for kids of any age!   Try this great recipe for Beef Meatloaf with Mushrooms and Onions . It is bursting with flavor and if you rather not make a meatloaf using beef, try using your favorite ground meat to create your own personalized dish. If you like serving meatloaf with ketchup or some other sauce, you can draw fun designs or smiley faces on the meatloaf for the kids for a fun and flavorful meal!   (   For an after dinner sweet treat, take your pick of these calcium rich desserts. If you ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7065-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7065_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:23:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/148262/maintenance-good</link><title>My Bariatric Life: Too Good to be True Holiday Brownies, Fudge, &amp; Cookies from Beans Recipes!</title><description>... Grains and desserts are not part of the bariatric diet! So many of us weight-loss surgery patients either miss out on Christmas confections, or we discredit ourselves and our success by taking in a few sugary starchy treats.  ...   ... Now, just in time for the holidays, is my favorite recipe book collection for grain-free desserts that are perfect for people who want to maintain their weight-loss and enjoy the occasional sweet during this "most wonderful time of the year." Click on the image below to see the entire grain-free desserts collection. ...   ... ...   ...   ... One of my favorite treats on occasion are rich dark chocolate brownies -- made guilt and grain-free! ...   ... Dark Chocolate Black Bean Brownies ...   ... Made from black beans, without a trace of flour, this recipe is too good to be true! Yummy brownies made from black beans, you say??? It's true! Even my flour and sugar-eating friends fall head-over-heels when I serve these brownies for dessert. I like them served... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>