<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7066">awk trim non-printable characters</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:24:26" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7066-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7066_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:24:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/114397/character</link><title>A Look Into Character</title><description>... We have been told mental illness is a "no fault" illness, much like diabetes. Indeed it is. But one can clearly assign blame to a person with diabetes who continues on a high sugar diet and won't take his insulin as prescribed. Can the same be said for someone with bipolar who equally tempts fate? Absolutely. But when we are severely depressed, we lack the cognitive skills, motivation, and energy to help ourselves. And in mania we are too far gone to be acting in our best interests. So when does fault kick in? Over the past eight or nine months, we have been exploring that ill-defined and highly subjective area where illness meets personality. The distinction lies between "state" and "trait." Episodes - depression, mania, anxiety - tend to be a departure from our personality (or temperament). But we can also have depressive or exuberant or anxious temperaments. Did I mention this gets complicated? I got started on this inquiry several years back when I noticed that those who appeared stu... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7066-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7066_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:25:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/819637/137560/jo-effect</link><title>Is this diet good and non jo-jo effect?</title><description>... Breakfast ... 1 Cup Fruit Juice 1/2 Cup Oatmeal 1 Cup Low-Fat Yogurt Black Coffee or Herbal Tea Snack ... Smoothie (1 Cup Berries blended with 1 Cup Trim (1%) Milk and Ice Cubes). ... Lunch ... 2 Slices Whole Wheat Bread 1/2 Cup Tuna (in water only) Salad (Tomato, Cucumber, Lettuce) with 1 teaspoon mayonnaise + 1/2 tbsp olive oil. Dinner ... 3.5 oz (~100g) chicken breast (skinless boneless) - cook in griller. 1 Cup Broccoli 1/2 Cup Brown Rice Meal Plan 2 ... TOTAL CALORIES ~1200 Breakfast ... 2 Slices Whole Wheat Toast with 1 tsp Butter 1/2 Cup Canned Fruit Cocktail (Fruit Salad) - in natural juice only 8 oz (1 cup) Trim (1%) Milk Snack ... 1 Medium-Sized Banana Lunch ... 6 Crackers with Low-Fat Cottage Cheese. Handful Mixed Nuts (Almonds, Walnuts, ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7066-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7066_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:25:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/autism/c/1443/145584/tips-communication</link><title>Tips for Teaching Non-Verbal Communication Skills</title><description>...   ... Although your child may not ever be completely comfortable with the non-verbal portions of a conversation, you can help them better use and understand non-verbal communication. ...   ... Play Charades - use short sentences or stories that convey emotion, such as "I saw the dog coming toward me and I was afraid." You can add that you can use sounds and actions to act out the sentence or story but no words are allowe... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7066-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7066_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:26:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/630701/69688/sex-relationships</link><title>About Dating, Sex, and Relationships (Non Traditional)</title><description>...   ... I appreciate the breadth of information here. I would like to add my own story as I believe it touches on some things not yet mentioned. ...   ... I have not been clinically diagnosed with bipolar disorder, but I am doing personal research as I believe there is a high probability that I may have this disorder. ...   ... I have dated and did so very promiscuously for years between age 19 - 29. I would go out with just about anyone who asked me out, and quite a few that I ran after myself. I am attractive, so I've been asked out a lot! I suffer from periods of high and low self esteem. I sometimes think that my promiscuity had a lot more to do with my long-held belief for so much of my youth that I was not attractive, and worthless, rather than a true reflection of my real appearance. I guess that by being with a lot of people for casual sex was a way for me to let it sink in that I was wrong, and that others may genuinely want ME. However, I have always fear... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7066-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7066_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:27:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/genital-herpes/c/18559/57811/television</link><title>The Absence of Herpes in Film and Television</title><description>... When was the last time you saw a TV show or a movie that featured a character with herpes?   I find it rather ironic that a disease as prevalent as herpes (or HPV or that matter) is rarely brought into the world of film and television.   Maybe those who work behind the scenes have never dealt with herpes.   Or maybe they don’t want to discuss such a pointless and sexual illness.   We’ve all seen movies in which characters have cancer, HIV, or heart disease.   But herpes and HPV are just not interesting or important enough…unless, of course, we’re laughing about them.   Maybe that’s why so many people are confused and misinformed about these viruses, or why there is such a stigma attached.   It is not the media’s job to educate people about STDs, but it would be nice to have some kind of representation in the film and television realm.   ...   ... It is estimated that one in five Americans has herpes, and one in four Ne... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7066-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7066_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:27:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/417/12706/asthma-graves</link><title>asthma and graves disease</title><description>... Does anyone have asthma and graves disease?  I have had asthma for about 25 years.  The last year my asthma was so out of control and then I became very ill and found out I have graves disease.  After being put on atd drugs to suppress my hyperthyroidism, my asthma has been almost non existent.  I can't believe it and neither can my doctor.  I am wonder now if my asthma problems was from the graves all along.   Any input from any of you.  I'm curious if anyone else has this disease and asthma.   Thanks for your help.  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7066-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7066_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:28:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/question/60441/44288</link><title>My mother has a paranoid personality, and my girlfriend's father was schizophrenic. Should we marry?</title><description>...   ... My girlfriend's father was schizophrenic. She has no mental illness that I'm aware of. ...   ... Is it prudent for us to marry and have children? I'm very worried that our children could inherit some severe mental illness. What are the odds? ...   ... Thanks a lot! ...   ... R ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7066-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7066_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:29:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/63/7097/disorder</link><title>Borderline Personality Disorder</title><description>... Borderline Personality Disorder Raising questions, finding answers Borderline personality disorder (BPD) is a serious mental illness characterized by pervasive instability in moods, interpersonal relationships, self-image, and behavior. This instability often disrupts family and work life, long-term planning, and the individual's sense of self-identity. Originally thought to be at the "borderline" of psychosis, people with BPD suffer from a disorder of emotion regulation. While less well known than schizophrenia or bipolar disorder (manic-depressive illness), BPD is more common, affecting 2 percent of adults, mostly young women. 1 There is a high rate of self-injury without suicide intent, as well as a significant rate of suicide attempts and completed suicide in severe cases. 2 , 3 Patients often need extensive mental health services, and account for 20 percent of psychiatric hospitalizations. 4 Yet, with help, many improve over time and are eventually able to lead productive lives. Symp... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7066-09"><link>http://www.healthcentral.com/erectile-dysfunction/c/354824/163078/inflammation</link><title>Orchitis is the common inflammation of male genital system</title><description>... Orchitis is one of the common diseases of male genital system. It is a kind of inflammatory lesion infected by various pathogenic factors. The  types of orchitis  are including non-specific, viral, mycotic, spirochaetal, parasitic, traumatic, chemical orchitis and so on. The usual routes of ingection are blood circulation and lymphatic. The pathogens also can invade the testicles through urethral tract, scrotum, seminal duct and epididymis.  ... The most common situations in clinic are non-specific orchitis and mumps orchitis, which are the usual pathogenesis of male infe... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7066-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7066_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:31:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabeteens/c/22669/79436/diabetes-iphone</link><title>Diabetes Apps on the iPhone (Day 1 at CWD FFL)</title><description>... Anyway, the folks here asked us what we thought of integrating diabetes management technology with the Apple iPhone. My response? Wow, Awesome! ...   ... A new iPhone app is in the works which would allow us to monitor our bgs on the iPhone, complete with little animated characters that pop up depending on whether your blood sugar is in or out of range. There isn't a whole lot of information available on this yet, but it's a great concept. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>