<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7067">used kindle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:31:52" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7067-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7067_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:31:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/151832/kindle-book</link><title>My New Kindle Book Is Out!</title><description>...   ... Raccoons Respect My Piss But Watch Out For Skunks: My Funny Life On a Planet Not of My Choosing That I Now - Maybe, Sort of, Not Really, Well Okay - Call Home. ...   ... I know - it needs a longer title. ...   ... Raccoons recounts my comically absurd misadventures in dealing with life on a planet seemingly built for other people. Here’s a sample from Chapter Eight: ...   ... Life, unfortunately, doesn't come with a manual, and the tech support is a joke. Seriously, when has God—or St Aloysius, even—ever gotten back to you? Is it too much for God to stop what He is doing for just one second and tell me that the vital piece of hardware I dropped on the floor—the one I desperately need to assemble my counter extender from IKEA—rolled un... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7067-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7067_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:32:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/7712/131930/fanning-kindling</link><title>Fanning the Flames: Can Kindling Explain Relapse?</title><description>...   ... The issue of relapse has never fully been understood beyond some of the factors known to, or suspected of, acting as triggers. One thing we know about mood disorders is that once they start people do not develop a tolerance to them. On the contrary, the evidence points to a likelihood of increased sensitivity to events or situations likely to trigger a relapse. This shouldn't be confused with the capacity to cope with or possibly even head off an event through insight and experience. ...   ... Life stress and biological susceptibility are thought to play important roles in the onset of mood disorders. The kindling model suggests that the first ever episode of mood disorder is more likely to be associated with major stressors than are episodes occurring later in... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7067-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7067_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:33:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/question/834144/82592</link><title>Bipolar 2 with mixed or rapid cycling or kindling vs. Borderline personality</title><description>... 34 year old female...after birth of daughter 5 years ago and tremendous streessors, lack of support etc..i started to get depressed 6 years ago..Since than sx have gotten worse..2 hospitalizations, opportunistic infections from stress (shingles, thrush), IBS, pmdd, worsening "black hole depression:, catatonic or sobbing, lash out...shear mental pain and unbearable...never manic...maybe hypomanic..agitation, irritability, agitation, panic attacks...had recent situation crises..suicide attempt, Dual diagnosis ....meds include lexapro, seroquel, abilify (new), klonopin, adderall (when severly depressed), buspar, and now back to alcohol after rehab b/c can't cope with up and downs daily...thoughts of suicicde but will not, hx of self mutilation, unbearably painful to be alone, can't sleep, work, need a relationship which are usually abusive..much more...but could it be Borderline with Bipolar 2...also i think i have ptsd, and definately hypochondriac...although have masters and whenworkin... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7067-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7067_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:34:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/question/834144/82593</link><title>Bipolar 2 with mixed or rapid cycling or kindling vs. Borderline personality</title><description>... 34 year old female...after birth of daughter 5 years ago and tremendous streessors, lack of support etc..i started to get depressed 6 years ago..Since than sx have gotten worse..2 hospitalizations, opportunistic infections from stress (shingles, thrush), IBS, pmdd, worsening "black hole depression:, catatonic or sobbing, lash out...shear mental pain and unbearable...never manic...maybe hypomanic..agitation, irritability, agitation, panic attacks...had recent situation crises..suicide attempt, Dual diagnosis ....meds include lexapro, seroquel, abilify (new), klonopin, adderall (when severly depressed), buspar, and now back to alcohol after rehab b/c can't cope with up and downs daily...thoughts of suicicde but will not, hx of self mutilation, unbearably painful to be alone, can't sleep, work, need a relationship which are usually abusive..much more...but could it be Borderline with Bipolar 2...also i think i have ptsd, and definately hypochondriac...although have masters and whenworkin... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7067-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7067_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:35:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/1443/155557/3-free-organization</link><title>3 Free Apps for Time Management and Organization</title><description>...   ... Evernote ... ... Price: Free ... ... Evernote allows you to capture your thoughts, copy and paste web content, make audio notes and sync the information between your phone, computer and iPad. In essence, it helps to organize your thoughts and puts them in one single place -  so you can later search and easily find them. ...   ... You begin by creating a “note.” Give your note a name to help you remember what is in it, type your thoughts or ideas, add images by dragging and dropping, include information from websites (by simply clicking the Evernote button on your browser) and finish your note. You can create a noteboo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7067-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7067_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:35:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/154742/reading-question</link><title>Summer Reading - The Bipolar Question of the Week</title><description>...   ... For fiction, there is John Kennedy Toole’s “Confederacy of Dunces,” which I purchased with good intent some time ago but abandoned only after a few pages. Maybe I will give it a second chance. ...   ... I won’t claim to actually read all these books, but one of them is bound to totally engage me, challenge my thinking, and immeasurably richen my inner experience. Notice, there are no mental health or brain science books on my list. I am on vacation, you know. ...   ... I see a... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7067-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7067_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:36:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/215658/154500/explainer</link><title>Cold Baths for Weight Loss? A HealthCentral Explainer</title><description>...   ... In an appearance on the Today show, author Venice A. Fulton – real name Paul Khanna, a British actor and personal trainer who holds a degree in sports science – described some of the tricks: skip breakfast, drink two cups of black coffee on an empty stomach and take a 15-minute cold bath every day. ...   ... What does a cold bath have to do with weight loss? ... ... Khanna, in his TV appearance, claimed, "When your body gets in a cold bath – it hates that – it ramps up metabolism to keep you warm.... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7067-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7067_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:37:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/5949/160654/free-fibromyalgia-poetry</link><title>Free Fibromyalgia Poetry Book</title><description>...   ... In honor of Fibromyalgia Awareness Day 2013, Eaton is making the Kindle version of his book Living with Fibromyalgia: A Young Man's Journey to Peace, Inspiration and Empowerment Through Poetry and Uplifting Words available for $ .99 on May 11 and for free on May 12. ...   ... Currently, the Kindle version of the book costs $3.99. If you choose to pay for the book, know that a portion of the sales from the Kindle version will support three foundations close to the heart of the author: Rockstar Ronan, Friends of Brianna, and the National Fibromyalgia and Chronic Pain Association. ...   ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7067-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7067_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:37:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/814377/164164</link><title>Having Chest Pain, severe lightheadedness, tingling in hands. What could it mean?</title><description>... Over the past 3 to 4 day, I have experienced severe lightheadedness,horrible thirst, lack of appetite, chest pain (TERRIBLE, TERRIBLE) chest pain, and strong tingling in hands. Along with headache. Should I be concerned or is this a type of virus? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7067-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7067_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:38:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/968433/137075/ha</link><title>Something that may help if your hands hurt like mine!</title><description>... I have always been an avid reader, until about two years ago when it became too  painful to hold a book or try and pin it to a lapdesk. I recently got a Kindle from Amazon.com. WOW!!!! Its so light and easy to use, I am all over reading again! Plus you can get tons and tons of books downloaded to it for free! I am also switching over my magazine subscriptions to it as well. I really love it already! If your hands are always sore like mine and you still want to read, get the Kindle! It will help for sure! :) ...   ... Brad ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>