<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7068">Speech and Language Processing: An Introduction to Natural Language Processing, Computational Linguistics, and Speech Recognition</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:39:12" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7068-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7068_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:39:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/538169/150495</link><title>Hi-My son, who is 7, is speech/language delayed...</title><description>... Hi- My son, who is 7, is speech/language delayed.  Recently, when doing homework, he has started saying things like 'my mind is saying no' when trying to recall information.  Just yesterday, we were working on spelling and vocabulary, and it was like a switch had been flipped...he could not only recall many of his words, but he was sounding out words he didn't know how to spell in order to spell them out loud...these were big words, not only those in his vocabulary lessons.  When we asked him how he knew all of these words, he said 'my brain is saying yes today'.  For a 7 year old, this seems highly intuitive as far as understanding what is going on in his head. Is there a disorder/disease that causes people to have trouble accessing memory and processing skills and to KNOW that they should be able to do it but can't get their brain to cooperate? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7068-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7068_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:40:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/19065/62561/related</link><title>How to Manage MS-Related Dysarthria (Speech Dysfunction)</title><description>...   ... The normal processes of speech and voice production are overlapping and require the following five processes to work together smoothly and rapidly: ... ... Respiration:   Using the diaphragm to quickly fill the lungs fully, followed by slow, controlled exhalation for speech. ... ... ... Phonation: &amp;nbsp... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7068-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7068_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:40:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/944320/118855/dyslexia</link><title>What Is Dyslexia?</title><description>...   ... Dyslexia is the only learning disability for which there is a definition-based on research , or, what is referred to in clinical practice as an evidence-based definition.   This definition, established by the International Dyslexia Association , states that: ... ... Dyslexia is a spe... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7068-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7068_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:41:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/35897/talk-disturbingly</link><title>Baby Talk and “Elderspeak” Disturbingly Related</title><description>... "Here you go, Hon. Anything else?" Though cringing inwardly, I smile outwardly and say, "No thanks."  The waitress, perhaps in her early thirties, is just trying to be nice to me. I understand that. I happen to be a small person, rather short, tiny bones - the kind of person where, when the prairie winds invade our metro area and tall buildings create wind tunnels, I could use a few rocks in my pockets to hold me down. However, that, plus the fact that I'm old enough to be this woman's mother, doesn't give her a right to talk down to me. ...   ... She, of course, doesn't realize she is talking down to me. She's just being nice and thinks I'm "sweet." But would she call a twenty-something woman "Hon?" I doubt it. ...   ... Where am I going with this, you ask? I'm referring to an ABC online news article titled, " 'Baby Talk' Irritates Alzheimer's Patients: Caregivers For the Elderly Should Avoid Certain Patterns of Speech, New Research Says ." This article is must reading for all ca... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7068-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7068_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:42:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/guides/000096_1.html</link><title>Encephalitis: Viral - Introduction</title><description>... Introduction Encephalitis is a rare but potentially life-threatening inflammation of the brain that can occur in people of all ages. The most common cause of encephalitis is infection by a virus. In very rare cases, encephalitis can also be caused by bacterial infection, parasites, or complications from other infectious diseases. This report focuses on viral encephalitis. Encephalitis: Viral Infection of the Brain Many viruses can cause encephalitis. The West Nile virus, for example, has been responsible for well-publicized outbreaks in the U.S. Most people exposed to encephalitis-causing viruses have no symptoms. Others may experience a mild flu-like illness, but do not develop full-blown encephalitis. In severe cases, the infection can have devastating effects, including: Swelling of the brain ( cerebral edema ) Bleeding within the brain ( intercerebral hemorrhage) Nerve damage ( neuropathy ) The damage may cause long-term mental or physical problems, depending on the specific areas of the brain... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7068-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7068_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:42:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/19/2382/dysphagia</link><title>Dysphagia: Difficulties Swallowing</title><description>... ... Luckily, everything got moving again and I’m more than 90 percent back to normal. But, it seems I’ve been having another side effect of my stroke, five years later. Lately, I’ve been having trouble swallowing. It feels like my throat is clogged up and lets food and liquids down either very slowly or not at all. When it’s not allowed, the water or whatever I’m drinking comes back up and into my windpipe, giving me quite a coughing fit. Some days, though, I don’t notice a thing, while other days I choke on my own saliva. Yes, I know, it’s disgusting and scary. ... ... It turns out, swallowing difficulty after stro... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7068-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7068_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:43:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/autism/c/1443/160401/service-dogs-autism</link><title>Service Dogs for Autism</title><description>... ... Service Dogs and Safety Issues ... ... One of the main benefits of having a service dog is the increased safety and security they offered. For example, many children with ASD will wander off, cross streets without looking or suddenly take off running. This behavior isn’t just frustrating for parents, it can be extremely dange... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7068-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7068_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:43:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/849319/136522/visual-thinking</link><title>Autism and Visual Thinking</title><description>...   ... Train in the bedroom by Max ...   ... ...   ... Penguin Bubbles by Max ...   ...   ... ...   ... Crocodile in the Bathtub by Max ...   ... (Examples of my son's visual thinking and artistic expression at age six and seven) ...   ... Have you ever thought about the way you think? I know it is a strange question but it is one that scientists are now looking at with regard to people who are on the autism spectrum. In a recent BBC news report , there is a story about how University of Montreal scientists found that people who have autism have highly developed areas of the brain to process visual information. It seems there is a price to pay for this brain specialization. They also found that certain parts of the brain in people with autism are less active. ...   ... The study authors analyzed brain imaging studies conducted over a span of 15 years and compared the brain images of autistic participants with those who do not have autism. They found that autistic individuals show more activity in the t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7068-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7068_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:44:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/4182/160119/kinect-diagnose-depression</link><title>Xbox Kinect May Help Diagnose Depression</title><description>...   ... Similarly, anyone familiar with an Xbox gaming console will probably also be aware of the webcam motion- sensing device known as Kinect. To date the device has largely been used for gesture recognition in order to support a variety of games and activities such as virtual tennis, skiing, fitness programs or other forms of interactivity. Here we can move alongside or even compete physically with the avatar on the screen to make it a more immersive and believable experience. ...   ... Clinical applications have been somewhat overlooked. Recently however, the device has been... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7068-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7068_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:44:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/5949/9790/anymore</link><title>What Cannot Be Said on Television About Health Care</title><description>... When I was growing up, there were quite a few things you couldn’t say on television.  Any kind of profanity or sexually explicit language was forbidden.  By contrast today, with the growth of cable TV, those limitations are virtually gone.  The only restrictions we see now are in the form of political correctness.   There is, however, a doctor who claims there are three things related to health care that cannot be said on TV –– not because they are too explicit not because they are politically unacceptable, but because they are no longer true.  In the May 16 issue of the Journal of the American Medical Association, Ezekiel J. Emanuel, MD, PhD wrote an article entitled, “What Cannot Be Said on Television About Health Care,” in which he listed three sentences that, once true, can no longer be said about the United States health care system.  Those sentences are: •    “The United States has the best health care system in the world.” •&amp;... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>