<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7069">Eames chair</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:45:24" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7069-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7069_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:45:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/question/2890/145910</link><title>i am overweight and have a hard time doing some of the exercizes on my malibu pilayes chair, can't pull up my weight on the chair, no ujpper body strength..any suggestions?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7069-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7069_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:45:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/question/2890/145909</link><title>i am overweight and have a hard time doing some of the exercizes on my malibu pilayes chair, can't pull up my weight on the chair, no ujpper body strength..any suggestions?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7069-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7069_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:46:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/23153/31764/solutions</link><title>Solutions for the Pain Pinch: Which Zero Gravity Chairs Really Work?</title><description>...   ... One of my favorite tools against aching, all-over pain is the zero-gravity chair. In fact, I cried when I tried it because for the first time my pain melted down a couple notches. Time and time again, patients try the zero-gravity chair in my office and fall in love.  ...   ... The key is your body's position that minimizes the effects of gravity. Your back is parallel to the floor and the hips are bent with the knees supported above your chest. It is the same position the astronauts are in before blast off. No ordinary recliner will do because the hips and knees must be bent to place the knees above the che... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7069-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7069_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:47:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/32873/108087/chair</link><title>MS Awareness Month: Tips for the Right Chair</title><description>... ... ... We want to continue to watch our overall health. Many people with MS have an uncomfortable or awkward gait. We often tire when walking any distance. A chair is often our safe-haven, but sitting for any length of time has an impact on our general health. ... What difference does sitting in one chair or another have to do with our health? The right chair is a factor that may improve our overall health. Most of us have heard this before, but a reminder never hurts. About 40% of MSers sit in wheelchairs, and that includes some who use the wheelchair only part of the time. Selecting a chair, whether it's a wheelchair or an office chair, is almost the same process. Of course when selectin... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7069-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7069_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:48:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/30210/46516</link><title>Where would I start my search for either an electric wheel chair or walker</title><description>...  As I was reading through my computer I came across a web page about Orbit Medical Wheelchairs.It said to fill out the questionnare and they would work with your insurance and help you to get one.Well I did that and someone did call me.She asked me if I had ever fallen.I said yes and once I broke my left foot twice and my right foot on May 30th of this year.So she said it sounded like I might qualify.But then I began to think of that heavy thing and how would I get it to where I was going.So I saw the walker with wheels that had a seat in it when you become tired or in pain.I thought about this as my mother had one and we both used it when she went shopping with me.I realized that I needed one also.My handicapped sticker says limited walking.Someone called me back and wasn't really rude but just sounded monotone like I was boring her or wasting her time.She said my insurance would not work with them.And I needed to find out which companies did.I called back and said the woman was... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7069-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7069_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:48:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/c/8248/8604/bit-im</link><title>My power wheel chair bit the dust and I'm tired of pushin it home.</title><description>... I quit. I fired the people I got the power wheel chair from, they never want to come and look at it. They tell me it is a new battery, they said that I wasn't charging it up right a night and that I shouldn'd be having the problems that I am. I wrote to them that I wanted an owners manual so I know how to care for the chair, also how do I take it apart to clean it, oil it and make sure that every thing is tighted down. No answer.Its like I wrote and nobody is home to care. Anyway I am tired and waiting is temp till I think of another stratigy ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7069-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7069_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:49:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/499724/134316/am</link><title>AmeriGlide Chair Lifts</title><description>...   ... Thanks! ... V ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7069-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7069_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:50:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/49545/35362</link><title>What is the best type of office chair to use?</title><description>...   ... thanx shelley ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7069-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7069_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:50:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/1009/36687</link><title>massage chairs</title><description>... im just wandering if medical insurances cover massage chairs for fibromyagia. or other conditions ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7069-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7069_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:51:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/407008/124299</link><title>Can Sitting In A Chair Cause Chest Pain</title><description>... i am having some discomfort  in chest when i sit in a chair any time .how to solve this problems. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>