<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7070">compact flash memory card</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:52:06" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7070-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7070_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:52:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/3213/credit-card-debt</link><title>Credit Card Debt and Seniors</title><description>... The Dallas Morning News published a story recently entitled “Retirees Sliding into Debt: Higher Costs of Housing, Medical Care and Utilities Can Overwhelm Budgets.” The story refers to a study by the National Consumer Law Center about seniors turning increasingly using credit cards to cover retirement costs.   The study found that the average credit card debt for consumers 65 to 69 years of age has increased 217 percent over the last decade and is close to $6,000. The NCLC’s study attributes this trend to three factors: (1) seniors’ stagnant or shrinking income; (2) higher expenses for housing, medical care and utilities; and (3) creditor practices that influence seniors to borrow. The study reported seniors average more than $3,500 in out-of-pocket medical costs annually, which is a 45 percent increase over a 10-year period.   This situation can be even more challenging when the senior has Alzheimer’s disease. My mom always enjoyed shopping as a diversion; for a couple o... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7070-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7070_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:52:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/101511/prescription-card</link><title>Prescription Discount Card</title><description>... ... ... ... The Front of the Discount Card ... ... ... The Back of that Card ... This card will work now for those of us who have third-part insurance. Roche tells me that they are "actively working on options for the uninsured." The card says that it isn't valid for people "reimbursed under Medicare, Medicaid, or other government healthcare programs." Those programs reduce the cost of test strips anyway. Right now the cards don't come with the other blood ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7070-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7070_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:53:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/182256/59978/activities</link><title>Memory Activities developed from Memories</title><description>... Before my mother's stroke her favorite hobbies were putting together large puzzles and playing cards. After her stroke the puzzles were impossible and there were no age appropriate small ones. Dad made her a card holder and she could play cards for a while. My mothers needs and frustrations played a key role to my developing Memory Jogging Puzzles and Memory Exercise Cards. After researching I discovered the same needs still existed today as when my mother was suffering from Alzheimer's after a massive stroke many years ago. My puzzles and memory cards have themes of the real life illustrations by Norman Rockwell - The Saturday Evening Post and they are beneficial not only to the person with Alzheimer's but to the caregivers. "Your puzzles do indeed show some promise, due to the fact that they engage persons with their emotional and recognition memory, but then rely upon "here and now" problem-solving skills." ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7070-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7070_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:54:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/182256/59977/activities</link><title>Memory Activities developed from Memories</title><description>... ... Before my mother's stroke her favorite hobbies were putting together large puzzles and playing cards. After her stroke the puzzles were impossible and there were no age appropriate small ones. Dad made her a card holder and she could play cards for a while. ...   ... My mothers needs and frustrations played a key role to my developing Memory Jogging Puzzles and Memory Exercise Cards. ...   ... After researching I discovered the same needs still existed today as when my mother was suffering from Alzheimer's after a massive stroke many years ago. ... ... My puzzles and memory cards have themes of the real life illustrations by Norman Rockwell - The Saturday Evening Post and they are beneficial not only to the person with Alzheimer's but to the caregivers. ...   ... ... "Your puzzles do indeed show some promise, due to the fact that they engage persons with their emotional and recognition memory, but then rely upon "here and now" problem-solving skills." ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7070-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7070_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:54:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/c/727598/155946/menopause-hot</link><title>Symptoms of Menopause May Go Beyond Hot Flashes, Night Sweats</title><description>... Recently a community member posted a question on HealthCentral’s Alzheimer’s site about her mother, who is 55. The mother had been diagnosed by a doctor with Alzheimer’s. The daughter, who questioned this diagnosis, said her mother was having some memory loss (like forgetting where she put her keys or how to get to the bank), although she was not having any problems with her daily routine, speaking, writing or reading. She knows time and place and isn’t having difficulty with judgment, changes in behavior or loss of initiative. In addition, the concerned daughter said the mother was experiencing body pain, nausea, dizziness, skin issues, sleep issues, chronic headaches, chest pain and fatigue, difficulty breathing after some exertion, vision problems and weight gain. The mother also has had hysterectomy. The concerned daughter wondered if her mother might be dealing with fibromyalgia. ... I’m not a medical doctor and fibromyalgia very well may be the ultimate... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7070-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7070_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:55:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/727598/162243/researchers-regions</link><title>Researchers Watch Brain Regions Light Up During Hot Flashes</title><description>... The study out of Wayne State University used functional magnetic resonance imaging to look deep inside the brain. This imaging process uses powerful magnets and radio waves that create snapshots of the brain as it functions, allowing for researchers to analyze by measuring and mapping brain activity. ... According to the University of California, San Diego’s Center for Functional MRI , the activity of neurons constantly changes based on what an individual is doing. For instance, simple tasks such as picking up a cup of coffee lights up specific areas of the brain while complex activities, such as understanding language in a conversation, will use other parts of the brain. The brain also lights up in different patterns when you do activities that involve vision, hearing, touch, language and... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7070-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7070_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:56:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/62667/jogging-dementia</link><title>Memory Jogging Puzzles Helpful Tool for People with Dementia</title><description>...   ... The puzzle designs are copied from Norman Rockwell's Saturday Evening Post covers.  "Memory Jogging Puzzles" have large, sturdy pieces that are easy to handle.  These puzzles are made of wood. Cardboard puzzles, with nostalgic themes, are also offered. ...   ... Many people with dementia just like handling the interesting puzzle pieces, feeling the shapes and weight. That is enough. ...   ... But to many people in early-to-mid-Alzheimer's stages , the simple pieces can be enough challenge to assemble that they feel like they've accomplished something (they have), but not so difficult that they get frustrated. They genera... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7070-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7070_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:56:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/c/96140/30480/menopause-memory</link><title>If You Have a Brain Like Swiss Cheese: Menopause and Memory Loss</title><description>... forgetfulness that accompanies it. I have no idea what causes it ... physiologically but sometimes I feel like my brain is Swiss cheese-lots of ... holes and pretty dense. Perhaps like many of you, I forget why I was headed ... into a certain room, forget acquaintances' names when I see them at the post ... office, forget if I fed the dogs, and just about everything in between. You can ... tell me about an appointment I have one minute and the next I am double-booking ... myself because I forgot about the appointment I made ONE MINUTE ago! ...   ... Does this happen to you? It seems to be a common problem, ... and here's how I've tackled it. Many years ago a dear friend, Ann, gave me a ... book, "Write It Down, Make It Happen" by Henriette Anne Klauser. Ann always ... seemed to pack so much into a day and almost never forgot anything, as far as I ... could tell. I was going through a rough patch in my life and was directionless. ... This book changed my life in so many positive... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7070-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7070_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:57:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/25260/toy-trigger</link><title>Toy Tractors Trigger Memories for Alzheimer’s Patients</title><description>... RDO Equipment, of Moorhead, MN specializes in agriculture. The company also specializes in giving back to the community. RDO services a metro area that is divided by the Red River of the North - North Dakota on one side, Minnesota on the other.   While the cities of Fargo, ND and Moorhead, MN are large enough to have an urban flavor, they are still rooted in agriculture, and the cities and small towns surrounding the area are well aware that agriculture is a major fuel for their economies. So, while I'm not likely to buy a tractor at anytime in my life, having agricultural business in the urban mix is just part of the fabric of life here on the plains.   The latest contribution from RDO to the community, and the reason for writing about it here, is that they recently gave 28 miniature tractors to Hospice of the Red River Valley. These tractors, when put in front of Alzheimer's patients, bring light into the eyes of elderly farmers who are under hospice care.   Most Al... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7070-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7070_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:58:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/6509/106456/circumstances</link><title>Look to Circumstances For the Causes of Memory Lapses</title><description>...   ... Spring is just around the corner, and I have put away all my winter clothing. While changing wardrobes, I discovered some surprises. In the back of my closet, I found a lightweight rain-type coat. Note: I've been looking online for almost a year for just such a raincoat and couldn't find what I wanted...WHEN did I buy this coat? WHERE did I buy this coat? HOW LONG have I had this coat? My mind is totally blank... I put it on and it fits perfectly-just had to brush off the dust which had accumulated along the top area above the hanger. Now, I can stop looking for a spring-type coat! I've got one. As a matter of fact, it was a rainy day when I wore it to the hair salon. An attendant hung my coat up for me. I didn't see where she had taken it. When it came time to get my coat, I had a hard time figuring out wh... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>