<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7071">buy LP politics yellowjackets</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:58:59" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7071-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7071_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:59:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/147140/thanksgiving-bipolar</link><title>Politics and Thanksgiving: Are You Ready? The Bipolar Question of the Week</title><description>... It's political season. Thanksgiving is approaching. Interesting convergence ... ... We have a Tea Party movement. We have Occupy Wall Street. We’re mere months away from the Presidential primaries. We all have opinions, we all have expectations. I certainly have mine, and - I really believe this - anyone who entertains a different idea to mine is blind to reality, probably sociopathic, and not worth a microsecond of my time. Okay, I'm wildly exaggerating, but not by much. Let’s be honest about this - I know the rest of you feel the same way I do. Here is what is going on: We have decades of research to show that our genetic makeup influences our gut-level reactions to all manner of things that go on around us. Recent studies strongly suggest that this also applies to our political preferences. One study, involving brain scans on political partisans, found that the participants lit up with pleasurable emotions after being supplied with unflattering facts about their respective ca... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7071-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7071_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:59:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/4535/22869/rate-year</link><title>Breast Cancer Is a Political Issue: Support Candidates Who Support Breast Cancer</title><description>... Elected officials, local, state, and federal, are usually willing to show up to cut the ribbon at the opening of the local breast center or to pin on a pink lapel ribbon to show support. But those things do little to move us forward to getting important answers about breast cancer. You know that breast cancer is a political issue - not just a scientific and medical one.   And there are laws and policies that have been well thought out and have the support of trained advocates across the country. We need to know where our political leaders stand on THOSE issues. Especially on election day, when your congressional Representative or U.S. Senator asks for your support for another term. We must demand they are accountable and the best way to do that is to ask them to support meaningful policies.   Earlier this month the National Breast Cancer Coalition released our interim 2007 Congressional Record of Support for NBCC's Priorities , something we do every year. It includes Member... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7071-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7071_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:00:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/32873/145356/active</link><title>Are You Politically Active?: Question of the Week</title><description>...   ... Would you protest by joining one of these groups or another like them? What topic would you like to see fuel a completely new protest movement? Are you politically active in a different way? How? Occupy Wall Street Movement The Occupy Wall Street Movement was inspired by the so-called Arab Spring demonstrators, young men and women who wanted democracy in Egypt and other countries across the Middle East. This movement started September 17 as a one-day protest against corporate greed. Celebrities visited, labor unions and other groups joined in adding assorted complaints and demands on issues such as global warming, gas prices as well as corporate greed. Most protesters seem to be fueled by the common thread of anger at the wealthy and powerful at the expense of the middle class and less fortunate. Some of the demonstrators have... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7071-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7071_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:01:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/incontinence/c/52/17723/issue-care-drug</link><title>An Important Political Issue: Health Care Costs and Drug Prices</title><description>... Wow, is 2007 almost gone? I always find this time of year an important time to reflect on the year that is winding down and look forward to the upcoming year. This next year is especially important as we head into an election year. I usually shy away from discussing politics but there are hot topics that affect me and my patients.   Probably the most important political issue for me is health care costs. One of the hardest things for me to have to deal with is the cost of treating people. I often find myself being controlled by insurance companies telling what tests I can and can't order and what medicines I can and can't prescribe. I am torn between doing what is right for my patient from a medical standpoint, and what is best from a practical standpoint. I always try to take costs into account, but there is often a conflict of interest and I spend a lot of time writing letters to insurance companies explaining that their "approved" treatment will no... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7071-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7071_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:01:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/1443/151776/negative-campaigns</link><title>Negative Political Campaigns and Anxiety</title><description>...   ... Campaign managers use negative ads to arouse your emotions. They want you to feel agitated because they are counting on this feeling driving you to the polls to cast your vote. According to a report, "Inside the Black Box of Negative Campaign Effects: Three Reasons Why Negative Campaigns Mobilize," by Paul S. Martin, the theory behind negative campaigns is to stimulate the "fight or flight" state and to focus on the fight. Flight, or avoidance, is... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7071-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7071_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:02:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/21749/46146/pollitics</link><title>Chronic Pain and Politics</title><description>... ...   ... Chronic Pain and Politics ...   ... It may not seem that there is a direct relationship between chronic pain and politics, however over the past few years it has become obvious to me that the level of care we receive, the education of medical professionals, and the type and amount of medical research funding can be influenced by the beliefs and experiences of legislators, and are directly impacted by the legislation these legislators approve. ...   ... As Election Day approaches we may all have different feelings about what has been going on in the campaigns, about the different candidates and their positions, or even whether our vote makes a difference at all.    Now, with the economy and financial condition of our country in such a vulnerable state, one might say a crisis, we have the stress related to how that is affecting us and our nation, added to the stress related to the normal election process.    But this hasn’t been a normal campaign season anyway; ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7071-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7071_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:03:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/4535/14206/work-cancer</link><title>Breast Cancer Caucus Plays an Active Role in Politics</title><description>... You must know that next month is Breast Cancer Awareness Month. Everywhere you turn, there will be a sea of pink. Pink stickers on cars, pink pins, pink buildings and bridges, even airplanes painted pink. How nice. I decided years ago that I've had it with pink: I want action. And action is what the National Breast Cancer Coalition is all about. This October we have decided to acknowledge awareness month with more action: we will launch our online Breast Cancer Caucus.   In August I outlined the questions we intend to ask the presidential candidates . The Breast Cancer Caucus will give you a chance to learn what the candidates actually said. You'll be able to see videos they sent, explaining how they would end breast cancer and their written responses to our questions.   The next step is yours. We want you to visit the Breast Cancer Caucus site, and vote for the candidate you believe would do the most to end breast cancer. We also want you to post your own videos on YouT... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7071-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7071_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:03:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/39653/46142/chronic</link><title>Chronic Illnesses and Politics</title><description>... Chronic Illness and Politics ...   ... It may not seem that there is a direct relationship between chronic illnesses, such as Multiple Sclerosis, and politics, however over the past few years it has become obvious to me that the level of care we receive, the education of medical professionals, and the type and amount of medical research funding can be influenced by the beliefs and experiences of legislators, and are directly impacted by the legislation these legislators approve. ...   ... As Election Day approaches we may all have different feelings about what has been going on in the campaigns, about the different candidates and their positions, or even whether our vote makes a difference at all.   Now, with the economy and financial condition of our country in such a vulnerable state, one might say a crisis, we have the stress related to how that is affecting us and our nation, added to the stress related to the normal election process.   But this hasn’t been a normal campa... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7071-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7071_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:04:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/2349/11252/reveal</link><title>Surgeon generals reveal political interference</title><description>... Former Surgeon Generals Dr. Richard H. Carmona, Dr. C. Everett Koop, and Dr. David Satcher have testified that they experienced repeated political interference, attempts to weaken or suppress important public health reports, and dismissal of pertinent health issues by administration officials because of political considerations.   Drs. Carmona, Koop and Satcher are only a few who have come forward to admit that politics often smother science within government and scientific agencies.   More from The New York Times : http://www.nytimes.com/2007/07/11/washington/11surgeon.html?pagewanted=1&amp;_r=2&amp;ref=todayspaper   Best of health, Maria ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7071-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7071_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:05:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/c/3414/11251/reveal</link><title>Surgeon generals reveal political interference</title><description>... Former Surgeon Generals Dr. Richard H. Carmona, Dr. C. Everett Koop, and Dr. David Satcher have testified that they experienced repeated political interference, attempts to weaken or suppress important public health reports, and dismissal of pertinent health issues by administration officials because of political considerations. Drs. Carmona, Koop and Satcher are only a few who have come forward to admit that politics often smother science within government and scientific agencies. More from The New York Times : http://www.nytimes.com/2007/07/11/washington/11surgeon.html?pagewanted=1&amp;_r=2&amp;ref=todayspaper Best of health, Maria Maria Gifford Community Moderator OsteoporosisConnection.com ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>