<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7072">price gibson howard roberts custom</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:06:12" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7072-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7072_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:06:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/news/custom-made-kneecap-replacements-worth-the-price</link><title>Custom-Made Kneecap Replacements Worth the Price</title><description>... Hip and knee replacements are fairly common for osteoarthritis today. But what about the patient with arthritis of the patellofemoral joint (kneecap)? In this study surgeons report the results of using a custom-made patellofemoral implant for 25 patients with isolated patellofemoral arthritis. All patients were 55 years old or younger. The anatomy of the patellofemoral joint is very different from patient to patient. Off-the-shelf implants have never worked well for this problem. Custom made implants to fit the patient's own curves and grooves may be the answer. In this study a computer program was combined with CT scan to map out a three-dimensional (3-D) model of each patient's knee. Information about the femoral groove was used to build a custom cobalt-chromium implant. The femoral groove is located on the lower end of the femur (thigh bone). A healthy patella moves smoothly in this groove. Arthritic changes can wear away the smooth surface of this groove. At the end of three years, ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7072-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7072_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:06:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/9227/prices-extortion</link><title>Medication Prices and International Extortion</title><description>... I don't know anyone who doesn't think the price of medications is too high. Not a single person. Why the prices are so high is another matter altogether. One thing that has always irritated the daylights out of me is that those of us in the U.S., where so many medications are manufactured, often pay the highest prices in the world. Medications are sold to "poorer" countries at lower prices. They're sold to Canada at lower prices because the Canadian government negotiates and regulates prices. It's my contention that the pharmaceutical companies should be selling their products at the same prices, regardless of where they're being shipped. Would people in those poorer countries be paying higher prices? Yes. But in the U.S., there are people who go without medications they can't afford. Others of us, even if we have medical insurance, are spending an increasingly disproportionate amount of our income on medications, and it's getting worse, no... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7072-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7072_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:07:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/3900/17353/robert-food-world</link><title>Interview with Robert Fisher -- Food Allergic World Traveler</title><description>... I had an opportunity to talk with Robert Fisher, professional travel writer and editor at Frommers.com. Bob and I could have been separated at birth we have so many allergies in common, but most inspiring is how he's safely traveled the world for the past 30 or so years with allergies. For anyone who has allergies or is the parent of a child with allergies, you know how frightening it can be to eat somewhere new, leaving your safe home base. Below, Robert tells me some of his experiences, both the good, the bad and the itchy.     SLOANE MILLER: What are your allergies?   ROBERT FISHER: I'm anaphylactically allergic to peanuts and legumes like green peas, as well as having asthma and the usual environmental allergies to pollen, dust , dogs and cats. SM: Wow, just like me! Do you have your Epi-Pen and Benadryl with you?   RF: Yes and prednisone as well.   SM: We're like twins! I have the same medications in my purse and I always carry th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7072-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7072_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:07:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/news-43426-5.html</link><title>Increased Patient Share of Prescription Costs Negatively Impacts Drug Treatment and Adherence</title><description>... The cost of prescription drugs is a major topic of conversation amongst Migraineurs and other patients who need prescription medications . Even for those who have insurance that covers medications, the amount paid by the patient has increased to consume a disproportionate amount of patient income and has left many patients with difficult medical and financial choices to make. Part of this phenomenon is coverage limits that affect the number of doses of triptans that are covered per month, a number that has recently been decreasing. A review of previous studies indicates that an increase in prescription drug cost sharing is associated with a decrease in drug spending and use of pharmacies; and for some chronic conditions, higher cost sharing is associated with greater use of expensive medical services (doctor appointments, emergency care, hospitalization, etc.), according to an article in the July 4, 2007, issue of JAMA . “… with recent increases in pharmacy spending, p... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7072-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7072_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:08:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/17629/migraine-prices-08</link><title>Migraine Medication Prices and Election ‘08</title><description>... One of the biggest complaints Migraineurs have is access to Migraine abortive medications, especially the triptans - Imitrex, Maxalt, Zomig, etc.   The problem isn't getting a doctor to prescribe triptans. Doctors prefer to prescribe abortive medications that can actually stop a Migraine in its tracks rather than pain medications that can do nothing but mask the pain for a few hours.   So, what IS the problem? It all comes down to the price of triptans. Triptan prices range from $18 to $70 per dose, an average of $25 per dose, and Migraineurs frequently use two doses to treat a single Migraine attack. This presents us with two main problems: Those without insurance often have problems affording triptans. Insurance companies are limiting the number of doses of triptans allowed per month. The insurance companies are being very short-sighted about this issue. None of us would mind them limiting our triptans IF they could also limit the number of Migraine... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7072-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7072_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:09:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/838696/162143/brand-topamax-reasonable</link><title>How to get brand Topamax at a reasonable price?</title><description>...   ... I have health insurance (actually primary &amp; secondary at the moment), but the best anyone will do is a 25% discount on brand which still leaves it priced at $975. I've gone through exhaustive conversations with Express-Scripts &amp; Humana and they just don't seem to offer brand at a reasonable price. Am I not saying the right thing to the insurance companies? Teri Robert mentioned the MedWatch division of the FDA, adjusting ones bioavailability regimine &amp; or finding a pharmacy who only uses 1 generic Topamax company. Can anyone expand on those options more? Is there a smarter route I could be taking such as who is the highly... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7072-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7072_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:09:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/9778/prices-patent</link><title>Migraine abortive medications - triptan prices and patent expirations</title><description>... Especially with the rising costs of health care (even for those of us with insurance), we have frequent discussions regarding the cost of triptans, generic triptans, and new developments. There has also been recent discussion on combining triptans and NSAIDS. Some Migraineurs have found that taking an NSAID along with a triptan offers improved Migraine relief. Trexima, a combination of sumatriptan (Imitrex) and naproxen sodium (Aleve) has been developed and clinical trials conducted.   The trial and safety data are now under review, and Trexima could appear on the U.S. market by the end of 2007. For more information about this combination medication, see Study Finds Sumatriptan-Naproxen Combination More Effective against Migraine Attacks . On the issue of triptan cost -- here are the average prices for one dosage of each of the triptans in tablet form: Triptan Pkg Price Price/Dose Imitrex, 100mg $ 179.23/9 $19.91 Maxalt, 10 mg $107.44/6 $17.91 Zomig, 5 mg $5... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7072-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7072_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:10:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/5949/118988/cognitive</link><title>Brain Exercises May Slow Cognitive Decline – But Not Without a Price</title><description>... A new study published today in the online issue of the journal Neurology shows that doing mentally stimulating activities such as crossword puzzles, reading and listening to the radio may slow the decline of cognitive abilities and even prolong the time until dementia begins, but once Alzheimer’s disease sets in, its progression may be faster.  You may be wondering what this has to do with chronic pain.  Actually, quite a lot.  Many of us who have chronic pain illnesses like fibromyalgia and ME/CFS struggle with cognitive functioning problems such as memory loss and difficulty thinking and problem solving.  It can get so bad that some patients say the cognitive problems bother them even more than the pain.  Study Methods and Results Researchers evaluated the mental activities of 1,157 people age 65 or older who did not have dementia at the start of the nearly 12-year study. Participants answered questions about how often they participated in mental activi... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7072-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7072_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:10:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/19231/08-vote-care</link><title>Election '08 - Vote for Better Migraine and Headache Care</title><description>...     Some people have said they don't vote because "one vote doesn't make any difference." A single vote may not make much difference, but if you added up all the people who don't vote for that reason, it could make a huge difference. With Migraines and chronic headaches, getting to the polls can be difficult, but if that's a problem for you, request an absentee ballot.   Casting an informed vote is both important and challenging. Tracking where the various candidates stand can be confusing. The HealthCentral Network is going to help with that problem.   Drum roll, please...   Today, we have launched our Healthcare '08 site to track the candidates' positions on issues such as healthcare reform, the uninsured, drug prices, prevention, technology, and stem cell research. Here's some information from a press release issued today: ARLINGTON, VA- Health care - and the candidate who can make affordable, ethical, and quality decisi... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7072-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7072_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:11:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/ibd/c/2623/17424/medical-cost-control</link><title>Medical Cost Control</title><description>... Anyone out there been hospitalized lately? Last year, I was hospitalized with a 103 degree fever after a trip to Tahiti left me with a rare case of pneumonia. For a week, specialists of all kinds huddled over me wondering what was wrong. I was tested for all kinds of tropical infectious diseases, gastrointestinal parasites, even AIDs, while getting a steady diet of intravenous antibiotics. That did a number on my stomach - nothing sets off my IBD quicker than antibiotics. On the fourth day my fever broke and the doctors agreed to discharge me, even though they couldn't figure out what caused my illness. My General Practitioner, however, was on the alert. During a follow up visit she did a blood test and figured out it was a rare type of pneumonia. Fortunately, the antibiotic cocktail I'd been injected with at the hospital included the right drug to kill the pneumonia bug, so I recovered anyway.   But this isn't about me - it's about the bills. Can anyone figur... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>