<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7073">buy bausack</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:12:10" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7073-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7073_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:12:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/7243/15167/start-local</link><title>Three Reasons You Need to Start Buying Local</title><description>... The movement to buy local, healthy food is spreading across the country and gaining momentum - and that is a very good thing.   It is driven by several factors - one, the taste of fresh, local food is just so much better than food that has traveled far. Two, it often costs less because it is seasonally produced and the food is generally abundant and there are few transportation costs. And third is the state of our planet and global warming. As we know, driving food across the country and using gallons of gasoline to do it contributes to our climate conditions and the damages the planet.     This week I attended a meeting that dealt with the need for reducing our demand for oil. There was a lot of discussion about Middle East tensions and global warming and how we all needed to "do something" to make a change. Of course, there were suggestions for driving less, flying less and avoiding petroleum-based plastics. I began to think that if we became active in the l... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7073-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7073_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:12:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/nbcam-3383-143.html</link><title>October 14th: Donate and Drive</title><description>... think about purchasing a breast cancer plate if one is available in ... your state. The few extra dollars you spend will benefit breast ... cancer research. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7073-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7073_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:13:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/59238/143325/convince-parents</link><title>Do kids convince parents to buy junk foods?</title><description>... Mom, please get me that new cereal with the special mix ins! ... Mom, I want a hamburger, fries and a soda.....now! ... Mom, I want to get that new super duper chewy snack I just saw on TV! ...   ... This may be going on in your house on a regular basis.  Kids get bombarded with cartoons and celebrity images associated with the latest food, snack or drink.  Most of these items have little nutritional value, and pack a hefty dose of trans or saturated fat, salt, sugar and are loaded with unhealthy calories.  And your kids want them....no, they demand them so much so, that researchers have acknowledged this "nag factor."  It's identified as the unrelenting request of children to have parents buy the very items they see non-stop on TV, in videos and in print ads.  Researchers at the Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health have spent some time looking at this phenomenon. ...   ... The researchers conclude that there is indeed a huge push f... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7073-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7073_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:14:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/coping-with-treatment-3169-143.html</link><title>Chemo Incognito: Everything You Need to Know About Buying a Wig</title><description>... A little more than one year ago, I was bald – compliments of chemotherapy for breast cancer. It was a tough time for me, losing the hair I really liked and adjusting to a changed appearance. It was not tough, however, to determine what I would do about my bald head. I knew before I lost my first strand of hair that I would need to cover my head – just as some women know instantly that going bald is their best option. So I did some research, did some shopping, and proudly bought a wig. If you plan to wear a wig, consider these tips before your own search for hair begins. • Before you lose your hair, try on a variety of wigs (pay attention to size – if the wig bends your ears, it’s too big), investigate colors, and make a purchase so your wig is ready and waiting when you need it. Hair loss typically occurs two weeks after the first chemotherapy treatment. • Talk to cancer survivors, hair stylists, and social workers for shopping advice and suggestio... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7073-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7073_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:15:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/110/10787/buy-pump-user</link><title>Should you buy an insulin pump from a previous user?</title><description>... ... Anyone buying a pump from another pumper ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7073-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7073_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:15:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/162481/66261</link><title>where do i buy chia?</title><description>... where do i buy chia? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7073-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7073_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:16:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/185392/98662</link><title>where i can buy Actoplus Met?</title><description>... where i can buy Actoplus Met? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7073-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7073_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:17:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/incontinence/c/question/261088/149415</link><title>Can I buy Cranbury AZO online. Was told here in town that it is no longer available</title><description>... Cranbury AZO can I buy it online ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7073-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7073_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:17:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/437708/108574</link><title>can i buy loratab from this site</title><description>... can i buy loratab from this site ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7073-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7073_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:18:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/question/319108/73337</link><title>BEST BRAND OF HYDROQUINONE FORMULA TO BUY?</title><description>... WHAT IS THE BEST BRAND FORMULA OF HYDROQUINONE TO BUY? ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>