<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7075">zimerman chopin ballade</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:20:07" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7075-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7075_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:20:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/question/952716/124713</link><title>What causes MS patients' sudden, involuntary walking sideways or backwards? (Most frequently when tired or stressed?) Thanks so very much.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7075-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7075_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:20:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/334470/119917/creativity</link><title>Bipolar illness and Creativity</title><description>...   ... I used to believe that because I was bipolar, the manic highs were providing me with the impetus to do really creative things, and that if i were being treated, all of that creativity would simply disappear. ...   ... Speaking from my own personal experience, this is simply not the case. I have been creative all of my life, but without some sort of management mechanism, it was essentially wasted because it was never properly channeled. During the period in which I was under management with medications and therapy, I slowly began to realize that I still had the ability to be creative, but with proper care, I was able to actually follow through with my creative endeavors. ...   ... To shorten the story, I completed my second CD. The first was a musical selection of Operatic arias and Ballads, the second...Jazz and Blues (Go figure. Only a Bipolar could swing from Opera to Blues.)  It's been great fun and it was ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7075-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7075_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:21:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/93829/32393/death-fear</link><title>Death Fear</title><description>...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ... Death Fear ...   ...   ...   ...   ... Coins fall in a ... Myriad of colors, as ... Confetti thrown at a ... surprise party- ... From a place that ... could be heaven ... My thoughts, ... broadcasted aloud. ...   ... Listen ... None but a ... celebration- ... A surprise is to see ... the dancing waters ... Rise and fall to the ... tune of Chopin’s waltzes. ... Drop a coin in a ... fountain, no matter how fluorescent the color. ...   ... My thoughts are ... muted, as ... Cotton fills each ... hollow space in my brain ... A strange and ... inexplicable sensation this is, ... Forever ... misunderstood-as the hands ... Of my digital watch, ... I would turn ... If it deemed ... possible- and count backwards fifty-one years ... A power struggle, it ... would be, against the romances of nature ... . ... Every clock ticks as ... Each hand, second by ... second advances, ... Carrying me to the ... unknown? ... Ashes to ashes, to ... hell or heaven, or could there even be an ...   Afterlife ... At all? ...   ... Coins fall from where ... could be heaven. ... I hear strange voices ... within a charnel house, ... Ever... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7075-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7075_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:21:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/20554/faces</link><title>Six Faces</title><description>... In my previous blog, I reported on a couple of what can best be described as teary moments that happened to me, even though real men don’t cry. I am in the middle of a massive website spring house-cleaning involving more than 300 articles, of which only about half will make the final cut onto my new site. A few weeks ago, reading my memoirs for the first time in years, my breathing failed on me. I found myself having to gulp down oxygen as painful memories came flooding back. There I was, at age six, a happy kid. What happened? Last week involved sorting through the “Famous People” section of my site. Twenty-one articles. All but one made the cut. Another got moved to a different section. Of those 19, four involve psychiatrists and three focus on themes rather personalities. Two articles deal with a pairing of individuals, of which one of them probably was not mentally ill. So if my math serves me correctly, we have 13 individuals in my gallery. So there I was, re-forma... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7075-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7075_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:22:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/59238/158500/theatre-obesity</link><title>New York Theatre May Hold Answer to Obesity</title><description>...   ... ... Bill Germanakos ... Jim Germankos ... Nicole Michalik ... Alfredo Dinten ... Suzanne Mendonca ... Erik Chopin ... Tara Costa ... ...   ... If you watch TV and weight loss shows, you should know all of these people.  They were contestants on The Biggest Loser, some of them winners from different seasons.  If you are wondering what they are doing, grouped together in this list?  They are now stars on Broadway.  Well, not quite, but they are performing in a theatre for a limited run, in a production called The Diet Show.   Presented and co-written by comedian Gilbert Godfrey, each contestant describes their personal battle with weight and their triumphs or failures before and after the NBC expeirence.  In the case of Mr. Chopin, who regained all 214 pounds lost on The Biggest Loser, you learn that keeping weight off after the show was not a given.  Alfredo Dinton, another contestant, shares that “if you don’t cut the pizza pie, it&amp;rsq... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7075-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7075_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:22:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/162250/sensitive-bipolar-question-week</link><title>Are You Highly Sensitive? - The Bipolar Question of the Week</title><description>...   ... There is nothing like being amongst my tribe, but introverts such as myself typically face special challenges. It’s not that we’re not social or sociable - it’s just that being around people for extended periods of time can be emotionally draining. On one hand, I will get excited and want to join in on everything. On the other, I will need to chill. ...   ... Fortunately, the didgeridoo people understand. We are, after all, a singular breed of who enjoy sitting alone in a quiet place blowing into a piece of pipe. ...   ... I’ve written about introversion a number of times here at HealthCentral, but this week I came across a related issue involving “highly sensitive people” (HSP). I started reading and - oh my! - this sounds like me. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7075-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7075_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:23:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/15/161111/music-depression-oppression</link><title>Music, Depression, Oppression, Salvation</title><description>...   ... A few days ago, the young Korean violinist, Ji-Hae Park, gave a TED Talk, entitled, The Violin and My Long Dark Night of the Soul . Ms Park began with an exuberant rendition of Vivaldi. Then she put down her violin and revealed that she had once suffered from severe depression and had been in total despair. ...   ... Depressives, of course, are drawn to music and the arts and literature. The condition informs their work. Writing in the Opinionator blog on the NY Times earlier this year, composer Keeril Makan disclosed that “the act of composing is in a dynamic relationship with my emotional life.” ...   ... But something else seemed to be going on with Ms Park. “The violin,” she related, “which meant everything to me, became a grave burden to me.” Ms Park did not elaborate, but we can take an educated guess that the musical prodigy career path that she had been pushed into had taken her to the breaki... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7075-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7075_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:24:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/59238/129316/tested-strategies</link><title>Weight Loss Strategies for Treating Obesity</title><description>...   ... If you haven't already, lose the liquid calories and make water, zero calorie flavored waters and unsweetened teas your beverages of choice.  Check out my past blog on milk to see which milk you'd like to include in your daily liquid intake.  One or two servings of 1% or fat free milk are a good way to get vitamin D and calcium. ...   ... Use tall skinny glasses whenever possible.  When we visually see a taller thinner glass, we tend to pour and drink less liquid which can be helpful when enjoying alcoholic or calorie laden beverages. ...   ... Nix serving any dishes "family style" except for an undressed salad or fruit salad.  Having large platters of food on the table encourages second helpings even when you're already full ...   ... Never use tablespoons , even for soups.  Using a teaspoon slow... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7075-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7075_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:25:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/72218/151757/ra</link><title>Celebrating RA Poetry and Community Creativity</title><description>...   ... ...   ... On HealthCentral, we will celebrate the talents of our own RA community and create a place to share our thoughts, our words, our poems throughout the month of April.  To get us started, I created a poem which features a side of rheumatoid arthritis.  ...   ... light ... by lisa emrich ...   ... rain beats down on the windowsill ... heat rises from the concrete ... early morning stretches ... undo glitches in ... my toes, ... as ... time stalls, ... outside children play ... in the sun rays and laugh while ... dawn drips down their faces and smiles ...   ... a gasp ... rings out while ... tangles twist about ... hands, knees click and clack, ... ravished joints mostly seek solace ... in the comfort of heat ... teasing light ... i love the ... sun ...   ...   ... In looking for inspiration,... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7075-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7075_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:25:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/9032/19156/anxiety-ways-soothe</link><title>Anxiety, anyone? Ways to Soothe Yourself</title><description>... "Music has charms to soothe a savage breast"-- Congreve Or an anxious one.   I was invited to attend a Sunday matinee performance of the 92nd street Y Lyrics and Lyricists series. The 92nd Street YMHA is one of the oldest and finest cultural and community centers the city has to offer. They have everything from religious services, a gym with a pool [very rare in NYC], auditoriums that feature music and lectures; one of the best literary series in the city -- all within affordable price points.   On this afternoon, the program was featuring the works of lyricist Sammy Kahn . If you don't know his name you definitely know his music: "Love and Marriage," "Three Coins in the Fountain," and "Call Me Irresponsible" are just a few of his most recognizable hits. The man was a hit monster really. You can listen to a podcast of Sammy from the 1972 show he did at the Y, which revitalized his career. While in the audience, listening ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>