<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7081">translation bloopers</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:47:14" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7081-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7081_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:47:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/148449/christmas-stories</link><title>Don’t Sweat the Small Stuff: Bloopers Can Add to Family Christmas Stories</title><description>...   ... Probably more worrisome for caregivers is how their aging loved ones will make it through the family events. Will Dad be sleepy from his medications or agitated from all from all of the excitement? Will Mom’s touchy stomach allow her to eat her favorite foods or will you spend the evening wondering if you need to make her a nutritional shake to drink while everyone else eats?   Will Aunty throw a tantrum over the fact that no one made white chocolate fudge this year and, well, Christmas isn’t Christmas without white chocolate fudge? ...   ... We can plan ourselves silly, but the unexpected will always occur. The only remedy... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7081-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7081_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:47:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/77/20111/research</link><title>Cardiology and Translational Research</title><description>... Like the rubric that has made the rounds for years "evidence based" medicine this term has become popular in medical schools and in the press. The former term, "evidence based" medicine, was meant to demand proof that each treatment worked on the basis of experimental protocols. Actually medicine was always based on some form of evidence, but the scientific method was not as well supported by new ways to look at things. Before 1900, information disseminated from one doctor, or country to another slowly, with a few journals, but more by word of mouth. If a doctor found something that worked for a disease better than prior therapies, he or she would tell as many other doctors as possible, or write an article in a journal. The therapy would be "picked up" slowly, and "tested" by others who could confirm (or deny) that the therapy worked. The first large scale trials using the relatively new field of statistics did not occur until the mid twen... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7081-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7081_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:48:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/news/translating-science-into-effective-knee-rehabilitation-strategies</link><title>Translating Science into Effective Knee Rehabilitation Strategies</title><description>... Injuries to the anterior cruciate ligament (ACL) of the knee have become fairly common, especially in athletes. Medical professionals agree that rehabilitation for ACL injuries requires a structured program of exercises. But there is some debate about which kinds of exercises are best. Studies like this one help rehabilitation professionals translate scientific findings about knee movement into effective ACL rehab programs. The ACL connects the femur bone in your thigh with the tibia bone in your lower leg. The ACL also keeps a check on how far the tibia can slide forward--or translate --under the femur bone. The further forward the tibia translates, the bigger the force on the ACL. Some types of exercise cause the tibia to translate more than others. The authors measured how far the tibia moved during two forms of exercise. One form is called open kinetic chain exercise , where the arm or leg is free to move in various directions. The example in this study is the standard knee extension... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7081-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7081_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:49:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/110/22475/status-stem-cells</link><title>Stem Cell Research For Diabetes: Will Success With Mice Translate?</title><description>... I recently received the following e-mail: "I'm a 17 year old diabetic who has been following the research and hoping that stem cells will be legalized. I haven't had any recent updates on how things are going, and I was curious if you could fill me in? Last I heard there was a very small conversion rate and a very very slim success rate. I'm just a sitting duck right now and know a lot about this already, but always trying to learn more. Thats why I am hoping also to get to try some experimental things after I turn 18 this month." My reply: "I understand your impatience and concern about your diabetes. "However, you must be realistic, and understand that the use of stem cells for treatment of diabetes is still a hope for the future rather than anything likely to be useful in the next few years. I wrote recently about a tantalizing report of stem cell success for diabetes in mice. This research demonstrated that indeed stem cells could be manipulated to cont... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7081-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7081_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:49:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/58426/42173/translate</link><title>How Physical Fitness Can Translate Into Personal Growth.</title><description>...   ... Leni, a mother of 2 and one of my current clients, came to me after one of my classes and told me that working out is teaching and motivating her to push herself beyond her comfort zone.  She credits her pursuit of physical fitness with inspiring her to step outside her comfort zone as she creates new boundaries for her life both mentally and physically. ...   ... How true and how simple!!  At the root of the word " growth " lies the meaning of growing past already established boundaries.  My 6 month old niece is teething right now and she i... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7081-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7081_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:50:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/531048/57052</link><title>Can someone translate?</title><description>...   ... I have the MRI report which is like reading chinese....here is what is says; ...   ... L4/5 Level: Bulging Disk ...   ... L5/S1: Anterior offset with unroofing of the disk whichis broad based and results in bilateral foraminal encroachment. ...   ... Possible L5 pars defets to account for the anterior offset which can be correlated with lumbar spine x-rays including oblique views. ...   ... Can anyone tell me what this means? ...   ... Thank you, ... D ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7081-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7081_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:50:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/genital-herpes/c/question/522677/120562</link><title>Lost in Translation!</title><description>...   ... Since then (and even before) we have never had any recurrance or possiblities. Until two days ago. Today I went to the doc's and she confirmed that I had GH. Which of course makes us think that the 1st doc was correct. DH is planning on being tested. ...   ... My DH and were not virgins before we were married, and we have always been faithful to each other. Quite frankly at this point, it doesnt matter who gave it to who. ...   ... So here is my question: if we both are infected, do we still need to be careful and protected? ...   ... We are not having any more children and we are in a commited, monogamous relationship. We... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7081-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7081_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:51:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/469704/64164</link><title>translation please</title><description>... what does ER an PR immunopositive mean. Im wondering exactly what immunopositve means ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7081-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7081_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:51:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/question/31626/30023</link><title>can anyone translate this for me</title><description>... my mri impresson says i have a dislocated menisci bilaterally.subchondral signal changes in the temporal bone articular eminences suggests a degree of chronic impaction or osteoarthritic type change . ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7081-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7081_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:52:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/727598/156247/translates</link><title>'Can Do' Attitude Translates to Healthier Lifestyle</title><description>... A new study out of Melbourne Institute of Applied Economic and Social Research involved data from 7,000 people that had been collected in the Household, Income and Labour Dynamics in Australia Survey. This data included information on each individual’s diet, exercise and personality type. The researchers found that people who believed that they were in control of their own lives through their actions actually ate a better diet, exercised less, smoked less and didn’t engage in binge drinking. ... The study also found that men and women have different takes on how a healthy lifestyle benefits them. The researchers found that men wanted to see physical results based on their healthy choices. However, women were more likely to enjoy leading a healthy lifestyle. ... Dr. Debo... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>