<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7083">I'm on the road again</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:59:22" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7083-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7083_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:59:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/dailydose/</link><title>Drowsy Driving</title><description>... 53 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7083-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7083_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:00:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/27148/138353/avoid-summer</link><title>How to Avoid Back and Neck Pain During a Summer Road Trip</title><description>...   ... Adjust the Seat : Seat adjustment is critical for avoiding pain on the road. The first thing to do when you buttocks hit the car seat is to adjust the seat to fit you. Starting from the top, the headrest should be centered squarely on the center of your head. Properly adjusted headrests do prevent whi... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7083-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7083_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:00:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/96/38993/giving-winding</link><title>Care Giving: The Long and Winding Road</title><description>... ... A Reflux Mom wrote to me: “By nature I think I am a pretty positive person. Lately I feel very stuck in anger/bitterness about the fact that it has taken so long and so many doctors telling us things were OK before my son was diagnosed with Gastroesophageal Reflux Disease (GERD) . I know I am not helping myself or anyone else with resentful feelings. I am going to seek help but I wanted to know from someone who has traveled down this road what you found helpful. If you had similar emotions, what helped? I can't change the past but I sure am tired of people in the medical profession letting me down. I don’t want to stay angry but I am.” ...   ... Taking care of an infant or child with a chronic condition such as GERD can lead to exhaustion and burn out. ( See our Parent's Guide to GERD for help! ) Believe me; I have certainly shared your thoughts and feeling.    At times, I still do to some degree. I guess there are many layers. During the search for a d... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7083-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7083_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:01:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/2998/13895/slip-road</link><title>A Slip On The Road of Recovery</title><description>... I know the road of recovery is not a straight shot road. I do consider myself in recovery--not recovered--as the process of recovery requires conscious awareness, medication and therapy compliance, and taking the time to practice self-care. Set-backs will occur sometimes, regardless of just how diligent I try to be. For me, there are no guarantees for the depression, anxiety and PTSD, just the willingness and commitment to be healthy. And for great chunks of time, I am doing great!   I am not filled with "gloom and doom" of my mental health diagnoses, but rather do my best to understand what it will require of me to not let these illnesses consume and/or dictate my life.   Currently, I am simply in one of those times where the emotional toll of experiencing life unfolding around me is chipping away at my own coping skills. I am a bit tired, and feeling a bit thwarted, by the resurgence of old symptoms.   I have been working closely with my therapist, but this thera... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7083-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7083_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:02:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/89/37766/zebras-robbery</link><title>Rutted Roads, Zebras and a Robbery</title><description>...   ... Last Friday was Nani Nani, a national Tanzanian holiday celebrating the agricultural communities, so I had hoped to sneak away for a safari, an activity I love, since we had a long break! I think I know who stole the money. I felt very violated, but ultimately prayed that whoever did steal it would use it for a worthy cause. ... But I decided that I needed to go on this break anyway. This really was my first "playtime" since I've been here (2 ½ months) and it suddenly seems that my time has become VERY short!!! ...   ... I left Friday morning and was excited to find there were only 4 of us going (plus a guide and a cook). The 3 other people were young women, volunteers from Great Britiain, working in a different program in another village. We drove many hours past Bomas (a Boma is a small cluster of primitive rondelas, ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7083-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7083_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:03:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/6509/102104/apnea-dementia</link><title>Sleep Apnea, My Road to Dementia</title><description>...   ... At least ten years ago, I fell asleep at the wheel of my car. I was less than two miles from home. At twelve thirty in the afternoon, I was returning from Vacation Bible School where I had spent an active morning teaching. In the back seat, I had precious cargo, my only grandchild and a young niece. I can remember singing children's hymns with them as we made our way home. And then it happened. Suddenly, an impenetrable sleepiness hit me. I put down the window, sang a little louder. We had only a little way to go; I knew we'd be okay. And then, I heard someone next to me blow their horn three times. It jarred me awake in time to avoid hitting the car in front of me which had put on its brakes. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7083-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7083_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:03:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/962/88961/portable-nebulizer</link><title>Take Your Asthma on the Road with a Portable Nebulizer</title><description>...   ... Nebulizers are used commonly in infants and young children, who are too young to use a metered dose inhaler reliably. But sometimes older children and adults can benefit from using a nebulizer too. ...   ... Unfortunately, until recently, most nebulizers were large, loud and a pain in the neck to travel with. As AC-powered electric devices, they also needed a power source. But now there is another solution. ...   ... There are a few newer varieties of truly portable nebulizers called mini-nebulizers. These tiny nebulizers are not only small, they are battery-operated and much quieter. And yet, they still get the job done in dispensing your asthma medication. ...   ... Some Example... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7083-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7083_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:04:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/896502/115186/cycling</link><title>Trying Something New - Off-Road Cycling</title><description>... The weather is really hot and humid where I live, but the lure of the great outdoors won this weekend as my friend, Sondra, and I went biking. Sondra and I used to ride 13 miles most mornings for about a year before she moved to another part of town. During these early morning treks, we’d weave our way through different neighborhoods, adding mileage by zipping into cul de sacs. Since Sondra’s move, my riding has been limited mostly to the gym’s stationary bikes so Saturday’s ride was not only a good workout, but also a chance to reacquaint myself with a hobby that I’ve always really enjoyed.     But this time, our outing had a twist to it -- we decided to do a little off-road riding, something I haven’t really done before. Sondra and I (along with her dog) went to a great park in the area and explored the trails. Ultimately, we did slightly more than 5 miles that day. Even though it was less mileage than we usually do, the ride had it... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7083-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7083_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:05:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/question/570000/125899</link><title>25 y/o son diag with TS OCD and possible manic depressive as 12 yr old. Quit taking meds at 18 and managing fine. Now he has become extremely out of control when driving. Road Rage, extreme, help</title><description>... today he drove with my other 2 children and after 5 hours on the road they are terrified and horrified. Someone almost tried to fight son. It has been excalating over time. This may have been his worst day ever. Otheriwise he is either sleepy, sick, working, or sitting around with girlfriend..how can I get an adult child to get help? I am thinking that perhaps I will give him a deadline to seek help, and if he doesn't I want nothing more to do with him. That is how extreme. He won't talk, cusses anyone out who tries to talk with him or ask him to stop. It is always other drivers fault and anyone questioning him is told to shut the __ up. He drives 60 miles daily RT for work. I am worried sick. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7083-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7083_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:05:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/7976/live-road-toto-were</link><title>Live From the Road: Toto, We're Not in Southern California Anymore</title><description>... I am on the last leg of my flight from San Diego. Sometime earlier, I had boarded the Red-eye Special to Charlotte, where I connected with a flight to Hartford/Springfield. The plane is well into its descent as it clears Long Island Sound and hits the Connecticut shore. Looking down, a strange sight hits me – strange white stuff on the ground. Whatever can it be? I get out of the plane and something totally weird happens: I instantly lose my California tan. Suddenly, I look like I did four months ago, a skinny version of the Pillsbury Doughboy. I’ve heard of the airlines losing luggage, but losing a tan? You mean I risked skin cancer all this time for nothing? My mother was supposed to greet me and say something like, “I nearly didn’t recognize you – why you look like a bald version of Harry Belafonte.” That would have been my cue to say, “Southern California is over-rated. The good weather lasts only 51 weeks of the year.” The automatic doors to the terminal slide open and the first da... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>