<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7084">Burn after reading review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:06:07" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7084-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7084_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:06:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/445363/140970</link><title>What is the best male enhancement pill. I have read multiple reviews and dont know which are a scam and which really work? Also what can help me with pre-mature ejaculation?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7084-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7084_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:06:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/92/16803/zone-diet</link><title>Popular Diets Reviewed: The Zone Diet</title><description>... I remember when the Zone Diet rose to popularity – I think it was a huge part of the re-emergence of the low carb craze. I was in graduate school at the time and one of our assignments was to research a popular diet, follow it and then critique the plan. I chose the Zone Diet. Written by Dr. Barry Sears, a biochemist, the Zone Diet is a low carb, high protein diet based on ratios of carbohydrate to protein and fat that Dr. Sears claims will produce optimum fat-burning and weight loss. The plan divides each meal into proportions, 40 percent of your calories should come from carbohydrates, 30 percent from protein and 30 percent from fat. What to Eat Each meal and snack should follow these ratios and include carbohydrate, protein and fat. Carbohydrates should come from mostly fruits and vegetables, beans and whole grains. Proteins should be lean meats and you should eat no more than 3 to 4 ounces per meal and 1 ounce per snack. Fats should come from healthy sources like olive and ca... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7084-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7084_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:07:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/92/15814/diets-atkins</link><title>Popular Diets Reviewed: The New Atkins Revolution</title><description>... Read all of our reviews of popular diets .   The Atkins diet has been around since the 1970’s but it was the re-release of the Dr. Atkins New Diet Revolution over 10 years ago that generated the low-carb craze that is pervasive in our society today. According to the New Atkins Diet, people are overweight because they eat too many carbohydrate-rich foods. By restricting carbohydrates, the body will burn fat, including fat stores, for energy. During metabolism, the body burns carbohydrates first and then moves onto fat. With the Atkins diet, there are very few carbohydrates to burn and so the body mainly burns fat and fat stores for energy. The metabolism of fat releases ketones into the body. A build up of this by-product will put the body into a ketogenic state or ketosis resulting in a decreased appetite and therefore a decrease in food intake. A ketogenic state also occurs in people with uncontrolled diabetes and during starvation. A build up of ketones over time can disturb... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7084-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7084_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:07:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/78/69441/life-metastasis</link><title>Book Review: Not Done Yet: Living Through Breast Cancer</title><description>... – Not Done Yet: Living Through Breast Cancer ... Laurie Kingston has posted regularly to this site, offering information and hope to all of us—and particularly to those who’ve had a metastasis, or “mets,” as insiders call it. Laurie, a 41-year-old Canadian mother of two young boys, began blogging almost immediately after her diagnosis of breast cancer in January 2006. Ten months later, the cancer had spread to her liver; she had “mets.” And she kept on writing. ...   ... ...   ... Now, Laurie has pulled her blogposts into a 2-year journal detailing her life as a woman with cancer: the good, the bad, the ugly, AND the beautiful. Not Done Yet: Living Through Breast Cancer is a candid look at motherhood, friendship, being a wi... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7084-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7084_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:08:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/28496/46450/things-told</link><title>Nik's Review: The Things I Wish My Mother Would Have Told Me</title><description>... The Things I Wish My Mother Would Have Told Me is a play that makes no attempt to conform to traditional rules of drama. While the play does progress through a story and uses many common dramatic devices - music, lighting, and props - it seems to be more acute than the typical Broadway show. Perovetz has a journey to relate and, not for a single moment, does she deviate onto another topic. Her mother died of breast cancer when Mia Perovetz was 11 and it took her a dozen or more years to figure out what it really meant. She struggled and suffered, and was only recently able to discover who she was without her mother. The play begins shakily with a lot of mood to which the audience is not able to relate. The story had not progressed far enough to warrant the depth of feeling seen in Mia's acting. But it's not long before the plot catches up with the dramatic opening. And once it does, Perovetz's play delivers on a level very rarely touched by any single story or any single experience. I... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7084-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7084_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:08:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/73302/46345/review</link><title>Book Review: The Diving Bell and the Butterfly</title><description>... The Diving Bell and the Butterfly ... was written by Jean-Dominque Bauby (1997) ...   ... I first heard about this book through word of mouth on Multiple Sclerosis blogs.  Why would someone who has MS read this particular book?  While this is not a book about MS, it is a book about extreme disability. It does capture the indomitable spirit of someone who is basically trapped by their body.  It is the memoir of a man who is completely paralyzed except for the use of one of his eyes to blink.  It is through this blinking that this book exists at all. ...   ... I suppose I am one who always insists upon lying on a psychological bed of nails.  I knew that reading this book would be emotionally cathartic for me.  I have a disease which impairs my movement.  I wanted to read about how this man survived not being able to move at all. ...   ... Here is a short synopsis of his story.  Jean Bauby had been a successful editor for the Fre... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7084-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7084_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:09:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/75934/20648/blog-iii-fda</link><title>Botox Blog Part III: The Reality, and The FDA Review</title><description>... As a dermatologist, it thrills me to see how happy Botox makes my patients, whether I'm treating them medically for excessive sweating or cosmetically for wrinkles.   Excessive sweating is no laughing matter. To those whose personal and professional lives, and clothing, it ruins, Botox often seems like a miracle. Take Jodie*, who told me that my Botox treatment of her underarms made her wedding day, and saved her dress. Or Peter, who's 21 and told me that Botox treatment of his palms allowed him to hold hands with a girl for the first time in his life. We can certainly all live with wrinkles but, as I've written previously , cosmetic surgery is inspiring and uplifting if you use it to project a positive image and to balance how you look with how you feel. Anne, a recently widowed 53-year-old, was one of the first patients to visit me after I opened my private practice. The Botox and laser treatments that I gave her helped her to cope with the stress of her husband'... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7084-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7084_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:10:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/30209/ada-day-1</link><title>Review: American Diabetes Association 68th Annual Scientific Session</title><description>... Association kicked off with a bang here yesterday. While the country's ... big press emphasized new results from two studies of using drugs to ... reduce our blood glucose levels, the hot topic here is exercise. I'm at the ADA's 68th ... Annual Scientific Sessions, a huge convention of about 14,000 diabetes ... professionals from around the world. From glancing at the name badges ... of others here, I wouldn't be surprised if most are from other ... countries. Hosting this meeting -- which most people here just call ... "the ADA" -- is theMoscone Convention Center in downtown San Francisco. ... This foggy city on the bay is cooperating so far with beautifully sunny ... weather in the high 60s and low 70s -- except for a very cold outdoor ... reception yesterday evening. The news in ... all of the papers available at my hotel trumpeted how both the ADVANCE ... and the ACCORD studies show that using drugs to cut our A1C levels to ... about 6.5 doesn't cut our risk of heart attack... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7084-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7084_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:10:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/155252/safe-supplements</link><title>How Safe are Fat Burning Supplements?</title><description>... We all have some bad habits, about that there is little doubt. Perhaps we leave lights on in rooms that are not occupied or place our shoes in areas where someone stumbling over them is guaranteed. Perhaps we borrow things from family members without asking. Perhaps we forget to lock doors or windows before going to bed at night. And, of course, there is now a universal habit that has become popularized in not just the United States but worldwide: Perhaps we eat in a way that is not only unhealthy but that will force weight gain or obesity. Overeating and the poor conditions that can result from overeating promote a desire for some immediate or near-immediate resolution. Borrowing property from family members is one thing, and swallowing a burst of laughter when that same family member tangles himself in the shoes we left lying about is another, but being overweight is all about us. It is our appearance, our esteem, the way we believe others perceive us. When our psychology is affected... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7084-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7084_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:11:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/30479/ada-day-5</link><title>Day 5 American Diabetes Association Convention: San Francisco Review</title><description>... over downtown San Francisco. More than 20,000 diabetes professionals ... have been here for the annual meeting of the American Diabetes ... Association. Those of us wearing ADA name badges not only filled the ... exhibition halls but also San Francisco's already crowded sidewalks. The ... city was a gracious hostess, providing the best possible accommodations ... and weather. We met in in the city's largest convention and exhibition ... complex, the Moscone Center . Built in 1981, the center is named for George Moscone, a former mayor of San Francisco who was assassinated in 1978. ... ... Moscone Center Entrance This ... vibrant city itself explains a lot why for me this was the best ADA ... ever. It almost tempts me to move back to California and to live in a ... big city again. But now we are leaving. I tried to stop this bus, but ... in vain. ... Stop the Bus! ... It ... was here a dozen years ago that the ADA introduced us to new ... terminology describing the types of diab... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>