<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7085">Adam rogers music</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:11:45" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7085-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7085_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:11:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/headache-specialists/montana-39937-5.html</link><title>Roger S. Williams, M.D. - Montana Migraine and Headache Specialists</title><description>... Doctor: Roger S. Williams, M.D. Clinic/Facility: Neurology Associates PLLC Address: 2900 12th Ave North, Suite 402E Billings, MT 59101 Telephone: 406-238-6670, 800-648-6274 Recommendation: Patient Feedback ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7085-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7085_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:12:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/headache-specialists/missouri-39930-5.html</link><title>Roger K. Cady, M.D. - Missouri Migraine and Headache Specialists</title><description>... Doctor: Roger K. Cady, M.D. Clinic/Facility: Medical Director, Headache Care Center Primary Care Network, Inc. Address: 1230 East Kingsley Street Springfield, MO 65804 Telephone: 417-886-2026 x240 Recommendation: Patient Feedback ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7085-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7085_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:13:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/news-44405-5.html</link><title>Capps, Rogers Introduce Legislation To Help Americans Suffering From Pain</title><description>... WASHINGTON, D.C. –Today Congresswoman Lois Capps (D-CA) and Congressman Mike Rogers (R-MI) introduced the National Pain Care Policy Act of 2007, legislation to improve pain care research, education, training, access, outreach and care.   “I am pleased to join my colleague Congressman Rogers and over one hundred organizations representing the pain care community in supporting this legislation that will help millions of Americans suffering from pain,” said Capps.  “Pain is the leading cause of disability in the United States and is straining our health care system.  Fortunately we don’t have to remain debilitated by pain.  This legislation takes several important steps to improve the assessment, understanding, and treatment of pain.  Hopefully this will provide much needed relief for many people suffering from pain.”   “Pain keeps sufferers from their family, work and the community, and in many cases it is so s... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7085-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7085_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:13:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/72843/teleconference-cady</link><title>Migraine Teleconference with Dr. Roger Cady Sunday</title><description>...   ... This month's topic is The Connection between Migraines and Emotional Health and How we Can Care for Ourselves in These Areas . The guest expert this month is Migraine and headache specialist Dr. Roger Cady . ...   ... After teleconference host Megan Oltman and Dr. Cady discuss the topic, the call will be open for questions or comments from other participants. ...   ... Roger Cady, M.D. is the Director of the Headache Care Center located in Springfield, Missouri.  ...   ... Dr. Cady is best known in the medical community for his pivotal contributions in the field of headache and migraine management.  He has authored and co-authored numerous books or chapters of books, numerous abstracts, and many articles.  Dr. Cady has presented countless lectures and seminars around the world on headache, migraine and ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7085-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7085_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:14:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/978365/153565/healthcentral</link><title>How Music Makes You Feel Better: A HealthCentral Explainer</title><description>...   ... Dentists seem to have been one of the first to understand what music can do when someone is facing a stressful experience, as headphones and music began to appear as enticement for dental patients wishing to avoid the rather vivid sounds of root canals and other dental procedures.  But experts say the secret to music’s positive effects on health go well beyond simply drowning out unpleasant noise.  Research has shown that the act of listening to music itself seems to affect the brain in a way that actually improves listeners’ sense of well being, and perhaps their overall health. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7085-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7085_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:14:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/19893/good-ol-days-mom</link><title>Music and Memory: Remembering the Good Ol' Days With Mom</title><description>... As I work through the process of mourning Mom 's death, I find that music - especially certain songs - tend to cause the tears to flow. Sometimes the songs are not surprising in their ability to tap into the well of grief, but other times a particular grouping of musical notes, a certain phrasing of words, an unusual inflection in the singer's voice will cause me to take a sharp inhale of breath and feel a twinge in my heart.   On a recent afternoon, I was watching television when Paul Anka came on, crooning "Times of Your Life," which at one time was Kodak's advertising jingle. Hearing him sing brought back mental images of me a young girl, following Mom's every move and wanting to grow up to be like her. And those memories quickly brought tears to my eyes.   (Thinking back on these memories, I find that I'm dreading the day when I unexpectedly hear "I Want to Hold Your Hand" by the Beatles; when it was initially popular, I was a you... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7085-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7085_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:15:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/154532/healing-question</link><title>Music and Healing: The Bipolar Question of the Week</title><description>...   ... Coincidentally, I will be talking with a lot of these people tomorrow. Let me explain: ...   ... I have been playing the didgeridoo for about five years. A couple of years ago, I began attending drum circles. A certain "Dr Jon" also attended. I first met up with Dr Jon at a NAMI walk, where he was playiing a metallic hang drum by a booth he was manning. I snuck up behind him with my didge and started honking along. Really, I'm not making this up. ...   ... I could write a book on the mental health benefits of drumming and didging, and someday maybe I will. Anyway, last year Dr Jon invited me to bring my didge to Stand Down. Dr Jon, it turns out, is Jon Nachison, a so... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7085-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7085_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:16:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/23153/34233/solution-pain</link><title>Solution for the Pain Pinch: Music Therapy</title><description>... Time for some music therapy. Music is a powerful healing force recognized around the world in many cultures. The beats, the lyrics, and the tones resonate within a person's soul. Even though personal preferences vary, the healing effects from music do not vary. Music evokes an emotional, calming feeling of positivity. Listening to music can actually lower heart rate and blood pressure. Plus, the beauty of music is that anyone (even those who can't hear it, but can feel it) can appreciate a melody, a harmony, and everything in between. ICU's, operating rooms, and nursing homes are all unleashing the power of music. Why don't you? ...   ... When I heard "Rocks in Your Shoes" by Emily West for the first time, I completely stopped what I was doing and turned up the volume. Go ahead and take a listen. ...   ...   ... ... ... ... ... ...   ...   ... Those living with pain know that there are "stones in the road" (More like an entire gravel truck dumped on you sometimes). Part of the keep-going attitud... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7085-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7085_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:16:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/896502/149272/listening</link><title>Listening to Music Can Make Your Workouts Seem Easier</title><description>...   ... But one time when I attended one of these sessions, the power went off in the whole building. Fortunately, the classroom where we were lifting weights was really light since there was a bank of windows on one side so the teacher decided to keep the class going. Her decision felt like a ton of bricks, literally, because those weights that were so easy to lift to a bouncy musical number by Beyonce suddenly felt like dead weight. I never had attended a class that seemed to last longer (and it o... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7085-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7085_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:17:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/c/727598/115573/soundtrack</link><title>Musical Provides Perfect Soundtrack for Menopausal Women</title><description>...   ... So what so appealed to this group? “Menopause the Musical” (MTM), which follows a chance meeting at New York City’s Bloomingdale’s Department Store by four middle-aged women beset with all the changes that menopause can bring. The four women brought different perspectives – one was an Earth mother, while another was a  soap opera star. The third woman was focused on her career, while the fourth person was a housewife visiting the big city from Iowa. The show, which was written by Jeanie Linders and first produced in 2001, has now been presented in 14 cou... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>