<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7086">falsifying pictures 21st centurie</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:18:08" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7086-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7086_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:18:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/110/89265/diabetes-century</link><title>Will diabetes be cured in the 21st century?</title><description>... ... Well, as a doctor with diabetes myself, I'll take the bait, and offer an opinion. But first things first: we'll have to define "cure" (and also define "remission" and "prevention") and also realize that any predictions inevitably will have to differentiate our guesses for type 1 vs. type 2 diabetes. ... ... Cure , to me, would be a situation where a person previously diagnosed with diabetes, who had well-documented elevated blood glucose levels and elevated A1C levels, later has normal BG and A1C without ongoing medications, surgery, dietary adjustments, or devices, as a result of some transient intervention. The problem is that although there are lots of bright ideas about what transient intervention or interventions might be able to create a cure, they a... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7086-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7086_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:18:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/6982/21st-century</link><title>Migraine personality? I thought this was the 21st century.</title><description>... "You have Migraines? They're all in your head? It's that type A personality of yours..." Need I say more to let you know where this is going? I think not. There used to be considerable conversation about the "Migraine personality." That was before advances in imaging technology, genetic research, and other progress that allowed scientists to identify Migraine as a genetic neurological disease with physiological (not psychological) triggers. We were so happy when that nonsense was put to rest. It always reminded me of some of the more barbaric and desperate measures employed to relive Migraine centuries ago. Thus the image here of a trepanned skull. Thousands of years ago, holes were actually drilled in the skull to relieve head pain. Yikes! Unfortunately, thanks to some so-called researchers in Italy, this inane theory has raised its ugly head again. I'm not even going to go into it more, but I do highly recommend that you pay a visit to another blog and read a bit more. My... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7086-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7086_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:19:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/nbcam-3461-143.html</link><title>October 21st: The Survivor Movie</title><description>... The Survivor Movie . ... And it will truly lift your spirits. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7086-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7086_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:19:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/77040/35161/mental-health-21st</link><title>Mental Health Humor : Weekly Review July 21st to 26th</title><description>... Saturday! Where did the week go? Time sure got away from me this ... week. Some unexpected stuff with which to deal. That’s life! Did your ... week go as planned? Or did you have to deal with some unexpected ... happening as well? In the words of a Prince song, “We got 2 go through ... it 2 get 2 it!” We made it through the week, now on to our Weekly ... Review. Did you have a good week?? Hope it was filled with a laugh or ... two?! Our Weekly Review gives me the opportunity to acknowledge all of ... your great comments and to express appreciation for your continuing ... support! This coming week, I hope to be getting into some topics I ... wanted to last week but couldn’t…due to circumstances. Please Subscribe ... to our blog via e-mail ( MentalHealthHumor.com ) and ... Stay “Tooned” ...   ... ... ... ... ...   ...   ... ... ...   ...   ... ... ... Sunday ... Sunday - Mid-night ... Madness, I shared a little story about my son. He keeps my wife and I... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7086-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7086_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:20:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/248736/112478/avoid</link><title>Time to Send It Back: How to Avoid Knee Pain</title><description>...   ... The "knee cap" or patella is an ovoid shaped bone whose main purpose is to act as a fulcrum that big muscle on the front of your thigh, the quadriceps. (I'll wait while you grab your high school physics book). There are plenty of folks who do not have patellae, but because this causes the quad muscle to work inefficiently, few of these folks can run or climb stairs well. The design issue with the patella is that it articulates, or rubs up against, the end of the femur bone (thus the "patellofemoral" joint). For those of us who have pa... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7086-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7086_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:21:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/168388/parasites-taking-brains-picture</link><title>Are Parasites Taking Over Our Brains and How Does Your Pet Cat Fit Into the Picture?</title><description>...   ... So here you are, a certain type of brine shrimp. A tape worm infects you and hijacks your brain so you socialize in a swarm with other infected shrimp. It also turns you red. Next thing, you are eaten by a flamingo.  ...   ... It seems the tapeworm needs the inside of a flamingo in order to reproduce. Essentially, the tape worm has turned you and your fellow brine shrimp into one very conspicuous floating buffet. ...   ... Parasites come in many forms. According to Mr Yong: “Manipulation is not an oddity. It is a critical and common part of the world around us.” Of special interest to us is the single-cell organism, toxoplasma gondii (T gondii or toxo), which has found its way into one-third of the human brains on the planet. ...   ... Toxo infects a wide variety of mammals, but can only reproduce in a cat. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7086-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7086_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:21:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/44361/15694/ease-pain</link><title>Before Alzheimer's becomes a national crisis, new programs are trying to ease the pain and stress of</title><description>... The latest issue of Greater Good magazine is out (Fall 2007).   This issue explores the "21st Century Family", discussing the many ways that American family life has been transformed in recent years. Families today face issues their grandparents could scarcely have imagined: the challenges of being a dual-income couple; the question faced by gay and lesbian parents and stay-at-home dads; and the obstacles confronted by all families today to find time for one another and make ends meet.   Matthew Wheeland is featured in this issue and has an article that shows how new programs acround the nation are trying to ease the pain and stree of caring for a loved one with Alzheimer's.    His article can be found at: http://greatergood.berkeley.edu/greatergood/current_issue/Wheeland.html   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7086-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7086_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:22:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/124870/95386/diabetic-rustler</link><title>Diabetic Rustler Prison Bound</title><description>... Diabetic Rustler Prison Bound He is a 21st century cattle rustler, a baby-faced cowboy and owes a few years behind bars. Oh, did we mention he has brittle diabetes? Roddy Dean Pippin is a mere 25 years of age and already a convicted criminal. He sports a bright smile and a cowboy hat. According to the American-Statesman, “Despite cries that to send him back behind bars might be a death sentence, Pippin was headed back to a state jail… to serve the remaining four years of his sentence. Pippin had been freed from state lockups and placed on house arrest about two years ago after questions were raised about whether he could receive proper medical care in prison because of the volatility of his diabetes.” ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7086-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7086_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:22:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/204/58403/conversations-years</link><title>Tune In Next Wednesay to Hear Summit Conversations to Improve Our Health Care Over the Next 4 Years</title><description>...   ... ... WASHINGTON, DC -(Saturday-January 17th, 2008)- Tuesday we  will actually watch history unfold before our very own light sensitive Migraineur eyes.  With it an uncertain path to better health care, so MAGNUM has turned to our friends from PALS for a better understanding for what the new Administration is willing to take on over the next four years to improve the disabled &amp; pain suffers quality of life.  ...   ... MAGNUM was honored by the Patient Advocacy Leaders Summit (PALS) in Philadelphia back in 2005.  Over the past few years PALS has reached out with various programs to support the NGOs in the health advocate community like us.  With a nation suffering from political burnout syndrome a summit of government thought leaders in the health care area just be helpful.  Having said that, we discovered PALS is working with an interesting group called ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7086-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7086_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:23:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/1950/101945/stress-good-days</link><title>Stress &amp; The Good Old Days</title><description>...   ... On average, and certainly in developed nations, the answer is probably yes. Recent studies suggest that one in three people suffer from stress and that figure is growing. There are all sorts of reasons for this but if we opt for a generalization it is easy to see how our way of life is become faster, more demanding and less healthy. Society has moved to a 24 hour, 7 day a week hub of activities. We sleep less well, work more, eat poorly and we don't exercise enough. We've all heard this and more besides. ...   ... Of course some of this is self-inflicted. We respond to the pressures of acquiring status and money in order to buy all the trappings that seem to make life a little better. My family isn't so different. We a... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>