<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7087">Jonathan Kreisberg discography</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:23:57" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7087-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7087_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:23:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/eorthopod/faq/years-discography-remember-3526</link><title>Two years ago I had a discography and to this day, I remember how painful it was.</title><description>... Two years ago I had a discography and to this day, I remember how painful it was. I was sure I had cancer. The doctor thought it was a disc. It wasn't either one. Why is it the memory of this test still so strong? Strong emotion of any kind has been shown to be linked with strong memories of that moment. The exact physiologic mechanism by which this happens isn't clear. Neuropeptides or biologic messengers that travel around the body may have something to do with it. The same effect is associated with stressful medical tests. Studies show that the level of pain reported and remembered for stressful or negative medical tests is higher than when the test was originally done. This phenomenon is called post-exposure modulation . It means that memory pain of acutely painful experiences is remembered inaccurately because it is exaggerated over time. This is especially true when the delay between experience and recall is six months or more. Discography is a painful test. It is designed to confirm... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7087-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7087_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:24:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/100/13411/nami-2007</link><title>NAMI 2007 Convention: An Interview with Jonathan Stanley</title><description>... Johnathan Stanley   Jonathan Stanley , J.D., is the Acting Executive Director of the Treatment Advocacy Center (TAC), which is a national nonprofit organization dedicated to eliminating barriers to the timely and effective treatment of severe mental disorders. After the onset of bipolar disorder, he graduated from law school, was a practicing attorney, and then joined the TAC in 1998. One of his colleagues (Mary Zdanowicz) said, "...Jonathan's work has made an indelible impression on the landscape of treatment law reform across the nation". He received the Anchor Achievement Award for Leadership and Excellence in Mental Health Advocacy in 2005. You can find more information about the TAC at http://www.treatmentadvocacycenter.org/ .   RC: You have quite an amazing story. When did you first become ill?   JS: I got ill in college with bipolar and then we found out I had psychotic features. I think I was about as sick as sick can get. Just briefly at the apex, I wen... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7087-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7087_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:25:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/community-2909-143.html</link><title>Meet Dr. Jonathan Krant, HealthCentral's New Osteoarthritis Expert</title><description>... Rheumatology at Berkshire Medical Center in Pittsfield, MA. A busy ... clinician, he oversees the care of 6,000 patients within a four ... state radius, and runs the clinical investigation unit at Berkshire ... Rheumatology Associates, where he is employed as a staff ... rheumatologist. Dr. Krant developed an interest in patients with ... musculoskeletal disorders while working under the aegis of Dr. Mary ... Betty Stevens as a student at Johns Hopkins University. He ... subsequently studied the epidemiology of arthritis among the Navajo ... and Yakima tribes while a medical resident at Dartmouth and ... research fellow at the University of Washington. A clinical fellow ... at the University of California in San Francisco, Dr. Krant ... developed a subspecialty interest in systemic lupus while working ... with Asian patients and continues to perform clinical research in ... therapeutics as an attending physician. ... He lives on a farm in Williamstown, Massachusetts, with his wife ... and ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7087-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7087_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:25:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/99191/18482/stress-cycle</link><title>Narrative of The Stress Cycle By Jonathan Strickling</title><description>...   I was injured at work. That is why I am here (Northern California Functional Restoration Program). I suffered a neck injury resulting in chronic pain in my lower neck, upper and mid-back, shoulders, and radiating pain running down both arms. I had discectomy on two levels of my cervical spine and fusion. I am still experiencing occasional numbness and tingling in my ring and pinky finger on my right hand, which also has tremors. The following is the narrative of the accounts of my pain, loss, and stress.   EVENT: My injury happened over a period of time. In late 2002 to early 2003 I began suffering from upper and mid-back pain. I thought it to be normal fatigue from commuting to and from a somewhat stressful job. I went to my family doctor, Dr. Siu in San Francisco, for the pain. Upon his examination he prescribed Cyclobenzaprine as a muscle relaxer. The stuff really knocked me out, so I stopped taking it. As time went on my pain increased. I started taking "over the cou... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7087-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7087_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:26:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/</link><title>Neighborly Advice: How to Decrease Monthly Insurance Payments</title><description>... My first thought was to encourage him to increase his deductible. Increasing the deductible means that for significant medical needs he would need to pay more up-front before the health insurance benefits kick in. So moving a deductible from $1,000 or $2,500 per year for his family to $10,000 would probably reduce his monthly payment significantly. But he'd have to balance that with access to money necessary for a medical "surprise". ... I forgot to mention coinsurance to him, possibly the most confusing health insurance term, since he was about to cut his lawn. Coinsurance is a way for the insurer to increase yo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7087-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7087_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:27:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/454788/93242</link><title>What medications will not wix with Tamiflu?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7087-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7087_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:27:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/510540/128096</link><title>girl lose virginity bleed the next day</title><description>... answer ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7087-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7087_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:28:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/732582/127900</link><title>Does Soaking Feet In Hot Water Improve Neuropathy</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7087-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7087_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:28:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/question/117958/103766</link><title>In morning, I notice hollows under my eyes, Can restylane or juvederm rid these hollows?</title><description>... The hollows are on the outer portion of eyes, above cheekbones. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7087-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7087_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:29:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/30575/28548/inspiration</link><title>Inspiration</title><description>... I wanted to say hi and say the website is wonderful I have been ADHD all my life ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>