<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7091">don't listen to a word i say</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:40:32" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7091-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7091_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:40:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/question/172413/147772</link><title>My 73 y/o neighbor has Late stage Alzheimer's. She cant finish a sentence. If words come out they don't make sense. I find that I nod or say OK, she gets frustrated. Is there something else I can say?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7091-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7091_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:41:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/46860/25792/don-word</link><title>Don't say the C word...</title><description>... I have suffered with chronic pain for almost six years now. I was diagnosed with Reflex Sympathetic Dystrophy, fibromyalgia, chronic back pain, chronic pelvic pain, and Restless Leg Syndrome. My RSD was a result of a caving accident that damaged nerves in my left side.  I just wanted to share my story of living with chronic pain and the fight we all endure in some way. ... Two years ago my husband divorced me because he could not live with me being in pain every day and the narcotics that made me so irritable. I was dealing with so much, I decided to move from New Mexico to Indiana where my family was. I was on Medicaid in New Mexico and thought it would transfer to Indiana, boy was I wrong. Indiana and New Hampshire are the only two states that do not recognize if you have been on Medicaid in another state. As a result, in waiting to be approved, I did not have the medications I needed. There were times that my pain got so bad, I wo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7091-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7091_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:41:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/151417/grief-words</link><title>Grief and Loss: When Words are Not Enough</title><description>...   ... Would there be a viewing? An open casket? A wake? A mass? A burial? What do I wear to the funeral? Do I send flowers? Give to charity? Send a card? Should I bring... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7091-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7091_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:42:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/721803/107131/doctors-listen</link><title>Doctors who don't listen.</title><description>... I am very upset over my psychologist telling me she finds it hard to believe about some things I tell her!  I feel like throttling her sometimes because she must think I am a liar!  I am not a liar and will not be in the future.  Why is it that sometimes doctors can be like that and how can they say such a thing to their patient?  She is messing up my disability from work (I KNOW that I cannot concentrate and remember things easily and also that I am in a depression - my new psychiatrist increased one of my meds for this).  However, what she wrote about to my lawyer is excellent for my Social Security case.  No one else but us on this site (and some others) know how we are and what we are capable of at the current time.  I struggle EVERY day.  Just because it doesn't look like it at times doesn't make it not true!  I am so aggravated but I am fighting back the best I can.  I am sorry for ranting and raving but I figure that this is the... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7091-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7091_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:42:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/2207/12735/gods-word</link><title>"Everything that satan means for evil shall be turned into God's glory," says His Word.</title><description>... Jesus is our deliverer, healer and savior.  Call upon the name of Jesus.  Read His Word and listen to it and get it inside you.  His Word Heals.  Get into a Spirit-Filled Church that the anointing will over flow into your life.  Get prayed for and pray in secret and the Lord will reward you openly.  If a voice or a thought speaks negative, DO NOT Listen. Speak what God says and tear down anything that interferes with the Peace and Love of God.  When I say tear down, I mean to cancel assignments of wrong words and thoughts by not speaking them but rather speaking over them with the word of God.  Pray the solution, not the problem. Concentrate on what is GOOD. Do not give up 5 minutes before the miracle. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7091-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7091_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:43:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/849319/106396/adhd-child-listen</link><title>How to Talk So Your ADHD Child Will Listen</title><description>...   ... One of the first questions you may ask yourself is, “Why is my child not listening?” The answers may be important in how you deal with their behavior. Don’t always assume that your child just wants to push your buttons. There may be other things going on that you need to be aware of. Your child’... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7091-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7091_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:44:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/800193/70532</link><title>My 4 year old will not listen unless yelled at...HELP!</title><description>... he is ALWAYS thirsty!!!that worries me... ... Is he too young to be diagnosed with ADHD? Is there anything I can do with herbs or diet? ... Unfortunatey I have ADHD too..a... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7091-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7091_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:44:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/57718/40446/listener-15-connected</link><title>How to Be a Better Listener: 15 Tips to help you Stay Connected</title><description>...   ... A woman with ADHD once told me that when she is in a conversation with someone and if the topic at hand isn't of much interest to her, she - like many with ADHD - zones out. As she put it, "I see their mouth moving but don't seem to hear the words. My inner world is much more interesting." ...   ... We miss so much- teachers' lectures, lovers' murmurings, children's innocent wonderings and questions, driving directions, movie plots...all due to our distractibility. How can we improve our listening skills so we're connected with our loved ones, bosses, friends and others? ...   ... 1. Become aware of your tendency to mentally roam. ...   ... 2. Stay in the here and now. Remind yourself that you can think about other things later. ...   ... 3. Find ways to stay connected. For some, it's watching the person's mouth or eyes. ...   ... 4. When your mind wanders, mentally repeat what the person is saying. ...   ... 5. Become more interactive in the conversation. If ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7091-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7091_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:45:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/38939/100255/talk-listen</link><title>I need to talk, and for someone to listen</title><description>...   ... All week long I've been the shoulder to cry on, the one to answer "tough" questions, the one that my friend has been looking to for support, but tonight I'm tired. Emotionally, spiritually, physically tired, because I know with final arrangements being made, and tears already flowing my friend is waiting for her mom to die. I can't bring myself to think about what it wou... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7091-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7091_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:46:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/living-well-271808-5.html</link><title>The Art of Conversation - Part 5: Active Listening</title><description>... I was one year out of law school. Very improbably, I had landed a senior editorial position as a financial journalist. I knew nothing about finance. I knew nothing about journalism. Moreover, I was a slow study. Believe it or not, all this worked to my advantage in my job interview. I did very little talking. I had nothing to show off, so I didn't come across as a smarty-pants. Instead, my interviewer interpreted my quiet demeanor as a sign of even temperament (ha!) and professionalism. The next day he called with a job offer. Silence is golden. But it was only a matter of time before my employer would realize I was a flat-out impostor. My goal was to delay the inevitable for a year. In the meantime, I had to live off my wits. One of my first assignments was to interview a prominent tax accountant. We settled into his well-appointed office, with a spectacular view of the harbor. I pulled out my notebook. It was time to pretend I was a journalist. The success or failure of my interview, ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>