<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7093">What do i need to go fly fishing?</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:52:14" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7093-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7093_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:52:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/67377/168420/flying-psoriasis-psoriasis</link><title>Flying with Psoriasis and How I Avoid the Psoriasis Beard</title><description>...   ... I travel frequently for work and nothing makes my skin more volatile than air travel (except beer). Over the years, I’ve chalked this up to a handful of reasons: my skincare regime is changed; I get dehydrated during the flight; sleep times are often interrupted; exposure to germs and viruses that may cause my immune system to work overtime. Here are some of my habits that lessen my psoriasis flares and the volatility that can follow air travel. ...   ... Please note, I am not a doctor, so please don’t take my advice as if it’s from a medical professional. That being said, I do a lot of research on psoriasis and I write for the... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7093-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7093_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:52:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/c/question/490481/70043</link><title>how much actual fish would need to be eaten to equal the recommended 3000 mgm of fish oil?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7093-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7093_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:53:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/868431/137896</link><title>Question about flying with diabetes and Doctors notes needed</title><description>... Hi, I am about to go on my second holiday since being diagnosed with Diabetes type 1. I was last on holiday in September 2010 for which I got a letter and repeat prescription off my Doctor stating my condition and medication needed etc. What I need to ask is, do I need a new letter/repeat prescription off my Doctor every time I  fly seen as the last one was obviously dated September? ...   ...   ...   ... I am really nervous about going through the airport and always imagine getting stopped or not being allowed on the plane for something I have forgotten or letter not being quite correct. I have searched on the internet but cannot find anywhere it states a new one is needed each time. ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7093-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7093_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:53:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/441331/59984</link><title>MY HUSBAND IS PETRIFIED OF FLYING, AND HE NEEDS TO GET ON A PLANE, WILL XANAX WORK?</title><description>... BECAUSE VALIUM DID NOT! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7093-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7093_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:54:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/948173/126371/parable</link><title>The Parable of the Bait Fish</title><description>... I have tears forming. This feels so good, cool sand in my feet (its morning so the sand is cooler than the air), waves crashing to my right, calls of sea gulls, smell of salt and seaweed washed up and shells. I think, have I ever really appreciated how good this feels? Have I ever really been thankful for taking a walk on the beach? ... I remember lying on the white living room sofa at home under ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7093-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7093_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:54:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/surviving-heart-attack-36549-5.html</link><title>Fish Oil and Heart Disease</title><description>... Omega-3 fatty acid is often misnamed an “alternative” or “natural” medication.   Penicillin was, of course, derived from a living organism and was therefore “natural” in the same way that Omega-3s are natural.   Currently, Omega-3 supplements are primarily derived from fish, and like penicillin, they have a therapeutic effect. Omega-3 fatty acids are often referred to as “essential” fatty acids (EFAs) because they are needed for human health but are not sufficiently produced by the body. The two major health promoting Omega-3 fatty acids are eicosapentaenoic acid (EPA) and docosahexaenoic acid (DHA). EPA and DHA are naturally found in certain cold-water fatty fish such as salmon, tuna, and mackerel. They can also be derived in the body from alpha-linolenic acid (ALA), which is an Omega-3 found in certain seeds and plant-based oils. However, the body is very inefficient at converting ALA into EPA and DHA, which is why sufficient amou... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7093-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7093_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:55:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/302657/52151</link><title>do i need to wear a medical id bracelet if i have ibs and a fish and shellfish allergy ?</title><description>... and i also have ibs ... do i need to have a medical id bracelet? ... can someone please help me :) ... thank you ... x ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7093-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7093_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:55:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/84299/31640/fear-flying</link><title>Fear of Flying</title><description>...   ... The most frequent phobia I have treated over the past 30 years is the fear of flying. It is a phobia that can significantly impact one's life. ... Studies ... estimate that between 10 to 20% of the population suffers from fear of ... flying or aviophobia. Many people fly with extreme anxiety and others ... have avoided flying for years.  ...   ... I have had patients who were unable to visit relatives or go on certain vacations because of their fear.   When someone is the only family member unable to fly it can create a great deal of conflict within the family.  ...   ... Most people with fear of flying are suffering from a specific phobia.  However, there are many people who actually have panic disorder and are afraid to fly because they believe they will have a ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7093-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7093_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:56:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/110/28196/diabetes-supplies</link><title>Tips for Flying with Diabetes Supplies</title><description>... Some suggestions about flying with diabetes supplies:    1. I pack my insulin in its original factory-supplied cardbox box (which has the pharmacy-applied label on it), inside a clear Ziploc-type bag, and inside a larger Ziploc bag that includes a freezer pack. I keep one of my business cards inside the insulin bag.       I put both clear plastic bags on top of my coat or shoes in one of those grey TSA bins, and point to them when at the screening machine, and say "Insulin and freezer pack". They have never asked me questions.    2. I carry my syringes and replacement fingerpokers and pen-needles in a clear plastic bag, which I leave inside my computer bag. Never been asked about them.    3. I also have copies of all the pharmacy paperwork for all my stuff, also kept in the computer bag. Never needed them. I've flown out of Newark many times, and many other US airports. Only non-US airport I've been through recently was Charles de Gaul... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7093-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7093_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:56:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/33722/40996/conquering-flying</link><title>Conquering Your Fear of Flying</title><description>... Several studies have shown that as many as 40 percent of American adults have some degree of anxiety about flying. According to the National Institute of Mental Health, 6.5 percent have a fear of flying that is persistent, intense, and irrational and qualifies as a phobia. ...   ... Flying and Other Phobias ...   ... Flying phobia is considered a specific phobia , which is a type of anxiety disorder . People with specific phobias experience a seemingly excessive and unreasonable fear in the presence of or in anticipation of a specific object, place, or situation—such as flying, driving over bridges or in tunnels, or riding in an elevator. The fear may not make any sense, but they feel powerless to stop it, a... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>