<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7094">calculate inertia sphere</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:57:14" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7094-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7094_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:57:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/c/question/85338/137031</link><title>This bodyfat calculator gave 6.7% body fat, which I know is low. I used the same numbers on another online calculator at http://www.bmi-calculator.net/body-fat-calculator/ and got 18.7%. Any idea why?</title><description>... 40 yr old male, 33 in waist, 37 in hips, 158 lbs, 14 in forearm, 7 in wrist. And my scale tells me anywhere between 15 and 17% bodyfat, which seems a bit high. These numbers are all over the place between my scale, and the various online calculators... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7094-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7094_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:57:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/24137/exercise-inertia</link><title>Overcoming Exercise Inertia</title><description>... Starting to exercise isn't easy for anyone. It sure wasn't for me, even though I knew all too well how important exercise is for controlling my diabetes. It's a particularly personal example of the universal problem called inertia , which Sir Isaac Newton told us about 321 years ago in the greatest single scientific work ever. Inertia means that a body at rest tends to remain at rest. But that's only part of it, the down side. Inertia's up side is that a body in motion tends to remain in motion. Once we get going it's easier to keep going than to stop. I know that Sir Isaac was right. Now, for me it's harder on my psyche -- to say nothing of my body -- not to exercise every day than to exercise. "I used to exercise and really liked to do that," a correspondent named Jan wrote me this week. But she stopped working out after going through several surgeries. Subsequently, she totally lost her desire to exercise. "I know you used to hate to... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7094-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7094_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:58:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/ideal-body-weight-7181-146.html</link><title>Calculating body frame size</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7094-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7094_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:59:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/c/question/849204/154656</link><title>how to calculated lipid profile reaio</title><description>... how to calculated lipid profile reaio ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7094-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7094_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 21:59:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/c/question/46198/47010</link><title>What is the formula to calculate the percentage of triglyceride reference to total cholesterol?</title><description>... What is the formula to calculate the percentage of triglyceride reference to total cholesterol? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7094-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7094_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:00:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/question/311754/79726</link><title>How do I calculate how many calories I can eat a day and still lose weight?</title><description>... Hi, I would like to know how to calculate the amount of calories that I can eat a day and still lose a moderate amount of weight. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7094-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7094_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:00:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/c/question/1002/40344</link><title>can you calculate fat in cholesterol</title><description>...   ... this a project question. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7094-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7094_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:01:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/7811/11607/calculator</link><title>Calculator</title><description>... A Simple Insulin Dosage Calculator   By Neil Bason, Managing Director of Thorpe Products, Ltd. (a Type 1 Caregiver)   For people who inject insulin with a basal/bolus regimen, it's often difficult to calculate the proper pre-meal dose. After watching my partner struggle with the math for fifteen years, I decided to design a simple calculator to mimic the mental process that she uses to calculate her meal-time dose of insulin.   To calculate the number of meal-time insulin units to inject, you must establish the following: Blood sugar level (using a blood glucose meter). The grams of carbohydrates consumed, from which you derive the number of insulin units needed to cover that intake. The amount of exercise to be taken post-injection. The mental process you must undertake to calculate your insulin dose is as follows:   1. Blood Sugar : Suppose your blood sugar reading is 195 and your target blood sugar is 100. Subtracting 100 from 195, you get 95, which is how much you nee... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7094-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7094_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:01:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/263918/74757</link><title>Is there a calculation doctors</title><description>... Is there a calculation doctors use to decide how many units of insulin are needed for a person just starting insulin therapy?  Or is it best guess or do you start at a very low dose and work up? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7094-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7094_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:02:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/17157/19694/mixed-foods</link><title>How to Calculate Diabetic Exchanges of Mixed Foods?</title><description>... What is the best method for calculating diabetic exchanges of mixed foods such as chicken pot pie or vegetable beef soup?  Could you please share the steps to this process?  Thanks! ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>