<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7095">iron in water supply</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:02:45" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7095-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7095_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:02:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/707333/119619</link><title>What do you think about the sick building theory and additives placed in our food and water supply?..</title><description>... I think that all the additives placed in our daily foods,water supply, dye additives in our clothing,junk put in our dry skin creams, hair care and nail care, crop dusting, electrical power lines for years is part of the major reasons so many new diseases have cropped up over the past 20 years.. ... What do you think? Bonnie ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7095-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7095_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:03:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/13725/165005</link><title>Has the use of Florean and clorean in our water supply been checked as a possible cause of some of the behaveuril problems experienced by children now?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7095-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7095_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:03:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/299905/161049/bottled-water-worth</link><title>Bottled Water – Is it Worth It?</title><description>... There is no question that drinking bottled water has become a way of life for most Americans. You will find bottled water everywhere you go – in offices, hotels, restaurants, gyms, street corners and homes. We spend over $15 billion dollars a year on bottled water, more than we spend on iPods and movie tickets. [1] However, unfortunately we have been persuaded that bottled water is a symbol of health and economic status, which couldn’t be further from the truth. For a product that is only a little more than 30 years old, it’s important that we understand the impact of the bottled water industry and begin to look for alternative ways to obtain pure water while also improving our city water sources and environment. The Environmental Working Group (EWG) [2] and The Story of Stuff Project [3] have been very helpful in educating us about the real contents of the water being bottled, the marketing tactics being used by the corporations producing them and the consequences for ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7095-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7095_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:04:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/9032/14963/aerosol-asthma</link><title>Aerosol Cleaning Supplies and Asthma</title><description>...   As part of Blog Action Day , today's blog will focus on the environment and allergies and asthma.   How many of you feel a little wheezy after using a spray in your bathroom to clean the tile or toilet? Perhaps you feel breathless after freshening the air and you don't know why?   According to this recent study published in the American Thoracic Society's American Journal of Respiratory and Critical Care Medicine, "The researchers found that cleaning sprays, especially air fresheners, furniture cleaners and glass-cleaners, had a particularly strong effect [in creating asthma symptoms]." The study continues: "Frequent use of household cleaning sprays may be an important risk factor for adult asthma ...The relative risk rates of developing adult asthma in relation to exposure to cleaning products could account for as much as 15 percent, or one in seven of adult asthma cases."   Jeez, this is not good news -- but it's certainly... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7095-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7095_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:04:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/727598/159403/mislabeling-questions</link><title>More Mislabeling Raises Questions About Food Supply Chain</title><description>... Well, the news has been full of stories about horsemeat in Ikea’s meatballs. Now Bloomberg Businessweek is reporting that consumers in South Africa are finding out that they’ve been eating burgers made out of donkey, sausage made out of goat and lunch meat made out of water buffalo. The country’s health department is starting an investigation after researchers found that 68 percent of meat products tests were species that were not declared on the product label. ... And that’s not all. You may be being misguided when you select seafood (which is really sad since I just wrote a blog about a large study that links the Mediterranean diet – which means a lot of seafood – to cardiovascular health). The Boston Globe did a two-part series that looked at whether fish is mislabeled in restaurants. T... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7095-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7095_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:05:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabeteens/c/22669/73220/protecting-sun</link><title>Protecting diabetes supplies from the sun</title><description>...   ... A Type 1 diabetic cyclist recently told me that he usually clips his insulin pump to the outside of his shorts while he is biking. One day the pump clip broke and he was forced to tuck the pump inside his shorts, close to his body. The bolus he gave for dinner a few hours later didn't work, and he figured out that the insulin in his pump had gotten so hot during the bike ride that it wasn't as effective as usual. This problem was something he had never anticipated, and it could really happen to anyone. ...   ... Whether you're sitting by the pool all afternoon or sightseeing in Peru this summer, you will probably have your insulin and glucometer close by. I... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7095-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7095_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:05:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/r/medications/mykidz-iron-fluoride-oral-147400/dosage</link><title>MyKidz Iron Fluoride Oral Dosage and Storage</title><description>... Generic Name: MULTIVITAMINS AND IRON WITH FLUORIDE LIQUID - ... ORAL MyKidz Iron Fluoride Oral Overdose ... If overdose is suspected, contact your local poison ... control center or emergency room immediately. US residents can call the US ... national poison hotline at 1-800-222-1222. Canadian residents should call their ... local poison control center directly. Symptoms of overdose may include ... vomiting, stomach/abdominal pain, green diarrhea, tarry stools, increased ... saliva, drowsiness, seizures. ... MyKidz Iron Fluoride Oral Missed Dose ... If you miss a dose, take it as soon as you remember. If it ... is near the time of the next dose, skip the missed dose and resume your usual ... dosing schedule. Do not double the dose to catch up. ... MyKidz Iron Fluoride Oral Notes ... This product is not a substitute for a proper diet. ... Remember that it is best to get your vitamins from healthy foods. It is ... important to maintain a well-balanced diet. ... Check the fluoride content of you... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7095-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7095_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:06:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/r/medications/ped-multivitamin-fl-iron-oral-2832/dosage</link><title>Ped Multivitamin-Fl-Iron Oral Dosage and Storage</title><description>... Generic Name: MULTIVITAMINS AND IRON WITH FLUORIDE LIQUID - ... ORAL Ped Multivitamin-Fl-Iron Oral Overdose ... If overdose is suspected, contact your local poison ... control center or emergency room immediately. US residents can call the US ... national poison hotline at 1-800-222-1222. Canadian residents should call their ... local poison control center directly. Symptoms of overdose may include ... vomiting, stomach/abdominal pain, green diarrhea, tarry stools, increased ... saliva, drowsiness, seizures. ... Ped Multivitamin-Fl-Iron Oral Missed Dose ... If you miss a dose, take it as soon as you remember. If it ... is near the time of the next dose, skip the missed dose and resume your usual ... dosing schedule. Do not double the dose to catch up. ... Ped Multivitamin-Fl-Iron Oral Notes ... This product is not a substitute for a proper diet. ... Remember that it is best to get your vitamins from healthy foods. It is ... important to maintain a well-balanced diet. ... Check the fluoride co... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7095-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7095_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:06:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/r/medications/poly-vi-flor-iron-oral-59545/dosage</link><title>Poly-Vi-Flor With Iron Oral Dosage and Storage</title><description>... Generic Name: MULTIVITAMINS/IRON/FLUORIDE CHEWABLE TABLET - ... ORAL Poly-Vi-Flor With Iron Oral Overdose ... If overdose is suspected, contact your local poison ... control center or emergency room immediately. US residents can call the US ... national poison hotline at 1-800-222-1222. Canadian residents should call their ... local poison control center directly. Symptoms of overdose may include ... vomiting, stomach/abdominal pain, green diarrhea, tarry stools, increased ... saliva, drowsiness, seizures. ... Poly-Vi-Flor With Iron Oral Missed Dose ... If you miss a dose, take it as soon as you remember. If it ... is near the time of the next dose, skip the missed dose and resume your usual ... dosing schedule. Do not double the dose to catch up. ... Poly-Vi-Flor With Iron Oral Notes ... This product is not a substitute for a proper diet. ... Remember that it is best to get your vitamins from healthy foods. It is ... important to maintain a well-balanced diet. ... Check the fluoride content ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7095-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7095_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:07:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/r/medications/polyvitamin-fluoride-iron-oral-59554/dosage</link><title>Polyvitamin W/Fluoride &amp; Iron Oral Dosage and Storage</title><description>... Generic Name: MULTIVITAMINS AND IRON WITH FLUORIDE LIQUID - ... ORAL Polyvitamin W/Fluoride &amp; Iron Oral Overdose ... If overdose is suspected, contact your local poison ... control center or emergency room immediately. US residents can call the US ... national poison hotline at 1-800-222-1222. Canadian residents should call their ... local poison control center directly. Symptoms of overdose may include ... vomiting, stomach/abdominal pain, green diarrhea, tarry stools, increased ... saliva, drowsiness, seizures. ... Polyvitamin W/Fluoride &amp; Iron Oral Missed Dose ... If you miss a dose, take it as soon as you remember. If it ... is near the time of the next dose, skip the missed dose and resume your usual ... dosing schedule. Do not double the dose to catch up. ... Polyvitamin W/Fluoride &amp; Iron Oral Notes ... This product is not a substitute for a proper diet. ... Remember that it is best to get your vitamins from healthy foods. It is ... important to maintain a well-balanced diet. ... Check ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>