<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7098">tour moscow</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:13:52" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7098-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7098_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:13:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/alzheimers-association-2889-149.html</link><title>Alzheimer's Brain Tour- From the Alzheimer's Association</title><description>... ... on the Alzheimer's Association Web site that uses interactive ... images and text to help you understand how the brain functions. ... ... ... ... ... The Alzheimers Association, the world leader in Alzheimer ... research, care and support, is dedicated to finding prevention ... methods, treatments and an eventual cure for Alzheimers. Our ... mission is to eliminate Alzheimers disease through the ... advancement of research; to provide and enhance care and support ... for all affected; and to reduce the risk of dementia through the ... promotion of brain health. Our nationwide organization of more than ... 300 local offices provides reliable information, referral, and ... supportive programs and services to families. ... www.alz.org . ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7098-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7098_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:14:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/849319/109043/russian-challenging</link><title>Russian Adoptee Sent Back to Moscow Because of Challenging Behavior</title><description>...   ... According to one CBS news report The Kremlin children's rights office shared the contents of the note which read: "This child is mentally unstable. He is violent and has severe psychopathic issues. I was lied to and misled by the Russian Orphanage workers and director regarding his mental stability and other issues. ... After giving my best to this child, I am sorry to say that for the safety of my family, friends... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7098-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7098_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:14:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/325197/135299/bike-research</link><title>Ride in the TD Bank Five Boro Bike Tour for Migraine Research</title><description>...   ... This is the largest recreational cycling event in America, and one of the hottest tickets in the Tri-State area. ...   ... The MRF invites you to raise awareness and critically needed funds for Migraine research by riding in this incredibly empowering and inspiring event... ...   ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7098-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7098_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:15:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/78/14240/time-tour</link><title>The Komen Community Challenge Tour</title><description>... O-BA-MA! O-BA-MA! HILL-A-RY! HILL-A-RY! 08–CAN’T WAIT! O8–CAN’T WAIT! As I write this, my ears are still ringing from 2 hours of standing in the midst of a shouting crowd of mostly young, very enthusiastic, and incredibly loud demonstrators. All eight Democratic Presidential candidates gathered for a debate tonight at Dartmouth College in Hanover, N.H., and the accompanying media circus attracted a throng of supporters to the college green–which, conveniently, is less than half a mile from my house.   Packed into a fenced-off area, jostling for position in front of the cameras filming for NBC and CNN and every other major station, it was an incredibly energetic scene. Remember the anti-war demonstrations of the early ’70s? This took me right back there. And I was smack-dab in the middle of it all.       New Hampshire Komen organizer Beth Richards talks strategy with supporter Charlene Gates.   I’ve lost my bellbottoms, my l... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7098-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7098_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:16:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/25188/43907</link><title>Are you going on Tour?</title><description>... Are you and Michael going on tour to let Children with ADHD get a chance to meet Michael.  As well as Mothers of children with ADHD get a chance to talk to you.  I don't think Michael knows how these children look up to him.  My daughter watched him every time he was on during the oylmpics and now when she sees him on a magazine or newspaper she will says "Mom look its Michael, when can I meet him"  I would love to take her to see him.  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7098-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7098_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:16:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/daughter-prestigious-dance-1586</link><title>Our 19-year-old daughter is a dancer on a summer tour with a very prestigious dance group.</title><description>... Our 19-year-old daughter is a dancer on a summer tour with a very prestigious dance group. She's been having problems with snapping and popping of her left hip. It doesn't hurt but it's loud enough to be heard on stage. We're trying to find out anything we can that might help her. Are there any tricks to keep this from happening without changing the way she dances? Many dancers and other athletes are affected by an annoying hip condition that results in a snapping sound and feeling that occurs whenever they bend or flex their hip. Coxa sultans is the medical term for this condition. But it is better known by a more descriptive term: snapping hip . The treatment depends on the cause. If it's something loose inside the joint (e.g., piece of bone or cartilage) that's getting caught, it might have to be removed surgically. If it's a tendon rubbing over a bone, then stretching might be the answer. Sometimes the only effective treatment is rest and stopping the motion that aggravates the condi... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7098-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7098_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:17:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/80422/52422/coming-story</link><title>Coming Jan 20th - My Life With Laura: A Love Story book blog tour</title><description>... The book can be downloaded from Lulu (linked above) for $5.00 or ordered as a paperback.  It is described as a love story, albeit a tragic one. Chad and Laura dated and married. Shortly thereafter, they gave birth to a beautiful daughter, Charlotte. Life was perfect...until they learned that Laura had breast cancer. This book describes the exciting experiences of courtship, the beauty of their wedding, the joy of family, and the struggles of dealing with illness. Laura remained a beacon of strength to many throughout her battle with breast cancer. She was strongly rooted in her faith. This memoir tells an inspirational story, even for those who did not know her. It is dedicated to Charlotte, so that she will better know her mother. ... On Janurary 20th I will be featuring a review of this tragic love story on my blog, Cancer is NOT a DEAT... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7098-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7098_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:17:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/110/110216/rockin-celebrities</link><title>Challenges of Diabetes as a Patient, a Parent, and While Traveling on Tour</title><description>...   ... Bret, a rock star for many years, and lead singer of the group Poison, was diagnosed with diabetes at age 6, and has not shied away from discussing it, and has been an active fund-raiser for diabetes. He has openly described the challenges of living with diabetes both as a patient, parent and while on tour. He recently was on the television series "Celebrity Apprentice"; his charity for the show is the American Diabetes Association. NBC states "Bret feels it's his duty to raise money and awareness for the American Diabetes Association. With the ADA, Br... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7098-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7098_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:18:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/designed-provide-statethe-1526</link><title>I just toured a new clinic designed to provide state-of-the-art hip and knee surgery.</title><description>... I just toured a new clinic designed to provide state-of-the-art hip and knee surgery. They even have computer capability to navigate some of the more technical aspects of the operations. Can we really afford this kind of health care? Do we really need it? What about the thousands of people who've gotten joint replacements just fine without all this technology? You raise some very good questions that deserve consideration. Researchers are applying themselves diligently to answering the risk-to-benefit ratio for many improvements in the health-care delivery system. Computer-assisted technology is one of them. Like all advancements in science and technology, there's always an early investment in research and development. The tremendous cost can seem way beyond the benefit derived by anyone. It brings up the idea that just because we can do something doesn't mean we should. An alternate way to look at this is to see the immediate benefit to a single patient. In the case of procedures like hi... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7098-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7098_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:18:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/winner-france-replacement-1321</link><title>I saw the winner of this year's Tour de France (Floyd Landis) needs a hip replacement.</title><description>... I saw the winner of this year's Tour de France (Floyd Landis) needs a hip replacement. He's only a young 30-something. What's the age of the average patient who gets a hip replacement? It used to be the average age of a total hip recipient was mid-60s or older. Because the typical implant lasts around 15 to 20 years, surgeons waited until patients were older before giving them a total hip replacement (THR). That policy is slowly changing based on several factors. First is demand. As adults remain active longer, the need for joint replacement earlier is increasing. Second, the materials and methods used with THR have improved dramatically over the last two decades. Better and better long-term results are being reported. The age and type of patients eligible for THR is expanding every year. According to a large 25-year prospective (looking back) study, the average age of patients getting their first THR has been around 69 years old. The age range was from 24 to 88 and older. If there are n... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>