<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7099">lecture manova</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:19:04" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7099-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7099_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:19:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/13541/38742</link><title>Free public lecture by leading researcher on Rheumatoid Arthritis in Brisbane, Australia</title><description>... Ranjeny Thomas from The University of Queensland's Diamantina Institute will be giving a free public lecture ... entitled 'Rheumatoid Arthritis: Hope for the Future'. ... Rheumatoid arthritis is a ... painful and disabling condition that affects 1 in 100 people, the majority ... women. In this lecture, we will explore our latest research into what causes ... rheumatoid arthritis, its treatment, and ways in which it could be prevented in ... the future. ... The lecture will be held at the Brisbane Exhibition and Convention ... Centre at 1.30pm on Wednesday 19th November. More information visit www.di.uq.edu.au/events . Please RSVP ... to Danielle by calling 07 3240 6623 or email d.fischer"at"uq.edu.au. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7099-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7099_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:19:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/967175/164439</link><title>my heartbeat goes high like hitting like a hammer,when i answered to the question or else asking doubt to the lecturer</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7099-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7099_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:19:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/question/136909/66617</link><title>I forget always the starting of lectures which I have been taught previous day, what is this?</title><description>... whenever I study any chappter by my self or tby my teacher, if I understand the chappter then at that time I can taught any body that chappter as like Sir,but after some time (one day) I completely forget the starting and the concept which i understad very sharply in that chappter beside of it I revise that chappter amny times in home.I am facing this problem about 2 years.I could also not keep remember a lots of study which is vary necessary for studies. I have also forgets basics of my study.Just I am frusted. what is this? and what I do? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7099-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7099_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:20:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/copd/c/88905/35040/pausch-modern</link><title>Randy Pausch: An Inspiration to All</title><description>...   ... Pancreatic cancer kills 75% of its victims within a year of diagnosis and only 4% live past five years. While certain lifestyle choices such as smoking or heavy drinking can increase one’s odds of getting the disease, the cause is unknown. ...   ... Pausch, a Carnegie Mellon University professor and computer scientist, knew his chances weren’t good after his diagnosis in September, 2006. One year later he gave his “last lecture” at the university, which subsequently gained international attention and led to a best-selling book. ...   ... The message Pausch conveyed in his lecture was about pursuing one’s childhood dreams and not letting setbacks get in our way. He suggested that "Brick walls are the... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7099-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7099_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:20:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/325197/73362/pain-migraine</link><title>How Do We End the Pain of Migraine?</title><description>... Recently, I attended a lecture given by a prominent neurologist on new advances in migraine research. Speaking to an overflow crowd, the doctor was bombarded with questions from the audience – all sufferers or family and friends of sufferers – about what can be done to end the debilitating pain of migraine. The audience’s hunger for information was reflective of a frustrating fact of life for sufferers. While much of the conversation about migraine centers on symptoms and treatment options, there is insufficient knowledge about the underlying causes of migraine. Without this, how are we to end the suffering of the 30 million Americans afflicted by it? The reason? Migraine is one of our nation’s most overlooked, misunderstood, and under-funded illnesses. Though migraine affects 1 in 10 – including children and a disproportionate number of women – and ranks in the top 20 of the world’s most disabling illnesses, funding for research into its cause... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7099-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7099_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:21:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/4182/151999/undergraduates</link><title>Supporting Anxious Undergraduates</title><description>...   ... I gave up my job as a university academic about three years ago. By then, the massification of higher education was well established, as was the well-worn phrase, ‘it's all about bums on seats.' There was more than a grain of truth about this but I always felt lucky that I worked in a place that prided itself on the level of contact academic staff enjoyed with students. Even so, times were changing and contact hours with students were diminishing and... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7099-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7099_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:21:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/849319/69238/interview-advocate</link><title>My Interview with Thomas McKean, author and advocate for those on the Autism Spectrum</title><description>... ...   ... I first met Thomas many years ago when my now teen-age son was diagnosed with autism.  Thomas is an incredible individual who has overcome so many of the challenges associated with having an autism spectrum disorder.  Thomas is a published writer, lecturer, poet, and has even been on Oprah.  Always candid, always forthright, Thomas is a tremendous advocate for parents and caregivers as well as for those who are on the autism spectrum.  Every time I talk to Thomas I gain a greater insight as to the struggles associated with autism as well as the great potential of each individual given this diagnosis.  I am honored to be granted this interview with Thomas.  I hope that you will gain as much enlightenment as I have from his shared experiences and words.  ...   ... I now introduce to you, Thomas McKean. ...   ... Blog sites :  Thomas Mckean                 &amp;n... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7099-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7099_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:22:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/7494/47375/month-recognizes</link><title>National Alzheimer's Month Recognizes Courage, Devotion</title><description>...     How ironic, as it turns out. Ironic, of course, because the late President eventually had Alzheimer’s disease himself and because it was his public disclosure about his condition that ultimately shed light on the disease in such a powerful way. ...     While the overall intent of the declaration has remained consistent—raising awareness of the brain disorder, the message, just like the incidence of the disease, has gotten wider over time. Today, the proclamation calls for a month, not just a week, and it talks about both research and care, about both the individuals with the disease and their families. ...    &amp;... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7099-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7099_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:22:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/240285/132665/life</link><title>do u wish u had a life like others?</title><description>... hello,im not really active on facebook but i just use to see the pic of my friends.my lecturers r also on facebook and ther is 1 lecturer who is living life king size and when i look at her pic,i feel jeolous ,i wish i could have life like hers,she is surrounded by friends,goes to parties and seems to b very close to her family,when u look at her pic ,it shows that life needs to b lived and we better enjoy ourselves and im so jeolous coz i have a boring life,since i dnt have many friends ,i dont go out . ... i sometimes not look at her pics coz this shows a huge contrast to my life but then i dream that my life could become like hers which i knw won't. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7099-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7099_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:23:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/164283/adapting-bipolar-sabotaging</link><title>Adapting to Aging: Is Bipolar Sabotaging Our Ability to Live Longer?</title><description>...   ... On Thursday, I attended a public lecture hosted by the International Bipolar Foundation, here in San Diego. The name of the talk was “Successful Aging and Mental Illness,” by Colin Depp of UCSD. Perhaps the best way of doing justice to the topic in the space of a blog post is to offer a few talking points. Let’s get started ... ...   ... First, some knock-me-over-with-a-feather moments: According to Dr Depp, “successful aging” was only first mentioned in 1960, and it took until 1987 before the term made it into a medical article. Even then, there is no expert consensus on what successful aging is. A 2006 review article co-authored by Dr Depp noted that 28 different studies came up with 29 different definitions. ...   ... Most of these studies focussed on aging from a physical disability perspective. ...   ... Successful aging i... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>