<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7100">korean bbq san francisco review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:23:36" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7100-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7100_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:23:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/30479/ada-day-5</link><title>Day 5 American Diabetes Association Convention: San Francisco Review</title><description>... over downtown San Francisco. More than 20,000 diabetes professionals ... have been here for the annual meeting of the American Diabetes ... Association. Those of us wearing ADA name badges not only filled the ... exhibition halls but also San Francisco's already crowded sidewalks. The ... city was a gracious hostess, providing the best possible accommodations ... and weather. We met in in the city's largest convention and exhibition ... complex, the Moscone Center . Built in 1981, the center is named for George Moscone, a former mayor of San Francisco who was assassinated in 1978. ... ... Moscone Center Entrance This ... vibrant city itself explains a lot why for me this was the best ADA ... ever. It almost tempts me to move back to California and to live in a ... big city again. But now we are leaving. I tried to stop this bus, but ... in vain. ... Stop the Bus! ... It ... was here a dozen years ago that the ADA introduced us to new ... terminology describing the types of diab... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7100-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7100_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:24:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/copd/c/question/708668/77925</link><title>In San Francisco, does a bar that is considered a "DIVE BAR" allowed to let patrons smoke? If not, w</title><description>... Yelp reviews have cited smoking at the ACE CAFE on Mission St.... ... So strong you can see it walking by when the 2 doors are open! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7100-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7100_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:24:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/copd/c/89783/35789/pharmacies</link><title>San Francisco Bans Cigarette Sales in Pharmacies</title><description>... As of October 1, 2008, San Francisco will be the first city in the nation to ban the sale of tobacco products at most pharmacies.  (The law bans the sale of all tobacco products at pharmacies in the city, but big-box stores like Costco and supermarkets like Safeway will still be allowed to sell tobacco.)  Nearby Marin County officials are already crafting similar legislation and are carefully watching the implementation of San Francisco's ban. Those of us in tobacco control have lobbied long and hard for pharmacies across the country to prohibit the selling of tobacco products and we applaud San Francisco's Mayor Gavin Newsom for pushing through this legislation. Mayor Newsom plans to analyze the effect of the new law before expanding it to other stores in the city. The prototype for such a ban has been established. Over ten years ago, pharmacists in Canada adopted the position that selling tobacco products is incompatible with their health care responsibilities and declared t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7100-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7100_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:25:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/sara-rheumatoid-arthritis-comics-274944-5.html</link><title>Rheumatoid Arthritis in Young Women -- Don't Forget to Pack Your RA</title><description>... Read the full text of Don't Forget To Pack Your RA and leave a comment!   Read all of Sara's Posts   Visit The Single Gal's Guide to Rheumatoid Arthritis ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7100-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7100_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:25:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/</link><title>Can you recommend a neurologist in the San Francisco area that treats MS as well as Lyme Disease?</title><description>... Started with left side facial paralysis and blurred/double vision on July 14, 2008. Had MRI that shows frontal lobe lesions. Doctors say MS, but have a lot of Lyme Disease symptoms such as brain fog, fatighe, shaking, leg pain, achy neck, difficulty sleeping, mood swings. After 7 weeks I still have the vision issue which I need some resolve!   Looking for a neurologist in the Sacramento or San Francisco area who can help and/or is "open" to the possibility of Lyme Disease and treatment. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7100-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7100_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:26:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/87090/27431/francisco</link><title>Upcoming PAID Study on SCHIZOPHRENIA PATIENTS IN SAN FRANCISCO-MAY 2008</title><description>... Plaza Research is a national market research company located in downtown San Francisco.  We are looking for patients and caregivers of Schizophrenia patients who would like to participate in a market research study that involves a blography over the course of a week and a couple of visits to your home. SUBJECT: DEVELOPMENT OF NEW DRUGS AND                TREATMENTS FOR SCHIZOPHERENIA WHO: SCHIZOPHRENIA PATIENTS DATE:     May 2008 HONORARIUM:  $550.00 for your participation If you are interested in participating, please call us at 1-415-984-0400 as it is necessary that I ask you a few questions to determine if you qualify for this particular study.  Please ask to speak to someone regarding the “SCHIZOPHRENIA” study.  You may also fill out an online survey by clicking on the link below or cut and paste the link into your browser to complete the survey: https://www.surveymonkey.... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7100-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7100_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:26:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/question/334451/87516</link><title>Is there any support group for family members in the The East Bay in California near San Francisco</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7100-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7100_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:27:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/5873/8102/san-blue-cross</link><title>Migraine specialist in San Francisco that takes insurance (Blue Cross)</title><description>... does anyone know of a specialist in migraines in SF (other than the Headache Clinic, which does not take insurance)..?? Thanks! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7100-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7100_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:27:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/question/197239/54946</link><title>Best humidifyer for asthmatics? If it matters, I reside in San Francisco, C</title><description>... Now that winter weather has set in, I find myself becoming dehydrated with difficulty breathing.  Thank you. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7100-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7100_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:28:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/698174/132290</link><title>I live in Monterey Ca. My asthma has gotten worse since I quit smoking 14 years ago and moved from the San Francisco Bay Area. My Dr. said I should move to Arizona, good idea or bad, I'm 56 years old</title><description>... I'm using Singulair, a Pro Air rescue inhaler and can't afford Advair. in some coastal areas (Aptos/Santa Cruz) I can't breathe and I use my rescue inhaler 3 to 5 times a day, in most of my "coughing fits" I cough up phlem, mostly clear or white. I just want to breathe ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>