<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7103">cystic fibrosis treatment</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:40:15" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7103-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7103_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:40:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/</link><title>Cystic Fibrosis</title><description>... There is no way to prevent cystic fibrosis. People with a family ... history of cystic fibrosis can seek genetic counseling to determine ... their chance of passing this disease on to their children. A blood ... test can detect most, but not all, of the genetic mutations that ... cause cystic fibrosis. ... Treatment ... Treatment for cystic fibrosis depends on the severity of the ... disease and which parts of the body are involved. Close, regular ... monitoring is essential. Lung disease can be treated with ... antibiotics, mucus-thinning drugs and chest physical therapy, in ... which a therapist or family member drums the person's chest and ... back with cupped hands to help clear mucus from the lungs. Older ... patients sometimes can do this therapy themselves, and machines are ... now available that can vibrate the chest to help loosen mucus. In ... severe cases, a lung transplant may be an option. Digestive ... problems are treated with high-calorie diets, pancreatic enzymes ... and vitamin supplements. ... Other treatments are being t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7103-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7103_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:40:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/</link><title>Cystic Fibrosis</title><description>... Call your doctor if your child has symptoms suggestive of cystic ... fibrosis, such as frequent respiratory infections, persistent ... abdominal discomfort and gas, repeated episodes of diarrhea, greasy ... foul-smelling stools or poor weight gain in spite of a good ... appetite. ... Prognosis ... The life expectancy of people with cystic fibrosis depends on ... the severity of disease and the parts of the body involved. Lung ... disease has the strongest impact on the severity of the illness, ... and death usually is caused by lung complications. With regular ... monitoring and improved treatment, the average life span of a ... person with cystic fibrosis has increased to 35 years, although ... some people with mild symptoms live much longer. ... Additional Info ... ... National Heart, Lung and Blood Institute (NHLBI) 6701 ... Rockledge Dr. P.O. Box 30105 Bethesda, MD 20824-0105 Phone: (301) ... http://www.nhlbi.nih.gov/ ... ... Cystic Fibrosis Foundation 6931 Arlington Rd. Bethesda, MD ... 20814 Phone: (301) 951-4422 Toll... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7103-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7103_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:41:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/</link><title>Cystic Fibrosis</title><description>... The symptoms of cystic fibrosis usually appear within the first ... year of life, but sometimes may not appear until late childhood or ... adolescence. The severity of symptoms varies from person to person. ... Some people have severe symptoms involving various organs in the ... body. Others have much milder disease involving only one area of ... the body. ... At birth, a child with cystic fibrosis can develop a swollen ... belly and vomiting due to a condition called meconium ileus, in ... which the bowel is plugged up with meconium, a thick, dark, sticky ... substance produced by the intestines of all babies while still in ... the uterus. It’s just more sticky in a newborn ... with cystic fibrosis. ... As the child grows, other symptoms can develop, including: ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7103-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7103_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:41:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/</link><title>Cystic Fibrosis</title><description>... Your doctor may suspect cystic fibrosis based on your child's ... symptoms and medical history, a family history of cystic fibrosis, ... and the results of a physical examination. To confirm the ... diagnosis, your doctor will order a sweat test, a painless ... procedure that can diagnose cystic fibrosis by measuring the amount ... of salt in skin sweat. In newborns, who are too tiny to make enough ... sweat for a sweat test, a blood test can be done to confirm the ... diagnosis. Many states now routinely screen newborns for cystic ... fibrosis. ... Expected Duration ... Cystic fibrosis is a lifelong illness that requires careful ... monitoring. The severity of the illness typically varies over time, ... with intermittent periods of worsening symptoms that may require ... more intense medical treatment and even hospitalization. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7103-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7103_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:42:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/000107trt.html</link><title>Cystic fibrosis treatment</title><description>... Treatment An early diagnosis of CF and a comprehensive treatment plan can improve both survival and quality of life. Follow-up and monitoring are very important. If possible, patients should be cared for at cystic fibrosis specialty clinics, which can be found in many communities. When children reach adulthood, they should transfer to a cystic fibrosis specialty center for adults. Treatment for lung problems includes: Antibiotics to prevent and treat lung and sinus infections. They may be taken by mouth, or given in the veins or by breathing treatments. People with cystic fibrosis may take antibiotics only when needed, or all the time. Doses are usually higher than normal. Inhaled medicines to help open the airways DNAse enzyme therapy to thin mucus and make it easier to cough up High concentration of salt solutions (hypertonic saline) Flu vaccine and pneumococcal polysaccharide vaccine ( PPV ) yearly (ask your health care provider) Lung transplant is an option in some cases Oxygen therapy may b... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7103-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7103_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:43:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/encyclopedia/408/222.html</link><title>Cystic Fibrosis</title><description>... Cystic fibrosis (CF) is a chronic , progressive and genetic (inherited) disease of the body's exocrine (mucus producing) glands which affects approximately 30,000 children and adults in the United States. Cystic fibrosis (CF) primarily affects the respiratory , digestive and reproductive systems, as well as the sweat glands. The mucus secreted is very thick and blocks passageways in the lungs and digestive tracts. Cystic fibrosis is transmitted to a child when both parents carry the recessive gene but do not have the disease. When such a couple has children, there is a 25 percent chance that one of their children will develop cystic fibrosis; there is a 50 percent chance that the child will carry the gene, but will not have the disease; and a 25 percent chance that the child will be totally unaffected. Cystic fibrosis is the most common fatal hereditary disorder for Caucasians in the U.S. About 1 in 2500 Caucasians are affected, and more than 10 million people (one in 31 Americans; on... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7103-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7103_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:43:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/003409.html</link><title>Neonatal cystic fibrosis screening overview</title><description>... Definition Neonatal cystic fibrosis screening is a blood test that screens newborns for cystic fibrosis (CF). Cystic fibrosis is disease passed down through families that causes thick, sticky mucus to build up in the lungs and digestive tract. It can lead to breathing and digestive problems. Alternative Names Cystic fibrosis screening - neonatal; Immunoreactive trypsinogen; IRT test How the test is performed A sample of blood is either taken from the bottom of the baby's foot of a vein in the arm. A tiny drop of blood is collected onto a piece of filter paper and allowed to dry. The dried blood sample is sent to a lab for analysis. The blood sample is examined for increased levels of immunoreactive trypsinogen (IRT), a protein produced by the pancreas that is linked to CF. How the test will feel The brief feeling of discomfort will probably cause your baby to cry. Why the test is performed Children with CF who are diagnosed early in life and start treatment at a young age may have better nutri... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7103-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7103_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:44:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/18135-146.html</link><title>Cystic fibrosis</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7103-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7103_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:44:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/000107prv.html</link><title>Cystic fibrosis prevention</title><description>... Prevention There is no way to prevent cystic fibrosis. Screening those with a family history of the disease may detect the cystic fibrosis gene in 60 - 90% of carriers, depending on the test used. References Flume PA, Mogayzel PJ Jr, Robinson KA, Rosenblatt RL, Quittell L, Marshall BC; Clinical Practice Guidelines for Pulmonary Therapies Committee; Cystic Fibrosis Foundation Pulmonary Therapies Committee. Cystic fibrosis pulmonary guidelines: pulmonary complications: hemoptysis and pneumothorax. Am J Respir Crit Care Med. 2010 Aug 1;182(3):298-306. Farrell PM, Rosenstein BJ, White TB, et al. Guidelines for diagnosis of cystic fibrosis in newborns through older adults: Cystic fibrosis consensus report. Journal of Pediatrics . Aug 2008;153(2). Stallings VA, Stark LF, Robinson KA, Feranchak AP, Quinton H. Evidence-based practice recommendations for nutrition-related management of children and adults with cystic fibrosis and pancreatic insufficiency: Results of a systematic review. Journal of t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7103-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7103_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:45:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/000107.html</link><title>Cystic fibrosis overview</title><description>... Definition Cystic fibrosis is a disease passed down through families that causes thick, sticky mucus to build up in the lungs, digestive tract, and other areas of the body. It is one of the most common chronic lung diseases in children and young adults. It is a life-threatening disorder. See also: Cystic fibrosis - nutritional considerations Neonatal cystic fibrosis screening Causes, incidence, and risk factors Cystic fibrosis (CF) is caused by a defective gene which causes the body to produce abnormally thick and sticky fluid, called mucus. This mucus builds up in the breathing passages of the lungs and in the pancreas, the organ that helps to break down and absorb food. This collection of sticky mucus results in life-threatening lung infections and serious digestion problems. The disease may also affect the sweat glands and a man's reproductive system. Millions of Americans carry the defective CF gene, but do not have any symptoms. That's because a person with CF must inherit two defective ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>