<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7104">How to go from New York to Montreal</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:45:40" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7104-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7104_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:45:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/lifestyle-26272-5.html</link><title>New York City Bans Trans Fats</title><description>... The New York City Board of Health passed a ban on trans fats in December. This widely used fat has been linked to heart disease . This ban, the first on a food item approved by the Food and Drug Administration (FDA), requires restaurants to eliminate trans fats from all of their foods by July 2008. They must stop using frying oils that contain trans fat by July of 2007. This ban is a controversial step towards better health in a city many associate with great food. Some argue that Mayor Michael Bloomberg is trying to legislate people’s diets. However, trans fats have been found to have an adverse effect on cholesterol levels because they lower your good cholesterol level while raising your bad cholesterol level. Trans fat consumption has been associated with an increased risk of heart disease. In fact, the FDA now requires all food manufacturers to include trans fat on the nutrition facts panel of all foods. Trans fats are used for frying and baking and are found in many com... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7104-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7104_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:46:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/486637/102085</link><title>I am looking for an RA support group in Queens, New York or Nassau County, New York. help?</title><description>...   ... Thank you ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7104-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7104_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:46:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/sara-nash-comics-baltimore-427485-5.html</link><title>The Spa Treatment of Rheumatology Appointments Comic</title><description>... Read the full text of The Spa Treatment of Rheumatology Appointments and leave a comment!   See all of Sara's Baltimore Comics     Visit The Single Gal's Guide to Rheumatoid Arthritis ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7104-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7104_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:47:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/856884/140808</link><title>can i get cesamet for chronic pain in new jersey or new york I have been suffering from myofacial pain syndrome for 2 years thanks for your help</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7104-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7104_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:47:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/237383/136677</link><title>can i get a new refill if my pain medication was stolen? what is the new york state law concerning this?</title><description>... someone stole my pain medication. what do i have to do? what is the ny state law concerning this? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7104-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7104_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:48:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/headache-specialists/new-york-39958-5.html</link><title>Alexander Mauskop, M.D. - New York Migraine and Headache Specialists</title><description>... Doctor: Alexander Mauskop, M.D. Clinic/Facility: The New York Headache Center Address: 30 East 76th Street New York, NY 10021 Telephone: (212) 794-3550 Recommendation: Patient Feedback Comments: Disclosure: This clinic has a commercial interest in Migra-Lieve. Statement from their web site: "We have a commercial relationship with this company and help to promote this product." ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7104-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7104_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:48:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/headache-specialists/new-york-39960-5.html</link><title>Derek Randall, M.D. - New York Migraine and Headache Specialists</title><description>... Doctor: Derek Randall, M.D. Clinic/Facility: Mount Sinai Medical Center Address: 20 East 35th St. New York, NY 10019 Telephone: 212-689-5616 Recommendation: Patient Feedback ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7104-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7104_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:49:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/headache-specialists/new-york-39964-5.html</link><title>Kejian Tang, M.D. - New York Migraine and Headache Specialists</title><description>... Doctor: Kejian Tang, M.D. Clinic/Facility: Neurological Associates of Northeastern New York Address: 1401 Union Street Schenectady, NY 12308-3009 Telephone: 518-381-1177 Recommendation: Medial Professional Recommendation ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7104-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7104_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:49:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/headache-specialists/new-york-39962-5.html</link><title>Kenneth Schwartz, M.D. - New York Migraine and Headache Specialists</title><description>... Doctor: Kenneth Schwartz, M.D. Address: 35 Myrtle Street Saratoga Springs, NY 12866 Telephone: 518-587-9557 Recommendation: Patient Feedback Comments: Dr. Schwartz is a family practice physician with a special interest in treating headaches and Migraine disease. He regularly participates in continuing education in the field and has been highly recommended by patients. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7104-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7104_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:50:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/headache-specialists/new-york-39954-5.html</link><title>Richard B. Brooks, M.D. - New York Migriane and Headache Specialists</title><description>... Doctor: Richard B. Brooks, M.D. Clinic/Facility: Neurological Associates of Northeastern New York Address: 1401 Union Street Schenectady, NY 12308-3009 Telephone: 518-381-1177 Recommendation: Medial Professional Recommendation ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>