<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7105">dark knight rises dvd</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:50:44" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7105-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7105_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:50:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/786646/141314</link><title>mam i m 24 years old.Since last 5-6 months my menstral cycle is disturbed as the flow is vry thick and of dark color.Tests showed abnormal rise in prolactin harmone.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7105-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7105_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:51:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/786646/141313</link><title>mam i m 24 years old.Since last 5-6 months my menstral cycle is disturbed as the flow is vry thick and of dark color.Tests showed abnormal rise in prolactin harmone.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7105-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7105_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:51:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/70293/33320/eye-darkness</link><title>Eye of Darkness</title><description>...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ... THE EYE OF DARKNESS ...   ... BY ...   ... KATIE MARIE LAWRENCE ...   ... (MARYA U. PYREK) ...   ... COPYRIGHT 1995 ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ...   ... ABSTRACT- This is an autobiographical essay.  It was written while  living with conflictual emotions both during and after hospitalization.  By writing such as account, I hope to instill in readers an understanding of the emotions experienced during a mental illness.  The primary objective is for this material to be used for educational purposes, assisting students focusing their studies in the area of mental illness and by broadening their existing knowledge, which in turn will widen their viewpoints.  I also hope that this essay may be used for research purposes.  I hope to present ‘a view from the... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7105-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7105_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:52:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/32624/18808/light</link><title>darkness and light</title><description>...     That last journal entry just made me sad, it's the truth and it just touches the tip of the iceberg of pain it represents.     The United States of America land built on genocide and slavery, did it ever end? I think not...Theories and suspicions, I think the USA government and the British monarchy were behind the rise of Adolf Hitler and the death camps to make money off all the sides of the war machine and the wholesale slaughter of millions, liquidating bank accounts, insurance fraud, clearing the land and pulling out gold teeth, and ways not even I can think of. When I was a child I blamed the general public of Germany now I think you can brainwash the general public into thinking whatever you want them to think. Ofcourse you can't fool all of the people all of the time.   I don't fall for any of it. I know you can say I'm paranoid schizophrenic...Pain...to spread Aids who does this but the most inhumane people on earth...... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7105-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7105_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:52:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/77780/161715/desperation-seemingly-rising</link><title>Desperation seemingly rising...</title><description>...   ... I've been laid off... all my dreams that I dared to dream because I dared to hope that I'd see a wonderful light at the end of the proverbial long cold dark tunnel was sniffed out ... and now I will receive absolutely no Unemployment Compensation because in NC, the employers pay the Unemployment Insurance Tax and/or fee. ...   ... From January 2012 until end of March 2013 (my "base period" for any current potential Unemployment claim)... absolutely not one employer paid any for and/or on me. ...   ... From January 2012 until August 2012, I was unemployed after 2 years of admin work with a MH/SA/DD agency.  So, because I was unemployed via no fault of my own and UE paid into, I drew Unemployment Compensation for upwards of 8 months. ...   ... However; from August 2012 until end of March 2013, I was employed as a 1099 Independent with another MH/SA agency and he - of course - did not pay ANY unemployment insurance tax and/or fee. ...   ... I took the job bec... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7105-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7105_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:53:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/138553/communities</link><title>Finding Support through Online Communities: The Good, the Bad, and the Ugly</title><description>...   ... This is one of those posts that I feel compelled to write just to get my thoughts out into the open.  I often find that I gain a clarity by processing events through writing so here goes. ...   ... I have personally been involved with online communities and forums for well over a decade now.  This started when my youngest son was diagnosed with autism .  It was then that I turned to the Internet for help. I joined multiple email groups and forums and tried to settle in with those which were a right fit for me.  I met some incredible people who helped me, a stranger on the Internet, on my journey as a parent of a child with special needs.  In time these people became like family.  ...   ... There is a deep bond which develops with people who are sharing a similar experience and especially one which is so emotional.  You are with people who "get it" and for whom you don't have to explain things.  They just know.  ...   ... I had the ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7105-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7105_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:53:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/26960/king-corn</link><title>Corn Might Be Linked to Obesity</title><description>... epidemic didn't just happen. The people who study the statistics agree ... with Dr. David Ludwig of Children's Hospital and Harvard Medical School ... that before the early 1970s, the prevalence of obesity was relatively ... constant in the United States. As he told the 63rd Scientific Sessions of the American Diabetes Association since then there has been a dramatic ... increase. What ... could have triggered it? Other people have pointed the finger at ... several different possibilities. But one primary factor stands out: Your tax dollars at work. The ... beginning of the obesity epidemic coincides too close for comfort with ... what looked at the time like enlightened legislation. The Agriculture and Consumer Protection Act of 1973 established target ... prices and deficiency payments to replace former price support payments. Before that time, our government paid our farmers not to grow crops, as unbelievable as it sounds today. When farmers took ... some of their land out of production, the reduced supp... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7105-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7105_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:54:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/93829/140963/auditory</link><title>Silence (on auditory hallucinations)</title><description>... Silence ...   ... No light breaks through the bleak darkness- ... Not even the moon or the stars are visible ... Through the dense fog outside my window- ... An eerie silence echoes about- ... While the rest of the world sleeps- ... There is a song inside my mind ... Singing a jovial tune- ... Gusts of wind rush throughout the ... Branches on the trees outside my window- ... A pleasing sound- not threatening as would be ... The sound of a multitude of people talking- ... The sound of silence is safe- ... Interrupted perhaps by voices only I can hear, while ... I can hear the ticking of the clock- ... I can hear the windows rattling in the wind and ... Rain falling upon the pavement ten stories below- ... These are welcome sounds and ... Knowing I am safe in my solitude- Is a welcome feeling, and ... I would dance upon the ceiling if I could and ... If I could I would wish the world away, and ... I would become the sole survivor. As the wind blows and the rain falls, ... I am reminded that I am not alone and ... When the sun rises above the skyline, ... This world shall c... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7105-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7105_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:54:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/368767/119925/plethora</link><title>Peaks, Valleys and Villages – The Plethora</title><description>...   ... Travel in the darkness ... Travel in the sun ... Travel in the light of being ... But, travel. ...   ... I love people. Having fibromyalgia, chronic fatigue syndrome and myofascial pain from unrelenting trigger points in my muscles doesn't change this fact of my life. ...   ... There are valleys, peaks and villages that make getting inside me intriguing. But mostly, it's about growing. Focusing only on setbacks and triumphs can stagnate who I am, like a river with no flow. ...   ... I see the valley as the peep hole that sometimes describes my life; I understand that though the hole is small, the vision is vast. It is a comforting warranty for better times; it is where I sometimes reside until I can identify the lessons. If I embrace that a valley is where animals come to escape the bitter cold of the peaks, where life thrives through a cycle, if I let it be my gathering place and stand still, I will feel the energy rise up through my feet. Then I will I kiss my passion, embrace my... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7105-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7105_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:55:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/93829/123448/innerself</link><title>Awaken- innerself</title><description>... Awaken ...   ... Red is the fire that rages within me- ... Black is the darkness that sears my soul- dead as night- ... Riding bareback upon a phantasmal comet- across the midnight sky- ... Venus glances –somewhere within the periphery of the universe- ... My fantasies awaken and come to life, as ... I fight the demons that disdainfully plague my spirit. ...   ... The moon is full before the sun rises- ... Stark white against that sky- ... Violet in hue as magenta clouds ... Hover above the horizon- I would soar if I had wings-and ... I would lift those wings and fly above the mountain tops- ... Only to escape from a world that terrifies me- ... The rising sun stares wickedly into my eyes as it chases away the night- ... While the sky turns a bright shade of cerulean blue- ...   ... Sapphire is the shade of the living dead arising-the color green is the essence of life- ... Viridian in its hue is the grass that grows ... Beneath my feet- Gray- are my tears cried for the trials of yesterday- ... Mysteriously darkening as the tears I weep for tomo... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>