<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7106">active learning survey</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:56:04" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7106-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7106_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:56:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/caregiver-2081-143.html</link><title>The Alzheimer's Foundation of America- Q&amp;A on Caregiving with founder Eric Hall</title><description>... The Alzheimer’s Foundation of America (AFA) released the findings of their I CAN: Investigating Caregivers' Attitudes and Needs survey. The survey uncovered significant trends among caregivers of Alzheimer’s patients, including a link between the stigma associated with the disease and dramatic delays in Alzheimer’s diagnosis. The AFA found that caregivers are in dire need of support and educational resources, and that despite the burdens of this tragic disease, caregivers often felt they came out stronger and more compassionate as a result of caring for a loved one. Our Alzheimer's spoke with Eric Hall, the president of the AFA, to hear more about the survey, what the AFA learned about caregivers, and what we can do to improve the quality of Alzheimer’s care in this country. A-I: Why did the AFA embark on this project of surveying the caregivers of Alzheimer’s patients? EH: The Alzheimer’s Foundation of America (AFA), as the nation’s l... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7106-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7106_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:56:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/5949/151600/fibromyalgia</link><title>Dual Fibromyalgia Surveys Reveal Surprising Results</title><description>... The results of a unique set of dual surveys were released last week by the American Chronic Pain Association (ACPA) in partnership with Forest Laboratories, Inc.  The two national surveys compared the general public's perceptions with the private realities of people with fibromyalgia.  Some of the results were pleasantly surprising. One of the biggest surprises, at least for those of us who have lived with FM for many years, was that people with fibromyalgia inaccurately believe the public views them negatively.  Actually, 41 percent of the general public believes people with fibromyalgia are courageous, while only 17 percent of people who have FM believe society views them this way. By contrast, 66 percent of people with FM think society views them as complainers but only nine percent of the general public actually described them that way.  People with FM listed "complainers," "weak" and "lazy" as the top traits they think the public ascribes to them.  In fact,... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7106-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7106_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:57:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/896502/145318/americans</link><title>Survey Finds Many Americans Are Trying to Make Healthier Food Choices</title><description>... Views on Importance of Diet and Exercise ... Seventy-three percent of women said diet and nutrition was very important, as compared to 59% of men. Women (65%) and men (61%) voiced a more similar view that exercise is very important.  Interestingly, diet and nutrition became much more of a focus as people aged. For instance, 50% of those ages 18-24 said their dietary choices were important, as compared to 76% of respondents who were 65 years old and older. Nutrition also was more of a focus for those who had completed a higher level of education. ... The realization of the importance of diet and nutrition has increased in both men and women over time. In 1991, about 40% of men said their diet was impo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7106-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7106_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:57:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/896502/145202/commitment</link><title>ADA Survey Examines Glimpse into Americans' Commitment to Diet, Exercise</title><description>... ADA researchers classified responses into three groups. These groups are: ... ... I’m already doing it. This group already tries to make healthy food choices and incorporates exercise into their daily routine. This group was mostly female and they considered nutrition to be very important. This group often is living with someone who is on a diet for medical reasons and also is more apt to use magazines to learn about nutrition. ... I know I should . This group, which was comprised primarily of people age 35-54, realizes they should make exercise and a healthy diet a priority, but fall... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7106-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7106_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:58:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/849319/116753/number-prescription</link><title>Survey Finds Switching Schools to Be Best Non-Prescription Option</title><description>...   ... ... 67% of parents rated drug therapy as the most effective treatment for their child with ADHD. ... ... ... 45% of parents surveyed reported that there was great benefit to switching their child’s school to one which was better able to handle their child’s challenges related to ADHD. ... ... ... 39% of parents felt that giving one instruction at a time was helpful. ... ... ... 37% responded that a private tutor or learning specialist was beneficial for their child. ... ... ... 35% of the parents reported that a structured schedule of activities was an effective strategy for their child. ... ...   ... In... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7106-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7106_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:58:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/5949/125542/fibromyalgia</link><title>Survey Shows Early Diagnosis Improves Fibromyalgia Outcomes</title><description>... ... Immediately – 19% ... Within one year – 22% ... 1 – 5 years – 31% ... More than 5 years – 23% ... ... Patients whose diagnosis was delayed were more likely to report severe symptoms.  For those whose diagnosis took five years or more, 68% reported their symptoms as severe, compared to 42% of those diagnosed within a year.  The top three reasons given for the delay in diagnosis were: ... ... 50% said their healthcare provider didn't automatically connect their symptoms with FM. ... 48% were not aware of fibromyalgia as a condition. ... 47% said their individual symptoms were treated as separate conditions. ... ... Another important... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7106-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7106_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:58:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/38695/27141/anxiety-widespread</link><title>Social Anxiety Disorder Survey Reveals Severity of Impact of Widespread Disorder</title><description>... Anxiety Disorders Association of America (ADAA) provides up-close and personal ... insight into the severe effects of social anxiety disorder.  ...   ... The survey conducted by Harris Interactive focuses on ... romantic and personal relationships, feelings of isolation and shame ... surrounding this disorder, and the positive benefits of treatment.  The survey also draws attention to the delay ... in obtaining treatment for this disorder and/or not seeking treatment at all: ... 36% report experiencing symptoms for a decade or more before seeking help; and, ... another 15% are not currently treating their condition.  These findings are troubling for the ADAA, a ... nonprofit organization dedicated to educating the public of all anxiety ... disorders and supporting treatment effectiveness for disorder management and ... cure. ...   ... Social Anxiety Disorder (SAD) affects 15 million Americans ... and is the second most widespread of all anxiety disorders (afte... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7106-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7106_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:59:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/education-260201-5.html</link><title>Learning Styles</title><description>... What Are Learning Styles   People tend to perceive information in different ways and this has an impact on how we learn. For example, some people are visual learners, they learn better if they can “see” the information. Other people may learn better through hearing, or touch. Although each of us is able to learn through all of the different learning styles, a person will learn and retain information easier through their learning style.   Most people will learn through more than one learning style, however, they will learn best through a specific style. This is not to say the will not combine different ways of learning, for example, although someone may learn best through seeing, they may find that both listening to a lecture and seeing the words together provide the best way for them to learn.     Why Are Learning Styles Important   Understanding your learning style is certainly important in a school setting. It can help in studying for upcoming tests... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7106-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7106_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 22:59:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/c/7986/73047/learn-fasting</link><title>Learn How to Eat by . . . Fasting</title><description>...   ... Fasting means going entirely without food and just making do with (plenty of) water. A fast can be as brief as 12 hours or as long as weeks, though the most common duration is between 18 and 72 hours. ...   ... I advocate brief periods of fasting for its many health benefits, such as reduction of blood pressure and blood sugar, reduction of inflammatory responses, weight loss, and reduced heart attack risk. Populations who fast enjoy less heart disease. The Mormons, for instance, who fast for 24 hours every 30 days, were shown to have 20-40% reduced likelihood of coronary disease and diabetes in a recent survey.  ...   ... How can fasting teach you any lessons about food and eating? People who fast will tell you that the experience: ...   ... --Helps you appreciate food tastes when you resume eating. After a fast, flavors are stronger; sensations like sweet, sweet, or salty are sharper; you become reacquainted with food textur... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7106-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7106_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:00:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/5319/14118/speak-diabetese</link><title>Learning to Manage Your Diabetes</title><description>... For patients with diabetes, learning about managing your disease is like learning a new language -- but often health professionals assume that what one might understand the other one will too.   Wrong! Diabetes affects people in all walks of life in different ways. Your diabetes team endeavors to work closely with them to manage these complex medical conditions. Often, (as noted by poor adherence to recommended treatment) there is a breakdown in communication between the patient and provider.   Communication is key factor in conveying disease management issues. However, a 1993 national adult literacy survey found that nearly one-third of people in the United States are unable to read and understand basic health-related materials because of various factors.   Another study found that among people with diabetes at a public hospital in the U.S., 38 percent had low health literacy. For people with low educational attainment, older people, and ethnic minorities, low health lit... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>