<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7107">grimm episodes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:00:44" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7107-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7107_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:00:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/692176/163082/disneyworld</link><title>DisneyWorld and the Disabled: a Modern oh so Grimm Fairy Tale</title><description>...      Walt Disney has inacted a new policy (*See CNN.com "Disney tightens up resort disablility program") beginning this October regarding how it deals with wait times for the disabled. I personally was unaware of their original 'Resort Program,' but I've always been able to get on quicker via the exit for Splash and Thunder Mountain which was quite helpful. Those rides have narrow isles which are difficult to navigate with a wheelchair (electric or manual) plus they have consistantly long wait times which if I tried to walk, I'd never stand that long.  At Epcot, I've been able to enter through the exit at Space Ship Earth ('the ball' ride as my nephews call it), but most other rides, required me to wait in line with everyone else.  Sometimes I'd betransfer to a manual wheelchair because the isles were way too narrow for an electric to navigate (which is fine if you are lucky enough to have someone with you who will push you - my wrists, elbows, and artifi... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7107-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7107_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:01:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/question/360770/165482</link><title>Do you have to feel both manic episodes and depressed episodes equally to have bipolar disorder? I feel depressed much more. Is there another disorder I might have or is bipolar the most possible one?</title><description>... I have done research on bipolar disorder, and found that I feel the depression episodes much more frequently than symptoms of manic episodes. Do you have to feel both to have bipolar disorder? I feel the irritation/aggression part of manic episodes. I don't feel the hyperactivity as much. I feel the depressed part much more than both. Is there another disorder I might have or is bipolar the most possible one? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7107-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7107_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:01:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/question/906939/129949</link><title>Hi! Does hypomanic episodes have a connection with cognitive impairments in the long term? And is there any other cause for these impairments in bipolar patients besides the mood episodes?</title><description>... I´ve read manic and depressive episodes have this effect and that dementia is more common on elder bipolar individuals. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7107-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7107_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:02:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/706185/132784</link><title>I have paroxysmal afib, but only one episode has ever lasted more than 12 hours. All other episode last 15 minutes or less, most being 5 minutes or less.</title><description>... The doctor has suggested coumadin or the new medicine. But if afib episodes are so short, is there really that much risk? I score 0 on the CHADS ranking. No congestive heart failure, no hypertension, I am 53 years old, I do not have diabetes, and no history of blood clots. I do have a stent in my LAD. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7107-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7107_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:02:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/374548/120053</link><title>My mom was having episodes of her heart racing, and super low blood-preasure they thought it was due to her thiroid, but they changed her meds. 2 weeks ago, and episodes are comimg back? thoughts?</title><description>... could this be a pre-cursor to a heart attack? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7107-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7107_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:03:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/question/727801/140870</link><title>Is it possible to be diagnosed with Bipolar after only six months of suffering from the symptoms and what appears to be one long-term depressed episode and one short-term (3 weeks) manic episode?</title><description>... From around February this year up to now I've had nearly all the symptoms of Bipolar at some point or another. At first it seemed like just uni-polar depression but then I had a short but quite extreme period of elation. My councillor then suggested that Bipolar is a possibility so when I have my next psychiatric appointment I'm going to bring that up and talk to them about it. But I was just wondering is a six month period of time and the way I've described my symptoms enough to be diagnosed? Or would they want to see how I was after a year or so before starting any treatment? Also I'm only 17 which makes getting a diagnosis of any kind hard because no-one wants to "label" a minor. I'm asking because in some ways I want to be diagnosed, so I can begin medication or therapy or whatever it is that will help me get better because at the moment I'm only getting worse and worse everyday. Thanks. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7107-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7107_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:03:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/190665/137260</link><title>Can recurring episodes of cluster headaches cause accumulative optic nerve damage in one eye or is a 5 year old head injury a better cause for it? 39 yr Female-just recovered from a 3 mo. episode.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7107-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7107_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:04:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/374548/120052</link><title>My mom was having episodes of her heart racing, and super low blood-preasure they thought it was due to her thiroid, but they changed her meds. 2 weeks ago, and episodes are comimg back? thoughts?</title><description>... could this be a pre-cursor to a heart attack? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7107-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7107_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:04:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/question/79099/37641</link><title>what is a mania episode and what is a hypomanic episode</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7107-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7107_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:05:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/202/148622/frequent-migraine</link><title>Frequent Nausea in Episodic Migraine</title><description>...     ... The AMPP is the largest study of Migraine and headache sufferers ever conducted in the United States. Beginning in 2004, questionnaires were sent to 120,000 selected homes of which close to 163,000 Americans over the age of 12 responded. Researchers then followed 24,000 participants who had at least one severe Migraine during the previous year and met the requirements according to the International Headache Society's International Classification of Headache Disorders, 2 nd edition. Episodic Migraine (EM) is defined as having fewer than 15 headache days a month. ...   ... Participants fr... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>