<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7108">renting car seattle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:05:44" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7108-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7108_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:05:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/71325/32234/sleepless</link><title>Not in Seattle, but still Sleepless</title><description>...   ... I'm living on my own for the first time, still in college, but not living in my parents house.  I'm trying to figure out what this whole being an adult thing is supposed to be like.  I'm looking for a job, so that I can contribute to the rent that my parents are so generously providing for me.  ...   ... Everything should be wonderful, but for the life of me I cannot sleep.  I have done everything short of take drugs or pay someone to hit me over the head each night.  I have prayed, I have a white noise machine, I have drunk camomille tea, I have had a glass of wine, I have exercised right before bed, I have tried reading, I have used deep breathing, I have tried focusing on a single word or phrase... ...   ...   ... The thing is... I don't want to take another d... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7108-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7108_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:06:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/444306/164635/car-project</link><title>car project</title><description>...   ... Have to keep going.  They gave me the rental car for half off which was the insurance rate, so that is very nice. ...   ... I will tell you, inside, I feel I "should have" found one by now.  Even though it has only been two weeks.  I just feel I need to be perfect and also don't like the pressure of waiting....but I can rent the car if I have to another week and it will only the the cost of two weeks with the discount... ...   ...  I need faith, calm and carry on.   Carry on, one task at a time.  I got the check all ready to go from the insurance, paid my rent, have been keeping up my home, and seeing cars.  Day by day.  Have to just acknowledge the fear sometimes and let it go, knowing that I will find the right one soon. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7108-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7108_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:06:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/44/3435/car-wars</link><title>Car Wars</title><description>... ... Take my recent car purchase: Ever since that December trip to Florida, I have been spending as much energy on purchasing a car as I have facing my long January list of medical check-ups. That trip made me realize that it was time to replace my gas-guzzling (17-mpg highway), mechanically capricious 13-year-old van with something I could drive safely and afar. ... ... It started with a Chevy Malibu I rented in December. The renta... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7108-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7108_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:07:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/accident-riding-compact-1776</link><title>I was in a car accident while riding in a compact car.</title><description>... I was in a car accident while riding in a compact car. My knees hit the glove box and I tore the PCL of my left knee. My diagnosis is PCL insufficiency. What does this mean? The posterior cruciate ligament (PCL) is one of the major ligaments inside the knee. It helps hold the knee joint steady during motion so that the thighbone and lower leg bone move and glide without shifting. Ligaments are not very elastic. When they are torn or damaged, they don’t “spring” back. Instead, scar tissue fills in the torn area and weakness occurs. This loss of strength is called PCL insufficiency. The ligament is unable to do its job to move, hold, and protect the joint. Reference: Michael J. Strobel, MD, et al. Arthroscopic Evaluation of Articular Cartilage Lesions in Posterior Cruciate Ligament-Deficient Knees. In Arthroscopy. March 2003. Vol. 19. No. 3. Pp. 262-268.' ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7108-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7108_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:07:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/208999/148785</link><title>my husband begins to itch and burn while sitting on my car seat. This does not happen anywhere else. the seats in his car are leather and he is not affected. Mine are cloth.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7108-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7108_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:08:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/116161/99666</link><title>can an ederly person have a delayed stroke from a car wreckwhich car flipped</title><description>... the emergency room same day but continued to have problems, such ... as excessive sleeping, dragging left leg, slugged speech and choking ... and coughing when eating. Taken back to E.R. 4 days later and ct scan ... showed she had a stroke.  An mri was also done and she had stroke on ...  right side of brain, which effects the left side of body.  She is now in a ... rehab again. She will probably live in a nursing home, as she has no family. ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7108-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7108_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:09:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/175833/61717</link><title>Where can I rent a TENS machine in the Tacoma area?</title><description>... Need info on how and where to rent the machine.... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7108-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7108_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:09:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/26837/93651/frustrated</link><title>Frustrated with renting</title><description>... I'm so frustrated with my landlord. He's good about most things, but really bad about the rent. I have been living here over 2 years and in that time have had rent paid in full no more than 2 days past the 1st of the month. Also, me being late on rent has been very rare. Due to being out of town for a couple days then being sick on top of that, I didnt get rent paid until today. Granted, I should have communicated my situation better but the landlord was not at all understanding. He wouldn't listen to anything I had to say then decided to put a $10 per day late fee if rent is ever late again. I could understand that if I was constantly late, but I'm not. I understand being a landlord is hard, but even the big rental complexes give their tenants a little leway once in a while. Thanks for "listening" to me vent. Things like this tend to get me down if I don't get it out. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7108-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7108_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:09:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/850274/139878/apartment</link><title>rent room, apartment, townhome, home</title><description>...   ... I don't think many places are other than that. I am sure I need more information. I am just very scared. Not enough support. ...   ... I don't want to move.  I love Charlie the cat so much.  Sounds strange but I really have so much comfort with him-and even my roommate, she is such a routine person and I think that helps me, as much as I have vented about her. I have my cat Lucy. I have just grown comfortable here, except the noise. And I am tired of change and change and change. ...   ... My roommate and I are friendly again.  We both apologized. ...   ... I am just confused over and over.   ...   ... Renting a room may be difficult with my cat.  Plus, no place for any of my stuff.  Then pay for storage. ...   ... I guess I feel depressed.   ...   ... Scared. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7108-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7108_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:10:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/question/367717/90473</link><title>i need help finding a appartment or house for rent that is able to meet my needs from ms</title><description>... need first floor as little stairs as possiple centeral air for cooling in the warm weather ... and warm in the extremly cold weather. need 3 bedroom and needs to be in new bedford mass ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>