<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7109">best place to eat pho in new york</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:10:41" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7109-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7109_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:10:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/sara-nash-comics-baltimore-296222-5.html</link><title>Single With Rheumatoid Arthritis in Another City Comic</title><description>... Read the full text of " Single with Rheumatoid Arthritis... In Another City! " and leave a comment !   See all of Sara's Comics   Visit the Single Gal's Guide to Rheumatoid Arthritis ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7109-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7109_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:11:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/59238/119359/apple-city-kids</link><title>The Relationship Between Obesity and Socioeconomic Status in New York City</title><description>... The snacks they prefer are higher in calories than they were 20 years ago ... The average teen gets 37% of their calories outside the home ... Teens get 17% of their calories from fast food ... Most kids/teens drink 3 cans of soda/day ... Most teen boys eat 34 teaspoons of sugar/day ... About half of a teen's weekly diet is junk food ...   ... An average teen girl eats 5467 calories of junk food/fast food weekly ... An average teen boy eats 9891 calories of junk food/fast food weekly ...   ... And the prize for the heaviest number of clinically obese teens (29%) in New York goes to....Corona, Queens.  The zip code in New York with the highest percentage of lean kids, belongs to the upper west side, 10069, which happens to be near Carnegie Hall and Central Park.  The median income there is double that of Corona, and there are more healthy supermarkets offering fresh selections of whole foods.  Washington Heights, Bushwick, Inwood and Harlem all... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7109-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7109_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:11:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/59238/123465/york-commissioner</link><title>New York Health Department Skews Facts in Soda Ad</title><description>... New York City's Health Department seems to have added their own spin to the whole soda and obesity discussion , in an effort to really inspire consumers to abandon sugary soda drinks.  According to a recent New York Post column, a significant number of discussions took place behind the scenes at the New York Health Department to discuss the merits of releasing negative ads about soda consumption that may not have been fully supported by science.  The slogan that you can "gain 10 pounds a year by consuming soda as a part of your daily diet" has not been fully vetted scientifically, though many experts have claimed to support the notion that daily consumption of sugary drinks does pack on the pounds and may ultimately be one significant contributing factor in the current obesity epidemic.  Hurling (scientifically) unsubstantiated claims to a citywide ad campaign that originates from a city health department is not good science business .  One top Assistant Commissioner... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7109-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7109_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:12:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/11/9722/living-cancer</link><title>Living with Cancer: The Survivor Monologues</title><description>... While I turn often to New York magazine when I need advice on where to eat or shop or what museum to visit when I’m on my way to Manhattan, I don’t often find the cover stories as compelling as the one in this week’s issue. The theme is “ The Survivor Monologues: Life After Diagnosis .” The cover art itself, 143 cancer patients and survivors who gathered in Central Park, sends a powerful message: there are millions of us out there, of various ages and races and shapes and professions, living and coping after cancer. The longest piece, by one of the magazine’s own editors, Jon Gluck, was the most moving. He tells how he was diagnosed, at age 37, with bone marrow cancer, and the toll it took on him, and his family, as seen from his vantage point now, three years later. While his story is universal—he’s a young, healthy, newly-married man, the father of a seven-month old daughter, then he gets cancer and his life changes in an instant—he tells it in a compelling way. The other pie... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7109-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7109_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:12:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/156121/78535</link><title>when my 15mos old sleeps in a new place she vommits. what should I do?</title><description>... we went on an overnite trip when she was 13 months and every time i put her to bed she would throw up. I would clean her up she would cry some more &amp; eventually sleep. Now we are getting ready to take another trip for a week. what should I do to prevent this extreme reaction to sleeping in a new place? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7109-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7109_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:13:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/26399/36837/place</link><title>New To This Place</title><description>... Well Hello to eveyone out there.  This is the first time I have tried to vent like this.  It was recommended by a close friend.  Well I had been diagnosed with Bipolar Disorder Manic Depression Anxiety and a few other things to make it sound absolutely nutty. I am not sure when to start but maybe from the begining.  I have a story and its a bit long.  I had a normal childhood for the most part.  Over protective mother and was molested when I was a young girl.  Now that I look back at it It all started when I hit my teen years.  I started to rage out.  Had bad mood swings, did risky things.  Fought alot with my parents and was over emotional.  Well I turned 18 and moved out.  Moved in with what I thought was the love of my life and over time I had 3 beautiful kids.  But with each pregnancy i had notice more and more I was depressed. I never did anything bad like try or even think of hurting my kids.  But I guess my e... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7109-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7109_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:13:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/2929/sh-keeping-quiet</link><title>Diabetes and the Work Place. How lying about your condition could get you fired.</title><description>... If you work for someone else – or even think that you might some day – you might not want to let people outside your family know that you have diabetes. But it’s a tough call. When other people know that you have diabetes, they can help you in many ways. Especially if they have diabetes themselves, they can share their knowledge and experience. They can warn you if they see signs that you’re going hypo. I can think of only one reason why you might not want others to know that you have diabetes. It can get you fired. It certainly happens, as a long and disturbing article in The New York Times on Boxing Day details. When one employee in Wisconsin asked where he could dispose of his insulin needles, the company fired him. An Oregon company fired a woman who had asked to eat at her desk to control her blood glucose. And more. But if they ask you whether you have diabetes, it would be worse to deny it. Nothing can get you fired quicker than lying. And while you might have some legal recour... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7109-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7109_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:14:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/89/48356/change-place</link><title>A Change of Place and Mind</title><description>...   ... People who don't know me well came up with myriad reasons why I shouldn't be doing this.... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7109-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7109_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:14:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/lifestyle-26272-5.html</link><title>New York City Bans Trans Fats</title><description>... The New York City Board of Health passed a ban on trans fats in December. This widely used fat has been linked to heart disease . This ban, the first on a food item approved by the Food and Drug Administration (FDA), requires restaurants to eliminate trans fats from all of their foods by July 2008. They must stop using frying oils that contain trans fat by July of 2007. This ban is a controversial step towards better health in a city many associate with great food. Some argue that Mayor Michael Bloomberg is trying to legislate people’s diets. However, trans fats have been found to have an adverse effect on cholesterol levels because they lower your good cholesterol level while raising your bad cholesterol level. Trans fat consumption has been associated with an increased risk of heart disease. In fact, the FDA now requires all food manufacturers to include trans fat on the nutrition facts panel of all foods. Trans fats are used for frying and baking and are found in many com... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7109-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7109_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:15:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/9472/kids-york-times-wrong</link><title>Antipsychotics in Kids: The New York Times Gets it Completely Wrong</title><description>... On Feb 1 this year, I turned up for a speaking engagement to NAMI San Diego. But first, the person who runs these meetings had two sad announcements: An individual who attended a nearby DBSA support group had committed suicide, and an advocate involved in NAMI in California had died of anorexia.   We bowed our heads in a brief moment of silence.   Last week , in a state of partial amnesia, in response to a New York Times story, I questioned the wisdom of a psychiatrist treating 12-year-old Anya Bailey, who had anorexia, with an antipsychotic. “ Bad decision,” I wrote. “Antipsychotics are never to be prescribed lightly. They are built for extremely serious mental disorders, usually in emergency situations, and come fully-loaded with onerous side effects.”   I also wrote: “Bipolar kids are not anorexic teens … Something very serious and in dire need of medical intervention is going on.”   My blog left the clear impression that anorexia is only a minor teen malady – ce... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>