<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7110">civil engineering jobs pennsylvania</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:15:37" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7110-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7110_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:15:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/146513/141156</link><title>I have been at a steel mill for 2 months working 50-60 hrs per week as a materials engineer and I feel like I cannot go in. I am homesick and depressed and I don't know why? Can you help me?</title><description>... I am a new graduate with a masters degree in Materials Engineering. My work and internships with the exception of 1 internship has been in nanotechnology. I left graduate school because I did not like the long hours of research and working on 1 project for 2 years. I have tried something new and I am working at a steel mill as a metallurgist (a professional) if you will and I am salaried. Its been nearly 2 months and I thought I was used to this job, but lately I have been feeling like I don't know why I am here; I am always anxious in the morning and though I get sleep; I dont want to go to work in the morning and I feel sad and depressed. My parents came to visit over the July 4th weekend and that made me homesick for the first time in my life. What is wrong with me? Also, I am working between 50-60 hrs per week which is normal at this job and I feel like I just made a mistake. Help me? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7110-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7110_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:16:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/1443/163631/domestic-partnerships</link><title>Marriage vs. Civil Unions vs. Domestic Partnerships</title><description>...   ... Some states, Colorado, Hawaii and Illinois allow civil unions. Oregon and Nevada have broad domestic partnerships. And WI has a limited domestic partnership. While these types of arrangements offer some legal protections, they do not provide the same benefits that marriage does. ...   ... Marriage ...   ... When two people marry, they are considered “family.” Under the law, they are provided with certain rights and responsibilities, for example, joint parental rights of children, “next-of-kin” visits in hospitals and the right to make medical decisions, joint filing of tax returns, rights to federal benefits such as Medicare and Social Security. These are just a few of the... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7110-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7110_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:16:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/index-3259-149.html</link><title>Americans with Disabilities Act</title><description>... ... Has your child been rejected by a preschool or excluded from a ... field trip because a teacher was afraid to use his or her EpiPen? ... Does a moldy carpet at work or school make you sick? Does stale ... smoke in offices, hotel rooms or conference centers make it hard ... for you to take part in routine business activities? ... The Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA) is a civil rights law ... that gives you the right to ask for changes where policies, ... practices or conditions exclude or disadvantage you. As of January ... 26, 1992, public entities and public accommodations must ensure ... that individuals with disabilities have full access to and equal ... enjoyment of all facilities, programs, goods and services. ... The ADA borrows from Section 504 of the Rehabilitation Act of ... 1973. Section 504 prohibits discrimination on the basis of ... disability in employment and education in agencies, programs and ... services that receive federal money. The ADA extends many of the ... ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7110-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7110_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:17:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/31385/37637</link><title>Does anyone know of a Support Group for depression in the Bucks County, Pennsylvania area?</title><description>... This is for my husband.  He is absolutely falling apart from depression.  As I write this, he is crying.  He said he gets no joy in anything, feels like if it wasn't for me and our kids, he would have taken his own life by now.  He just wants to get out of pain.  I have tried to convince him to check himself into a hospital but he refuses due to his job, responbilities, etc.  He has been on medication after medication over the last 15 years and nothing seems to help.  I suggested a support group in our area and he seems good with that.  Does anyone know of anywhere in the Bucks County, Pennsylvania area for a support group??  Thank you!!  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7110-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7110_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:17:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/141334/occupations</link><title>Happy Jobs: Which Occupations Can Boost Your Mood?</title><description>...   ... The Least Stressful Occupations ...   ... Everyone experiences some stress on the job . But excessive stress can le... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7110-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7110_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:17:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/4182/142321/depressing-jobs</link><title>The Most Depressing Jobs</title><description>... I was drawn to one such survey. Actually it was reported in 2007 from an exercise conducted between 2004-06. Government researchers tracked the incidence of depression within 21 major job categories. Anyway, the upshot of the exercise was to say that people who look after the elderly and severely disabled have the highest rates of depression. Nearly 11 percent of personal care workers reported a period of depression lasting two or more weeks. ...   ... In the subsequent hierarchy of figures we learn that cooks, bartenders, waiters and waitresses had the second highest ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7110-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7110_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:18:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/157571/110284/stressful-jobs</link><title>The Top Ten Most Stressful Jobs in America</title><description>...   ... Recently CareerCast.com came up with a top ten list of the most stressful jobs in America. To come up with this list they came up with “Mega Factors” or what they felt were the most important factors to affect stress levels on the job. ...   ... Among the factors they looked at included: Work environment, job competitiveness, opportunity for ei... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7110-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7110_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:18:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/sleep-disorders/c/question/914072/111165</link><title>Job options?</title><description>... I have been diagnosed with idiopathic hypersomnia.  I am 33 and didn't develop sleeping problems until 7-8 years ago.  However, I need 9.5-10 hours sleep a night to be productive the next day.  I used to require more, but fortunately I found some safe, sleep medicines that help me alot: Ambesleep and Melatonin.  ... But now that I'm requiring this much sleep I am considering a career change.  I've been a computer programmer up to this point and have my bachelors in Electrical Engineering.  But now I've thought about changing to the medical field to become an LPN and eventually an RN.  This would be mainly so that I could try to work 3 or 4-day shifts.  That way I can still get my sleep and then have the extra time off to get other stuff done.  ... I am well-educated, so other non-standard hours jobs would  not be challenging enough for me--like security.  Other than the medical profession are there any other jobs I could purs... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7110-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7110_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:19:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/105955/161315</link><title>Disability , 48yrs old cant land job 7 yrs , anxiety , depression</title><description>... i applied disability, for depression, anxiety, arthritis, knee pain,high blood pressure, short leg syndrome, I am 48 yrs old, I have been on and off out of work for 7yrs.  I had had over 40 jobs in this period of time. I feel severely unwanted . I cant land a decent office job. It seems employers dont want me , Im not married, I dont have health insurance, I am a victim of discrimination. bigtime. i m loosing my home in foreclosure, my time is limited  to 4 or 5 months. my car went to junk yard, cracked engine, i live in plainfield suburb , no plublic transit, my daughter 24 is severely depressed too. gaining weight. this has been the most difficult eriod of my entire life. i live wth 74.00 a week in unemployment. my income last yr. 4k. social security can see all the job i have had. i have tried or 7 yrs. thousands of resumes and interviews.total w aste of time. i was tring so hard, yet no progress at all. just deeper in the hole. can i be approved. i see psychiatrist ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7110-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7110_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:19:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/adult-adhd-251087-5.html</link><title>Finding Your ADHD Friendly Job</title><description>... ADD is different in each person, so what may seem like a great ADD Friendly job to you, may be a disaster for another individual with ADD.  There are some common complaints of adults with ADD, including time management problems and organization.  However, some a dults with ADD have compensated by structuring their day and are extremely organized.  Many people have asked what specific jobs are best for individuals with ADHD, but each person is unique and ADD brings out different strengths and weaknesses in each person.  Every industry also provides a wide array of jobs so that for any interest, a job can be found.  While an engineer with ADD might find it to be boring and tedious working in a large office, he might do well as an independent contractor where each job he undertakes is new and refreshing.  So, how do you determine what job is best for you?  Understand that this is a process and will not be completed in a day or a week.  It may take a... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>