<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7112">facebook icons</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:24:19" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7112-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7112_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:24:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/956385/136346</link><title>I want to share my stuff. But I do not know how to use facebook, nor do I want to learn. Is there any other way to be able to SHARE without facebook being involved. All I know how to do is email!</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7112-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7112_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:24:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/news-36776-5.html</link><title>Kurt Vonnegut passes away at the age of 84</title><description>... Kurt Vonnegut's Battle With Depression by Deborah Gray On the Passing of Kurt Vonnegut   By Christopher Lukas Kurt Vonnegut: A Story of Wisdom, Courage and Inspiration   by G.J. Gregory Everything was Beautiful, and Nothing Hurt: A response to Kurt Vonnegut’s Death by Christina Bruni Kurt Vonnegut: Humorist, Skeptic, and Social Critic   by Lynne Taetzsch   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7112-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7112_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:25:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/100/8612/kurt-icon</link><title>Kurt Vonnegut: An Iconoclastic Icon</title><description>... Kurt Vonnegut’s iconoclastic life and literary style unintentionally rendered him a beloved icon.  He seemed unafraid to direct his biting satire at anything or anybody he found worthy, including himself.  Often his writings were transparent assaults upon social absurdities and those who, perhaps unwittingly, sought to perpetuate these.  Readers without the courage to take a hard look at themselves in a full length mirror could laugh at his hapless characters and their folly, never realizing it was their own.  Those who dared to actually study his work, convoluted as a carnival house of mirrors, often found reflected images of unusual clarity and truth. This writer has concluded that no small measure of Vonnegut’s genius was a product of his continuing struggle with clinical depression.  This brain disorder, when untreated, often reduces its victims to intellectual and emotional essentials.  From these, the afflicted must reconstruct for themselves, on a ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7112-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7112_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:26:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/r/medications/tl-icon-oral-152542/images</link><title>TL Icon Oral Medication Images</title><description>... TL Icon Oral FOLTRIN CAPSULE ... TL Icon Oral FEROTRINSIC CAPSULE ... TL Icon Oral FEROCON CAPSULE ... TL Icon Oral FEROCON CAPSULE ... TL Icon Oral CONISON CAPSULE ... TL Icon Oral FEROTRIN CAPSULE ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7112-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7112_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:26:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/r/medications/tl-icon-oral-152542/dosage</link><title>TL Icon Oral Dosage and Storage</title><description>... Generic Name: IRON/VITAMIN C/VITAMIN B12/INTRINSIC FACTOR - ... ORAL TL Icon Oral Overdose ... If overdose is suspected, contact your local poison ... control center or emergency room immediately. US residents should call the US ... National Poison Hotline at 1-800-222-1222. Canada residents should call a ... provincial poison control center. Symptoms of overdose may include: stomach ... pain, nausea, vomiting, diarrhea. ... TL Icon Oral Missed Dose ... If you miss a dose, take it as soon as you remember. If it ... is near the time of the next dose, skip the missed dose and resume your usual ... dosing schedule. Do not double the dose to catch up. ... TL Icon Oral Notes ... Do not share this medication with others. ... Laboratory and/or medical tests (e.g., complete blood ... count, vitamin B12 levels) may be performed periodically to monitor your ... progress or check for side effects. Consult your doctor for more ... details. ... There are many iron supplement products available. Some ... ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7112-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7112_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:27:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/r/medications/tl-icon-oral-152542/uses</link><title>TL Icon Oral Uses and How to Use</title><description>... Generic Name: IRON/VITAMIN C/VITAMIN B12/INTRINSIC FACTOR - ... ORAL TL Icon Oral Uses ... This medication is a multivitamin product used to treat or ... prevent low blood levels of iron (e.g., for anemia or during pregnancy). Iron ... is an important mineral the body needs to produce red blood cells and keep you ... in good health. Vitamin C improves the absorption of iron from the stomach. ... Vitamin B12 is important for growth, cell production, and nerve function. ... Intrinsic factor is identical to a substance that is made naturally in the ... stomach. It improves the absorption of vitamin B12. ... How To Use TL Icon Oral ... Swallow this medication whole with a full glass of water ... (8 ounces or 240 milliliters), usually once daily or as directed by your ... doctor. If you are taking the long-acting product, do not crush or chew the ... capsules. Doing so can destroy the long action of the drug and may increase ... side effects. ... This medication is best taken on an empty stomac... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7112-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7112_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:27:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/r/medications/tl-icon-oral-152542/side-effects</link><title>TL Icon Oral Precautions and Side Effects</title><description>... Generic Name: IRON/VITAMIN C/VITAMIN B12/INTRINSIC FACTOR - ... ORAL TL Icon Oral Precautions ... Before taking this product, tell your doctor or pharmacist ... if you are allergic to any of its ingredients; or if you have any other ... allergies. This product may contain inactive ingredients, which can cause ... allergic reactions or other problems. Talk to your pharmacist for more ... details. ... This medication should not be used if you have certain ... medical conditions. Before using this medication, consult your doctor or ... pharmacist if you have: ... ... iron overload disorder (e.g., hemochromatosis, ... hemosiderosis) ... ... Before taking this product, tell your doctor or pharmacist ... your medical history, especially of: ... ... use/abuse of alcohol ... liver problems ... stomach/intestinal problems (e.g., ulcer, colitis) ... vitamin B12 deficiency (pernicious anemia) ... ... During pregnancy, this medication should be used only if ... clearly needed. Discuss the risks... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7112-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7112_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:28:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/r/medications/tl-icon-oral-152542/interactions</link><title>TL Icon Oral Medication Interactions</title><description>... Generic Name: IRON/VITAMIN C/VITAMIN B12/INTRINSIC FACTOR - ... ORAL TL Icon Oral Interactions ... See also How To Use section. ... Your doctor or pharmacist may already be aware of any ... possible drug interactions and may be monitoring you for them. Do not start, ... stop, or change the dosage of any medicine before checking with them ... first. ... Before taking this medication, tell your doctor or ... pharmacist of all prescription and nonprescription/herbal products you may use, ... especially: ... ... chloramphenicol ... methyldopa ... ... This product can decrease the absorption of other drugs ... such as bisphosphonates (for example, alendronate), levodopa, penicillamine, ... quinolone antibiotics (for example, ciprofloxacin, levofloxacin), thyroid ... medications (for example, levothyroxine), and tetracycline antibiotics (for ... example, doxycycline, minocycline). Therefore, separate your doses of these ... medications as far as possible from your doses of this product. A... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7112-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7112_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:28:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/84/12950/dr-barry-icon</link><title>Dr. Barry Ginsberg: A Diabetes Icon Explains... Everything</title><description>... Republished by permission of Amy Tenderich of diabetesmine.com .   Well OK, maybe not everything , but it was pretty inspiring interviewing the endo who led the research team for the landmark DCCT (Diabetes Control and Complications Trial)!   Dr. Barry Ginsberg is internationally recognized as an "iconic figure" in diabetes, blood glucose monitoring technology and implantable sensors. He's published over 100 articles in peer-reviewed journals and has received over 5 million dollars in research grants. He recently retired from 15 years as vice president for worldwide medical affairs at BD Medical's Diabetes Care unit. And very lucky for us, he was generous enough last week to share some of his accumulated wisdom with our community via DiabetesMine.com . He's so refreshingly down-to-Earth -- you just have to read this! DM) You've seen a lot of changes in diabetes care over the years. What do you think is the most important new development underway righ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7112-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7112_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:28:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/common/images/image.html</link><title>News Icon</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>