<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7115">pittsburgh steelers news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:39:34" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7115-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7115_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:39:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/question/516191/85926</link><title>I need help finding a specialist in Pittsburgh, Pa that treats Schizophrenia</title><description>... can you please help me find a good doctor in Pittsburgh, Pa that specializes in Paranoia Schizophrenia. My current pheonsea is suffering from depression and Schizophrenia and i need help finding a good doctor to assist in a better way of life, in dealing with this problem. My name is Douglas Battle and my other half is Joyce Jacobs of North Carolina she was diagnosed with Paranoia Schizophrenia a year ago and i need to bring her to Pittsburgh, Pa for better help and to be near her emediout family. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7115-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7115_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:40:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/10128/pittsburgh</link><title>Off to Pittsburgh</title><description>...   ... Between conferences, I have limited production windows that represent ‘now or never” moments in terms of cranking out work. Fortunately, I met my deadlines without burning myself out, and hopefully I will do the same between Pittsburgh and NAMI. I’ll arrive in Pittsburgh late evening tomorrow, with a whole day the next day to chill out and adjust to the time zone changes. Then there’s an evening function, followed by two solid days from morning till into the evening, plus a third full day. ...   ... The whole time I need to be ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7115-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7115_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:40:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/10349/back-pittsburgh</link><title>Back From Pittsburgh</title><description>...   ... There is no way to describe my feeling of gratification. Again, a picture tells a thousand words. More later … ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7115-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7115_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:40:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/10223/live-receive-award</link><title>Live From Pittsburgh: Journalist to Receive Award</title><description>...   ... “At the Seventh International Conference on Bipolar Disorder being held this week in Pittsburgh, three distinguished individuals and one advocacy group will be honored for their contributions to bipolar disorder research, education and service,” the release goes on to say. ...   ... Now some background: ...   ... “The Mogens Schou Awards were named in recognition and appreciation of Mogens Schou MD, Dr Med Sci … whose groundbreaking research 50 years ago proved lithium’s significant mood stabilizing effects for the treatment of bipolar disorders. ...   ... Now the set-up sentence: ...   ... “’This year’s Mogens Schou Awards continues the strong tradition of honoring those heroes who are making major advances that bring hope to those suffering with bipolar disorder,’ said David J Kupfer MD, the Thoms P Detre Professor and chai... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7115-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7115_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:41:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/70895/39026/pittsburgh</link><title>Need a pain doctor in Pittsburgh</title><description>... I am a 65-year old woman, wife and mother, who has been a chronic pain patient for more than 15 years. For most of that time, I have been very, very lucky. Although I was never pain free, I still was able to care for myself, keep the house clean, and even work part-time. Until recently, when break-through pain became a problem. My primary care physician wrote me a prescription for more morphine sulfate IR ("instant release") and sent me on my way. I wasn't worried. From what I had learned after years of reading about chronic pain, I wasn't worried. This was what leading pain specialists usually recommended doing. ... But the break-through pain continued. My PCP wrote a prescription for even more morphine sulfate IR. Now, I was worried. This was not what I remembered be... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7115-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7115_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:41:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/10204/road-live-pittsburgh</link><title>On the Road: Live from Pittsburgh</title><description>...   ... Wow, I bet the people who can afford these rooms don’t drive cars with 200,000 miles on them, either. I could very easily get used to this. ...   ... Naturally, I’m not paying for the room. When I go to conferences, I’m usually in something in the two-star range. But the Seventh International Conference on Bipolar Disorder, hosted by the Western Psychiatric Institute and University of Pittsburgh , is picking up my tab this time around. Tomorrow evening, at a function, I will be one of three people that the conference organizers will be singling out. ...   ... It is very important that I mention ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7115-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7115_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:42:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/651280/59002/regeneration</link><title>Beta Cell Regeneration: The Latest Update from the University of Pittsburgh</title><description>...   ... In early Janua... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7115-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7115_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:42:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/question/431735/100501</link><title>Is there a local support group in Pittsburgh PA for parents and grandparents of people with bipolar?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7115-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7115_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:43:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/1443/143415/watching-increase</link><title>Watching the News Can Increase Anxiety</title><description>...   ... Without this preparation and these warnings, would more people have suffered? Would the death toll be higher? Certainly the chances of this happening are high and the evacuations and warnings helped us understand how our lives could be impacted. ...   ... On the other hand, how much news is too much? When does a good-intentioned warning become an anxiety provoking newscast? There have been several studies through the year linking watching too much television to depression and anxiety: ... ... In 2009, researchers at the University of Pittsb... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7115-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7115_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:44:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/724322/140488/mental-health</link><title>Mental Health news recap: 6/25</title><description>...   ... Depressive Symptoms: Like Father, Like Child by Bruce Jancin/Internal Medicine News ... ... His study also demonstrated that the adverse impact on children’s behavioral and emotional functioning is compounded when both the mother and father have mental health problems. For example, in homes where both parents experienced depressive symptoms, fully 25% of children had emotional or behavioral problems, a rate more than fourfold greater than when neither parent was affected. ... ... Criteria Changes for Bipolar Disorder proposed for DSM-V by Deborah Brauser/Medscape News ... ... June 17, 2011 (Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania) — The upcoming Diagnostic and Statistical Manual of Mental Disorders, Fifth Edition (DSM-5) , may include revisions for diagnosing mixed episodes while keeping the current duration cri... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>