<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7116">pumpkin pie recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:44:52" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7116-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7116_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:44:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/39/163735/pumpkin-pie-popsicles</link><title>Pumpkin Pie Popsicles</title><description>...   ... Reflux Friendly Cooking is a weekly feature that will be full of quick and easy food ideas that are acid reflux friendly and can be easily modified to meet the needs of everyone in your family! Each week I’ll provide a simple menu that is designed for easy digestion. I’ll also give you suggestions on how to modify the same recipe for others in your family without acid reflux disease. Bon Appétit! ...   ... Pumpkin Pie Popsicles ... This week, I visited a nearby farmers’ market and they were selling pumpkin pie popsicles. Eating one of these felt so wrong and so right all at the same time. It was like summer and fall happening all at once. This recipe is gluten free, dairy free and I left out the cinnamon since it can be a trigger for some with reflux. ...   ... Ingredients for about six popsicles (depending on the mold size): ... 1/2 can pumpkin ... 1/2 cup coconut milk ... 1/4 cup sugar ... 1/2 tsp. vanilla extract ... 1/4 tsp. ground ginger ... 1/4 tsp. ground... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7116-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7116_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:45:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/458275/163733/smoothie-infographic</link><title>Wellness Recipe: Pumpkin Protein Smoothie (INFOGRAPHIC)</title><description>...   ... ... (click to enlarge or download) ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7116-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7116_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:46:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/c/41167/52782/holiday-pirlau</link><title>Low-Fat Holiday Recipe: Ham and Pumpkin Pirlau</title><description>...   ... Ham and Pumpkin Pirlau Recipe by: Frank Stitt, Highlands Bar &amp; Grill, Birmingham, AL ... This recipe serves: 4 ... Preparation time : 10 minutes Cooking time : 40 minutes ... Ingredients 2 tablespoons unsalted butter 1 cup peeled, seeded and diced pie pumpkin or butternut squash 2 carrots, peeled and diced 1 large onion, chopped 1 leek, trimmed, cleaned, and sliced 1/2 inch thick 1 sweet potato, peeled and cut into 1/2 inch dice 1 bay leaf 1 cup basmati rice, rinsed 3 cups low sodium chicken broth 2 medium ripe pears or apples, peeled, cored, and diced 2 thyme sprigs, leaves removed 6 very thin slices country ham or prosciutto, cut into julienne strips ... Cooking Instructions 1. In a large sauté pan or a Dutch oven, melt one tablespoon of the butter over medium-high heat. ... 2. Add... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7116-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7116_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:46:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/1443/157217/pumpkin-good</link><title>The Smell of Pumpkin Pie May Be Good for Your Sex Life</title><description>...   ... Thanksgiving and Sex ...   ... Stuffing yourself until you can’t move doesn’t always lend itself to a hot and steamy night.  But one part of your Thanksgiving meal, or rather dessert, may help your love life. The Smell and Taste Treatment and Research Foundation in Chicago recently discovered that the scent of pumpkin pie was found to both increase penile blood flow in men and sexual desire in women. Some believe that the scents of vanilla and cinnamon, which may be ingredients in your pumpkin pie also help sexual desire. ...   ... Other scents that increased penile blood flow were licorice, doughnuts and lavender. One of the most effective was a combination of pumpkin pie and lavender scents. But if the traditional... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7116-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7116_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:46:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/common/images/image.html</link><title>pumpkin pie, promo, flickr, mfhiatt</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7116-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7116_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:47:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/c/844/49154/thanksgiving</link><title>Thanksgiving Holiday Recipes: Pumpkin Bisque</title><description>...   ... Pumpkin Bisque ... This recipe serves 6 ...   ... Ingredients: ... 1 tbsp peanut oil ... 1/3 cup of finely chopped onions ... 1/3 cup of finely chopped celery ... 1 tsp fresh thyme ... 1 bay leaf ... 1 medium sized pumpkin (approx. 3 lbs) ... salt to taste ... freshly ground black pepper ... about 1 quart of low-sodium canned chicken stock (Try Pacific Organic Free Range Low-Sodium Chicken Broth; it has only 70 mg/sodium per cup) ... 2 tbsps toasted pumpkin seeds (optional) ...   ... Cooking Instructions: ... 1. Preheat the oven to 350 degrees F. ...   ... 2. Pierce the pumpkin several times and cook in the microwave until the shell softens using high power for approximately 3 to 5 minutes. ...   ... 3. Cut the pumpkin in half and scoop out the seeds. Save the seeds for toasting if desired. Place the pumpkin halves cut-side down on a baking sheet. Bake in the preheated oven about 40 minutes... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7116-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7116_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:48:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/13031/63805</link><title>we like apple pie but we dont have a diabetic recipe for it so where can i find one</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7116-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7116_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:48:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/5741/66386/pie-meatballs</link><title>Lemon pie, meatballs and paradise</title><description>...   ... Moving right along to meatballs. YUCK! They were the worse meatballs I ever cooked! I tried a recipe from our favorite Italian restaurant. They sure as heck didn't even come close to theirs. YUCK!  Well needless to say that recipe got shredded. ...   ... Then there's paradise. Right here in Binghamton's 1st ward. Margaret is amazing. She puts up with me no matter what. ..even through crappy meatballs. ...   ... We got a call yesterday from the garage that inspected our car last year. It was a reminder that the inspection is due. OMG! I totally forgot. Thankfully they called. I take it in tomorrow. ...   ... At Walmart today my hand started tingling and pain was shooting up my arm. Margaret talked me into going to the doctor's office. He couldn't find anything wrong. He did a thorough exam. He said if it doesn't get better to call his office. ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7116-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7116_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:48:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/c/41167/45716/halloween</link><title>Halloween Treat: Super Moist Pumpkin Bread</title><description>... Super Moist Pumpkin Bread ... This recipe serves: 8 ... Preparation time : 20 minutes Cooking time : 45 minutes ... Ingredients 1/2 stick unsalted butter 1/2 cup sugar 1 large egg 1/2 cup canned pumpkin 1/4 cup nonfat, plain yogurt 1/4 cup honey 1 teaspoon vanilla extract 1 cup flour 1 teaspoon baking powder 1 teaspoon cinnamon 1/4 teaspoon salt 1/4 teaspoon ground ginger 1/4 teaspoon ground allspice ... Cooking Instructions 1. Preheat oven to 350°F. Spray a bread pan with nonstick cooking spray. ... 2. In the bowl of an electric mixer, beat together the butter and sugar on high speed until smooth. With the mixer on low speed, add the egg and combine. Add the pumpkin, yogurt, honey and vanilla and combine until smooth. ... 3. In a separate bowl, combine the flour, baking powder, cinnamon, salt, ginger and allspice. Fold... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7116-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7116_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:49:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/727598/162710/allspice-star-pumpkin</link><title>Enjoying a Pumpkin Spice Latte? Toast Its Health Star, Allspice</title><description>... But first, let’s identify what this spice is. According to the Great American Spice Company , allspice is a highly aromatic dried berry. The name allspice was selected because the flavor resembles a combination of cloves, cinnamon and nutmeg. This berry also is referred to as Jamaican Pepper. You can purchase allspice as a berry or in the ground version. The whole berry, which is the fifth pepper that is included in five peppercorn blends, is often used in pickling, meat broths and gravies. ... And this spice may be our ally in the battle against cancer. A new study out of the University of Miami created a solut... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>