<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7118">part time jobs texas city</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:54:45" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7118-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7118_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:54:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/134165/suspends-migraine</link><title>Texas School Suspends, Punishes Student for Migraine</title><description>... ... Now, imagine that you're 12-years-old, and you get a Migraine at school. You do what's supposed to be the right thing. You go to the school nurse. And what does the school nurse do? She decides you're not ill. You've taken an illicit drug. She calls the campus police liaison and you're subjected to field sobriety tests. ... ... That's what happened to Aliah Rowe, a student at Blocker Middle School in Texas City, Texas, on February 21. Aliah hadn't been feeling well, but she still went to school. When she had a severe headache and achy stomach come mid-morning, she went to the school nurse. Aliah said she thought the nurse "would just call my mom and send me home because a lot of kids were getting sick from the flu and stuff." 1 ... ... Instead, the nurse decided that her behavior and appearance were indicative of drug or alcohol use and called the campus police liais... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7118-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7118_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:55:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/1443/157697/teens-adhd-job</link><title>Teens with ADHD: Getting a Job</title><description>...   ... Benefits of Employment ...   ... A job gives teens a sense of purpose and independence. It makes them feel worthwhile and builds self-esteem. Working also provides “practice” for life outside of high school. It gives them a chance to learn to get along with a variety of people, work together with their co-workers to accomplish goals; helping them to improve their social skills. It helps them to understand how the working worl... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7118-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7118_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:55:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/489227/118677</link><title>carrie my sons girlfriend just found out she has breast cancer.she is 41 and has only a part time job and no medical insurance. where can she get help?</title><description>... she applied for medicare and was told she is not elgeible.if she doesn't get surgery she will die ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7118-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7118_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:56:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/14967/bosss-day</link><title>Celebrating Boss's Day in Relation to Caregiving</title><description>... Tuesday, October 16 marks Boss's Day in the United States. This is often a day of breakfasts, luncheons, cards, and gifts that are given to bosses by employees. Although this day provides an important way to thank our organizational leaders, I also think that Boss's Day also provides a good day to reflect on what our current corporate environment is like - and what actions our organizational leaders can take in support of caregivers.   Let me first of all say that I've been very fortunate to have worked for a number of wonderful bosses during my professional career who have coached and prodded me in achieving success and helped me to climb the proverbial corporate ladder. Each of those bosses had a "do whatever it takes" approach regarding work, whether it be demanding that I put in extra hours on the job during the day or over the weekend, or be available and willing to rearrange my schedule for a business trip. I quickly aligned myself to their demands witho... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7118-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7118_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:56:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/5868/11726/fulltime-job</link><title>Diabetic Pregnancy: My New Full-Time Job</title><description>... Pregnancy Tracker: 16 weeks 2 days Size of the Baby: Almost 5 inches long! Biggest Obstacle: Finding time to exercise daily   A diabetic pregnancy demands much of the mother-to-be, but first and foremost, you have to be organized. Being pregnant, having diabetes -- and managing both successfully -- can feel like a full-time job, or at least a very demanding part-time job. I figured as much before becoming pregnant, so I made sure to lessen my other workloads first.   For the last couple of years I have been balancing a full-time job at an accounting firm and working on my Masters degree in history. I knew I didn't want to add a pregnancy to my already full plate, so my husband and I waited to get pregnant until I completed my thesis and graduated. The timing could not have been more perfect. We were lucky enough to get pregnant in our second month of trying, so I turned in my thesis the very day I took my positive pregnancy test!   Boy, am I glad that we wa... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7118-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7118_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:57:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/autism/c/1443/152590/asperger-syndrome</link><title>Should Your Teen with Autism or Asperger's Syndrome Get a Summer Job?</title><description>...   ... Paid, Volunteer or Internship? ... When we think of work experience for teens, the first thing we think of is a paid position, usually for minimum wage. But this doesn't have to be the case. ...   ... Summer jobs are used for a variety of reasons. They can: ... ... Help develop ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7118-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7118_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:57:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/454019/114309</link><title>How do most RA paitents cope with working a full-time job?</title><description>... I read about all of these RA patients that are very motivated about being able to work full-time and possibly even a part-time job. The pep talks are really great, but the reality for alot of us is that it is just not an option. Is it just me?, or are there others out there that feel the same. I am 43 yrs. old, have always been a TYPE A personality, my mind imagines all types of scenerios, but my body just will not cooperate. What type of jobs do other RA patients have? I do not receive any type of disability, just trying to readjust our way of living. Could there be a difference in the degree of one's own disease that would effect one's ability to work a full-time job? I battle with RA and Fibromyalgia. I have always been the type of person who motivates others. When I read these posts, I sometimes can't help but feel like "what is wrong with me?"-when I know they are intended for a more positive purpose. Is it just me, does anybody else feel this way? What kind of jobs do they ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7118-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7118_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:58:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/63356/162178/pregnant-diabetic-full-time</link><title>Why Being Pregnant &amp; Diabetic Is a Full-Time Job</title><description>...   ... I'm spending most of my energy on checking my bloodsugars (10+ times a day), getting acquainted with my Continuous Glucose Monitor (CGM) to help me track trends, writing down all my bloodsugars, boluses, carbs, anomalies and typing up twice-weekly report of aforementioned info and sending it to my diabetes support team. I’m talking to the diabetes nurse at least twice a week, and going to appointments at the OB about every two weeks or so now. ...   ... Between the constant tweaking of... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7118-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7118_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:58:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/question/199463/153449</link><title>should i go for job? mama ask me to leave my study and go for job 'cause i failed 4 time in 12th. I want to make my study but people and family say that I should go for job,what i have to do?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7118-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7118_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:59:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/18/108555/job-depressed</link><title>Looking for a Job When You Are Depressed</title><description>...   ... Remember the first rule of a job search: you already have a job. That job is searching for your new job. The energy, skill and creativity you bring to this job every day while you search for your new job will determine both your monetary and psychic income for years to come. You may be depressed right now, but remember that it's your ultimate objective to put depression be... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>