<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7119">chocolate photo</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:59:38" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7119-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7119_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 23:59:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/question/905078/146111</link><title>does chocolate affect patients with GERD or acid reflux ? because I love chocolate bars.</title><description>... is chocolate a bad thing for patients who have GERD or acid reflux to have ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7119-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7119_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:00:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/2259/8541/style-step-2</link><title>Chemo Style, Step 2: Post Your Photos</title><description>... Now that you have registered or signed in, it's time to create a SharePost to show off your Chemo Style photo. Step 1: Choose a Role . Are you a survivor? A sister? Please tell us! Step 2: Come Up with an Inspiring Title. You are most certainly going to inspire a whole bunch of women with your photos. Tell us who's in the photo -- or what you're doing. If you don't want to share your name, choose something fun as a replacement. Step 3: Upload Your Photo. Show us your stuff!   Special Thanks to Angela Lemke of InspiredByYou.org for allowing us to use photos of her hats with hair. The model in this photo is Angela herself! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7119-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7119_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:00:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/917/13270/added-photos</link><title>Chemo Style: Added Some Photos from Breast Cancer Treatment</title><description>...   2005, Me Pre-Cancer   9/6/2007-- I just posted some pics to my profile, and a few below.   Wow, did cancer ever change me looks-wise. There is one photo where you definately can see a drooping in one side of my face.     During Chemo: Hair Loss     During Chemo: Billiard Ball Hairdo   I developed Bells Palsy at one point, a shock and surprise to all my docs. But all is well now. I have a nasty thyroid condition (and I'm sure chemo didn't help it) that causes me weight gain. But y'know, large or small, hair or not..my heart never changed, nor my personality.   I'm still Leslie, through and through.   Find more inspiring photos, or upload your own, in the Chemo Style section. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7119-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7119_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:01:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/77812/41961/pornography</link><title>Stolen Jamie Lynn Spears Breast Feeding Photo Triggers Pornography Investigation</title><description>...   ... One of the pictures shows Jamie Lynn breast feeding Maddie, and the 17-year-old's left breast is exposed, TMZ reports, adding that the photos were taken on Aldridge's digital camera. ... ... Click here for the TMZ report ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7119-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7119_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:01:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/7399/78486/conference</link><title>Mental Health America Conference: Highlights and Photos</title><description>... ... There were so many great subjects for taking photos! Here's Gina. Gina came all the way from Guam to attend the conference. In this photo, she's standing next to the Mental Health Bell. Do you know the story of the bell? I didn't until I heard it at the conference, and the story is truly inspiring. I can't tell the story as well as it's told on the Mental Health America site , so I'm going to quote them: ... ... "During the early days of mental health treatment, asylums often restrained people who had mental illnesses with iron chains and shackles around their ankles and wrists. With better understanding and treatments, this cruel practice eventually stopped. In the early 1950s, Mental Health America issued a call to asylums across the country for their discarded chains and shackles. On April 13, 1956, at the McShane Bell Foundry in Baltimore, ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7119-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7119_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:02:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/87031/64223</link><title>how do I upload my photo</title><description>... How do I upload my photo ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7119-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7119_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:02:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/576299/60382</link><title>How do I uplaod photos?</title><description>... I do I upload photos.?. What am I doing wrong? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7119-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7119_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:03:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-cancer/c/question/993264/120627</link><title>Tried to get a photo of the lesion I had described earlier.</title><description>... Can I submit a photo? If so, how? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7119-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7119_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:03:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/905735/97317</link><title>photo</title><description>... Y can i not up load a photo on my home page? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7119-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7119_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:04:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/question/354902/65792</link><title>adding photos to profile</title><description>... Iknow this is dumb but how do you add photos to profile ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>