<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7120">tortellini pasta salad</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:04:31" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7120-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7120_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:04:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/511540/52096</link><title>can mayonaise or pasta affect RA patients.</title><description>... I had a mayonaise salad last evening and before i can reach home my back and all my joints were hurting. Could it be the mayonaise. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7120-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7120_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:05:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/3232/11744/dreamfields-pasta</link><title>Dreamfields Pasta</title><description>... Great tasting, healthy pasta... only 5 grams of digestible carbs. Plus twice the fiber of regular pasta! I am so excited with having the Dreamfields Pasta.  I have been able to have spaghetti, pasta salad and look forward to having macaroni and cheese real soon.       Its hard when you are on a 1200 calorie meal plan and eat foods you enjoy and stay in your carb count for the day. Dreamfields has made this possible.  Plus my blood sugar doesn't go up like it does with regular pasta. And I can tell you the taste is great!     Dreamfields is a great choice for diabetics.    Here is the link the link for Dreamfields Pasta The pasta is slightly high in price but you can get a $1.00 coupon at the website.   Make the Healthy Switch To Dreamfields Only 5 grams of digestible carbs per serving 65% lower glycemic index than regular pas... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7120-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7120_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:05:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/12415/dreamfields-pasta</link><title>Dreamfields Pasta for Diabetics</title><description>... When I returned from a hike in the mountains yesterday, I was tired, cold, and wet and had food on my mind. I wanted pasta as a variation to my recent diet of salad for lunch and beans (as in chili) for dinner. But the Italian restaurant near where I live was closed for remodeling. No problem. I remembered that I had a couple of packages of Dreamfields Pasta as well as olive oil and garlic at home. Those simply ingredients have everything going for them – they make a dish that is easy to prepare, tasty, and low glycemic healthy. Unlike practically everything else made from wheat, pasta is naturally low glycemic. Linguine, for example, typically has a glycemic index of about 50. That’s on the scale where white bread has a glycemic index of about 70. But Dreamfields Pasta typically spikes our blood glucose much less than that. That is typical , but it does spike the levels of some people, apparently those who are quite insulin resistant. Dreamfields Pasta President Mike Crow... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7120-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7120_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:06:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/11759/pasta-lemon-zucchini</link><title>Everything Pasta: How I Discovered Lemon Zucchini and Became Enlightened</title><description>... What do you call someone who comes up with a lemon zucchini?   A benefactor to humanity.   Okay, I'm not the first one, but I think I found a new twist. My neighbors up the street have llamas and zucchini on their property. I think their pet unicorn died. Anyway, they were hosting our Sunday meditation group while our regular hosts are on vacation. I didn't become enlightened, but I did return home with three fresh zucchini.   I had intended to use the stuff in a ratatouille, but you know how things go. You start sticking it in everything. So here's the situation. We were low on food in the house. Time for my everything pasta.   McMan's Lemon Zucchini Everything Pasta   Hmmm. What's in the fridge? Ah, some kielbasa sausage (low fat) and mushrooms. Something to work with. The mushrooms happened to be the button kind rather than my preferred portabella, but I have a remedy for that.   First the sauce. Since this is going to be a quick pasta, I have ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7120-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7120_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:06:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/2835/winter-pasta-sauce</link><title>McMan's Winter Pasta Sauce</title><description>... ... ... ... We wind the clock back to... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7120-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7120_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:07:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/7291/38108/tips-choosing</link><title>10 Tips for Cardiovascular Health at Salad Bars: Pulses over Dressings, Colors</title><description>... Often we're guilty of choosing food at random, without stopping to think carefully if we're making the healthiest choice. So, before you begin making your choices, take a moment to look over the selection (at the salad bar, or at home), so that you can choose wisely. ...   ... A good rule of thumb to help you stay on track is that half your plate should be filled with vegetables that are leafy, raw, and without dressing. After this, you can begin choosing meats and other side options. ...   ... Here are 10 simple steps to a healthier salad bar meal: ... 1. Choose dark green leafs as your base , for example baby spinach leaves, endive, or mixed leaves. These are a better option than iceberg lettuce, whic... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7120-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7120_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:07:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/42712/salad-fixings</link><title>The Best Salad Fixings</title><description>... Recently I wrote here about the tastiest and healthiest salad dressing, which you can easily prepare at home. If you can find anything like it at a restaurant, I would be surprised. The best you can do when eating out is to use a traditional olive oil and vinegar dressing. Complementing the best salad dressing are the best salad fixings. You can easily prepare this salad and salad dressing at home for the nutrition that all of us, whether we have diabetes or not, need. Even when you eat out, you can find often good salad fixings -- along with many others that you might regret eating. If you can stand the crowds and the usual lack of ambiance, you can find the best ingredients in the deli section of Whole Foods stores. Many of their ingredients are organic. Salad bar restaurants are sprouting up all over the country. While I don't know of any others that offer organic fixings, if you pick and choose, you can find a great variety of ingredients at Souplantation and Sweet Tomatoes out We... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7120-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7120_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:08:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/138200/salad</link><title>When is a Salad Not</title><description>... Salad is health food. Salad is unhealthy. The answer to this riddle is what you call “salad.” Salad can be one of the best dishes that people with diabetes eat. It can be low in carbohydrates and provide us with a great variety of green leafy vegetables similar to what our ancestors have eaten for thousands of years. Or it can be loaded with starches and sugars that will boost our blood glucose levels unacceptably high. The people who make unhealthy salad choices based on what we call them are precisely those who are trying to eat better. People who are trying to lose weight by eating virtuously are more likely than non-dieters to choose unhealthy foods that we call healthy. This is the conclusion of a fascinating study scheduled to appear in the October 2011 issue of the Journal of Consumer Research. The abstract of the study, “The Impact of Product Names on Dieters’ and Non-Dieters’ Food Evaluations and Consumption,” is online . The authors of the stu... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7120-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7120_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:08:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/670/120530/white-bean-salad</link><title>Diabetes Friendly White Bean Salad Recipe</title><description>... Yes, I was shocked, too! ... I have found that eating low-carb makes blood sugar management a little easier.  Not having the spikey bits after meals keeps my numbers more in range and less "riddled with chaos."  However, I like bread.  And pasta.  (I have a little bit of Italy in my family tree - does it show?)  And that whole "feeling full" thing.  ... Turns out a good dose of fiber gives me that full feeling without sending my blood sugars straight into orbit.  I had a really tas... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7120-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7120_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:09:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/17100/fiberpasta</link><title>Pasta For Diabetics: FiberPasta Verses Dreamfields</title><description>... They know a thing or two about pasta in Italy. And now an Italian company is poised to enter the American market with pasta for people with diabetes. This new pasta is coming from a company called Industria Prodotti Dietetici in the town of Monte San Vito, Italy. A 2001 decree of the Italian Ministry of Health declared the company’s FiberPasta as the only pasta “suitable for diabetic people.” The company presented their FiberPasta to the U.S. at this June’s scientific sessions of the American Diabetes Association in Chicago. While I was at that huge convention, I wasn’t able to connect with them. However, they were aware of my three articles about Dreamfields Pasta, including my most recent one here in September. Consequently, Fabiana Molinelli of the company’s export department, arranged for their importer to send me a case each of their spaghetti and of their fusilli, which is similar in shape to rotini. FiberPasta also comes in the form of penne and... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>