<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7121">who is the man in the m&amp;m commercial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:09:45" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7121-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7121_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:09:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/28649/81597</link><title>How can we get excedrin to pull their new Head-Ache/What-Ache commercial?</title><description>...   ... Is there anyway we can get Excedrin to pull this commercial? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7121-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7121_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:10:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/408006/87724</link><title>what drugs do commercial pilot drug tests test for?</title><description>... We have a lot of friends that are commercial pilots.  Although several of them suffer from mild depression they will not get treatment because they do not want to be diagnosed with depression.  They would not be able to take anything because they would lose their job.  I have seen several pilots refuse to go to the doctor because if their medical concerns are diagnosed they would be grounded and/or lose their job completely.   How is this safer then getting treatment, and keeping their job?  I talked to a friend of ours that is a doctor who told one of our pilot friends not to get tests for some issues he had because he could potentially lose his job.  How is this safer for those of us who are passengers.  I know that I would personally feel safer knowing that the pilot flying my airplane is being treated for his medical issues. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7121-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7121_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:10:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/521061/97174/commercial</link><title>Seroquel Commercial</title><description>... I am watching Dr. Oz right now and I just saw a commercial for Seroquel.  Just like the depression medication commercials, take a pill and feel better.  I wanted to throw my remote at the TV.  I am on Seroquel along with Lithium and both are working quite well for me along with help from my primary care Doctor, Therapist and Psychiatrist.  Today I actually woke up with Hypomania and I hope it lasts for a long, long time.  Now to get back to my point about the commercial.  The drug companies should also suggest talk therapy along with the pill to feel better.  I really do not believe that the drug company commercials actually help with mood disorders, but reinforce the stigma in the eye of the public.  I would really like to see the commercials change.  What do you think? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7121-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7121_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:11:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/80355/116140/ra</link><title>Hi everyone - casting director looking for women with RA for commercial</title><description>...   ... Gabrielle Schary Casting in Santa Monica, CA is looking for women with Rheumatoid Arthritis for a commercial that will provide information for people who have been diagnosed with RA. ... Please see the casting notice below, and I would be so appreciate if you could respond to the email / phone number below or pass this on to anyone who might be in the area who would be interested in auditioning for this commercial. ...   ... Thank you so much! ... Amanda ... Gabrielle Schary Casting ...   ...   ... CASTING NOTICE If you or someone you know is suffering from moderate to severe Rheumatoid Arthritis and is interested in the chance to appear in a commercial providing information about Rheumatoid Arthritis, please contact our casting office as soon as possible. No acting experience required, but must have a medical diagnosis of moderate to severe Rheumatoid Arthritis Seeking Females, 35-55 years old and able to speak comfortably and naturally on camera. We are currently casting in New York, and Lo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7121-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7121_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:11:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/question/304690/63973</link><title>How do I lose weight faster without ordering something from those commercials that never work.</title><description>... Hi! I'm 11 years old and turning 12 in about 30-35 days on April 25. I'm overweight by about 45-50 pounds. I would like to lose weight without having to secretly order something from those commercials that never work. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7121-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7121_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:12:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/907150/81232</link><title>Home brew and commercial beer sugar content.</title><description>...   ... Home Brew: For 23 litres of water and beer mix you add 1Kg of sugar. I just wonder if this is much different content to a similar strength beer purchased off the shelf. ...   ... Diabetic brewer, ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7121-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7121_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:12:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/59238/110496/kids-eat</link><title>Kids Eat Unhealthy Foods They See in Commercials</title><description>...   ... The typical cut off point of sugar in a "healthy cereal" is about 3 teaspoons (12 grams of sugar).  As a nutritionist I employ a much tighter standard (6 grams of sugar/serving) and I then coach clients to add fruit or apple butter or nuts to add taste to these less sweet cereals.  The conundrum gets further complicated when you begin to realize that certain manufacturers are ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7121-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7121_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:13:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/147203/123863</link><title>what else is included in a commercial ibuprofen caplets besides the active ingredient that dissolves in mineral acid? Any binders ?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7121-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7121_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:13:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/question/730157/132670</link><title>What are the indications,characteristics,and food selections for house formula and commercial formula</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7121-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7121_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:14:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/545697/122107</link><title>I am a commercial truck driver in Calif.</title><description>... I was recently prescribed Zoloft.25 and Xanax 1 mg 2XD. We take a DOT physical every one or two years. We are given a form to fill out listing any medications we may be taking.Does anyone know if I could possibly lose my license by disclosing this info to DMV? ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>