<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7122">horse dog pics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:14:26" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7122-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7122_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:14:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/14055/20093/good-dog-bad-dog</link><title>Good Dog vs. Bad Dog?</title><description>...   This SharePost is a response letter to a friend from this forum as it represented where my head is at this am.  Hope you don't mind, MC.   Dear MC,   Thanks for your comments. It's true that when I write, I challenge my intentions; it's almost like I have discussions with my 'self,' on paper. Hey, why not? We do it all the time in our heads. It's kind of fun when you write it down as you can actually see the demons working away at you, each trying to have their way with you. Kind of P_____sses them off when you see them, exposed.   I wrote a blog a month or so ago, in which I saw for myself, firsthand, this ongoing discussion - (fight for controlling interest of my head).   Check it out if you are interested ... http://www.uswalker3.blogspot.com/   I write a daily email inspiration (positive life affirming quotes, poems, parables, etc).  This daily mailing  which has taken on a life of it's own&amp;nb... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7122-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7122_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:14:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002066sym.html</link><title>Charley horse symptoms</title><description>... Symptoms ... ... When a muscle goes into spasm it feels very tight and is sometimes described as a knot. The pain can be severe. ... ... Signs and tests ... ... Your health care provider can diagnose muscle spasms by the presence of tight or hard muscles that are very tender to the touch. There are no imaging studies or blood tests that can diagnose this condition. If the spasm is caused by nerve irritation, such as in the back, an MRI may be helpful to find the cause of the irritation. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7122-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7122_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:15:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/610653/130425</link><title>trying to find a pic.of oxycodone 15 mg.brother in law has cancer and got them for break through pain the dr. said cannot find a pic. of them to research for him</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7122-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7122_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:15:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/9993/76526/diabetes-control</link><title>Using a Guide Dog for Diabetes Control</title><description>...   ... I volunteered my home in Richmond as a foster home for homeless Golden Retrievers.  At one time, we had 12 dogs in our home and I loved every minute!  To explain, we brought home one female and 4 tiny puppies rescued from a shelter that could not care for them.  We kept those puppies for 10 weeks nursing them away from deaths door and finding good homes for them.  One week after the puppies moved to permanent homes their 3-year-old mother died, all of it from human neglect. ...   ... My greatest satisfaction has been being a canine mother.  Bosco is my exuberant Chocolate Lab, who sleeps on a wind... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7122-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7122_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:16:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/r/medications/pic-200-oral-93235/images</link><title>PIC 200 Oral Medication Images</title><description>... PIC 200 Oral FERROUS FUMARATE 324 MG TAB ... PIC 200 Oral NU-IRON 150 CAPSULE ... PIC 200 Oral FERREX 150 CAPSULE ... PIC 200 Oral POLY-IRON 150 MG CAPSULE ... PIC 200 Oral NIFEREX 100 MG/5 ML ELIXIR ... PIC 200 Oral FER-GEN-SOL 15 MG/0.6 ML DROP ... PIC 200 Oral FERROUS SULF 75 (15) MG/0.6 ML ... PIC 200 Oral FERROUS SULF 75 (15) MG/0.6 ML ... PIC 200 Oral FERROUS SULF 15 MG/0.6 ML DROP ... PIC 200 Oral FERROUS SULFATE 325 MG TABLET ... PIC 200 Oral FERROUS SULFATE 325 MG TABLET ... PIC 200 Oral FERROUS SULFATE 325 MG TABLET ... PIC 200 Oral FERROUS SULFATE 325 MG TABLET ... PIC 200 Oral FERROUS SULFATE 325 MG TABLET ... PIC 200 Oral FERROUS SULFATE 325 MG TABLET ... PIC 200 Oral FERROUS SULFATE 325 MG TABLET ... PIC 200 Oral FEROSUL 325 MG TABLET ... PIC 200 Oral FERROUS SULFATE 325 MG TABLET ... PIC 200 Oral LONGS FERROUS SULFATE TAB ... PIC 200 Oral CVS IRON 325 MG TABLET ... PIC 200 Oral CVS IRON 65 MG TABLET ... PIC 200 Oral FERROUS SULFATE 325 MG TAB ... PIC 200 Oral FERROUS SULF 325 MG ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7122-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7122_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:17:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/r/medications/pic-200-oral-93235/dosage</link><title>PIC 200 Oral Dosage and Storage</title><description>... Generic Name: IRON SUPPLEMENTS - ORAL PIC 200 Oral Overdose ... If overdose is suspected, contact your local poison ... control center or emergency room immediately. US residents should call the US ... National Poison Hotline at 1-800-222-1222. Canada residents should call a ... provincial poison control center. Symptoms of overdose may include: stomach ... pain, nausea, vomiting, diarrhea. ... PIC 200 Oral Missed Dose ... If you are taking this product on a prescribed schedule ... and miss a dose, take it as soon as you remember. If it is near the time for ... the next dose, skip the missed dose and resume your usual dosing schedule. Do ... not double the dose to catch up. ... PIC 200 Oral Notes ... If your doctor has prescribed this medication, do not ... share it with others. ... Laboratory and/or medical tests (e.g., complete blood ... count) may be performed periodically to monitor your progress or check for side ... effects. Consult your doctor for more details. ... This medication ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7122-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7122_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:17:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/r/medications/pic-200-oral-93235/uses</link><title>PIC 200 Oral Uses and How to Use</title><description>... Generic Name: IRON SUPPLEMENTS - ORAL PIC 200 Oral Uses ... This medication is an iron supplement used to treat or ... prevent low blood levels of iron (e.g., for anemia or during pregnancy). Iron ... is an important mineral that the body needs to produce red blood cells and keep ... you in good health. ... How To Use PIC 200 Oral ... Follow all directions on the product package, or take as ... directed by your doctor. Do not take more than the recommended dosage. If you ... are uncertain about any of the information, consult your doctor or ... pharmacist. ... This medication is best taken on an empty stomach 1 hour ... before or 2 hours after meals. Take with a full glass of water (8 ounces or 240 ... milliliters) unless your doctor directs you otherwise. If stomach upset occurs, ... you may take this medication with food. Avoid taking antacids, dairy products, ... tea, or coffee within 2 hours before or after this medication because they will ... decrease its effectiveness. Do not lie ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7122-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7122_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:18:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/r/medications/pic-200-oral-93235/side-effects</link><title>PIC 200 Oral Precautions and Side Effects</title><description>... Generic Name: IRON SUPPLEMENTS - ORAL PIC 200 Oral Precautions ... Before taking this medication, tell your doctor or ... pharmacist if you are allergic to it; or if you have any other allergies. This ... product may contain inactive ingredients, which can cause allergic reactions or ... other problems. Talk to your pharmacist for more details. ... This medication should not be used if you have certain ... medical conditions. Before taking this medication, consult your doctor or ... pharmacist if you have: ... ... iron overload disorder (e.g., hemochromatosis, ... hemosiderosis) ... ... Before taking this medication, tell your doctor or ... pharmacist your medical history, especially of: ... ... use/abuse of alcohol ... liver problems ... stomach/intestinal problems (e.g., ulcer, colitis) ... ... If your brand of iron supplement also contains folic acid, ... be sure to tell your doctor or pharmacist if you have vitamin B12 deficiency ... (pernicious anemia) before taking it. Folic... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7122-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7122_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:18:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/r/medications/pic-200-oral-93235/interactions</link><title>PIC 200 Oral Medication Interactions</title><description>... Generic Name: IRON SUPPLEMENTS - ORAL PIC 200 Oral Interactions ... Your healthcare professionals (e.g., doctor or pharmacist) ... may already be aware of any possible drug interactions and may be monitoring ... you for them. Do not start, stop or change the dosage of any medicine before ... checking with them first. ... Before taking this medication, tell your doctor or ... pharmacist of all prescription and nonprescription/herbal products you may use, ... especially: ... ... certain antibiotics (e.g., penicillamine, chloramphenicol, ... quinolones such as ciprofloxacin/norfloxacin) ... bisphosphonates (e.g., alendronate) ... levodopa ... methyldopa ... thyroid replacement drugs (e.g., levothyroxine) ... ... Avoid taking this medication at the same time as antacids ... or tetracycline antibiotics. Wait at least 2 hours between taking this ... medication and an antacid or tetracycline. ... If your brand of iron also contains folic acid, be sure to ... tell your doctor or pharmacis... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7122-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7122_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:19:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/9135/16648/ice-pic-headache</link><title>Ice pic headache</title><description>... I was reading the article Terry wrote about ice pick headaches, but my migraines sometimes feel like brain freeze I get ice pick headache pain as well sometimes small pain like something running around in my head. I wonder if anyone else has experience this. And what do they do to stop it or lessing the pain. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>