<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7123">raleigh bike</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:19:44" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7123-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7123_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:19:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/298168/50634/neurloigist-nc</link><title>Need a neurloigist in Raleigh, NC</title><description>... I am looking for a neurologist in Raleigh, NC that does Botox for spatic Cerebral Palsy.  I don't drive and need the Dr office to be on the bus route.  It would also be helpful if they did have experiene in Migrine headaches.  Please help me out. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7123-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7123_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:20:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/copd/c/19257/114349/american-associaton</link><title>Honoring Fathers: Man Bikes 50 Days for American Lung Associaton</title><description>...   ... Inspiration Mark’s father-in-law, Leo Lambert, was a loyal volunteer with the American Lung Association of Maine and New England for many years, and always played an active role during an annual cycling event, the Trek Across Maine .  In fact, Leo did the ride himself at age 70, completing the 3-day, 180-mile ride on an old bike. ... Mark, as a young boy, loved to ride a bike. Over the years there were times when he did a lot of riding, taking trips and seeing amazing sites. But, there were also ti... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7123-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7123_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:20:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/325197/135299/bike-research</link><title>Ride in the TD Bank Five Boro Bike Tour for Migraine Research</title><description>...   ... This is the largest recreational cycling event in America, and one of the hottest tickets in the Tri-State area. ...   ... The MRF invites you to raise awareness and critically needed funds for Migraine research by riding in this incredibly empowering and inspiring event... ...   ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7123-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7123_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:20:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/tore-mountain-biking-week-2644</link><title>Help! I tore my ACL mountain biking last week.</title><description>... Help! I tore my ACL mountain biking last week. I'm supposed to have surgery but I'm also getting married in six weeks. I don't want to walk down the aisle on crutches or wearing a brace. Can I put the surgery off until after the honeymoon? Will waiting two months make a big difference? Anterior cruciate ligament (ACL) injuries are often accompanied by damage to other soft tissue structures of the knee. Patients are advised to have surgery sooner than later, especially when there are combined injuries, but also to prevent additional injuries. Surgeons are advised to carefully evaluate the joint for any additional ligament or cartilage tears before doing surgery for the ACL. Sometimes patients like yourself opt out of surgery for any number of reasons. They decide to wait before having the operation. It's natural to wonder what effect that might have on your injury and recovery. Surgeons know that without the stabilizing force of the ACL, patients can end up with meniscal tears that were... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7123-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7123_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:21:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/24804/21413/bike</link><title>Need a durable exercise bike</title><description>... I need a stationary bike, most likely recumbent, that won't fall apart in less than a year like my Proform has. I chose recumbent because the seats on the uprights are a debilitating pain in...well...you know the expression.   Is there a specific brand with a great reputation you can recommend or are there keywords I need to look for? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7123-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7123_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:21:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/question/909701/160378</link><title>will 30 minutes of riding stationary bike yield same benefit as 30 minutes of walking? Thank you!</title><description>... my Doctor recommends that I replace walking with stationary bike-riding to prevent damage to my badly-arthritic knees. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7123-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7123_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:22:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/injured-biking-accident-1795</link><title>I injured my knee in a biking accident.</title><description>... I injured my knee in a biking accident. The arthroscopic exam showed a torn ACL and MCL. I tore my other ACL several years ago so I know the rehab can take many months. Will having a second injured ligament prolong the rehab time? In most cases...yes. Combined injuries can be complex. One damaged ligament can affect the healing of others. Joint instability can be worse with two deficient ligaments. Fortunately, the medial collateral ligament (MCL) tends to heal quickly and even restores some stability to the joint. A torn anterior cruciate ligament (ACL) is less likely to heal with enough strength to restore joint function. Your past experience with rehab is to your advantage. As they say, "you know the drill." Since you know what to expect you'll have a better idea when the rehab program can be progressed. Working with a knowledgeable physical therapist should help keep you on track. With so much damage to the joint, it's best not to push yourself past what the healing tissue can handle.... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7123-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7123_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:23:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/hurt-knee-biking-accident-2048</link><title>I hurt my knee in a biking accident.</title><description>... I hurt my knee in a biking accident. The doctor said I tore the meniscus and called it a bucket handle tear. What does that mean? The meniscus is a C-shaped piece of cartilage in the knee joint. It helps the joint move smoothly and acts as a shock absorber. It can also help transfer the load through the joint. The knee joint has two menisci (plural), the medial (inner portion) and lateral (outer portion). When the outer edge of the cartilage is torn, it looks like a crescent-shaped moon or bucket handle. At one time it was thought the meniscus didn't have any real function. A tear would result in surgery to remove the whole thing. Later scientists found this treatment led to joint damage and early arthritis. Now most surgeons prefer to repair the tear or just take out the torn section. Reference: K. Donald Shelbourne, MD, and Michael D. Dersam, MD. Comparison of Partial Meniscectomy Versus Meniscus Repair for Bucket-Handle Lateral Meniscus Tears in Anterior Cruciate Ligament Reconstructed ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7123-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7123_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:23:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/806002/138279</link><title>hi.im 24.i go 2 work by two-wheeler.my work place is 15kms 4um my home.i almost travel more than 35kms/day.i heard tht-by riding bike(lots)girls might lose der virginity (break hymen).is it possible?</title><description>... started riding bike (with this far distance)some 1year back. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7123-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7123_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:24:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/sunday-bike-group-friends-2737</link><title>I was all set to go on a Sunday bike ride with a group of friends when I got THE call -- Mom fell.</title><description>... I was all set to go on a Sunday bike ride with a group of friends when I got THE call -- Mom fell. Dad didn't know what to do. We got her to the hospital and into surgery for a broken leg. The bottom end of her thigh bone was busted into three or four pieces. I found out after the fact that she has a titanium nail through the bone to hold it together. Is there anything special we should know about this kind of hardware? Everyone dreads the call that tells them, Mom (or Dad) fell and broke something . Bone fractures in older adults can be disabling and even life-threatening. The surgeon often has to use metal plates, screws, or nails to hold the bone fragments together while they heal. This treatment approach is called internal fixation . Most fractures in older adults occur in the upper portion of the femur (thigh bone). Distal femoral fractures (at the bottom end of the femur) present a different type of problem. The bone is much wider at the distal end and more difficult to stabilize.... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>