<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7124">yves saint laurent boots</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:24:34" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7124-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7124_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:24:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/201654/53571/fitzgerald</link><title>Michael P. Fitzgerald</title><description>... My name is Michael Patrick Fitzgerald. I want it to go on record that Carla was my girlfriend, life partner, lover and the best friend one could ever wish for. ...   ... Carla and I met in April of 2007 at an AA meeting at Radford Hall. I had admired her for a year or so prior to meeting her.   Finally, one Friday night I was there with a couple of friends I had met in rehab. A conversation began with Tom, John and Carla after the meeting out back where could smoke. I was out of the conversation until she mentioned she was a graphic artist. (I have been doing graphics for the last 20 years and own a company that specializes in entertainment advertising.) ... Immediately we connected and began a conversation about art and painting, and the rest of the people just seemed to fade away. ...   ... She expressed interest in what is called a Wacom Tablet. I told her I had one that was not in use that she could borough it if she liked.   She was overwhelmed at my offer. I grabbed the tablet fr... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7124-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7124_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:25:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/120/15397/wisdom</link><title>Serenity, Courage and Wisdom</title><description>... The elements of a successful recovery that one can look forward to are serenity, courage and wisdom. Serenity comes into play when we accept this life-long struggle as part and parcel of what God gave us. He never gives us anything we can't handle. To be serene, an image of Buddha or a contemplative person in a yoga pose often comes to mind. The Oxford American College Dictionary defines serenity thus: "the state of being calm, peaceful and untroubled."   Here's the trick: to have troubling thoughts and yet be serene, achieve peace of mind by deflecting worry. How do we do this? The solution is simple yet brilliant: keep active. As best we can, get out of the house and be involved in the life around us. The more opportunities we have to distract ourselves from our worry, the better outcome we have in recovery. My friend Merry was pleased in this regard when I told her I was stacking the plates up again. Another friend, Zoë, admitted she took a gift shop job e... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7124-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7124_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:25:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/157571/101848/adventures</link><title>Phobic Adventures: Fearful and Flying</title><description>... They say that phobias are irrational fear.  I say, I don't care what you call it.  I am feeling it and it is real to me.  One of my phobias is flying on an airplane.  My palms are sweaty just thinking about it right now.  A good clue that you might have a phobia is if the mere thought of the object of your fear makes you sweat.  I hadn't always been terrified of flying.  I remember as a little girl having my mother describe riding on an airplane like it was some magical experience.  She told me about seeing the clouds from the window appear like big puffs of cotton candy passing by.  She told me it was like a party up there with people serving you snacks and food and even offering you pillows.  I had no idea what flying was like but it sure sounded wonderful.  I was very apprehensive for taking my first airplane trips as a young adult but I was soon gaining confidence.  ... Perhaps flying could be rather magical as my mother had ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>