<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7125">psychological effects of obesity in children</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:26:06" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7125-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7125_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:26:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/156210/emotional-teen</link><title>The Psychological and Emotional Effects of Obesity on Teens - My Bariatric Life</title><description>...   ... Sadly, many overweight and obese children miss out on a happy childhood because they are outcasts owing to their weight. ...   ... The Emotional Burden of Being an Overweight Teen ... Teen years fall somewhere between the “best days of a life” to an unwillingness to repeat the ordeal even for all the cash between the East and West coasts. If you are popular – great! If you are central in the pecking order,  good enough. If you have any attribute that targets you for ridicule, well… you are probably unwilling to repeat the teen ordeal. Among the many targets that predatory peers hone in on is being overweight, or worse yet, being obese. O... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7125-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7125_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:26:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/255251/162361/ways-children-fight-obesity</link><title>Six ways for children to fight obesity</title><description>... ... A new report by the Centers for Disease Control (CDC) shows one in eight children ages two to four is overweight, despite an overall decline in childhood obesity rates in the U.S. during  the past ten years. The CDC says children who are overweight or obese face increased risk for obesity during adolescence and adulthood. While it is unclear if obesity directly causes other conditions, it is often associated with high cholesterol, high blood sugar, asthma and mental health problems. These six small changes to your child’s lifestyle can help them reap the benefits of exercise.   ...   ... Limit screen time ...   ... ... (Source: Sara Ross, Flickr ) ...   ... According to the journal Pediatrics , the amount of time children spends in front of the television or computer can affect their psychological abilities. One study , conducted by researchers at the School for Policy Studies at the University of Bristol, showed children who spent more than two hours per day watching t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7125-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7125_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:27:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/163657/overweight-children-develop</link><title>Overweight and Obese Children Develop Heart Problems</title><description>... ... Source: HBO The Weight of the Nation ...   ... There's a powerful connection between being overweight or obese and having heart disease as an adult. The heart, our hardest-working muscle, spends every second of every day vigorously pumping blood to the farthest reaches of our bodies. The larger we become, the harder our hearts have to work to keep blood circulating. The bottom line: Being overweight or obese places you at a higher risk of developing heart disease and suffering a stroke as an adult . ...   ... The Bogalusa Heart Study ... Overweight and obese children have risk factors for heart disease even at a young age, according to the Bogalusa Heart Study. The Bogalusa Heart Study is the longest and most detailed study of a biracial (black-white) population of children in the world. The community of Bogalusa, Louisiana, is comparable to many other communities in the southeastern United States. The study included 9,167 children ages 5-17 years examined in... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7125-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7125_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:27:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/299905/159399/preventing-children</link><title>Preventing Obesity in Children</title><description>...   ... Sugar ... One of the primary reasons for obesity for both adults and children is the high consumption of sugar, especially high fructose corn syrup (HFCS), which is an ingredient in almost all processed foods and beverages. What many people don’t understand is that sugar leads to fat storage, m... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7125-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7125_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:28:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/152073/psychological</link><title>Obesity As A Psychological Disorder - My Bariatric Life</title><description>... Overeaters Anonymous (OA) is a twelve-step group that adheres to the basic premise of any twelve-step group. The membership shares a specific illness or "disease." Admission that one has the illness is the initial step toward "recovery" or pushing the illness into remission. The group lends support to one another to best accomplish this goal. The disease concept of OA is compulsive eating or the unfettered drive to engage in the irrational act of excessive eating. The only requirement to participate in OA is the ambition to end compulsive eating. When this premise of restraint is acknowledged, a person has begun the process of recovery. Some passionately endorse twelve-step programs while others dismiss them altogether. The legitimacy of these programs will not be supported nor dismissed in this writing. The point of focus is the contention made that  overeating is an illness or a disease. The scientific community may be in agreement. The Compulsion to Eat in Excess Prior to my ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7125-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7125_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:28:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/651280/157245/adolescents</link><title>Obesity and Bariatric Surgery in Adolescents</title><description>...   ... There are several tiers towards tackling obesity: ... ... Nutritional counseling ... Exercise ... Education ... Elimination of carbohydrate rich/fatty food from school lunches ... Family intervention and culture change ... ...   ... If all else fails, some teams are electing to consider bariatric surgery in adolescents (Bariatric surgery is offered at Children’s National Medical Center, but the adolescents are screened very carefully.) ...   ... A recent paper published in the International Journal of Obesity (... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7125-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7125_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:29:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/erectile-dysfunction/risks-000015_3-145.html</link><title>Erectile Dysfunction (Impotence) - Lifestyle or Psychological Causes</title><description>... Risk Factors More than 18 million American men over age 20 have erectile dysfunction, and about 600,000 men age 40 - 70 experience erectile dysfunction to some degree each year. Age For most men, erectile dysfunction is primarily associated with older age. While ED affects less than 10% of men in their 20s, and 5 - 17% of men in their 40s, about 15 - 34% of men in their 70s have ED. Nevertheless, ED is not inevitable with age. In a survey of men over 60 years old, 61% reported being sexually active, and nearly half derived as much if not more emotional benefit from their sex lives as they did in their 40s. Severe erectile dysfunction often has more to do with age-related disease than age itself. In particular, older men are more likely to have heart disease, diabetes, and high blood pressure than younger men. Such conditions and some of their treatments are causes of erectile dysfunction. Lifestyle Factors Smoking . Smoking contributes to the development of erectile dysfunction, mainly becaus... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7125-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7125_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:29:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/encyclopedia/408/179.html</link><title>Obesity</title><description>... Article updated and reviewed by Hubert Chen, MD, Associate Director of Medical Sciences, Amgen Inc. and Assistant Professor of Clinical Medicine University of California, San Francisco on July 8, 2005. Obesity refers to an increase in total body fat . The easiest and most widely accepted method of determining whether you are obese is by measuring your Body Mass Index , or BMI. To calculate your BMI, follow these steps: 1. Multiply your weight in pounds by 705; divide by your height in inches; divide this number by your height in inches a second time. 2. You may also use an online BMI calculator at the National Heart, Lung, and Blood Institute. Go to http://www.nhlbisupport.com/bmi/ . A normal BMI = 18.5-24.9; overweight = 25.0-29.9; obese = 30 or greater; and morbidly obese = 40 or greater. Why Should I Care About Obesity? Obesity has become an epidemic in the U.S. and other developed countries. As many as one-third of all Americans are obese based on the BMI criteria. In addition to body imag... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7125-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7125_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:29:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/651280/156114/philadelphia</link><title>Obesity and Progress in Philadelphia's Public Schools</title><description>...   ... According to Mr. Sapatkin, obesity rates for the Philadelphia public school children “fell significantly over the last 4 years. The rate of obese local public students dropped nearly 5 percent between 2006 and 2010 when national obesity rates remained unchanged after tripling since the mid-1970s.” The declines were greates... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7125-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7125_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:30:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/155022/including</link><title>Exercise Is a Way to Prevent Obesity, including Genetic Obesity</title><description>... There is a consensus that one of the most effective ways to prevent obesity is to exercise regularly . Sixty minutes of moderate to vigorous sessions of exercise on a near every day basis while not exceeding the daily recommendation of calories will manage body weight as well as prevent unhealthy weight gain. Maintaining weight loss requires sixty to ninety minutes of moderate-intensity physical activity per day while not pushing beyond the recommended number of calories per day. ... While it is true that daily or near daily exercise will prevent obesity as well as promote a general improved standard of health , it is equally true that 70% of adults in the United States do not engage the recommended 30 minutes of physical activity per week . Of that population, 49% state that they do not incorporate any physical into their schedules at all. Because we have esse... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>