<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7126">alicia keys brand new me lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:31:07" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7126-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7126_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:31:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/86453</link><title>Put on a Happy Face (lyrics)</title><description>... I'm not sure which forum this post belongs to, so someone can move it if there is one where it fits better.  What is wrong with me?  I wish I could understand.  No, I'm not looking for another diagnosis or label, I have enough of those. ...   ... In any one day, I go from feeling fabulous to suicidal, and everything in between.  It makes me feel sick.  Nausea.  Headache.  Insomnia.  Irritable.  If it just happened once in a while, that would be normal.  (I think.)  I could cope.  But every day? ...   ... I understand that being in therapy means there are going to be some uncomfortable moments, things maybe I don't really want to own up to, along with the impulse to jump in my car and drive to Arizona where I can take on a new identity.  Right?  Unfortunately, I don't have enough money for the fuel to get to Arizona, much less start a new life.  ...   ... Is it worth it?  Is the pain worth it to try to get to some ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7126-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7126_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:31:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/news-289011-5.html</link><title>Glutamate: A New Key To Migraine Treatment?</title><description>... Information presented at the 61st Annual Meeting of the American Academy of Neurology (April, 2009) indicates that glutamate receptors may play a role in Migraine treatment. Trial Phase IIa data showed Addex Pharmaceuticals' ADX10059, an investigational glutamate receptor inhibitor, could prove helpful for Migraine prevention. Other early trials have shown ADX1005 to be an effective abortive treatment for acute migraine attacks. Glutamate is a neurotransmitter, a chemical occurring naturally in the brain that transmits messages from one nerve cell to another. A theory under investigation is that since glutamate receptors are found in regions of the brain involved in Migraine, inhibiting transmission through glutamate receptors could lead to Migraine treatments. Dr. Peter Goadsby of the UCSF Headache Center and investigator in the study commented: "Medication is available to prevent migraine but these treatments are often secondary uses of the drug and come with po... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7126-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7126_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:32:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/patient-guide-44591-6.html</link><title>What is the key to healthy diabetes management?</title><description>... There is no diabetes cure. Diabetes management includes the control of diabetes symptoms through: Diet to control blood glucose level Exercise Blood glucose testing Oral medication Insulin Diet: There is no official diabetes diet. Different diets work for different patients. The goal of a healthy diabetic diet is to provide nutrients and balance energy requirements. The recommended diabetes diet is very similar to that suggested for people who don't have diabetes. It's important to eat at least 3 meals per day and not to skip a meal. Patients should eat a variety of foods, including high-fiber foods such as whole grains, vegetables and fruits. Less than 30% of daily calories should come from fat. Carbohydrates and monounsaturated fat (such as olive oil) should provide 60% to 70% of calories. Protein should provide 15% to 20% of total calories. Exercise: Exercising helps the body use insulin and lower blood sugar levels. Ideally, diabetics will exercise 4-6 times a w... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7126-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7126_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:32:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/635083/74142/brand</link><title>Brand New</title><description>...   ... I am new to the group, female from New York. Looking to learn and share. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7126-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7126_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:33:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/78/14084/brand-cancer</link><title>More on Aromatase Inhibitors and Tamoxifen: Highlights from a Brand New Breast Cancer Symposium</title><description>... The American Society of Clinical Oncology (ASCO) , over 25,000 members strong, includes representatives from all areas of cancer care: oncologists, oncological radiologists and surgeons, oncology nurses, and other practitioners whose main focus is cancer care. Billed on its Web site as “the world’s leading professional organization representing physicians who treat people with cancer,” this non-profit organization of cancer professionals is over 40 years old, with a stated goal of “improving cancer care and prevention and ensuring that all patients with cancer receive care of the highest quality.” I LIKE this group. ASCO was the chief sponsor, along with five other professional groups, of a first-time breast cancer symposium, Sept. 7-8 in San Francisco. Oncologists attended seminars detailing the latest and greatest breast cancer treatments and research breakthroughs, and also had the opportunity to network–which, if you’ve ever attended a pro... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7126-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7126_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:33:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/770402/59286/brand</link><title>Brand New</title><description>... Hello my name is Trina and I am brand new to this website. I have been searching for someplace for quite sometime where I felt like I could fit in, I am excited to join the community here and hopefully be able to build some relationships with others that can understand so here is a little about me...........I am 39 years old and I was born with ADHD and SPD(Sensory Perception Disorder) As a child no one knew anything about either disorder and felt my parents should put me in an institution. Of course my parents did not. The challenges to get through every day life have been a struggle from my earliest of memories. I have always felt like I am on the inside looking out. As a child I was never medicated and as an adult I tried medication on for a time but the side effects were worse that the actual disorders and nothing could ever make me feel the "normal" i so badly wanted to feel. I have chosen to stay unmedicated at this point. My goal in becoming part of this website is to be able t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7126-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7126_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:34:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/brand-knee-replacement-2272</link><title>I have a brand new knee replacement (this year).</title><description>... I have a brand new knee replacement (this year). When I travel, I notice some airport detectors go off and others don't. Why is that? Many people have reported differences not only from airport to airport but even from time to time through the same security detector. To solve this puzzle, Dr. Robert F. Ostrum, Chief Orthopaedic Surgeon at Cooper University Hospital in Camden, New Jersey did a little research on the topic. He found that airport metal detectors generate a brief magnetic field. When a metal object passes through the detector, the magnetic field is reversed and a sharp electrical spike sets off the alarm. Many other factors come into play as well. For example, the more metal you have (say from multiple implants) or the larger the pieces (mass), the more likely it is that the detector will sound the alarm. The type of metal can also make a difference. Anything with iron in it or other type of metal that can be magnetized increases your chances of detection. Detection units ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7126-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7126_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:34:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/209710/48821</link><title>i'm switching brands of birth control. will it still be effective as soon as i start taking the new?</title><description>... i've been on a brand called trinessa for the past 2 months, but have been switched to reclipsin because it is cheaper. i start the pack of reclipsin tuesday. will i still be protected against pregnancy or do i have to wait the full month for the new pill to become effective? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7126-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7126_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:34:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/brand-ceramic-replacement-1403</link><title>I have a brand new ceramic hip replacement and it squeaks when I walk.</title><description>... I have a brand new ceramic hip replacement and it squeaks when I walk. What in the world causes this? Will it go away? Total hip replacements come in two parts. There's the cup to replace the acetabulum (socket) and the round head at the top of the femur (thigh bone) and femoral neck. These component parts can be made out of a variety of different materials. Ceramic was first introduced about 30 years. It wears well but tends to fracture. Improvements in materials and design have increased its popularity again in the last few years. Ceramic-on-ceramic implants have the lowest wear rate but squeaking can be a problem. Surgeons aren't quite sure yet what might be causing this to happen. Not all patients are affected. And sometimes it goes away on its own. Studies so far suggest there may be two main reasons for this squeaking. The first is a lack of lubrication in the joint. This is called dry joint . But what causes the dryness is still unknown. There are many theories so far. It could be t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7126-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7126_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:35:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/15088/32427/brand</link><title>Brand New</title><description>...   ... Brand new to the group. but glad I found it. ... Have been struggeling with terrible migraines since ... I had a stroke on 2-22-08 I am only 36 was 35 at time of stroke. ... Have been in and out of hospitals since then. ... Now the neurologists are looking at familial hemiplegic migraines. ... which is very rare. I dont care what it is as long as they make the pain and numbness go away. I cant take much more of this. I have NOT had a pain free day since 2-22 ... I have had a few days of tolerable but thats it. ... Ill take any ideas you all have. ...   ... Gaelicbabe ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>