<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7127">which cities surround long beach ca</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:35:34" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7127-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7127_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:35:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/question/54267/83355</link><title>Is there a group in Culver city,Hermosa Beach, Manhattan beach, redondo Beach, westchester, Calif.</title><description>... I have a son need to get constructive input on how to help instead of hinder him. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7127-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7127_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:36:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/incontinence/c/question/80257/84920</link><title>can I wear my cloth diapers and plastic pants with a long t-shirt to the beach?</title><description>... I live in Daytona Beach and would really like to be able to go down to the beach. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7127-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7127_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:36:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/8674/9270/year-son-week-long</link><title>Is it dangerous to take my shellfish-allergic eight year old son to a week long beach vacation?</title><description>... I will ask his allergist this question shortly. The facts are I think I can successfully control what he will ingest even though there are so many seafood restaurants there.... Will just "being there" be dangerous to him in the air that he breathes? Will I have to prevent him from going into the ocean or collecting seashells? Any advice would be greatly appreciated! .... a worried mom. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7127-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7127_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:37:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/611828/124754</link><title>Any body on this site know of a pain management Doctor around Long Beach NY</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7127-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7127_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:37:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/1443/115491/colors-surround</link><title>What Colors Do You Surround Yourself With?</title><description>...   ... My question this week is, after looking around, what colors do you surround yourself with? What color is your living room? Your bedroom? Do you surround yourself with soothing colors or those full of energy? Those that are uplifting or those that are calming? ...   ... Personally, my living room has blue walls. Yellow, however, has always been my favorite color. ...   ... What about you? ...   ... Eileen ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7127-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7127_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:38:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/158470/surroundings</link><title>Physical Surroundings and the Risk for Obesity</title><description>...   ... People may be born from the same mold, but once we spring free we are pretty diverse. One person’s comfort zone might be a surge of people, hustling and bustling to points unknown but alive with immediacy. They must get here or go there, and the rush of their purpose is shared. There is comfort in shared identity, the simple knowledge that we are not alone or on our own. There are other possibilities, as well. Sandy white beaches coated in the aroma of sea salt while the ocean gently moves in and then out again. The hot sun that feels like a body massage and the occasional soft breeze across open skin. Perhaps you have placed yourself in a great forest, thick with trees and the flow of unseen streams. Dried b... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7127-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7127_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:38:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/5868/51678/diabetic-sense</link><title>The Importance of Knowing Your Surroundings When You are a Diabetic</title><description>...   ... This weekend I suddenly felt a deep sense of home in my neighborhood, and it was a uniquely diabetic experience: ...   ... My mom, Dennis, Sienna, and I attended the annual December Nights in Balboa Park event. Previously known as Christmas on the Prado, this festival has been a tradition for Dennis and me since we were dating. It's a lovely display of various cultures from around the world and provides San Diegans with a wonderful holiday atmosphere, as we bundle... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7127-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7127_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:38:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/163775/69000</link><title>Husband on Methotrexate. Son is coming from Mexico City 5/12. Should they stay apart/how long?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7127-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7127_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:39:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/299905/160706/maintaining-health</link><title>Maintaining Good Health in the City</title><description>...   ... These da... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7127-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7127_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:40:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/84/44726/visit-south-beach</link><title>A Visit to South Beach</title><description>...   ... I may be the last would-be weight watcher in the country to discover the South Beach Diet. The cover of the book by Dr. Arthur Agatston, MD , brags that it's a New York Times bestseller, and it even sports a pop-out button stating "lose belly fat first." Definitely not my usual thing. ...   ... But my hubby read the book last year and hasn't stopped talking about it since. "It's the only diet that's sensible, that teaches you how to eat right in the long-term..." he says. "In fact it's not a ‘diet' at all, but a way of life." From the beginning, he insisted that with my carbohydrate-shy and gluten-free eating habits I was essentially on the South Beach Diet by default. Hmmm. ...   ... I took advantage of the transatlantic flights all on my own this summer (!) to read the book at long last. Wisdom indeed. No wonder my partner understood the the basics of Type 1 diabetes eating principles much better after reading th... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>