<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7128">where to donate clothes in nyc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:40:27" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7128-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7128_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:40:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/3900/47584/clothing-allergenic</link><title>Is there Milk in Your Clothing? Watch Out for Allergenic Fabrics</title><description>...   ... So I hit Uniqlo , a Japanese-based clothing store that has a big outlet here in downtown New York City. One of the defining features on Uniqlo is their very inexpensive cashmere sweaters and fashionable (if not overly tall and overly skinny) jeans. What I also discovered was they have a very inexpensive line of basic tee shirts, camis and turtlenecks . I bought a bunch of turtlenecks and camis for less than a NYC dinner at a nice restaurant and combined with my staples in my closet, I'm outfitted for the winter. ...   ... Cool right? ...   ... Well, the "Heat Tech" that Uniqlo's thin under-layer underthings sport has an added bonus: milk protein. Yes, milk protein is IN the fabric of the clo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7128-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7128_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:40:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/212555/76645</link><title>can sperm travel through clothes when a clothed penis is rubbing a clothed vagina?</title><description>... My boyfriend and I were making out he laid on me and we were both clothed. Our genitals rubbed against eachother. There was no penetration. Could i be pregnant? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7128-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7128_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:41:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/59435/46573/t2d-patient-focus</link><title>T2D Patient Focus Group in NYC</title><description>... We are looking for 6-8 Type II Patients who are willing to attend a 2-hour focus group in NYC (Midtown-East).  We are hoping to hold this group on November 3 or 4 in the early evening (just after work hours). We are working to develop a patient support program and patient education materials that address the emotional and lifestyle changes that come with a diagnosis of Type II Diabetes. You must currently be on medication and still need additional help in getting your levels down to goal. Patients will receive $100 for their opinions and help in this group...or, if you prefer, a donation can be given to the ADA or Diabetes-related group of your choice. If you think your physician or the Diabetes Nurse Educator you work with might also be interested, we would love to have their opinions in a separate group, also to be held November 3 or 4. For more information, please respond to this post, or directly to TypeIIDiabetesCurious@gmail.com ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7128-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7128_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:41:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/72218/149120/life</link><title>Give a Pint. Save a Life. Become a Blood Donor.</title><description>... For years, my father and I had a routine we shared during the holidays when I would travel home from college.  We would go downtown into Oklahoma City to the Oklahoma Blood Institute to donate blood.  That became part of our New Year’s celebration.  ... Since 1970, January has been recognized as National Blood Donation Month in the United States.  It is a time of year where blood is traditionally in short supply, partially due to the holidays, travel schedules, inclement weather and illness.  No matter the time of year blood is always in need. ... Blood donation centers frequently offer special incentives to encourage healthy, eligible individuals to donate.  Each pint of blood can be life-saving.  For me, it was the promise of a t-shirt which added to the reward of donating blood each Christm... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7128-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7128_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:41:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/genital-herpes/c/question/632877/84984</link><title>can you get genital herpes from a pool or hot tub or washing your clothes with infected clothing?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7128-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7128_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:42:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/49580/1-donations-memory</link><title>6 Women, 1 Infant, 2 Dogs and $1,300 in Donations: One Team's Effort in the Alzheimer's Memory Walk</title><description>...   ... Each of our team members is very busy with a family, career and lots of interests; however, each decided to carve out a little time in their schedule for the walk. Mara and I participated in the 2007 walk, so we decided that we would sign up again this year (and see if we could get a team together). Sondra participated "to show my concern ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7128-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7128_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:42:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002784.html</link><title>Dyes - cloth overview</title><description>... Definition ... ... Cloth dyes are chemicals used to color cloth. Cloth dye poisoning occurs when someone swallows large amounts of these substances. ... This is for information only and not for use in the treatment or management of an actual poison exposure. If you have an exposure, you should call your local emergency number (such as 911) or the National Poison Control Center at 1-800-222-1222. ... ... Alternative Names ... ... ... Dyes - cloth ... ... ... Poisonous Ingredient ... ... ... Corrosive alkali ... ... Today it is rare to find this poisonous ingredient in most household cloth dyes. ... Most common household cloth dyes are made from nonpoisonous substances, such as: ... ... Mild soaps ... Pigments ... Salts ... ... Although these substances are generally considered not dangerous, they can cause problems if swallowed in large amounts, especially in small children. ... ... Where Found ... ... ... Certain dyes to color cloth or fabric ... ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7128-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7128_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:43:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/5949/142635/fibromyalgia</link><title>Dressing With Fibromyalgia: Do Your Clothes Cause You Pain?</title><description>... Fibromyalgia has brought many challenges and limitations into my life, not the least of which is finding clothes that are not painful to wear.  The hypersensitivity brought on by fibromyalgia can manifest itself in many forms and may vary with each individual.  Some are hypersensitive to light, sound, scents, chemicals, medications, heat and/or cold.  We frequently have many allergies, which is also a type of hypersensitivity.  In my case, one of my biggest hypersensitivities is my skin.  There are very few lotions, soaps, facial products, etc. that don't cause me to break out in a rash.  But what is even more difficult to deal with is the fact that most clothing hurts me.  However, since society and personal modesty dictate that I be covered, I'm forced to do the best I can. Although for some reason it is rarely discussed, I suspect many of you have a similar problem.  So I thought I would share with you the things I've found that work best for ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7128-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7128_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:43:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002784sym.html</link><title>Dyes - cloth symptoms</title><description>... ... Breathing difficulty (from breathing in the dye) Throat swelling (may also cause breathing difficulty) ... ... Severe change in acid level of blood (pH balance), which leads to damage in all of the body organs ... ... Loss of vision Severe pain in the throat Severe pain or burning in the nose, eyes, ears, lips, or tongue ... ... ... Blood in the stool Burns and possible holes (perforations) in the esophagus Severe abdominal pain Vomiting ... Vomiting blood ... ... Collapse ... Low blood pressure that develops rapidly ... ... Burns Holes (necrosis) in the skin or tissues underneath Irritation ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7128-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7128_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:44:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002784trt.html</link><title>Dyes - cloth treatment</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Dyes - cloth ... ... ... Home Treatment ... ... Seek immediate medical help. Do NOT make a person throw up unless told to do so by Poison Control or a health care professional. ... If the chemical was swallowed, immediately give the person water or milk, unless instructed otherwise by a health care provider. Do NOT give water or milk if the patient is having symptoms (such as vomiting, convulsions, or a decreased level of alertness) that make it hard to swallow. ... If the chemical is on the skin or in the eyes, flush with lots of water for at least 15 minutes. ... If the person breathed in the poison, immediately move him or her to fresh air. ... ... Before Calling Emergency ... ... Determine the following information: ... ... Patient's age, weight, and condition ... Name of the product (ingredients and strengths, if known) ... Time it was swallowed ... Amount swallowed ... ... ... Poison Control, or a local emergency number ... ... The National Poison Control Center (1-800-222-1... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>