<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7129">avg home edition</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:44:30" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7129-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7129_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:44:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/c/question/79083/122720</link><title>my sys is very low avg 80 to 90, yes i typed that right, - my low bp has been 32 to 46 ish, since the massive attack at 40 ,with no heart probs ever b4,bk to q,, my sys is low now and my dy</title><description>... my dys is low also 66 ish ,wigh pulse rate of 111 avg, i just had the atack month ago, had stent serg, thy found no reasons for the attak iv not gotten records yet to know the name but i guess wht i had was very rare, it dmged the bottom of my heart, im 41, this is was it was in the hospital, albany med center, i beged them to let me go home on the forth day, DUMB !! OK HERE IS WHT IT WAS, THY WERE CONCERND VERY ABOUT THESE READING,ESP THE LOWER ONE ,IN HOSP WAS 42 ISH LOW,HIGH 120 I THINK , NOW HOME THE LOW IS STILL LOW AT 40 MOST OF THE TIME TO SOME TIMES 32 ! I SHLD BE IN COMA THY DONT KNOW WHY IM NOT,, IM AFRAID I WILL NOT WK UP ONE NIGHT, ANY HOW HERES THE MAIN Q- MY LOW AT TIMES IN FEW DAYS HAS BEEN LOW-64 ISH HIGH 89 ISH , PULS 111 OR HIGHER SHLD I WORRY ABOUT THIS, HOPE U CAN READ ME I HAV DYSLEXIA, NOT WELL ENUFF TO SPELL CHK ,SO SORRY ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7129-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7129_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:45:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/28154/133355</link><title>I can see with an A1C of 5.7 and an avg. BG of 147, I should have an avg of 117. This is really an eyeopener. My Dr. will be interested in this.</title><description>... This converter is really neat. I am on a pump and is easy to see my 7,14 &amp; 30 day avgs. + before &amp; after meals for 7,14 &amp;30 days. When you get an A1C done in a lab as I do because I'm a Med. Tech and can keep track of it every mo. it doesn't tell the right story in my opion. this isn't a question but a few facts. Kay Emmons ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7129-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7129_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:45:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/c/question/98761/123776</link><title>B/P Meds not working. I am a 42 yr old white male 5'8'' and 200 lbs. I was diagnosed with hypertension when I was 17 and 120 lbs. My bloodpressure avg 144/92.</title><description>... I started taking Zestoretic 10-12.5 about 10 years ago, My B/P avg 145/92, after several years my meds were incresed to 20-12.5 and my B/P remained the same. I stayed on this does for several more years. A few weeks ago my meds were increased again to 20-25, I have been monitoring my B/P very closley and it continues to avg 144/92 but now I also get frequent headaches and feel lighthead daily. I decided to stop taking the meds because I could not handle the Headches and dizzyness,I have been off the meds for a few days and My B\P still avg 144\92. I am seen at a teaching hospital/clinic so I see a different Dr everytime I go and I have explained, and they have seen from my records over the past 10 years that regardless of the dose my B/P runs around same. I have a strong family history of hypertension and I am concerned that My Dr's are not factoring that into the equation and their answer is always increase the dose of the same meds. should I demand a different class of medication? a... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7129-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7129_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:46:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/343615/95217</link><title>Doctor says my heart is working at 31% , avg. how long till it stops.</title><description>... defibrillator. ...   ...   ...   ...                                       ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7129-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7129_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:46:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/question/29295/153658</link><title>Hi - I want to lose 15lbs in max three months - 5lbs avg per month starting tomorrow. Please give me some advice how best to achieve this</title><description>... I currently weigh 150lbs and I am 2.6lbs overweight. My ideal weight range is 134-147.4 lbs and I would like to be at 135 lbs. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7129-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7129_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:46:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabeteens/c/question/16522/40730</link><title>I eat two cookies and small icecream a day and avg. 100. Is this ok</title><description>... I have had diabetes one year and exercise daily and eat right kinds of food and watch carbs but have always had a sweet tooth and normally everyday eat a couple cookies and small dish of ice cream or yogurt. I take my sugar once and sometimes twice a day and a1c is 5.5. My doctor says I am doing great so far. I take Junuvia which has really helped me vs. Metformin. I had read on internet that a carb is a carb and 15-20 carbs for two cookies is no worse than same carbs for something else.  Jim ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7129-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7129_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:47:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/c/question/468984/95033</link><title>my avg heart rate is 55 my blood presure was 137/96 (it is normaly low)what does this mean?</title><description>... I have been dizzy for 3days and had my blood pressure checked at the doctors today it was 137/96,My blood pressure is usualy low,my normal heart rate is 55. ...   I am a 45 female and generaly fit. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7129-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7129_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:47:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/cold-flu/c/question/802707/157961</link><title>How many cc(s) should an avg. sized adult take of oral Tylenol Cold- night - time SX? I cannot find directions with my bottle.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7129-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7129_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:48:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/c/question/21604/43361</link><title>my avg blood pressure this past week has been 154/110 should i seek medical attention</title><description>... my doctor has told me to just monitor for a couple of weeks but im concerned until this past week ive always had normal  bp. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7129-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7129_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:48:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/question/86453/47683</link><title>question -- editing post</title><description>...   ... Carolyn ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>