<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7130">l1 versus l2 regularization</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:49:12" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7130-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7130_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:49:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/577512/165446</link><title>I'm looking for a comparison of Actos versus Tradjenta. Why would a doctor favor Tradjenta over Actos? I didn't get a good answer from him.</title><description>... I'm type 2 and using metformin and Levimir insulin. My A1c was great while also taking an Actos generic. I got a new doctor because of insurance and when I mentioned that I get a little low sometimes, he had me drop the Actos. Three months later after tripling my insulin trying to keep my levels good, my A1c went up about a point and a half. I asked about going back on the Actos generic but he said this Tradjenta should be better for me. So far after a couple weeks on the Tradjenta, I don't see any improvement. I am still taking double the insulin I did while on Actos but can have a morning level over 200. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7130-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7130_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:49:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/568286/155461/pen</link><title>Humira Pen Versus Humira Syringe in Treatment for RA</title><description>...   ... After totally botching three out of seven injections with the pen, I asked my doctor if it would be possible to switch to the pre-filled syringe. ...   ... The pen was causing so much anxiety that I actually looked forward to skipping injections, rather than actually taking my medicine. ...   ... The loud noise of the pen really bothered me, and the botching of multiple injections made me feel very insecure about the whole thing. ...   ... I was used to using a regular syringe when I was on Methotrexate, so I felt that switching to the Humira syringe would make a difference for me. ...   ... My nerves were still shot, so I had other people do the first two injections with the Humira syringe. I did the third one myself. ...   ... Overall, I feel that the syringe method is fairly fool proof. If you haven’t used a syringe before, it might seem more complicated than the pen, but for me, I wanted to ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7130-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7130_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:49:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/c/42538/48701/cholesterol</link><title>Lower Cholesterol: Butter versus Margarine</title><description>...   ... First of all, both are fats.  Therefore, the number of calories in 1 Tbsp of butter is equal to the number of calories in 1 Tbsp of margarine.  The difference is the type of fat they each contain.  ...   ... Butter consists of saturated fat .  Saturated fat is found mainly in animal sources.  Sources of saturated fat include meat, milk, cheese, ice cream, shortening, lard, coconut oil, and palm oil.  The more saturated fat a product contains the more solid it will be at room temperature.  For example, a stick of butter has more saturated fat than tub butter.  Saturated fat leads to increased cholesterol levels. ...   ... Margarine is made of partially hydrogenated vegetable oils.  Vegetable oils are unsaturated.  Unsaturated fats are better f... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7130-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7130_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:50:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/45112/52823/disease-fish</link><title>Omega-3s and Heart Disease: Flax Oil versus Fish Oil</title><description>...   ... Flax oil contains the omega 3 fatty acid ALA (alpha-linolenic acid), while fish oil contains EPA (eicosapentaenoic acid) and DHA (docosahexaenoic acid). The benefits of ALA continue to be studied, but EPA and DHA have been positively linked to heart benefits. ...   ... The body can convert ALA to EPA and DHA, but it's been well known that this conversion process is not efficient. According to a recent study published in Nutrition Reviews, 8-20% of ALA is converted into EPA. From this, only 0.5-9% is converted to DHA. ...   ... To test the benefits of ALA supplements (flax oil) in amounts commonly consumed, the study followed 62 firefighters. The participants were divided into 6 groups and monito... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7130-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7130_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:50:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/84/12952/dumbest-idea</link><title>The Debate over A1C versus Average Glucose</title><description>... Reprinted with permission of Amy Tenderich of diabetesmine.com .   Remember that little discussion about abandoning the established A1c for a new Average Glucose (AG) measurement? Well, guess what? This is pretty much the "dumbest idea ever floated" in diabetes, according to my favorite irreverent industry expert, David Kliff of Diabetic Investor .   Indeed, the ADA and a number of other powerful health organizations -- the International Federation of Clinical Chemistry (IFCC), European Association for the Study of Diabetes (EASD), and International Diabetes Federation (IDF) -- now have an agreement in place to evaluate the accuracy of the A1c and potentially switch to the new AG units, contingent on results of an international study currently underway. The new standard apparently won't change the chemistry of the test itself, but only the "reference method," i.e. how the machines that conduct the tests are calibrated, and how the results ar... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7130-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7130_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:51:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/9993/47293/yoga-pilates</link><title>Yoga Versus Pilates</title><description>... Yoga vs. Pilates ...   ... In David’s recent post on yoga someone raised the question of yoga or Pilates, which is better? My first exposure to Pilates was in 1990, when I met a guy who opened a fitness center for elite athletes in Boulder, Colorado.   The center was all integrated approaches to helping the elite body stay injury free.   There were boards to stand on for balance at the time known as “K boards,” but no traditional weight machines or typical PT equipment.   In addition to the owner, who had PhD in kinesiology and exercise physiology, there were acupuncturists, massage therapists and a chiropractor. ...   ... In the midst of the large workout room there were pulley systems attached the wall, straps for resistance work and something called a Cadillac.   When I asked about the Cadillac, in walked two regular clients and also professional triathletes, Mark Allen and Scott Tinley.   Putting me on the floor next to these guys felt ridiculous! &amp;... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7130-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7130_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:51:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/ibd/</link><title>Stay Regular: Prebiotics and Probiotics Support Digestive Tract Health</title><description>... By Christy Estes, RD, LD Diarrhea or constipation? Are you somewhere in between? If not, you are probably like many Americans who are striving to find the balance called regularity. Regularity is defined as having a bowel movement (that's not too soft or too hard) three times a day to three times a week. (1) If you are having persistent diarrhea or constipation, you should check with your doctor to try to determine the cause. Your doctor may suggest trying to include foods that contain prebiotics or probiotics to help improve regularity. Pre Versus Pro: What's the Difference What are prebiotics and probiotics? We began a discussion of this topic in " Your Digestive System, a Powerful Source of Health ". We learned that prebiotics help sustain the balance of potentially harmful and helpful bacteria in the microflora of your colon. They do so by stimulating the growth of helpful bacteria in your gut. While probiotics are live bacteria that, when consumed, have a helpful eff... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7130-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7130_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:52:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/357383/73791</link><title>what if a heart patient stops eating medicians and maintains regular dieat regular exicess</title><description>... what if a heart patient stops eating medicians and maintains regular dieat regular exicess ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7130-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7130_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:52:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/991788/145092</link><title>If your normally regular period has been arriving late, and you suspect you may have some type of thyroid/ hormone problem...do you make an appointment with your gynocologist or your regular doctor?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7130-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7130_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:53:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/erectile-dysfunction/c/29454/33066/good</link><title>Regular Sex Prevents Erectile Dysfunction</title><description>...   ... Dr Juha Koskimäki, the study author, stated that regular sex should be something that clinicians actively support in their patients. Not only does regular sex help to prevent erectile dysfunction it may also have an influence on general health and quality of life, Koskimäki said. ...   ... Dr Laura Berman is a sex educator, researcher and therapist. Dr Berman sees an association between a healthy body and a healthy sex life. This simple principle involves the sex lives of men and women as one affects the other. ...   ... Starting with the bedroom, Berman recommends get... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>