<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7131">golf games</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:53:48" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7131-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7131_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:53:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/game-affected-hip-replaced-1501</link><title>Do you have any idea how my golf game might be affected by having my hip replaced?</title><description>... Do you have any idea how my golf game might be affected by having my hip replaced? Right now, the pain keeps me from going more than 9-holes once a week. And my drive falls way short of what it used to. Can I even play golf after this kind of surgery? Golf is a low-impact activity that can be resumed after rehab for total hip replacement. If you let your physical therapist know of your interest in getting back on the golf course, your rehab program can be advanced to include specific sports-training for golf. This is a good idea in order to prevent further injuries and to spare your implant excess torque or load. Studies show that of all the sports patients are involved in before joint replacement, golf is the one more people return to. There's some evidence that your handicap may increase as well as the your drive length. The average change in handicap is an increase of 1.1 strokes. The average drive length increases by 3.3 yards. Even though golfing can involve a fair amount of walking... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7131-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7131_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:54:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/question/25074/27551</link><title>My husband has AD. His golf game has been affected. What exactly causes that?</title><description>... My husband's passion is golf.  He's gone from shooting in the low 90s to 140.  He's in the mid-stages of AD, and golf is his only exercise.  He is humiliated and now says he must quit.  What about AD causes problems  with golf?   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7131-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7131_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:54:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/question/627179/79471</link><title>Do meds (depakote/seroquel) impact one's golf game in a negative manner?</title><description>... Do meds (depakote/seroquel) impact one's golf game in a negative manner?  Normally I'm a very good golfer and now it's as if I'm a beginner and I'm not playing with my group of friends.  I miss it and think the meds are impacting my swing from the nervous system. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7131-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7131_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:55:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/627179/79469/golf-medications</link><title>Anyone experience bad golf with medications?</title><description>... I have been taking Depakote and Seroquel for 4 months now, and my golf game has been non-existent since - I have only played a few times and it's like I'm a beginner.  Does anyone have any experience with this?  Normally I'm a very good golfer (not trying to brag) just very frustrated with not being able to play with my friends.  I miss it and want to be back out there.  My Dr. says it's because the meds hit the nervous system.  That makes some sense to me. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7131-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7131_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:55:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/8534/25827/perfect-sport</link><title>Golf: The Perfect Sport</title><description>... say that? My avid-golfer-of-a-husband must be feeling giddy right about now. ...   ... And I know some of you may be thinking, "That is the ... slowest moving activity around, how could it possibly be the perfect sport?" ...   ... Well, hear me out and you just might begin to believe. There ... are other sports, like soccer and basketball, which obviously require lots of energy, ... strength, and endurance. Golf, on the other hand, does not require too much of ... those...at least not at first glance. Golfers can have a caddy carry their clubs ... for them, hop in little carts and take off to the next hole, having really only ... walked to and from the cart (possibly even with beverage in hand). And then it's ... off to the snack shack. Not too demanding, from a fitness aspect at least. ...   ... But having a caddy, using a cart, and/or heading for the ... snacks and beverages are choices the golfer makes. Yes, it is often the norm, ... but no one is forcing this. You c... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7131-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7131_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:55:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/95808/53881/mii</link><title>Playing Nintendo Wii Games as Multiple Sclerosis Therapy</title><description>... Right after Thanksgiving I wrote a piece titled " Wheeeee!!! " in which I stated that Mandy and I succumbed to Wii madness, purchased one of the video game consoles, and planned to delve into the world of Wii, Miis, and daily fitness tests. We guessed that perhaps, because of the physical nature of Wii gaming, playing Wii would actually prove beneficial to Mandy who, like so many others, suffers from Relapsing-Remitting MS . Now, after a month of playing, we believe that we were correct and that Wii is proving itself well worth the investment. At the risk of being a commercial for Nintendo, I'm going to plow ahead and talk about our experience to date. When you buy Wii it comes with a Sports Games disc. There are five games on the disc from which to choose: Tennis, Bowling, Boxing, Golf, and Baseball. Each game requires a level of physical and mental control over one's limbs. Mandy started slowly and, believe it or not, tired easily after playing just a few of the different games. I could... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7131-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7131_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:56:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/896502/139724/athletes</link><title>Senior Games Provide Competitive Opportunities for Athletes Who Are Older than 50</title><description>... For instance, Houston, Texas will host more than 10,000 athletes for the 2011 National Senior Games.  This event is the largest multisport competition for male and female athletes who are 50 years old and above. Events include track and field, swimming, bicycling, golf, racquetball, bowling, triathlon, archery, race walking and power walking, tennis, archery, basketball, and softball. These games are coordinated by the National Senior Games Association (NSGA) , which is a non-profit member of the United States Olympic Committee that is dedicated to motivating older men and women to lead a healthy lifestyle through these events. ... State chapters of NSGA also coordinate s... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7131-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7131_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:56:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/common/images/image.html</link><title>video game, gaming, tv, siblings, game</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7131-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7131_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:57:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/c/question/372039/51877</link><title>play golf with osteoporosis</title><description>... Golf has twisting motions. is it okay to play golf if one has osteoporosis? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7131-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7131_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:57:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/579805/54973</link><title>golf ball sized painful knot</title><description>... I have a golf ball sized knot on side of left breast near underarm. mammogram and ultrasound came back showing nothing. It is vey painful and uncomfortable. What could it be ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>