<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7132">massachusetts general hospital jobs</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:58:03" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7132-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7132_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:58:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/94560/20231/trip-mass</link><title>anticipating my trip to Mass General Hospital</title><description>... Tomorrow is my visit to Mass General Hospital, orthopedics, which I have been waiting for. Im nervous, this is a very big day for me because I have in chronic pain going on 6 months now. It became severe in September, a month before my 25th birthday. Im scared, I need this appointment to go very well. I need to be clear, but how do I describe my symptoms well enough for the doctor to see the problem, and fix it???  Im 25 years old, I just want my life back so I can get back to my studies in college. What do I say tomorrow, what do I do?? I am so nervous... I just need to make sure that I get there, despite the nausea and gut wrenching pain that puts me to sleep. I will, I will do well too, I hope!  If all goes well and I get into MGH pain management center then I will recieve acupuncture through them and not have to pay out of pocket. Acupuncture was helpful and would be nice to have again because I found it to be helpful. A combination of conventional and alternative treatm... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7132-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7132_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:58:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/ibd/c/question/359064/120066</link><title>I have Ischemic Colitis, been hospitalized twice in 2 years. Changed my diet, but generally afraid to eat. I have lost too much weight,skinny. What to eat to put weight on and not cause a flare-up?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7132-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7132_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:59:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/000748prv.html</link><title>General paresis prevention</title><description>... Prevention Treating primary syphilis and secondary syphilis infections will prevent general paresis. Practicing safe sex, such as limiting partners and using protection, may reduce the risk of getting infected with syphilis. Avoid direct skin contact with patients who have secondary syphilis by wearing gloves. References Beck BJ. Mental disorders due to a general medical condition. In: Stern TA, Rosenbaum JF, Fava M, Biederman J, Rauch SL, eds. Massachusetts General Hospital Comprehensive Clinical Psychiatry . 1st ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Mosby Elsevier; 2008:chap 21. Verma A. Infections of the nervous system. In: Bradley WG, Daroff RB, Fenichel GM, Jankovic J, eds. Neurology in Clinical Practice . 5th ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Butterworth-Heinemann; 2008:chap 57. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7132-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7132_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 00:59:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/treatment-overview-10571-1.html</link><title>Generalized anxiety disorder</title><description>... Alternative Names GAD; Anxiety disorder Prevention References Anxiety Disorders . National Institute of Mental Health. U.S. Department of Health and Human Services. Accessed February 5, 2010. Hoffmann SG, Smits JA. Cognitive-behavioral therapy for adult anxiety disorders: a meta-analysis of randomized placebo-controlled trials. J Clin Psychiatry . 2008;69:621-632. Pollack MH, Kinrys G, Delong H, Vasconcelos e S D, Simon NM. The pharmacotherapy of anxiety disorders. In: Stern TA, Rosenbaum JF, Fava M, Biederman J, Rauch SL, eds. Massachusetts General Hospital Comprehensive Clinical Psychiatry . 1st ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Mosby Elsevier;2008:chap 41. Connolly SD, Bernstein GA. Work Group on Quality Issues. Practice parameter for the assessment and treatmetn of children and adolescents with anxiety disorders. J Am Acad Child Adolesc Psychiatry . 2007;46:267-283. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7132-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7132_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:00:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/1443/153902/asked-generalized</link><title>Frequently Asked Questions about Generalized Anxiety Disorder (GAD)</title><description>...   ... How Can I Tell the Difference Between Worrying and Generalized Anxiety Disorder? ...   ... Everyone worries at some time or another. You may worry about an upcoming job interview, worry about your child’s health, a fight you had with your spouse, finances or health. For most people, these worries do not interfere with their life. They can put their worries into perspective and move on when the situation is resolved. But for those with GAD, worries are excessive. According to the diagnostic criteria, a person with GAD worries ab... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7132-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7132_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:01:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/1443/118911/passionflower</link><title>Passionflower for Treating Generalized Anxiety Disorder</title><description>... ... Nervousness ... Drowsiness ... Flushing ... Headache ... Nausea or stomachache ... Increased heart rate ... Diz... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7132-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7132_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:01:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/11407/165833/ready-unexpected-hospital</link><title>How to Be Ready for an Unexpected Hospital Stay</title><description>...   ... It can happen to anyone. It is even more likely to happen to someone with a chronic disease.  So what happens next? What do you do? ...   ... Here’s what anyone with a chronic condition should know in case they unexpectedly land in the hospital. ...   ... Know your medications and drug allergies. ... ... If you have a chronic illness, or multiple illnesses, chances are you take an array of medications. Carry a list in your wallet or purse with the name(s) of your condition(s), types of drug allergies, and the names, strengths, and dosage of your prescriptions. But don’t depend solely on the list. If possible, you should have it memorized in case you’re rushed to the hospital and you don’t have it... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7132-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7132_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:02:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/153935/decline-alzheimer</link><title>Hospital Stays Often Cause Decline for People with Alzheimer's</title><description>... “Get your hands off me, you big oaf,” Mom demanded. No, she wasn’t talking to my father. In this case, she was talking to a nurse who had come into her hospital room to help reposition her to be more comfortable. But because of Alzheimer’s disease, Mom didn’t understand what the nurse was doing. Mom had been admitted to the hospital a few days earlier because she was suffering from a respiratory infection that was threatening to become pneumonia. This was a very serious situation since Mom also had Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease (COPD), which already had robbed her of approximately 80 percent of her lung capacity. Thanks to the hospital staff’s care, Mom started to improve and soon was discharged to return to the nursing home. But only a few days later, Mom started declining mentally and died within 10 days of her hospitalization. ... It turns out that some sort of decline – whether mental or mortal – is often seen once people with Al... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7132-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7132_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:02:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/headache-specialists/massachusetts-292806-5.html</link><title>Herbert Markley, MD - Massachusetts Migraine and Headache Specialist</title><description>... Doctor: Herbert Markley, MD Address: 85 Prescott Street, Suite 101 Worcester, MA 01605 Telephone: 508-890-5633 Recommendation: Patient Feedback ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7132-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7132_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:03:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/headache-specialists/massachusetts-39923-5.html</link><title>Susan R. Beluk, M.D. - Massachusetts Migraine and Headache Specialists</title><description>... Doctor: Susan R. Beluk, M.D. Address: 65 Newburyport Turnpike Newbury, MA 01951 Telephone: 978-465-9770 Recommendation: Patient Feedback ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>