<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7133">museum of natural history</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:03:32" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7133-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7133_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:03:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/651280/142381/development-1</link><title>Risk of Development of Type 1 Diabetes and TrialNet Natural History Study</title><description>...   ... The TrialNet Natural History Study was initiated to help predict the possible future development of autoimmune Type 1 diabetes based on the presence of islet autoantibodies. In most cases, pancreatic islet ce... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7133-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7133_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:03:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/309824/74932</link><title>Can chewing "natural" chewing gums made with natural latex lead to developing latex allergy?</title><description>...   ... (To the best of my knowledge, I do not have a history of latex allergy, though I am allergic to many plant-based ingredients--I tried switching to natural skin moisturizers, and almost everyone caused my face to get red.  I need to chew gum because bruxism has led to the beginnings of gum recession and also to scraping the enamel off the top of several molars, so I r... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7133-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7133_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:04:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/poetry-contest/poems-37752-5.html</link><title>My Private Museum</title><description>...   Shimmering visions of color at the edge of my sight. Taunting me with beautiful images. Impressionist paintings no one else can see. My private museum. My focus of joy while enduring the vise grips crushing my skull.      Next: Nothing will Ruin this Day   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7133-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7133_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:05:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/425109/58336</link><title>my husband has a family history of HBP his has been 150/90 for 12 mnths what to do we have no ins.?</title><description>... My husband has a family history of HPB and High Cholesterol.  His mother, father and 39 yr old brother are on medication for HBP.  My husbands average th elast 12 months when we check it is around 150 over 90.  He's not been feeling so well lately, but we have no insurance so he won't go get checked.  Any suggestions on how he could bring his blood pressure down naturally?  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7133-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7133_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:05:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/646356/151212/lipid-naturally</link><title>Finally, My Glucose and Lipid Levels are Under Control NATURALLY!</title><description>... Finally, after my close encounter with death last year, a good friend back in November gave me a couple of samples of a patented, all natural product listed on the prescriptionPDR(physician’s desk reference) to try. Of course, like most people I was skeptical, another natural product, I thought but I decided to give it a try. At the time my A1C was 6.8 controlled by prescriptions. My cholesterol level was 278 and my trigs were 364 also control by prescriptions. ... Fast forward 21/2 months. My A1C is 6.1 and I have not... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7133-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7133_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:06:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/65058/41499/orgasmic</link><title>Orgasm History Revealed by the Way You Walk!</title><description>...   ... By first establishing the sexual history of volunteers and then videotaping the way they walk, trained sexologists discovered that the sum of the stride length and vertebral rotation was greater for vaginally orgasmic women. "The discerning observer may infer a woman's experience [with] vaginal orgasm from a gait that comprises fluidity, energy, sensuality, freedom and absence of both flaccid and locked muscles," reports the study published in The Journal of Sexual Medicine. ...   ... Lead researcher Stuart Brody suggests that vaginally orgasmic women do not have blocked pelvic muscles. Because of this, the way they walk is natural. Put another way, the orgas... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7133-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7133_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:06:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/89879/illness-awareness</link><title>A Mental Illness Awareness Week Special - A Brief History of Mental Illness</title><description>...   ... 790,000 BC, give or take a few years - Discovery of fire. Anyone crazy enough to take a burning tree into their cave and find a practical application had to have been dealing with bipolar. So, you nonbipolars out there, listen up: We give you the gift of civilization, and how do you thank us? That’s right. You marginalize us. (By the way, sorry we couldn’t get fire to you sooner.) ...   ... 2000 BC - Ancient Egyptians view mental illness symptoms as physical, caused by disorders of the heart. ...   ... 400 BC - Hippocrates and fellow ancient Greeks explain physical and mental illness in terms of “the four humors.” Melancholia literally means “black bile,” a condition Aristotle assigns to Socrates. Later, Galen refines the humors into “temperaments.” Bottom line: Mental illness is considered biological. ...   ... Second c... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7133-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7133_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:06:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/chronic-fatigue-151675-5.html</link><title>The History of Chronic Fatigue Syndrome</title><description>... Much of the history of chronic fatigue syndrome revolves around the efforts to define it and the debates over what to call it. Other diseases that started out being called by one name were later renamed, either for the sake of medical accuracy or political correctness, but one has to wonder whether any other illness has ever had so many names or so much trouble finding its own identity. In Search of an Identity ME/CFS (myalgic encephalomyelitis / chronic fatigue syndrome) has been called the “Disease of a Thousand Names.” While 1,000 may be a bit of an exaggeration, there are or have been a number of different names used to describe this controversial illness at various times and in various parts of the world, among them:  Myalgic Encephalomyelitis Benign Myalgic Encephalomyelitis Epidemic Neuromyasthenia Chronic Epstein-Barr Virus Syndrome Chronic Mononucleosis Syndrome Raphe Nucleus Encephalopathy Low Natural Killer Cell Disease Atypical Poliomyelitis Epidem... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7133-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7133_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:07:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/livingwithit-278085-5.html</link><title>Artificial Christmas Trees May Trigger Fewer Asthma Symptoms</title><description>... Doc, I get sick every Christmas and end up missing a few days of work. I take my family out to pick a live tree the weekend after Thanksgiving every year and 1-2 weeks later my asthma flares up. Could I be allergic to my Christmas tree? (Have questions or comments? Click here!) The Christmas holiday season brings more than song and joy to asthma and allergy sufferers across the nation. After Thanksgiving, for many families the next order of business is to hunt for the most perfectly shaped, live Christmas tree from their favorite outdoor nursery. In northern parts of America, many evergreen trees are pre-cut and bound together in stacks until time for display. The cold weather allows for some trees to be well preserved despite being cut weeks before being sold. But as they lie in waiting, mold, bacteria, dust and dirt collect on their blades and branches. A Pile of Evergreens -- Millions of dormant molds lay with them Live evergreen trees are preferred by many families because of their ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7133-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7133_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:07:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/814501/163446</link><title>I want to know the natural method of treatment of dysfunctional uterine bleeding</title><description>... Need help with abnormal vaginal bleeding , that is bleeding excessively for weeks . ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>