<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7134">history of yoga</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:08:18" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7134-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7134_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:08:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/255251/168354/yoga-poses-runners</link><title>Best Yoga Poses for Runners</title><description>...   ... ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7134-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7134_02.pdf" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:08:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/common/includes/guides/guides/diet-exercise/Yoga_poses_for_runners_pdf.pdf?1396446198</link><title>Best Yoga Poses for Runners</title><description>... Running is one of the best exercises to burn fat, lose weight and improve overall health. It can also help reduce stress and boost self-esteem, and all you need are a pair of running shoes and a can-do attitude. Despite the benefits of running, it also brings a relatively big chance of injury—more so than many aerobic activities. If you are just getting into running or have been running for quite some time, try incorporating these yoga poses into your routine in order to prevent and alleviate pain in the legs, knees and back. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7134-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7134_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:09:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/223360/139321/arthritis</link><title>Yoga To Ease Arthritis Pain</title><description>...   ... Why Is Yoga Recommended? ...   ... The slow, mindful movement of joints is helpful for Arthritis patients. It improves the blood circulation in the joints and limbs. Yoga also helps detoxifies the body and boost the immune system which is very important for people with (RA). Because movement can sometime be painful, many patients do not get enough exercise. If they do not move because of the pain the situation worsens. ... Even though drug treatments have improved for OA and RA there ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7134-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7134_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:09:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/manage-251275-5.html</link><title>Yoga: A Natural Prescription</title><description>... Yoga: A Natural Prescription The focus of my work is helping others create a healthy balance in their day-to -day life. And yes, I personally struggle with the same stress, pressure, and “not having enough time in the day to squeeze it all in” as everyone else. The day-to-day wear and tear of our demanding lifestyles takes its toll on all of us. Our bodies can put up with it only for so long until our stress manifests as a physical or emotional problem. One of the first steps in managing stress is to become aware of it. How many times at the end of the day do you sit back and think about how you felt during the day? Did you feel rushed? Tired? Angry? Over-whelmed? Frustrated? Just plain cranky? Recognizing your feelings is a huge step on the path to controlling them. Learning to use yoga, breathing, and meditation as remedies helps me stay in balance avoiding stress and all its negative side effects. If you learn how to incorporate these practices into your life, th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7134-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7134_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:09:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/153311/bariatric-yoga</link><title>Bariatric Yoga - My Bariatric Life</title><description>... Yoga is a practice that originated between four to eight thousand years ago with suggestions of the form surfacing in the Indus Valley civilization  around 3000 BC. ... The idea of uniting the mind, body, and soul in a single cosmic unit did not present until around 800-100 BC. I suppose by now you get the general idea by now: Yoga is really old. It also is really effective. Yoga Today As practiced in the West, yoga is less spiritual and focuses more on stretching and breathing. It has become more exercise than religion in Western culture whereas the Hindu population of India practice it daily in its more traditional form. Whatever your choice, it is a popular approach for promoting health. There are 30 million Americans currently practicing hatha yoga, as well as 800 million Hindus of India who maintain it as part of their daily living. What is Yoga? Yoga is a science meant to unify the mind, the body, and the spirit to create a harmony that allows self-healing. Yoga is a therapeutic dis... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7134-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7134_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:10:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/43503/alzheimer-benefits</link><title>Yoga for People with Alzheimer’s is Showing Quality of Life Benefits</title><description>...   ... I suffered from severe migraines. As a person who'd been born limber, I hadn't considered it necessary to do much to stay that way, but I did think some poses in a book I received from a book club could possibly help my migraines. The moves were effortless for my young body, but I felt good when I did them. They didn't cure my migraines, but I continued doing the poses just for that relaxed, "stretched out" feeling. ...   ... Throughout the years, I dropped the practice time and again. I was too busy. I didn't need it. Whatever. Yet, I'd pick up the book from time to time, and relearn the moves - generally when I wasn't feeling all that great, physically.  My children, now grown, remember me doing yoga moves in the living room and warning them not to jump on me when I was in a po... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7134-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7134_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:10:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/24582/137377/yoga</link><title>When a Yoga Girl Joins the Gym</title><description>... ... I love practicing yoga at home or at a studio, or even at the beach, but one place I have never done yoga is in a gym.   Gyms just aren’t my thing. I will cop to being a bit of a snob here. I like being in calm, zen-like spaces filled with orchids and incense when I get my exercise. I like it to feel spiritual and about well-being, not just burning calories. I don’t like donning spandex and heading over to an impersonal sweathouse filled with people burn-baby-burning on the treadmill, grunting as they pump iron, or worse, suffering away in a ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7134-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7134_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:11:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/223360/134686/practicing</link><title>Practicing Yoga at Any Age</title><description>...   ... One of the first people to introduce me to the art of yoga was an 80 year-old man named Kinkar. I was a teenager at the time. He was a practicing yogi who had traveled to India several times and was able to hold a headstand for what seemed to me an eternity. He had such a peaceful, relaxed, fun and vibrant personality. It was always a great pleasure to be in his presence. I lost track of Kinkar over the years but his memory and inspiration live with me to this day. He was practicing yoga long before it was fashionable and something in me registered "Hey, look at him practicing headstands at 80, I think he may be on to something". I didn't know what that something was at the time but I certainly do now! ...   ... A few years ago I bought a book called 'Awakening The Spine'. It had such a beautiful cover and title. I was immediately drawn... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7134-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7134_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:11:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/223360/134683/yoga-image</link><title>Yoga and Body Image: Part II</title><description>...   ... Again, what is perfection? Different cultures and different time periods in history have all had different ideas and beliefs about what was and is considered attractive. I often think about the 1950's and early 60's when Marilyn Monroe and her gorgeous full figure were considered the epitome of sexy and "perfect." In some cultures being too thin is a social stigma. It is assumed that you do not have enough money to feed yourself. Even within our society there are people from diffe... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7134-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7134_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:12:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/299905/154025/beneficial</link><title>Yoga &amp; Meditation Beneficial for Alzheimer's disease</title><description>...   ... Most of the time, disease creeps up on us when we least expect it. Up until that moment, we may have ignored our health and wellbeing, believing that we were invisible and that we could somehow avoid disease with very little effort. This is certainly not the case for everyone, but I believe that a society that was once primarily ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>