<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7136">Soccer trick</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:17:04" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7136-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7136_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:17:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/player-college-scholarship-2087</link><title>I'm a high school soccer player hoping for a college scholarship to play soccer.</title><description>... I'm a high school soccer player hoping for a college scholarship to play soccer. My coach thinks I should focus on training my dominant leg. How can I tell which one this is? I'm right handed, but I kick equally will with either foot. The dominant leg is usually the same side as the preferred hand. Sometimes people do have mixed dominance. This means like you they use the hand on one side and the leg on the other side most often. There is also eye and ear dominance based on which side is preferred. Some soccer coaches think being able to use either leg equally is better than being strongly dominant on one side of the other. Your coach may not know you already use either leg equally well. You may want to discuss this further before training one side more than the other. Reference: Kazutomo Miura, MD, et al. The Effect of Local and General Fatigue on Knee Proprioception. In Arthroscopy . April 2004. Vol. 20. No. 4. Pp. 414-418.' ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7136-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7136_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:17:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/injured-knee-soccer-game-1881</link><title>My son injured his knee in a soccer game.</title><description>... My son injured his knee in a soccer game. The arthroscopic surgery showed there was nothing wrong despite chronic swelling and pain. The MRI showed a tear of the medial meniscus. Why was the arthroscopic exam normal? Arthroscopic examination of the knee is done with a needle inserted into the joint. There's a tiny TV camera on the end of the scope giving the doctor a view inside the joint. The test is usually very accurate. The arthroscopic exam may be considered "negative" (normal) if and when the tear is small and remains flat against the rest of the meniscus. This is called a nondisplaced tear. Meniscal tears are graded based on their location, direction of tear, and depth of injury. A horizontal partial-thickness tear may remain undetected when nondisplaced. It's also the case that mild tears can become severe tears with re-injury. If your arthroscopic surgery was done before the tear was complete then a false-negative test may be obtained. This means the test was negative for a meni... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7136-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7136_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:17:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/15-daughter-smacked-soccer-2152</link><title>Our 15-year old daughter got smacked in the leg during a soccer game.</title><description>... Our 15-year old daughter got smacked in the leg during a soccer game. She ended up in the emergency room 12 hours later. They did surgery for an anterior compartment syndrome of the thigh and said it was a "rare" problem. With all the athletic injuries we see every week, how can something like this be "rare"? Anterior compartment syndrome (ACS) itself isn't too rare. Most likely the location of the problem is what they were referring to. ACS is a sudden, large amount of swelling in an area where there isn't enough room to hold all the fluid. ACS of the lower leg and forearm are most common. The thigh, buttock, arm, hand, shoulder, and foot can also be affected. The other factor that may be considered "rare" is the fact that your daughter only had a single injury. Most cases of ACS occur after multiple injuries, burns, fractures, crush injuries, or bleeding disorders. Doctors are starting to report an increased number of cases of ACSC with contact sports with high-speed collisions such a... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7136-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7136_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:18:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/question/659995/119884</link><title>I play soccer and practice everyday for over an hour. I tend to have sore hips and ankles at the end of the day. Does that mean I have low potassium and can you get potassium in pills?</title><description>... Do I need to take potassium if my bones are hurting after soccer practices? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7136-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7136_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:18:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/soccer-seasoned-excellent-1672</link><title>Having played soccer since I was eight, I'm a seasoned player in excellent shape.</title><description>... Having played soccer since I was eight, I'm a seasoned player in excellent shape. But last month, I tore the anterior cruciate ligament in my knee during my last high school game. I still don't know what happened. One minute I was after the ball, the next minute I was down on the field and unable to get up. How do these injuries happen? Most ACL injuries occur when the knee is perfectly straight or slightly bent. This type of injury can happen when a player is running, jumping, or standing still. In soccer, the ACL is most likely to be injured when a player is running and changing directions quickly, stopping suddenly, or twisting the body over the foot. Jumping and landing on the foot with the knee twisted can also cause problems. New technology has allowed researchers to measure the strain placed on the ACL. One important discovery has been that stopping suddenly (rapid deceleration) puts a high level of strain on the ACL. This occurs when the foot makes contact with the ground and th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7136-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7136_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:19:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/athlete-compete-country-2646</link><title>I'm not a super athlete but I do like to compete in several areas such as soccer, cross country, and tennis.</title><description>... I'm not a super athlete but I do like to compete in several areas such as soccer, cross country, and tennis. I notice whenever it's soccer season, I seem to have the most problem with my patellar tendon. I keep tweaking it and it never heals all season long. This doesn't happen with any of the other sports I engage in. Can you help me figure out what I'm doing wrong? Sports injuries command a lot of attention in the orthopedic world. Keeping athletes in tip top shape and in playing or competitive mode is a top priority for sports medicine specialists. Toward that end, researchers are trying to understand what causes tendon problems (called tendinopathies ) in this group of individuals. Sports athletes like you are often faced with chronic problems like this that they can't seem to rehab or exercise away. If we can understand how and why tendon disorders develop, then maybe we can prevent them from occurring in the first place. If the idea is correct that repeated overload of the tendon i... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7136-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7136_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:19:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/year-tore-playing-soccer-2036</link><title>My 17-year old son tore his ACL playing soccer.</title><description>... My 17-year old son tore his ACL playing soccer. The doctor told us it was torn before the MRI confirmed it. Why did we need the expensive MRI test if the doctor already knew what was wrong? Magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) has become the standard test for knee injuries. But you're right about the expense. One study stated that MRI is equal in cost to a doctor'sexam only if the cost of the MRI is less than $250.00. MRIs can cost much more than that. The pendulum is now swinging back the other way. Studies show a doctor's exam is just as good as an MRI . . . most of the time. This assumes the doctor is well-trained in evaluating knee injuries. An MRI does offer some information to help the doctor direct treatment. The MRI can show where the cartilage (meniscus) or ligament (ACL) is torn and how large the tear is. This helps in deciding between rehab and surgery. This information can be very helpful withelite athletes trying to get back on the field. Reference: Yavuz Kocabey, MD, et al. The V... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7136-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7136_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:20:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/80106/37882/joy</link><title>U.S. Soccer Olympian Joy Fawcett and Rheumatoid Arthritis</title><description>... Joy Fawcett has played for the U.S. Women's soccer team in three Olympics -- 1996 in Atlanta, 2000 in Sydney and 2004 in Athens -- and was on the field every minute. Each time, the team won a medal - one silver and two gold. She is the mother of three girls. She has rheumatoid arthritis. ...   ...   ... Joy is also an enthusiastic spokesperson for the new GeneRAtions program run by Centocor Corp. , the makers of Remicade . Last week, I had the opportunity to speak to her about her career as an athlete, Rheumatoid Arthritis and the GeneRAtions program. ...   ... Introduced to soccer at an early age by her older siblings, Joy fell in love with the sport and developed into what many considered the best defender in the world. Although she has played in three World Cups and three Olympics, she has a special place in her heart for her first Olympics, the 1996 Atlanta Games, where playing in her own country with her whole family watching added an extra thrill to winning the gold. ...   ... By 20... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7136-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7136_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:20:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/year-knee-playing-soccer-2279</link><title>Our 15-year old son hurt his knee playing soccer.</title><description>... Our 15-year old son hurt his knee playing soccer. It looks like a combined MCL and ACL tear. What are his chances for finishing the season? Combined MCL and ACL tears in adolescent athletes are on the rise with increased sports participation. These type of injuries are much more common in adult athletes. Treatment is usually with bracing for the MCL tear and surgery for the ACL tear. A recent study from Children's Hospital of Philadelphia (CHOP) reported on 12 cases of MCL-ACL tears in children ages 11 to 15. Hinged-bracing was used on the knee for four to six weeks. Bracing was used to treat the MCL injury. Arthroscopic repair of the ACL was done after that with a follow-up rehab program. Patients were able to go back to their preinjury level of sports participation. All had pain free range of motion and near normal strength. Recovery from surgery and rehab doesn't allow the athlete to finish the current season. Most are able to return within one to two years. Reference: Wudbhav N. Sankar... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7136-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7136_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:20:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/playing-soccer-sprained-2419</link><title>I fell on my knee playing soccer and sprained my PCL.</title><description>... I fell on my knee playing soccer and sprained my PCL. I wanted to play out the rest of the season, so I wore a brace instead of having surgery. It's still a little tender around my knee. Maybe I don't need any further treatment. What's the worse that can happen? It's not clear what is the natural history of mild posterior cruciate ligament tears. Natural history refers to what happens over time after an injury occurs if no treatment is provided. In the case of mild PCL injuries (grade one or two), it appears that the knee can recover. Rehab to help strengthen the muscles around the knee can help. No one is quite sure what is the final outcome. Follow-up studies of athletes with PCL injuries are limited. There are some reports of permanent instability of the knee joint. Arthritis may develop resulting in a loss of knee function. Until more is known, most experts recommend a rehab program to recover strength, proprioception (sense of joint motion), and endurance. A physical therapist can h... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>