<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7137">Cat movies</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:21:25" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7137-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7137_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:21:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/414836/122877</link><title>Should someone undergoing chemo have a cat? I know pregnant women should not change a cat box, so, get rid of the cat?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7137-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7137_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:21:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/940620/132132</link><title>I have been around cats most of my life, there was a period of ten years that I didn't have a cat. I have had one for about4yrs and it seems to me Iam allergic now. Can this happen ?</title><description>... allergies to cats ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7137-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7137_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:22:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/656957/128430</link><title>Could a cat in a downstairs apartment affect my cat allergies?</title><description>...   ... I have my opinions. I'm inclined to think it will be fine, but a part of me says it could be trouble. I just don't know what the factors of being in an apartment above a cat are. The HVAC is separate. I don't know details about my cat allergies, just that i was tested and the results were 'maximum' allergic in a scratch test. ...   ... _Thank you_ ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7137-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7137_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:22:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/123918/155111</link><title>Is it possible to be allergic to a long haired cat and not another cat?</title><description>... I have a cat with long hair and my friend says he thinks he is allergic to it , he owns two cats but they have short hair to which he isnt allergic. I was wondering if he could be allergic to my cat? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7137-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7137_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:23:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/811007/156504</link><title>Kathy Dowdy I have COPD and would love to get a kitten for company. I live alone. I have been told that a Abassyian cat would be best rather then a long haired cat. Your thoughts on subject.</title><description>... Had a cat 10 years ago, it died of cancer. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7137-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7137_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:23:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/672734/142732</link><title>I've a known allergy to cats; but, I once stayed at a friend's, and had no reaction to her cats. Can allergies change?</title><description>... In the past, my reaction to cats was typical - sneezing, itchy eyes, irritated throat, etc.  Since I had no reaction to my friend's cats, I decided, six months ago, to adopt a cat.  I've had no symptoms.  But now, for about a month, I've been dealing with hives.  I'm working with my doctor and a dermatologist to find the cause; but I suspect the cat.  I received corticosteroid treatment, and it all cleared up.  Then, was out of town for 4 days.  About one to two hours after returning to my home, the hives returned.  Can this be a reaction to the cat?  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7137-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7137_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:24:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/18095/35735</link><title>can cat saliva cause illness in a newborn baby when the cat uses the baby's pacifier</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7137-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7137_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:24:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/146976/depicting-week</link><title>Favorite Movie Depicting Mental Illness? The Question of the Week</title><description>...   ... I want to talk about movies this evening.  I absolutely adore movies and films.  I like the way you can totally forget about the outside world when you immerse yourself in a good movie.  For me, the message and details of certain movies stay on with me for years.  Recently I think I have seen such a movie which will undoubtedly linger in my mind for a long time.  ...   ... If you were to list some of the best movies depicting mental illness I am sure many of you might list films such as The Soloist or A Beautiful Mind.  ...   ... I am adding a new movie to my list, an independent film called Take Shelter .  ...   ... Christina Bruni, the community leader for SchizophreniaConnection, was able to get an interview with the writer and director of this award winning new film .  This is a not to be missed interview as this director and film will surely receive universal acclaim.   ...   ... In addition, on our anxiety site I wrote my own... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7137-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7137_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:25:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/67078/21127/ms</link><title>Movie Outline of Multiple Sclerosis</title><description>... A crack of lightening followed by rolling thunder. The lights flicker for a moment, then go out. The glow from the streetlight casts erie bluish shadows throughout the house. There is a deafening crash from the basement and the plaintive wail of a dog in the distance. The phone rings and a startled young woman reaches for it. Nobody there. The curtains blow with the incoming wind and rain. Eyes wide, she lights a candle and heads toward the basement door to investigate. Slowly she inches forward, beads of perspiration at her brow. The music forewarns you that something bad is about to happen. Your heart pounds and you lean forward. “Don't open that door!” You don't yet know what is in the basement, but you know it is not good. Once her hand turns that doorknob, nothing will ever be the same... Munching popcorn, we've all watched countless renditions of that scene in the movies. We enjoy it because it is fiction. For some of us, multiple sclerosis is our very real m... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7137-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7137_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:25:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/148013/suicide-cinema</link><title>Suicide and Cinema: What We Can Learn About Suicide from Movies</title><description>... -Quote from the film Oldboy (2003) ...   ... One of my interests outside of writing is film and movies. Recently I have been collecting movies including what are considered to be classics, some independent films, and a new genre for me-Asian horror and drama. One weekend I watched three very different movies and by sheer coincidence all three films had a theme of suicide . It dawned on me after watching these movies that suicide  is such a pervasive part of our humanity that this theme crosses all geographic boundaries and cultures. In this post we are going to explore some of the messages that film and movies give us about one of the most serious and potentially fatal symptoms of depression. Some of the questions we will try to answer include: Is there anything we can learn from film about the way a suicidal person thinks? Can we learn anything about cultural beliefs regarding taking one’s life. Wh... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>