<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7138">lance armstrong oprah</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:26:10" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7138-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7138_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:26:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/2385/12797/cancer-forum</link><title>Lance Armstrong's Cancer Forum Suggestions</title><description>... Craig Stoltz, former Health Editor of the Washington Post , weighs in with his thoughts on the Livestrong Presidential Cancer Forum.   The risk with any debate, forum, town hall meeting, or virtual digital interaction is the risk of a gas leak. Which is to say a rush of hot air, as candidates deliver their well-rehearsed bob-and-weave soundbites.   Today's Livestrong Presidential Cancer Forum--by permitting extended questioning and dialogue on a single issue in addition to prepared speeches--pulled at least a few details out of the candidate who participated.   Herewith, a few observations from Lance's cancer forum:   We're No. 1--or Not   A lot of people at the forum, including Lance Armstrong, repeated that cancer is the Number 1 killer in America. You have to wrestle the mortality stastics pretty hard to support that statement. In total deaths, heart disease still kills more people than cancer. But to declare one disease No. 1 is an unnecessary act of ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7138-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7138_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:26:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/copd/c/88905/21043/part-ii</link><title>Influence of Celebrities and Smoking, Part II</title><description>... Lance Armstrong is visiting Madison and Milwaukee this week to advocate for a smoke-free Wisconsin. His visit supports a proposed senate bill that bans smoking in all workplaces, including bars and restaurants. Having celebrities such as Armstrong work to help reduce this country’s leading cause of cancer is a breath of fresh air, and we’d love to see more of it. A few weeks ago, I wrote about Ben Affleck’s appearance on the Oprah Winfrey show where he talked about quitting smoking for the sake of his child and wife in "The Influence of Celebrities Who Smoke." In the meantime, untold numbers of photos and movie scenes depicting other celebrities smoking have appeared. The actions and words of celebrities have a measurable impact on the rates of smoking among teens and young adults. In fact, researchers at Dartmouth Medical School in New Hampshire determined that “teen viewing of movie smoking could as much as triple their risk of starting to smoke&amp;rdqu... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7138-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7138_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:27:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/5124/12647/lance-forum</link><title>Expert Patient Jeannette Vagnozzi Answers Questions Regarding the Threat of Breast Cancer</title><description>...     Expert Patient Jeannette Vagnozzi shares a broad range of cancer-related questions for Lance Armstrong and the Presidential candidates participating in the Livestrong Presidential Cancer Forum on August 27 and 28.       1) Federal Cancer Research Funding Cuts   For the first time in thirty years, federal funding for cancer research and cancer related programs was cut. How do you plan to restore the funding that was unfunded this year as well as expand it in future years?   2) Bigger Threat: Terrorism or Cancer?   According to www.reason.com , Americans have a lifetime risk of being attacked by a terrorist of 1 in 1300. According to the American Cancer Society, more than 2 in 5 Americans will be diagnosed with cancer in their lifetime. The average American has a much greater risk of being diagnosed with cancer than being attacked by a terrorist. Why is there such a great disparity in funding?   3) Young Breast Cancer Survivors &amp;nb... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7138-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7138_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:27:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/87/12697/cancer-forum</link><title>LIVESTRONG Presidential Cancer Forum: A Medical Oncologist's Questions</title><description>...     Dr. Kevin Knopf, a medical oncologist, shares his questions for Lance Armstrong and the participants in the Livestrong Presidential Cancer Forum .       1) Breast Cancer and Race. Breast cancer continues to show a survival disparity by race - women of color continue to fare more poorly in terms of survival and have a later stage of cancer at diagnosis. How do you propose to reverse this?   2) Environmental Causes of Cancer. It is thought that many cancers may be attributable to environmental causes - diet, tobacco, and pollution. How do you propose to reverse the trends in the US and make us a healthier country?   3) Federal Cancer Research Funding. Funding for the NIH has not kept up with the pace of inflation these past eight years. The National Cancer Institute had served as the cornerstone of President Nixon's "war on cancer". How much funding do you think the NCI should have, and where will it come from?   4) Fu... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7138-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7138_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:28:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/78/12639/cancer-forum-7</link><title>Political Questions from a Breast Cancer Survivor</title><description>...     Expert Patient PJ Hamel, a breast cancer survivor, offers seven questions to Lance Armstrong and the presidential candidates participating in the Livestrong Presidential Cancer Forum .     1) If you choose to make cancer a focal point of your health care agenda, it will certainly please voters who've had experience with this illness. But what about voters whose health issue is heart disease, diabetes, or any of a number of other conditions more prevalent than cancer? Do you risk alienating those voters by not addressing their concerns in as strong a voice?   Why this is important: It's all about the votes. Only if they think they can parlay cancer support into more votes than, say, support for cardiovascular research, will it truly become a focus. 2) Have any of you had personal or family experience with cancer? How has this experience (or lack of) helped position cancer on your national health care agenda?   Why this is important: Beca... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7138-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7138_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:28:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/2385/12672/forum-5</link><title>Five Questions on Cancer for Craig Stoltz, Washington Post Health Editor</title><description>...   Health Journalist Craig Stoltz, former Health Editor of the Washington Post , offers his questions for the candidates participating in the Livestrong Presidential Cancer Forum on August 27 and 28. The cancer debate will be moderated by Lance Armstrong and Chris Matthews.     1. Which firms have given more money to your campaign, pharmaceutical companies or cigarette companies?   2. Would you trust a private, for-profit company to maintain and secure your family's medical records?   3. Why shouldn't cervical cancer vaccine be required the way vaccines for whooping cough and German measles are?   4. Should there be a No Child Left Behind program for physical education?   5. Why haven't you chosen a consumer-directed health care plan for your family?   For more on Lance Armstrong's cancer forum, visit our special section:   Livestrong Presidential Cancer Forum: Our Breast Cancer Community's Questions and Advice   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7138-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7138_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:28:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/4370/12660/brand-drugs</link><title>LIVESTRONG Presidential Cancer Forum: Access to Brand Name Prescription Drugs</title><description>... Dear Lance Armstrong and Presidential candidates,   My name is Doug Haberstroh, and I am a breast cancer husband . I'm here because I hope people can learn from the story of my wife, Keri Haberstroh. Keri was diagnosed with breast cancer at age 25, about nine months after we were married. I lost Keri this past November. My two questions for the participants in the Livestrong Presidential Cancer Forum have to do with access to the right prescription drugs for cancer patients: 1) What is your position on access to name brand versus generic prescriptions for cancer patients?   2) Would you pass a bill stating that cancer patients would be allowed brand name prescriptions no matter what their healthcare insurance providers dictate in their policies? Here's the real-life story behind my questions for Lance Armstrong's cancer forum:   When Keri's breast cancer spread to her bones, she was in a lot of pain. Keri was prescribed a brand name pain pill called O... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7138-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7138_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:29:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/8832/12842/review-forum</link><title>A Survivor's Review of the LIVESTRONG Presidential Cancer Forum: Democratic Candidates</title><description>... Politics isn't necessarily my thing, but cancer is. So I tuned into the Livestrong Presidential Cancer Forum on Monday, August 27 to hear what the Democratic candidates had to say about the cancer question.   Why a forum on cancer? To make sure the candidates we have now and the two who ultimately fight for the presidency discuss the number one killer in this country, says Livestrong founder Lance Armstrong. Just like they'd talk about war, terror, and taxes, Armstrong says they should address the issue of cancer. And they did. Well, four of them did.   Senator Hillary Clinton, former Senator John Edwards, Governor Bill Richardson, and Congressman Dennis Kucinich all weighed in on this country's burden of cancer. The others? They didn't participate. Perhaps their absence speaks of their commitment to the cancer crusade. Maybe my leap to judgment is way off target. Regardless, the four who spoke to me today made me really think.   In November - one ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7138-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7138_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:29:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/1699/healing-power-louis</link><title>The Healing Power of Louis Armstrong</title><description>... ... Okay, let’s start with the ultimate musician playing the ultimate instrument. That would be Louis Armstrong and his trumpet. One gorgeous clear F above high C and I am transported into a different realm. The culturati are all unanimous in their verdict that his Hot Five and Hot Seven sessions early in his career rank as among the most outstandin... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7138-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7138_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:30:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/4370/12795/forum-keris</link><title>Livestrong Presidential Cancer Forum: Fighting Insurance for Oxycontin</title><description>... My name is Doug Haberstroh, and I am a breast cancer husband . As a follow up to my posting for the Presidential candidates participating in Lance Armstrong's cancer forum, I am sharing a letter that my wife Keri wrote, as she fought for access to a brand name prescription painkiller (Oxycontin) for breast cancer that had spread to her bones.   While Keri is not with us today to prepare a video for the Livestrong Presidential Cancer Forum, I think her letter and plight are relevant to the discussion, especially in light of John Edwards's remarks this morning about the way the insurance system is set up in this country. Edwards said he thinks the "entire system is set up to deny coverage" for those who need it, and that rings true for Keri and her breast cancer fight.       Here is Keri's letter.   Dear Senator:   I am writing you to express my concern over the policy of my healthcare provider. I am a one time Breast Cancer survivor and ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>