<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7141">Cambridge must do</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:40:29" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7141-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7141_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:40:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/erectile-dysfunction/c/question/67142/32845</link><title>Just saw an ad for Cambridge Medical clinic with "guaranteed" ED treatment...ever heard of it?</title><description>... clinic advertsies free visit if their "product" does not work on first visit ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7141-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7141_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:41:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/428/55475/sclerosis</link><title>Cancer Drug Shows Promise Against Multiple Sclerosis</title><description>...   ... Many of you have read this headline and wondered if this is the right medicine for you. ...   ... I received multiple phone calls at our Comprehensive Multiple Sclerosis &amp; Migraine Center at the University of Florida &amp; Shands Jacksonville. There were questions from the media, public relations and Wall Street analysts, besides the many questions from patients. ...   ... So what is this “cancer drug” and what is new about it? ...   ... Alemtuzumab is a monoclonal antibody directed against the cell marker CD52 which sits on white blood cells (T cells and to a lesser degree B cells and monocytes). ...   ... [Side note: I love that people with MS are so educated that I can say things like B cells etc., and most of you know what I mean. If you don’t, then please email mstar.mspn@gmail.com and I will write a blog about it.] ...   ... We have known for some time that alemtuzumab suppresses the lymphocytes (w... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7141-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7141_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:41:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/1443/158357/quitting-smoking</link><title>Quitting Smoking Can Reduce Anxiety Levels</title><description>...   ... The feeling of relaxation comes not from the cigarette, but from giving your body the nicotine it craves. According to an article on NHS Choices, “…Many addiction experts argue that the perceived beneficial effects of smoking are actually due to the physical and psychological cravings for nicotine being relieved. They put forward the case that cigarettes actually create higher levels of stress and that they only offer temporary relief before more cravings occur.” [1] ...   ... Researchers looked at 491 smokers who were attending or using some type of smoking cessation program. A little more than 20 percent of the smokers had a diagnosed mental illness – p... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7141-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7141_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:41:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/57879/passing-people</link><title>Make Time to Mourn the Passing of All People in Your Life</title><description>... Mourning isn’t easy to go through, but what if you’re mourning a loved one’s death that you can’t acknowledge publicly? Researcher Dr. Kenneth Doka and grief counselor Mary McCambridge recommend that you need to make time to grieve the passing of these loved ones instead of bottling up feelings in “Mourning Becomes Neglected,” published in the February 2009 issue of O Magazine . ...   ... An example of this type of mourning cited in the article could be an ex-husband who passes away. The ex-wife’s friends may not understand why grieving matters to the ex-wife. And although not stated in the article, this scenario could easily involve the ex-husband having Alzheimer’s disease and not remembering the marriage to the ex-wife. ...   ... McCambridge warns that avoiding grieving can leave a person with intense feelings that can lead to deep resentment as well as to the possibility of illness. To avoid these responses, McCambridge and Doka rec... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7141-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7141_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:42:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/420250/85738</link><title>Electricty in the heart</title><description>... A doctor told me that the electricity in my heart did not y off as normal but it j  ed off supplying only to one side of the heart, that we would need to address this after my surgery that was a year ago, I havnt been back since. what can happen if I continue to ignore this problem. I have also been having some chest pain and numbness in my left arm and left hand and fingers. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7141-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7141_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:42:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/699469/111644/convenient</link><title>Drivers for the use of more convenient injection devices</title><description>... your help would be much appreciated. Kind regards. Charlie Hopkins Master's in Bioscience Enterprise 2009/10 Cambridge University Email - cehh2@cam.ac.uk ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7141-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7141_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:43:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/9274/16086/ms</link><title>Genetics of MS Workshop</title><description>... Experts from the United States, UK, and Australia are gathering in Cambridge this week to participate in the Genetics of MS workshop. Dr. Stephen Sawcer quoted in MedicalNewsToday.com said that, "the genes behind MS are more difficult to find than we thought and no individual group of researchers has enough power on their own." The article asserts that uncovering the genes responsible for the development of multiple sclerosis is necessary for the advancement of treatment options for the disease.    Hopefully, some progress will be made at the workshop. I will keep my eyes and ears open for any updates.  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7141-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7141_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:43:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/c/9487/14773/bones-made</link><title>Bones Are Made of Sugars, Not Proteins?</title><description>... Scientists in Europe are developing a new theory about the composition and structure of bones. The researches, based in Cambridge and Berlin, say that they key organic building blocks responsible for bone's stiffness and toughness are sugars, not proteins as previously thought. If true, this new understanding could revolutionize work on new drugs to help protect bones.   Read more about this intriguing research at http://www.sciencedaily.com/upi/index.php?feed=Science&amp;article=UPI-1-20071008-15463500-bc-britain-bones-crn.xml   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7141-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7141_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:43:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/15122/ben-attack</link><title>Ben Affleck's first reported Migraine attack</title><description>... On the forum this morning, I noticed a thread about Ben Affleck having a Migraine. To give our readers a bit of background, here's what I wrote about his first reported Migraine attack in May of 2006... Migraine Shoots Down Ben Affleck He was shot down by German fighters over England and then became the hero in Pearl Harbor . This time, Migraine disease shot down Ben Afleck. Actor Ben Affleck spent part of his Memorial Day in the emergency room of Mount Auburn Hospital in Cambridge, Massachusetts, when a Migraine attack went out of control. Hospital publicist Ken Sunshine commented this morning, "Ben Affleck was treated for a migraine at Mount Auburn Hospital in Cambridge... He was released (yesterday) afternoon and is recuperating at home." Photographer Paul Adao saw Afleck and wife Jennifer Garner arrive at the ER. He said Afleck was holding an ice bag and Garner was helping him. Approximately two hours later, when the couple exited the emergency room, Afleck sported a p... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7141-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7141_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:44:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/163877/interview-sibling-caregiving</link><title>Interview With Carol Bradley Bursack Features Sibling Issues While Caregiving</title><description>...   ... Board certified Psychiatrist Dr. Anne Hallward hosts Courageous Conversations. During her broadcasts, Dr. Anne interviews experts about topics that many people find difficult to discuss. Dr. Anne hopes that by getting these subjects out into the open she can help others understand and better communicate their own feelings. ...   ... Dr. Anne Hallward is a Board certified psychiatrist in Portland, Maine.  She trained at Harvard Medical School, and served on the faculty at Harvard, teaching at Cambridge Hospital, before moving to Maine.  Her interest in creating space for open conversation about difficult subjects began in her teens when she noticed that very few adults seemed to be talking about intimate or difficult subjects. Her latest Courageous Conversation s... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>