<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7142">Amsterdam museums</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:44:58" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7142-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7142_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:44:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/poetry-contest/poems-37752-5.html</link><title>My Private Museum</title><description>...   Shimmering visions of color at the edge of my sight. Taunting me with beautiful images. Impressionist paintings no one else can see. My private museum. My focus of joy while enduring the vise grips crushing my skull.      Next: Nothing will Ruin this Day   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7142-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7142_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:45:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/1376/74360/washington</link><title>Greetings from washington</title><description>... ... Take Care and I will write again after I return home. ... ... sincerely yours, ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7142-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7142_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:46:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/89758/24248/love</link><title>Mustard Love</title><description>... My favorite micro-brewery/restaurant sponsors "mustard month" every March in conjunction with the "world famous" Mustard Museum in Mount Horeb, Wisconsin (See www.mustardmuseum.com ). They bring in hundreds of jars of mustard - in all varieties - and offer them as bonus condiments to their customers.   I've always loved mustard and sometimes spring for those expensive, designer flavors like Beaver Hawaiian Pineapple Mustard or Fox Meadow Farm Raspberry Honey Mustard, two of my many personal favorites. Every March, I discover a few new must-have flavors and promptly order them to enjoy at home with sandwiches or in deviled eggs.   Mustard, as you probably know, is much healthier for you than ketchup or mayonnaise. Mayo, of course, is full of fat, and ketchup's sugar content is a wee bit too high for those of us concerned about diabetes. The calorie count in mustard is almost always nil (or negligible). And the flavor mustard imparts ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7142-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7142_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:46:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/5645/9986/building</link><title>Historic Building</title><description>... This is a building where the museum is currently. Because of its age, needs too much updating and not handicap accessible, they are not going to use it much longer. This building is part of the history, and will begin to sit empty and they will soon move to a new building. My life, too is much like this building. I have been through many years of experiences, have stories to tell, and now I am sitting here empty. I do not give up, yet wondering why I try so hard to make things right. There are things that I have done, regret, yet go and still do them again. I do these in order to feel needed and young, yet turn around and continue to suffer still. How long will it be when my body no longer can be used and left to be destroyed? Destroyed beyond what I have already done? Everyday I do more damage than good and was doing so well at one time. Maybe it is my time now. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7142-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7142_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:47:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/migraineurs-564687-5.html</link><title>Famous Migraineurs: Anne Frank</title><description>...  Anne Frank's contribution to the history of the Holocaust is well known; but did you also know she may have suffered from Migraines ? Due to the various symptoms she describes in her dairies , Migraine researchers believe that Anne probably had Migraines and tension-type headaches . Anne was born on June 12, 1929, to parents Otto and Edith Frank. Anne and Margot, her older sister, lived in Frankfurt, Germany until Anne was five-years-old.   Otto, being in the banking business, had business connections in Amsterdam. This enabled him to escape there just weeks before the Nazi's began their rise to power in 1933. He went to Amsterdam, leaving behind his wife and two daughters with their grandparents in Aachen, Germany. The Franks were reunited in February, 1934, with Anne being the last family member to arrive in Amsterdam. It wasn't until 1942 that German and Dutch authorities began to concentrate on the Jewish people throughout the Netherlands, tracking ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7142-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7142_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:47:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/migraineurs-574802-5.html</link><title>Famous Migraineurs: Vincent Van Gogh</title><description>... Vincent van Gogh, born in Groot-Zundert, Holland, on March 30, 1853 may have suffered from Migraine or another headache disorder during his short, yet prolific art career. Certainly, there were references to "headache" in his personal correspondence. Researchers speculate that Van Gogh also had bipolar disorder and epilepsy. Born to Theodorus Van Gogh, a minister, and his wife Anna Carbentus, he came from a large family of five siblings; Theodorus, Cornelius, Anna, Elizabeth and Withelmein. The year before Vincent was born, his parents had another child, who was unfortunately stillborn. Van Gogh's parent's named this baby Vincent, then buried him near the family home, placing a tombstone with his namesake on it. This surely would have been a haunting memory for any child. Van Gogh's early education was spent in village schools, where he drew and painted on a regular basis. His mother was a great source of encouragement for him. During his pre-teen ye... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7142-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7142_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:47:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/question/55714/40310</link><title>Mobility Options?</title><description>... I have RA in my feet, knees, hands, and wrists. I have OA in my ankles and knees. I am having trouble walking any distance at all. I can handle the walking in the house. I am not able to go with my family to museums, zoos, malls, county fairs, flea markets, etc. I was wondering if there was a way for me to get mobility back to join in family fun again. ... jdfwood ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7142-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7142_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:48:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/483906/50201</link><title>My LDR BF says he did not have sex for 2 years if not with me. that is once a year. is this possible</title><description>... HE is 23 and i am 20, he says he loves me and sex does not really matter plus he says I was his first.  he lives in amsterdam and we can only see each other once a year, and then we dont have much time for sex so its like 1 or 2 times. everybody is laughing at me because of this relationship and i get really suspicios of him we had a lot of fights cause i think he is sleeping with woman he knows or his college or drom friends. I wonder is he for real is this possilbe, and is it healthy how long can this go on? or should i set him free? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7142-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7142_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:48:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/18/96808/making-winter</link><title>Getting Through The Winter With Depression</title><description>...   ... In the winter, the gray skies and short days tend to exacerbate our depression. Granted, it's very likely that you'll find someone with depression hanging out inside in the summer instead of enjoying the beautiful weather. But at least in summer there's a choice. When staying in more often than not is a condition that is imposed on you, your house or apartment can seem like a cell after a while. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7142-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7142_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:49:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/18/57615/cocooning</link><title>Successful Cocooning to Cope with Depression</title><description>... ... I know it's difficult when your energy is sapped by depression, but try to spend a weekend or two taking care of all those little things around the house you keep meaning to do. Otherwise, your home will be less a soothing oasis than a source of irritation. ... Look at your home's lighting situation. If it's a dark cave, you might end up feeling... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>