<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7143">from dusseldorf to washington dc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:49:53" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7143-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7143_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:49:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/33779/34567/conversation</link><title>A Dose of Conversation Online</title><description>...   ... Check it out: A Dose of Conversation Online ...   ...   ... This article serves as a true testament to you, our community members, who make this site provocative, helpful and at times crucial to those seeking not only medical information but the support of people who have been there. ...   ... I want to thank all of you for your continued support as we strive to make the best health resources available! As always, any comments on the article, or MySkinCareConnection.com, are appreciated below! ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7143-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7143_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:50:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/headache-specialists/washington-40131-5.html</link><title>Michael A. Elliott, MD - Washington Migraine and Headache Specialists</title><description>... Doctor: Michael A. Elliott, MD Clinic/Facility: Virginia Mason Clinic  Address: 1100 Ninth Avenue Seattle, WA 98111 Telephone: 206-341-0420 Recommendation: Patient Feedback ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7143-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7143_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:50:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/headache-specialists/washington-40129-5.html</link><title>Sheena Aurora, M.D. - Washington Migraine and Headache Specialists</title><description>... Doctor: Sheena Aurora, M.D. Clinic/Facility: Swedish Medical Center. Neuroscience Institute Address: 1221 Madison, Suite 1026 Seattle, WA Telephone: 206 215-2243 Recommendation: Patient Feedback ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7143-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7143_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:51:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/84/44748/learned-healthdesign</link><title>Project HealthDesign Expo in Washington D.C: Suggestions</title><description>...   ... ... What I told them essentially was what I believe advancements in medicine and medical technology mean to real people with real illnesses: they represent the chance not only to survive , but to live healthy, productive, and enjoyable lives . But at the same time, there are so many people with diabetes (and other burdensome conditions) out there struggling just to make ends meet.  Fancy new technology is not helpful for people who have no access to it.  I hope to post the video of my talk here as soon as it's available. ...   ... So that's what I had to say.  Meanwhile, the day was packed with presentations of... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7143-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7143_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:51:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/139052/washington</link><title>Lobbying and Learning about Migraine in Washington</title><description>... Monday, Nancy and I are off to Washington, DC, on Migraine business. The Alliance for Headache Disorders Advocacy is headed to Capitol Hill on Wednesday to talk with our Senators and members of the House about the need for better Migraine and headache treatment. ...   ... We'll be starting with a meeting on Tuesday to "train" everyone who will be making Hill visits. As in previous years, we have quite a few doctors and researchers attending. This year, we'll also have more patient advocates attending. It promises to be an interesting couple of days, and I'll tell you more about it when I return. ...   ... After Headache on the Hill, we'll be staying several days for the American Headache Society's 54th Annual Scientific Meeting. This is one of the medical conferences we attend to continue learning about Migraine so we can then share the information with all of you. These are the same conferences doctors attend for continuing medical education, so they can be pretty intense. A few of the to... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7143-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7143_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:52:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/840524/149318</link><title>I priscilla washington want to know that I have pain in my leg and feet what dose that mean</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7143-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7143_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:52:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/204/58408/headache-washington</link><title>Headache on the Hill Comes Back To Washington, DC</title><description>...   ... Headache on the Hill or as known in the medical community "HOH" is an initiative to increase the National Institutes of Health (NIH) funding for Migraine disease and headache disorder research and is sponsored by the Alliance for Headache Disorders Advocacy ( http://www.allianceforheadacheadvocacy.org/ ). ...   ... Go to MigraineBlog to continue reading Headache on the Hill Comes Back To Washington, DC . ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7143-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7143_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:52:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/question/31562/65577</link><title>Hello, do you now how to find a doctors who treat bipolar desorder at Washington DC area?Thanks</title><description>... Hello, do you now how to find a doctors who treat bipolar desorder at Washington DC area? Thanks ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7143-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7143_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:53:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/8133/road-live-dc</link><title>On The Road: Live from Washington DC</title><description>... I will be flying out of Washington DC later today, headed back to San Diego after 11 days on the road. To rewind the tape back a bit:   I pull into Union Station at one in the afternoon. I will be giving a talk later that evening to a local DBSA group in the auditorium at George Washington University Hospital . HealthCentral (which hosts my blogs on BipolarConnect) will be doing a video of the talk. On the spur of the moment I decide that my winter sports jacket is way too wintry and tweedy for the occasion, so I pop into a clothing shop in the station and pick up something more seasonal and a bit hipper.   The camera is on, and I’m a bit more self-conscious and stiff than I was the night before in Morristown , NJ . Nevertheless, eighty percent of what I am now beats a million percent of what I used to be, so I call it a win. It’s a small crowd, but practically everyone there buys my book, so I must be doing something right.   Becky, my producer from BipolarConnect is the... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7143-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7143_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:53:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/prostate/c/1349/34554/dose-healthcentral</link><title>A Dose of Conversation Online: HealthCentral in the Washington Post!</title><description>...   ... Check it out: ... Seeking a Cure, Patients Find a Dose of Conversation Online ...   ... This article serves as a true testament to you, our community members, who make this site provocative, helpful and at times crucial to those seeking not only medical information but the support of people who have been there. ...   ... I want to thank all of you for your continued support as we strive to make the best health resources available! As always, any comments on the article or how we can continue to improve our site are appreciated below! ...   ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>