<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7144">can headphones cause hearing loss</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:54:04" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7144-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7144_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:54:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/501293/137374</link><title>Hello, can anxiety cause hearing problems and hearing loss?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7144-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7144_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:54:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/501293/137375</link><title>Hello, can anxiety cause hearing problems and hearing loss?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7144-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7144_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:55:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001045.html</link><title>Age-related hearing loss overview</title><description>... Definition ... ... Age-related hearing loss, or presbycusis, is the slow loss of hearing that occurs as people get older. ... ... Alternative Names ... ... ... Hearing loss - age related; Presbycusis ... ... ... Causes, incidence, and risk factors ... ... Tiny hairs inside your ear help you hear. They pick up sound waves and change them into the nerve signals that the brain interprets as sound. Hearing loss occurs when the tiny hairs inside the ear are damaged or die. The hair cells do not regrow, so most hearing loss is permanent. ... There is no known single cause for age-related hearing loss. Most commonly, it is caused by changes in the inner ear that occur as you grow older. However, your genes and loud noises (such as from rock concerts or music headphones) may play a large role. ... The following factors contribute to age-related hearing loss: ... ... Family history (age-related hearing loss tends to run in families) ... Repeated exposure to loud noises ... Smoking (smokers are more likely to h... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7144-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7144_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:55:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/c/727598/167117/hearing-emerge-menopause</link><title>Hearing Loss May Emerge After Menopause</title><description>... First, let’s look at hearing loss in middle-age women. A 2009 study out of Sweden involved 104 women who were, on average, 51 years of age. Their hearing was tested twice during this longitudinal study.  The researchers found that the menopausal transition may trigger rapid hearing decline in healthy women. This decline is seen first in the left ear within four years after the last menstrual period. Hearing in the right ear tends to decline between 5-7 years after the final menstrual period.  From that point until the 13th year after a woman’s last menstrual period, the decline in hearing in both ears seems to be more subtle. ... Now, let’s talk about the link between hearing loss and brain shrinkage. A new study out of Johns Hopkins University lo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7144-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7144_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:56:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/426731/109669</link><title>can RA cause inner ear "burning" and hearing loss?</title><description>...   ... Now that I am suffering from RA symptoms, during flares, my inner ears feel full and like they are on fire.  I am wondering if there is a connection.... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7144-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7144_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:56:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/38/2331/loss</link><title>Does Rheumatoid Arthritis Cause Hearing Loss?</title><description>... First, patients taking NSAIDS (non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs) as well as the DMARD (disease-modifying anti-rheumatic drug) Plaquenil can develop symptoms of tinnitus and decreased hearing. ... ... Second, patients with Sjogren’s Syndrome can develop hearing loss, although severe hearing loss is unusual. Sjogren’s Syndrome is an autoimmune disorder in which inflammation of the glands that produce tears and saliva lead to eye and mouth dryness. Sjogren’s Syndrome is also commonly associated with connective tissue disorders such as RA, lupus or scleroderma. People with RA see to have an increased incidence of also develo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7144-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7144_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:57:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/c/question/410953/147182</link><title>Can Hearing Loss Be Caused By A Stroke?</title><description>... Stroke 9 yrs ago and lost partial hearing after the stroke, could it be due to the stroke or age ( 70 yrs , now 79 yrs old ) hearing was fine before. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7144-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7144_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:57:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/294853/54298</link><title>Is there any corelation between noise cancelling headphones, flying and acute onset of migraines?</title><description>... Twice, on long flights (greater than 4 hours) when wearing BOSE noise cancelling headphones I have had acute onset, splitting migraines - to the point of nausea and vomitting. Maxalt did help.  I am trying to figure out if the trigger is flying, long flight, or the headphones which seem to work by changing the pressure in my head.  Regular earplugs do not seem to cause the same headaches although I am nervous about truly figuring this out :)  Thank you for any help you can give me. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7144-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7144_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:58:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001048prv.html</link><title>Occupational hearing loss prevention</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Hearing loss - occupational ... ... ... Prevention ... ... ... Protect your ears when you are exposed to loud noises. Wear protective ear plugs or earmuffs to protect against damage from loud equipment. ... Be aware of risks connected with recreation such as shooting a gun, driving snowmobiles, or other similar activities. ... Do not listen to loud music for long periods of time, including using headphones. ... ... ... References ... ... Lonsbury-Martin BL, Martin GK. Noise-induced hearing loss. In: Cummings CW, Flint PW, Haughey BH, et al, eds. Otolaryngology: Head &amp; Neck Surgery . 5th ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Mosby Elsevier;2010:chap 151. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7144-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7144_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:58:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/encyclopedia/408/598.html</link><title>Hearing Loss</title><description>... Hearing impairment is a disability affecting about 1 in 10 North Americans. Hearing impairment results from a structural abnormality (such as a hole in the eardrum) that may or may not produce a functional disability (such as diminished hearing). Hearing loss can be conductive (due to faulty transmission of sound waves) or sensorineural (faulty sound reception by nerve cells), or both. Common causes of conductive hearing loss are wax blocking the ear, a perforated eardrum, or fluid in the ears. Common reasons for sensorineural deafness are noise exposure, age-related changes, and ototoxic drugs (that damage hearing). Hearing loss can be: mild (a loss up to 40 dB) - with trouble in hearing ordinary conversation moderate (40-60 dB) - where voices must be raised to be heard severe (over 60 dB loss) - where people must shout to be heard. According to the World Health Organization, the term "deaf" should only be applied to individuals with hearing impairment so severe that they cannot be... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>