<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7145">why do cats purr</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:59:07" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7145-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7145_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:59:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/sleep-disorders/c/5954/49452/cat-bed</link><title>Help! There's a Cat on my Bed</title><description>... I had to get up this morning at 2 AM to let my cats out. They have a perfectly good litter box, but would much rather use the great outdoors as a bathroom. ...   ... I live in northern Canada. The temperature early this morning was close to twenty degrees below zero, too cold to leave my pets outside for four or five hours. I waited up. They must have done a bit of exploring because a half hour passed before they returned. ... Edith C. sleeps with her cat. She says she often gets muscle cramps because she hesitates to roll over or change positions during the night. It might disturb her pet, you see. ...   ... This reminded me of a news article I read I read a while back. Dr. John Shepard, medical director of the Mayo Clinic Sleep Disorders Center had a patient tell him a story very similar to mine. He began to wonder just how many people with sleep problems shared their lives with pets. ...   ... Between February and September of last year Dr. Shepard questioned 300 patients at the clinic and fou... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7145-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7145_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:59:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/414836/122877</link><title>Should someone undergoing chemo have a cat? I know pregnant women should not change a cat box, so, get rid of the cat?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7145-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7145_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:00:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/940620/132132</link><title>I have been around cats most of my life, there was a period of ten years that I didn't have a cat. I have had one for about4yrs and it seems to me Iam allergic now. Can this happen ?</title><description>... allergies to cats ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7145-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7145_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:00:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/656957/128430</link><title>Could a cat in a downstairs apartment affect my cat allergies?</title><description>...   ... I have my opinions. I'm inclined to think it will be fine, but a part of me says it could be trouble. I just don't know what the factors of being in an apartment above a cat are. The HVAC is separate. I don't know details about my cat allergies, just that i was tested and the results were 'maximum' allergic in a scratch test. ...   ... _Thank you_ ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7145-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7145_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:00:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/123918/155111</link><title>Is it possible to be allergic to a long haired cat and not another cat?</title><description>... I have a cat with long hair and my friend says he thinks he is allergic to it , he owns two cats but they have short hair to which he isnt allergic. I was wondering if he could be allergic to my cat? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7145-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7145_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:01:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/811007/156504</link><title>Kathy Dowdy I have COPD and would love to get a kitten for company. I live alone. I have been told that a Abassyian cat would be best rather then a long haired cat. Your thoughts on subject.</title><description>... Had a cat 10 years ago, it died of cancer. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7145-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7145_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:01:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/672734/142732</link><title>I've a known allergy to cats; but, I once stayed at a friend's, and had no reaction to her cats. Can allergies change?</title><description>... In the past, my reaction to cats was typical - sneezing, itchy eyes, irritated throat, etc.  Since I had no reaction to my friend's cats, I decided, six months ago, to adopt a cat.  I've had no symptoms.  But now, for about a month, I've been dealing with hives.  I'm working with my doctor and a dermatologist to find the cause; but I suspect the cat.  I received corticosteroid treatment, and it all cleared up.  Then, was out of town for 4 days.  About one to two hours after returning to my home, the hives returned.  Can this be a reaction to the cat?  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7145-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7145_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:02:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/18095/35735</link><title>can cat saliva cause illness in a newborn baby when the cat uses the baby's pacifier</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7145-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7145_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:02:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/encyclopedia/408/314.html</link><title>CAT Scan</title><description>... The CAT (Computerized Axial Tomography) scan, also known as the CT (computed tomography) scan, is an x-ray technique that produces a film representing a detailed cross section of tissue structure. The standard CT scan procedure is painless, noninvasive , and requires no special preparation. In this test, a computerized axial tomography (CAT or CT) scanner is used to produce a series of cross-sectional x-ray images of a selected part of the body. A computer operates the scanner, and the resulting picture represents a slice of the body. Areas above and below the chosen slice do not appear on the image. The computer can combine the information in several slices to create other images of the structures inside the body. These images can detect many conditions that cannot be seen in regular x-rays. It takes the machine only a few seconds to photograph each slice, and 10 to 30 slices are usually taken. The computer then displays the chosen slice on a TV screen. Information from several slices can... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7145-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7145_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:03:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/encyclopedia/408/351.html</link><title>Cat Scratch Disease (CSD)</title><description>... Cat Scratch Disease (CSD), or cat scratch fever , is an acute infection caused by a bacteria, Bartonella henselae, that is transmitted from cats to humans as the result of a scratch or bite, or from the contact of cat saliva on broken skin or the eye. CSD affects a higher percentage of children than adults due to higher exposure. The infected animal usually shows no signs of carrying the bacteria. Within a few days of a scratch or bite, one-third of patients with cat scratch disease will develop a bump or ulcer at the site. About one to three weeks later, fever, headache , fatigue and general malaise often occur. The local lymph nodes may become enlarged and tender, and may remain enlarged for months. Weight loss, sore throat and draining lymph nodes are symptoms which occur less commonly. A rare complication of cat scratch disease is encephalitis . Encephalitis is a serious and sometimes life-threatening inflammation of the tissues of the brain and spinal cord. Call the doctor or seek treatm... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>