<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7146">why do leaves fall</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:04:29" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7146-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7146_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:04:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/8684/16079/leaves-fall</link><title>Leaves of Fall</title><description>...     I see the semi-naked trees about our community, their stature seems interesting yet ugly &amp; stark to me.  The leaves, having nurtured the trees now turn brilliant colors in their final days &amp; tummult to the ground below.  Sometimes they are carried off a bit by a gust of wind.  I see them withered, dry, old &amp; colors fading, veins dominant.  The striking similarities between myself &amp; the leaves of Fall are all too much to ignore.  I can only hope that I will have been as purposeful in my life as the leaves were during theirs; hope that the sometimes stark tree I help sustain seems more interestingly staturesque &amp; less ugly; that I too may become brilliantly colorful in my final days &amp; be carried away from my world of pain by a gust of wind. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7146-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7146_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:05:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/8684/16206/leaves-fall</link><title>Leaves of Fall</title><description>... I see the semi-naked trees about our community, their stature seems interesting yet ugly &amp; stark to me. The leaves, having nurtured the trees now turn brilliant colors in their final days &amp; tummult to the ground below. Sometimes they are carried off a bit by a gust of wind. I see them withered, dry, old &amp; colors fading, veins dominant. The striking similarities between myself &amp; the leaves of Fall are all too much to ignore. I can only hope that I will have been as purposeful in my life as the leaves were during theirs; hope that the sometimes stark tree I help sustain seems more interestingly staturesque &amp; less ugly; that I too may become brilliantly colorful in my final days &amp; be carried away from my world of pain by a gust of wind.11/08/'07 ~kat ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7146-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7146_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:05:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/855719/147549</link><title>My boyfriend is depressed and our relationship is about to fall apart, how do I deal with this? Do I stay and get treated bad or do I need to leave and will suffer even more?</title><description>... My boyfriend and I have been together for 2 years now. We fell in love very quick and have been an item ever since. When I moved in things started to go in a bad direction. My boyfriend started to point out things that I apparently do wrong. I think he has ocd and if I dont do it exactly like he wants something it isnt good enough. We worked on it and it got better. We have had so many great and happy times, but he seems to always talk something bad when he is upset. He is depressed now , he says he has no feeling for anything, work, life, or me. He says he loves me and he wants to be there for me but he cant. We were talking about marriage and I really got my hopes up but one day he told me that he just cant. He has a difficult past, his mom has schizophrenia and his dad got married 4 times. He never had a woman as a respects person. ... I am really hurt and dont know what to do. It got worse and worse, he daily told me what I need to improve on, ( I already do all I can, I am a student... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7146-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7146_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:06:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/444306/163437/fall-weather</link><title>fall like weather</title><description>...   ... My mood is getting depressed and I am trying to do positive things. ...   ... Today, I went for a short walk.  Yesterday I went to the gym and for a short run. ...   ... I have been juicing each day.  Kale, spinach, mango, apples, peaches, whatever is ripe in the store. ...   ... The parks are closed still so I ran down a dirt road. ...   ... Guess I have to keep positive and keep doing baby steps each day. ...   ... I feel down for sure and wish I had a few more friends who could just come over and not do much, just hang out, maybe cook dinner together.  Company I don't know just takes a lot out of me to have. ...   ... Guess I am down on myself, probably from the last few emails with my father... ...   ... he told me to budget better, don't spend money for example, on organic. I disagree and do spend money on organic.  I did manage to call the internet and phone company and get my bills reduced by... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7146-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7146_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:06:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/665834/54345</link><title>My daughter is having what i think is a seizures.Also her hair is all falling out please helo</title><description>... My daughter has had alot of stress latey.Her exboyfriend was very abusive she dosnt see him anymore but still after 6 monthes he stalks her all the time,she cant even leave the house he waits for her and beat her up and tells her that hes going to kill her.Her hair is falling out in clumps now she has had what seems like a seizures only the first one lasted twenty minuties she had foam on her mouth;and her eyes rolled around then fell over and looked like she stoped breathing.When she came out of it she had no idea that anythig happend.The last one she had wasnt as long still she had no idea it happend.These seizure like symptons just started in the last week and shes had two of them.Also her hair is falling out so bad she has bald spots.This guy has ripped her hair out strangled her untill she stoped breathing. If and i pray some has some advise help her PLEASE. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7146-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7146_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:07:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/4337/10802/leaving-nest</link><title>Leaving the Nest</title><description>... As most of you know by now, my daughter Stacy has moved to San Francisco.  She has always been a bit of a bohemian, so it is a perfect place for her.  She loves the city, and it has been her dream to move back there.  Moving was quite an ordeal because Stacy is a charter member of the procrastinators club, and I am the queen of organization.  I promised my husband that I would NOT help her pack, she was on her own, and I meant it this time.  (Sure I did.)  As usual everything went down to the wire, and in the end she packed, though I had to do some serious prodding.  (Actually it was more like aggressive nagging.)  I moved to a smaller place at the same time she was making her trip to San Francisco.  My husband is still in Alaska, and will be there until late August.  So, here I am alone... if you can call living with 3 dogs and a cat alone.  I thought at first it was going to be heaven.  I have several books that I want to ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7146-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7146_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:07:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/question/151036/83185</link><title>How can I help my mother who is leaving a mania state and entering depression?</title><description>... I am an adult daughter of an elderly mother with bipolar disorder.  My mother self discontinued treatment 4 years ago and until recently has been in a state of mania.  She is now falling apart.  She has destroyed important relationships with her cruelty and has spent huge sums of money and is in great debt. She continues to reject the need for help. What can I do to support her emotionally? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7146-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7146_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:08:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/question/284304/92353</link><title>i feel psychologically abused by my family but if i leave they will say im a protected citizen or th</title><description>... my family would report me missing if i leave the house. or the car missing. but it is alway a physical assault when they tell me to do chores. im light headed and dizzy and cant' climb a ladder or move furniture. i can't mow the lawn i alway feel like im in a heat wave. dad recently wrenched my arm to climb a ladder to change the air filter. he needs a handy man or a spotter to watch him do his home improvement. im living on serequel and cant be dads handyman. it results in psychological assault when i can't to home improvement with him. he pushed me on up the ladder claiming he would catch me if i fall. when i came down the ladder there was a fist in my chin ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7146-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7146_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:08:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/299905/160111/leave-processed-meats</link><title>Leave Processed Meats Behind</title><description>...   ... Processed meats include hot dogs, bacon, salami, beef jerky, pepperoni, sandwich meat slices, breakfast sausages, and meats in canned and frozen foods. Anything smoked, cured, salted or preserved fall into the processed meats category. Excess saturated fat consumption alone is not the biggest worry when it comes to this type of processed food. The most dangerous risk ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7146-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7146_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:09:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/74979/40686/fall-ing</link><title>Fall. ing.</title><description>... Falling every Fall, as expected. ... The days grow shorter, nightfall descends upon me earlier every day. ... The dark cloud of sadness and depression and loneliness descends upon me earlier every day. ... Finding joy in the leaves that fall in splendid color is my daily task. ... The colors fill me with awe then quickly that morphs into gloom.... ... What is this, this descent I can rely on as surely as the sun setting every night? ... Don't haunt me, don't taunt me-why can't you come in peace. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>