<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7147">breast cancer review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:09:34" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7147-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7147_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:09:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/78/69441/life-metastasis</link><title>Book Review: Not Done Yet: Living Through Breast Cancer</title><description>... – Not Done Yet: Living Through Breast Cancer ... Laurie Kingston has posted regularly to this site, offering information and hope to all of us—and particularly to those who’ve had a metastasis, or “mets,” as insiders call it. Laurie, a 41-year-old Canadian mother of two young boys, began blogging almost immediately after her diagnosis of breast cancer in January 2006. Ten months later, the cancer had spread to her liver; she had “mets.” And she kept on writing. ...   ... ...   ... Now, Laurie has pulled her blogposts into a 2-year journal detailing her life as a woman with cancer: the good, the bad, the ugly, AND the beautiful. Not Done Yet: Living Through Breast Cancer is a candid look at motherhood, friendship, being a wi... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7147-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7147_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:10:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/78/9378/atul-book-means</link><title>Book Review: What Atul Gawande's Newest Book Means for Breast Cancer Patients and Survivors</title><description>... On reading the title of the book, Better: A Surgeon's Notes on Performance , and glancing at its cover, which pictures a gowned-up surgeon, you’d expect it to be a graphic exploration of surgery, a “you are there” treatment of what goes on in a typical hospital operating room. But, by the time you get through the introduction, you realize that this book, though it includes scattered accounts of actual surgery, is much, much more. It’s about what it takes -- besides a medical school diploma, brains, and a major amount of talent –- to be a truly good surgeon. And the characteristics author Atul Gawande outlines –- diligence, doing right, ingenuity, and the ability to change –- can be carried over into anyone’s career, and certainly into life after breast cancer. Gawande, the modern definition of a Renaissance man, combines science and art in equal measures. A surgeon at Brigham and Women’s Hospital in Boston and a Harvard Medical School professor, he’s also a staff writer for The... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7147-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7147_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:10:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/2334/8485/breast-cancer</link><title>Having Breast Cancer</title><description>... I was 45 years old, the mother of two adult children and married to my second husband for 3.5 years when I received that dreaded phonecall. For some reason a few weeks earlier i had decided to go to the breast cancer screening mobile unit that was in town. I don't know why. I didnt have any symptoms, no lumps of dimpling, no sign that anything was wrong. But it was. Two masses and lymph node involvement. I was never so scared in all my life. Surgery first, which was a mastectomy followed by 8 rounds of dose dense chemo (yes, my hair fell out ) and then 16 radiation treatments. To say it was difficult would be a great understatement. It was awful there were good days and bad days. But as the chemo progressed the bad outweighed the good. BUT we got through it!! My hair is almost all back now it takes a long time for it to grow back in. Or mine did anyway. I am living with slight lymphedema in my right arm, a risk from the surgery that is aggravated by the radiation. It is doabl... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7147-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7147_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:10:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/78/20174/breast-cancer</link><title>Is Breast Cancer Curable?</title><description>... Is there a more poignant question coming from the lips of a breast cancer survivor than this: "Am I cured?" After the slash, poison, and burn of treatment, the months of trying to keep to a normal schedule of working and cooking and mothering while you feel like you've been run over by a cement truck, the constant fear-is the treatment working?-you get to the end, and tentatively, diffidently ask your oncologist: Am I cured?   The answer to that $64,000 question is "Yes." Or "No." Or "Well..." It all depends on what kind of cancer you have, how far along it was, and how your body reacted to the treatment.   Happily, the answer is a resounding "yes" for most of you with non-invasive cancer ("in situ," e.g., DCIS ). Ductal carcinoma (cancer) in situ (in one site) means that the cancer has remained confined to the ducts in your breast, and hasn't broken through the walls of those ducts to move into the su... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7147-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7147_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:11:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/78/18468/2007-year</link><title>Top Breast Cancer Headlines for 2007</title><description>... What’s the most significant breast cancer news to make headlines during the year just past? Here’s my totally opinionated, unscientific list of 2007 's Top-10 Breast Cancer Milestones:   Susan G. Komen for the Cure. Celebrating its 25th anniversary, this grassroots breast cancer advocacy organization marked the milestone by working to become ever more visible in the media, while stepping up its work on both the national and international levels. • Komen earned press coverage with edgy new print ads, launched last spring. “If you’re going to stare at my breasts… you could at least donate a dollar to save them.” This is NOT your mother’s foundation.   • Komen passed the $1 billion fundraising mark in its 25th year; and pledged to raise another $1 billion in the next 10 years. It’s second only to the federal government in generating breast cancer research and advocacy funding.   • In this Presidential election y... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7147-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7147_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:11:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/78/7442/short-takes</link><title>Important News Articles for Breast Cancer Patients</title><description>... Three bits of news appeared online recently that will make any breast cancer survivor sit up and take notice… while no doubt inducing in the rest of the world a case of terminal boredom. There’s something about having had breast cancer that makes any news on the subject absolutely riveting–be it the driest scientific account of gene therapy, or the most general “prevent breast cancer by eating more vegetables” broadcast. Maybe, since we’ve faced our own mortality, we grasp at straws. Or maybe we just keep reading these articles hoping that one of them is the very first step towards the REAL cure. But whatever the reason, here are three “short-bites” to chew on. Predicting How Effective Post-Treatment Drugs Will Be: Researchers at the University of Cincinnati have identified a biomarker that may be able to predict when a woman with estrogen-receptive breast cancer (which includes two-thirds of all women with breast cancer) won’t respond favorably to classic ER hormone therap... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7147-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7147_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:12:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/44/8282/sculptured</link><title>Sculptured Celebrations</title><description>... ... Remember the “Ancient Breast Exam”, a photo my friend Marie took of a sculpture in Stresa, Italy, that I included in a December SharePost? Well, Marie’s been upstaged. Last night, during a gallery walk with a group of Bay City artists, musicians and writers, my friend Carol, just back from Nicaragua, presented me with the above sculpture. “It’s from San Juan de Limay , a remote village in the mountains of Nicaragua,” she told us after our art tour as we sat around small tables eating pizza. “I had the hardest time finding it. Limay is famous for sculptures hand-carved from what the artisans called 'marmolina,' because the stone resembles marble. Most of the carved female figures were earthy, but I wanted a woman without breasts, as a present for you, to honor your struggle with breast cancer.” What Carol found was this lovely piece sculpted from volcanic rock with no help from electric tools. She lugged the two pounds of it all the way back, along with ten pounds of Nicaraguan c... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7147-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7147_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:12:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/78/3000/risk-cancer</link><title>Risk of Breast Cancer Recurrence: Do You Get the Message?</title><description>... There’s a saying among marketers that the typical consumer has to hear a message seven times before he or she internalizes it. I’m sure you’re thinking, “Oh sure, I hear any number of obnoxious ads on TV a whole lot more than seven times, and I didn’t really want to hear them even once!” But think of another kind of message: a message that’s very important to you personally, one that might, in the end, spell the difference between life and death. Would you internalize a message like that right away? Or do you need to hear it seven times? Or more? The message I’m talking about now is one you’ve probably been reading in women’s magazines, or hearing on talk shows, for years. Once you have cancer, you hear it again—loud and clear—from your health care professionals. Maybe, by now, it’s even sunk in. But what are you doing about this message? The lead article in the January 2007 issue of the Harvard Women’s Health Letter , a publication of Harvard Medical School, is “Seven for 2007: Seven t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7147-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7147_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:12:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/78/25284/news</link><title>Breast Cancer In the News: Exercise, One-Step Radiation, Clean Margins and More</title><description>... Amazing how fascinating the subject of breast cancer becomes once you have it, huh? It’s a passion, albeit an unwanted one. A passion for food leads to overflowing shelves of cookbooks and an addiction to the Food Channel. Passion for the outdoors might translate to Vasque hiking boots and a garage packed with Mountain Hardwear gear. But that uncomfortable passion we have for breast cancer? It leads to reading. To going online to research each new term that we hear in the oncologist’s office. To setting up a Google news alert for the search terms “breast cancer.” And to feeling your body go on alert when, standing at the sink washing the breakfast dishes, you suddenly hear the word “cancer” in among the jumble of words pouring out of the radio. Cancer in the daily news is always exciting. We know cancer news is seldom allowed space among the reports of suicide bombings, Presidential debates, and the endless stream of ads that fill the airwaves during... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7147-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7147_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:13:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/78/9918/cancer-safe</link><title>Chemicals in Your Home May Cause Breast Cancer</title><description>... For years, we’ve been hearing that “environmental factors” might play a role in the development of breast cancer. Most of us probably thought, “Oh, they mean if you live near a toxic waste site.” Or “Yeah, maybe for women who encounter a lot of second-hand smoke at work…” As it turns out, our everyday environment might be more toxic than we ever thought.  “Environmental Factors in Breast Cancer,” a comprehensive review of scientific research on environmental factors that may increase breast cancer risk, is a study and paper created by The Silent Spring Institute, Newton, Mass., and published this month in the scientific journal Cancer, a journal of the American Cancer Society. It includes a database referencing 450 different studies involving the relationship between environmental factors and breast cancer, and it’s being cited as the most comprehensive roundup yet compiled regarding this complex issue. The paper’s introduction reads as follows: “At the invitation of Susan G. Ko... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>