<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7150">senior java developer</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:23:22" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7150-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7150_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:23:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/teen-adhd-260203-5.html</link><title>Using Your Senior Year of High School to Prepare for College</title><description>... As teens with ADHD near the age going off to college, fears and apprehensions may begin to take over. Living on their own and being responsible for taking care of themselves and studying for classes may seem overwhelming. Taking the senior year of high school to begin preparing for the college years can make a big difference and set up a pattern of success.   The following are steps high school seniors can take while living at home to prepare themselves for living in a college situation and for developing independence   1)       Discover your personal learning style . People learn in different ways, understanding your learning style can improve both your retention and understanding of subjects being taught. 2)       Begin to take over your daily activities . If you are not already, do your own laundry. Shop for personal grooming items, such as toothpaste, shampoo, razors. Get up each morning with an alarm clock. Learning to do thes... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7150-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7150_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:23:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/3262/made-easier</link><title>Communicating With Seniors Made Easier</title><description>... I’ve always thought I was pretty intuitive. I’m not a controlling person and can be patient to my own detriment. Why am I telling you what a great person I am? Because, after reading HOW TO SAY IT To Seniors: Closing the Communication Gap with Our Elders, I realize that I could have done some things better, as far as my elder caregiving was concerned.   I’ll spare you the details of how I beat myself up, and yes, I’m getting over it. I did the best I could, and I did pretty well. However, David Solie, M.S., P.A., an expert in geriatric psychology and the CEO and medical director of Second Opinion, a life insurance brokerage corporation, has written a book that can really open the eyes of caregiver and senior alike.   The book puts out for examination Solie’s opinions, and I’m sure there are those who would argue a few. Overall, though, I’d say he offers numerous examples of how the aging brain works, that, once thought about, would bring many an “aha! moment” to the aver... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7150-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7150_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:24:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/43/32821/senior-moments-log</link><title>Having Senior Moments? Keep a Log!</title><description>...   ... Senior moments are most often benign symptoms of a busy aging brain, but unfortunately they may also be a sign of Mild Cognitive Impairment (MCI), a subtle precursor to Alzheimer's Disease. MCI can last 5-10 years and then not everyone, but a large percentage, will progress to Stage One Alzheimer's, where symptoms get worse for 2-4 years. ...   ... Everyone ignores MCI and Stage One because the short-term memory loss and intermittent and slightly odd behaviors aren't that bad and are chalked up to just getting older. The proble... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7150-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7150_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:24:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/1443/156123/adhd-symptoms-seniors</link><title>ADHD Symptoms Still Present in Middle-Age and Seniors</title><description>...   ... Middle Age Adults ...   ... A study completed in Australia looked at over 2000 middle-age adults with almost half being male. Each participant took the WHO Adult ADHD Self Report Screener (ASRS) and 6.2 percent of participants were found to score high enough to be associated with an ADHD diagnosis. Some of the findings were: ...   ... ... There was a high correlation between ADHD symptoms and the presence of depression / anxiety symptoms. The correlation was seen whether ADHD symptoms were mild or severe, indicating that, at least in this group, those with ADHD had a ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7150-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7150_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:25:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/eorthopod/news/new-pain-measurement-scale-epca-2-may-benefit-non-verbal-seniors</link><title>New Pain Measurement Scale, EPCA-2, May Benefit Non-verbal Seniors</title><description>... Determining pain levels in patients is not an easy task since pain is such a subjective sensation. In verbal patients, they can be asked to rate their scale from 0 to 10 and to describe the intensity. Non-verbal patients, particularly the elderly who may also have dementia, are not as able to express the quality and quantity of pain. The authors of this article developed a non-verbal pain scale, the Elderly Pain Caring Assessment (EPCA-2). The 8-item scale based on patient behaviors is meant to be used in day-to-day practice by healthcare professionals, particularly nurses. To develop the scale, the authors recruited patients 340 patients who were 65 years or older (mean age: 79.4 years) and unable to verbally communicate complaints of pain. The diagnosis included bedsores (78 patients), cancer (74), dementia (68), stroke (54), other neuropathy (20), arthritis (26), or bone fracture (30). One hundred twelve patients were taking opioids, 171 were taking non-opioids, and 57 were taking no... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7150-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7150_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:25:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/32873/97799/aging</link><title>Research Needed on Seniors with Multiple Sclerosis</title><description>... Aging of MSers brings with it a new set of problems. Are these the same whether or not MS is a factor? I started a new series on Aging with MS . We talked about problems such as weakness, vision, fatigue and other health issues that plague MSers as well as any person who is aging. It all sounds pretty similar, but as I concluded, the real problem may be that there is little research about older MSers. Many cultures seem to respect and even revere their elders, but that is not particularly true in America. There are services for older Americans, but not necessarily any that specifically target the needs of older MSers. Why not? We do not even know clearly what the differences may be. It is not likely that people with MS who age require the same things as people without MS? In the following topics, there are questions to be asked and solutions to be found: Treatment Medications available for MS treatment are usually not being tested on the older MS population. Treatment solutions for older ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7150-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7150_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:25:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/eorthopod/faq/citizens-center-everyday-3757</link><title>Mom is 87-years-old and comes back from the Senior Citizens Center with something new everyday.</title><description>... Mom is 87-years-old and comes back from the Senior Citizens Center with something new everyday. This time it's some kind of cream for her arthritis that burns like crazy. is this product really safe to use? It's called Capsaicin. Older adults often find that managing the chores and activities of daily life are a challenge enough without pain being added to the mix. Suddenly, making a cup of tea can become impossible -- much less preparing a nutritious meal. Sleep is disrupted, thinking becomes cloudy, and the affected adult is no longer getting out with other people. Persistent pain in this age group can create a steady decline in physical and cognitive function. Pretty soon, folks will try just about anything. But the good news is that capsaicin is safe and effective. This cream is designed to act as a counter irritant. It does cause a mild burning sensation and brings blood flow to the painful area. The result can be temporary relief from the pain. There are other topical creams and ge... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7150-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7150_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:26:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/154237/increase-chinese</link><title>Tai Chi shown to boost brain size, increase memory in Chinese seniors</title><description>...   ... Tai chi, as described by the   Mayo Clinic   website, is “… a noncompetitive, self-paced system of gentle physical exercise and stretching. To do tai chi, you perform a series of postures or movements in a slow, graceful manner. Each posture flows into the next without pause, ensuring that your body is in constant motion.” ...   ... Scientists from the University of South Florida, together with researchers from Fudan University in Shanghai, conducted a 40-week randomized controlled trial with 120 community-based seniors who do not have dementia. ...   ... According to the article, the scientists “compared the cognitive health of tai chi practitioners to that o... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7150-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7150_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:26:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/c/78/124034/alcohol-seniors</link><title>Alcohol: Bad News for Young People, Better for Seniors?</title><description>... Alcohol. Is it bad for you? Not so bad? Or does drinking actually show a potential health benefit? First, the bad news. If you spent your wild youth pursuing a lifestyle that included regular heavy drinking, you probably did irreversible damage to your bones. And you’re now at increased risk for osteoporosis due to those youthful transgressions. Now, the better news. If you’re an adult who enjoys the occasional drink; or even a daily drink, you’re probably not hurting your bones. And you may even be helping them. But before you breathe a sigh of satisfaction and settle back with a bottle of wine or a six-pack – read on. Let’s start with heavy drinking as a teenager and young adult. If you indulged in it, your bones are probably paying the price now, years later. As we grow from child to adult, we’re constantly developing new bone mass: strengthening our bones. It’s a lifelong cycle: cells called osteoblasts build bone; other cells, osteoclasts, break... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7150-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7150_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:26:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/seniors-exercise-senior-1955</link><title>I joined a group of seniors in an exercise group at the local senior's center.</title><description>... I joined a group of seniors in an exercise group at the local senior's center. I was doing good until last week when my arthritic knee started acting up again. Does this mean I just won't be able to exercise anymore? Not at all. You may have just done a bit too much or progressed your exercises too fast. Once your arthritic symptoms are under control, try again. Start at a very slow pace with only a few repetitions of each exercise. Wait a day to see how you feel. Most people don't know they've done too much while they are exercising. It's not until 24 to 36 hours later that the body shows signs of distress from overdoing it. Give some thought to the kind of exercise you are doing. Arthritic knees do respond well to the right kind of movement and exercise. Using a stationary bike is a good idea. This keeps the knee in a straight plane of motion without any twisting motions. It keeps the joint moving through its range of motion without the weight of your body putting a load on it. An aqua... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>