<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7152">haskell hash string</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:32:07" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7152-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7152_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:32:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/003735.html</link><title>String test overview</title><description>... Definition ... ... A string test involves swallowing a string to obtain a sample from the upper part of the small intestine. The sample is then tested to detect the presence of intestinal parasites. The string test is rarely used in the United States. ... ... Alternative Names ... ... ... Duodenal parasites test ... ... ... How the test is performed ... ... You swallow a string with a weighted gelatin capsule on the end. Four hours later it is pulled back out. Any bile , blood, or mucus attached to the string is examined under the microscope for cells and parasites or parasite eggs. ... ... How to prepare for the test ... ... You may be asked not to eat or drink anything for 12 hours before the test. ... ... How the test will feel ... ... You may find it difficult to swallow the string, and you may feel an urge to vomit when the string is being removed. ... ... Why the test is performed ... ... The test is performed when the doctor suspects a parasite infection, but no parasites were found in a stool sample. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7152-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7152_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:32:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/003735ris.html</link><title>String test risks</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Duodenal parasites test ... ... ... What the risks are ... ... ... ... Special considerations ... ... Previous drug treatment can affect the test results. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7152-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7152_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:33:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/003735res.html</link><title>String test results</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Duodenal parasites test ... ... ... Normal Values ... ... No presence of blood, parasites, fungus, or abnormal cells is normal. ... Normal value ranges may vary slightly among different laboratories. Talk to your doctor about the meaning of your specific test results. ... ... What abnormal results mean ... ... Abnormal results may indicate the presence of giardia or another parasitic infestation. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7152-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7152_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:33:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/768406/81387</link><title>does this mean your pregnant if a string goes in circles over your stomache</title><description>... are you pregnant if a peice of string goes in circles over your stomache ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7152-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7152_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:34:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/question/702001/74823</link><title>String Test</title><description>... Does anyone know where I can get a capsule and string test- chicago, IL ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7152-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7152_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:34:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/277433/80912</link><title>Mirena IUD strings are longer, do they just need to be trimmed after 3+ years of problem free use?</title><description>... I had my Mirena IUD put in May 2006, 6 weeks after the birth of my second daughter. When I first had it put in my husband was bothered by the string so I went back the Doctor and had the string trimmed. She trimmed it to 2 cm. Recently my husband informed that he was feeling it again (about 10-12 days ago). I had an appt for my yearly physical about 5 days later so I had her check it. (Not the original doctor who put it in. She said the string was longer, a little over an inch, which I knew, because I could feel it was different. She did not see the tip of the IUD at my cervical os and said I "should" be fine, if he continues to feel it I can come in and get an ultrasound done to locate it. A few days later it was still long so I am assuming that it isn't connected to the monthly shifts in the cervix so I called my OB/GYN office. The secretary said I should come in and get the string trimmed. I found this to be strange, why should I get the string trimmed? It isn't really bothering me... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7152-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7152_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:34:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/552176/82884</link><title>Second day, longer IUD strings?</title><description>... Yesterday I had my IUD inserted, when I felt for the strings last night they were so far up that I could barely feel them, today (day after insertion) I felt for them and they were only an inch and a half or so away from my vaginal opening. I can't feel anything coming out of my cervix yet but I'm worried something will. It's a little after midnight and if I want to be seen now I have to go to the emergency room, Planned Parenthood opens at 9am. Is this an emergency or can I wait until morning? I'm not in any pain. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7152-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7152_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:35:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/copd/c/question/659739/117352</link><title>I have had excessive stringly mucus that I cough up.</title><description>... I have had this for about 4 months.  I can string the mucus plugs I cough up between mhy fingers.  I always feel like my lungs are producing mucus and I want to clear my throat or lungs.  No excessive cough.  Have had chest Xray that showed coarsening but no overt infiltrate or mass.  Have had a normal spirometry and Alpha-1 Antitrypsin.  I am 56 years old and do not smoke.  What tests should I pursue?  Both my parents died of smoking related lung cancer.  Should I be concerned?? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7152-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7152_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:35:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/54103/26750/puppet-string</link><title>"I" Puppet On A String</title><description>... Red Tape. Red Tape. Red Tape. ... I want a man that can cut through all the red tape and get the job done pronto! ... The only option open to you, Sir ......... ... There's only one correct way to find the carrot stick, you; laboratory mouse in the maze ......... ... Sure you can choose your course of studies. You can choose all of your courses, but we feel you would be best qualified pursuing this .......... ... Never give a sucker an even break ........ ... The key to riches is never to give nothin' away for nothin' ....... ... Business is business ..... Don't let your personal feelings get in the way ...... ... If you can't even trust your family, then, who can you trust .......? ... The less information others have on you the less likely you'll be taken for a ride ....... ... We live in a sick schizophrenic society ....... ... "THE AMERICAN PSYCH IS STRAINED." ... Well? If all society is so sick, why am I medicated? ... Well .... This is the slow season. I have to lay you off. Don't you ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7152-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7152_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:36:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/003735prv.html</link><title>String test prevention</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Duodenal parasites test ... ... ... References ... ... Semrad CE, Powell DW. Approach to the patient with diarrhea and malabsorption. In: Goldman L, Ausiello D, eds. Cecil Medicine . 23rd ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Saunders Elsevier; 2007:chap 143. ... Sears CL. Giardiasis. In: Goldman L, Ausiello D, eds. Cecil Medicine . 23rd ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Saunders Elsevier; 2007:chap 372. ... Hill DR, Nash TE. Giardia lamblia . In: Mandell GL, Bennett JE, Dolin R, eds. Principles and Practice of Infectious Diseases . 7th ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Elsevier Churchill Livingstone; 2009:chap 280. ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>