<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7153">pig latin help</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:36:42" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7153-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7153_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:36:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/question/949254/148418</link><title>Is there a free way to get gastyric bypass for people who have no money? I would even be willing to be a guinea pig if need be...please help</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7153-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7153_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:37:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/454793/117364</link><title>Plast.Surgeon said he uses a substance that was pig/cow without the cells or dna</title><description>... I am having bilateral masectomies with reconstruction. he said depending on how much the surgeon leaves he might be able to just give me a silicone implant right away instead of doing the expanders.. thats when he mentioned he uses this substance that was pig or cow without dna or cells, he says it comes in sheets. ... Is this normal ??? are their risk ??? and is this only used inside the breast ??? ... Please help ... Thanks so much ... Julie ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7153-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7153_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:37:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/240381/157163/holiday</link><title>Holiday Eating: Portion Control or Pig-Out</title><description>...   ... Think about the pounds that you have already shed this year. Think about your resolution to lose weight next year. Think about your aching knees, your aching back and your closet full of clothes that are just too tight. Now that I’ve captured your attention, think about portion control. ...   ... How do you control your impulsive eating? How do you indulge without gorging? How can you satisfy your need to experience all the tastes that the Holiday season brings without dishonoring your commitment to your health? ...   ... Try eating mindfully. Take that spoonful of pumpkin pie into your mouth and savor. Don’t talk. Don’t read. Don’t do anything accept engage fully with all the senses that are experiencing that one bite... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7153-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7153_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:38:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabeteens/c/22669/33641/playing-guinea</link><title>Playing the Guinea Pig Role</title><description>...   ... As Diabetics, we can get in on this hot market! ...   ... Being a part of a research experiment can be very rewarding because you know that you are helping advance scientific breakthroughs which just might lead to a cure, plus you often get paid for your time. Participating in a trial can involve something as simple as writing down what you eat for a day, or as unpleasant as getting your blood drawn. ... Although volunteering in a research trial is jokingly referred to as being a Guinea Pig, the truth is that the volunteers are taking the place of mice. The scientists base their ideas and procedures for these human experiments on what they have already done with mice in the lab! (Oh well, they have to test humans eventually! And u... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7153-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7153_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:38:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/90847/61775/country</link><title>Going Country Do you Really Know What a Pig Pickin Is?</title><description>... When we went to Georgia every summer.  I knew that grandpa was going to have a pig pick'in.  Truth be known the annual Pig Pick' in is probably responsible for most of the world's African High Blood Pressure. That is a sure enough family gathering a good time to be had by all.  At the annual pig pick'in is where we see family that we have not seen for years.   Now being from the city, and I was not from the big city. But it was big enough.  We did not know anything about picking pigs.  How do you pick a pig?  When Grandpa would say, "come child we got to pick a pig for the pig pick in."  I did not know what in the world he is talking about.  He would have the farm hands; dig a hole, what was that all about?  Then off we would go to the hog pen.  One day he said pick a hog child, but make sure that it is a good medium size one.  I said for what grandpa, he replied, "So it will be enough for everyone to eat.  I said g... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7153-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7153_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:39:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/78/49815/guinea-pig</link><title>My Breast Cancer Treatment: I'm an Arimidex Guinea Pig</title><description>...   ... Compared to the daily 6-week... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7153-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7153_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:39:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/473728/85162/growing-pickin</link><title>Growing up country, Do you Really Know What a Pig Pickin Is?</title><description>...   ... When we went to Georgia every summer.  I knew that grandpa was going to have a pig pick'in.  Truth be known the annual Pig Pick' in is probably responsible for most of the world's African American High Blood Pressure. That is a sure enough family gathering a good time to be had by all.  At the annual pig pick'in is where we see family that we have not seen for years.   Now being from the city, and I was not from the big city. But it was big enough.  We did not know anything about picking pigs.  How do you pick pig?  When Grandpa would say, "come child we got to pick a pig for the pig pick in."  I did not know what in the world he is talking about.  He would have the farm hands; dig a hole, what was that all about?  Then off we would go to the hog pen.  One day he said pick a hog child, but make sure that it is a good medium size one.&amp;n... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7153-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7153_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:40:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/question/163954/93740</link><title>will a pig skin, skin graph ever turn the color of the person it is placed on?</title><description>... see my boyfriend has 2nd degree burns on his chest face and neck and when he was in the augusta burn center in augusta ga he had a skin graph done on his face and it was done with pig skin. so i was wondering if it would stay the dark color it is now or go back to his color(white). ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7153-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7153_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:40:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/58426/40934/lipstick-pig</link><title>Lipstick On A Pig - Are "Diet" Soda's Making You Fat?</title><description>...   ... Studies have shown that drinking diet soda's double your risk for obesity.   For example, a person who drinks a diet soda may feel it's acceptable to make up for those calories with another high-calorie food. ...   ... ABC News medical contributor Dr. Marie Savard, pointed to a recent Purdue University study released in the Behavioral Neuroscience Journal which showed that rats on diets containing artificial sweetener such as saccharin gained more weight than rats given other sugary foods.  ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7153-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7153_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:40:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/645224/99998</link><title>IF one has an allergy to grass will hay(timothy hay fed to guinea pigs) bother them?</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>