<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7154">stones satisfaction</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:41:13" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7154-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7154_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:41:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/896502/144029/americans</link><title>Many Americans Missing Out On the Satisfaction of Creating Their Own Meals</title><description>... This poll, which was reported by MarketWatch.com , involved 1,087 participants who were at least 25 years old and who were selected in order to closely match the population demographics in the United States. The findings are interesting. For instance, 28 percent of the respondents said they don’t cook because they don’t know how. More than 50 percent reported that someone else in the household (such as a spouse or partner) does the cooking. Twenty-one percent said they don’t have enough time to cook. And a quarter of respondents said they didn’t cook because they didn’t want to have to clean up the mess after the meal. ... If you asked me to participate in this study about 15 years ago, I would have been among the naysayers. My reasoning at that time of my l... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7154-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7154_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:41:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/question/348544/122023</link><title>i feel like i always have to justify something whether its to be good for a social situation or to get the exact satisfaction i need about something. my main problem is im a perfectionist</title><description>... get the right type of satisfaction that makes me feel good. thats y i start getting plans to justify or correct any situation given in life whether its a thought or a feeling or a life situation in general. i feel like i have to narrate every single thing that comes in my head. the worst i get is when i comed to a crash. this feels like my tank is out and i need to go to a safe zone or something to refuel by getting deppressed and then uncovering another plan. what should i do coping wise so i could move on and enjoy my life? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7154-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7154_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:42:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/erectile-dysfunction/c/92532/16264/sati</link><title>satisfaction</title><description>... I have tried all the other alternatives, and am considering a penile implant of the inflatable type. I would like to hear from those who have already done so: what is your level of satisfaction? What do  you like and not like about it? What problems have you had? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7154-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7154_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:42:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/1443/164014/marital-satisfaction</link><title>Is Marital Satisfaction a Matter of Genes?</title><description>... ... We inherit an 5-HTTLPR allele - a gene variant - from our parents. There are short alleles and long alleles. A recent study showed that those with short alleles are more likely to be dissatisfied with their marriage than those with long alleles. ... ... The researchers followed 156 couples since 1989. Every five years the couples met with researchers, assessed their marital satisfaction and interacted with one another in a lab, where the scientists could observe the interactions, looking at facial expressions, body language, tone of voice and topic of conversation. A majority of the couples, 125, recently gave DNA samples. ... ... The researchers looked at the 5-HTTLPR allele and found that those with two short alleles were “mo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7154-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7154_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:43:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/1443/163229/satisfaction-life-years</link><title>Does “The First Time” Shape Your Satisfaction with Your Sex Life - Even Years Later?</title><description>...   ... A research study conducted the Universities of Tennessee and Mississippi, and published in the Journal of Sex and Marital Therapy, looked at “whether the circumstances of losing one’s virginity have lasting consequences.” [1]  Researchers asked 331 participants (206 women and 113 men) to complete a questionnaire on when and how they lost their virginity and how that sexual experience was - such as were they content or did they regret it/ They were also asked about their current sex life - how satisfied they were, did they feel a sense of control? Finally, they were asked to keep a “s... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7154-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7154_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:43:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/news/patient-satisfaction-with-total-knee-arthroplasty-differs-from-surgeon-s</link><title>Patient Satisfaction with Total Knee Arthroplasty Differs from Surgeon's</title><description>... Total knee arthroplasties (TKA), or knee replacements, may need to be revised or replaced in some patients due to malfunction of the hardware or other problems. Doctors have noted that patients who understand the reasons for the initial replacement and the revisions tend to have realistic expectations regarding the outcomes than do those who are not better informed. This can extend to the rate of complications and unexpected outcomes, as well. Studies have been done that looked into the issue of unexpected complications, however, they are most often performed on patients who underwent hip replacements rather than knee replacements. The authors of this study examined the level of understanding the patients had before the surgery and their level of satisfaction with the revision and the reason for the revision. Researchers contacted 408 patients who had undergone first-time TKA revisions; 238 patients responded and consented to participate in the study. The patients were asked 10 question... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7154-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7154_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:43:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/eorthopod/news/predicting-satisfaction-from-tens-depends-on-outcome-measure</link><title>Predicting Satisfaction from TENS Depends on Outcome Measure</title><description>... TENS, transcutaneous electrical nerve stimulation, is an increasingly popular non-medication pain treatment, but there has not yet been any definitive studies regarding its effect on chronic pain. There are several causes of chronic pain, but the two mechanisms are muscle and joint tissue pain and nerve pain. The authors of this study examined the effects of TENS and if researchers could predict if high intensity TENS would be successful in patients with chronic pain. Researchers recruited 163 subjects who had chronic noncancer pain. These subjects were divided into three groups, those with: - osteoarthritis, osteoporosis, bursitis, or tendonitis- peripheral neuropathic pain, nerve pain- bone, soft tissue, and visceral (organs in the body) pain The subjects were then randomized to receive either high intensity TENS or a sham treatment that looked identical to the TENS. They received 10 days of treatment and were assessed before and after the 10-day period. The researchers evaluated whether... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7154-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7154_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:44:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/687619/144342/satisfaction</link><title>Bipolarity - Taste Cravings and Satisfaction</title><description>...   ... I also crave the sweet things that are the worst things for someone with diabetes. In the past I've had times where I'd eat four to six Three Musketeers bars a day, or an entire bag of Raisinets after coming home from work. Now I generally have red velvet cake with cream cheese frosting for breakfast. ...   ... For a long time the four basic tastes were sweet, sour, salty and bitter. Scientists have now added umami to the basic tastes which, as far as I can determine, just means "delicious." Ayurvedic medicine goes in a different direction, adding pungent (hot and spicy) and astringent (dry and tart). Tart is another favorite of mine - I add vinegar to spaghetti sauce instead of sugar, as many people do, and I prefer apples and tomatoes to be tangy. ...   ... In talking with other people who have bipolar, I've fo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7154-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7154_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:44:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/6823/13816/sit-home</link><title>all Dreams on hold,as I sit in my DREAM home, unable to enjoy,ARt my only hope,for Satisfaction</title><description>...  3+ years before,I beged my husband,Just lets move away from this desert!I miss family,I hate the heat,i am sick,It makes me tired. Here I sit,3+ years later,in My 250 year old Dream House,a 3 story Historical Home,in my home State of NEW JERSEY. Here is where I thought I would become more funcitional,PAiN Free..PRehapps a great distraction from myself,    well My dreams for becomming who I use to be,be the good mom,the great wife and homemaker,cook,clean,decorate MY DREAM HOME! this is MY DREAM HOME.....it didnt work my only out?? ART.it is the only thing i can do that dosent require me to  preform ,as I did before, Because even though,I allways have been a creative WOMAN  i was never a ARTIST! I am now a ARTIST,self proclaimed.ARt is my Escape,Detachment,Connection and ACCOMPLISHMENT,first i had myself fooled thinking,oh i am allmost a empty nest! and oh its too hot,and oh bla bla bla...I was to get a smaller home?a ONE STORY RANCH,well  here I sit in... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7154-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7154_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:45:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/1443/122083/lower-satisfaction</link><title>Medical TV Dramas Lower Satisfaction with Life</title><description>...   ... A recent study indicates that people who watch these types of shows are less satisfied with their lives than those that do not watch them. According to an article on UPI.com, people watching these shows are more apt to feel there is nothing they can do if they become sick and this leads to more dissatisfaction with life. ...   ... You can read the entire article: TV viewing may be hazardous to health ...   ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>