<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7155">ted talk mooc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:45:41" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7155-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7155_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:45:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/15/165122/andrew-solomon-depression</link><title>Andrew Solomon on Depression - You Have to See This TED Talk</title><description>...   ... Andrew Solomon Depression TED Talk   ...   ... Feel free to comment below ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7155-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7155_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:46:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/159215/dancing-question-ot</link><title>Dancing to Your Own Drum - The Bipolar Question of the Week</title><description>...   ... At a TED-x talk delivered at the Burning Man festival, Tending the Sacred Fire, yoga teacher Shiva Rea cited a 2010 study published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Science that found that 120 infants between the age of 4 and 20 months responded in a rhythmic way to the sound of rhythm. ...   ... Basically, they danced. In the words of the study authors, “human infants spontaneously display rhythmic motion of their bodies to music, rhythmical patterns with a regular beat ...” ...   ... If you want to see what dancing babies look like, here’s a link to a video I shot while visiting my grandson (then 8 ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7155-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7155_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:46:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/78/84781/kennedy-claimed</link><title>Ted Kennedy's Death from Cancer Inspires Survivors</title><description>... And we cancer survivors, those of us who daily battle the long-lasting effects of this vicious disease, have lost our champion. ... I use the word champion here as a verb, as in someone who champions a cause. Because if ever the issue of health care for all Americans had a champion, it was Ted Kennedy – the Lion of the Senate. ... His mantra, words Americans heard him repeat over and over again throughout his 47-year Senate career, was this: ... “Health care is a fundamental right for all, not just an expensive privilege for the few.” ... I think about those words today, as Ted is laid to rest in Arlington National Cemetery. And I consider what they mean to us, members of the breast cancer community. ... Health care for all means not having to make a choice between eating, putting a roof over your head, and finding out why there’s a lump growing in your breast. ... Universal health care means you can lose your job, and still have the mastectomy... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7155-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7155_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:47:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/86453</link><title>can I talk about this here?</title><description>...   ... I think a lot of people self-harm because they do not have outlets for expression of anger.   A friend of mine did yelling therapy, where she would scream out obscenities and rail against whatever she felt like.  The therapist even invited my firend's parents in for a taste of invective.  But that was back in the 80's.  Do they stil... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7155-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7155_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:47:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/15/161111/music-depression-oppression</link><title>Music, Depression, Oppression, Salvation</title><description>...   ... A few days ago, the young Korean violinist, Ji-Hae Park, gave a TED Talk, entitled, The Violin and My Long Dark Night of the Soul . Ms Park began with an exuberant rendition of Vivaldi. Then she put down her violin and revealed that she had once suffered from severe depression and had been in total despair. ...   ... Depressives, of course, are drawn to music and the arts and literature. The condition informs their work. Writing in the Opinionator blog on the NY Times earlier this year, composer Keeril Makan disclosed that “the act of composing is in a dynamic relationship with my emotional life.” ...   ... But something else seemed to be going on with Ms Park. “The violin,” she related, “which meant everything to me, became a grave burden to me.” Ms Park did not elaborate, but we can take an educated guess that the musical prodigy career path that she had been pushed into had taken her to the breaki... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7155-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7155_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:48:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/330514/105075/talking</link><title>Talking the Talk</title><description>...   ... Possibly in attempt to help me, Billy decided to let me have it about eating that much and how I would regret it in the morning. I told him that three pieces of pot pie was no big deal since I generally eat a very healthy diet, but he would have none of it. What finally came out was that I have no right to stuff my face like that and give him a hard time ab... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7155-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7155_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:48:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/568286/163160/knowing-talk</link><title>Knowing How To Talk The Talk</title><description>...   ... In moving from Michigan to New York, I wanted to make sure that I had enough medication to get me through moving, transitioning to school, and getting care set up in New York. ...   ... I went to the pharmacy and they told me that because my insurance would most likely deny giving me refills since it was too soon to fill (a week early), that I should try and call my insurance company, have them approve it, and then go back to the pharmacy. ...   ... So I called the insurance company, and when I explained that I was moving, they told me that there wasn’t really anything that they could do for me.  ...   ... But they told me that if I asked for a vacation override, they would approve it. ...   ... I guess my vacation in Hawaii is more acceptable than relocating.  ...   ... Interesting. ...   ... Okay, so maybe I’m just jealous of people who ne... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7155-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7155_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:49:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/895597/121695</link><title>I am getting lockjaw for 3 months now it happens when i wake up; and eat talking which is getting very painful now sometimes when i talk my month would fall to the side which is very uncomfortable</title><description>... i dont know if getting lockjaw is normal but i have been getting for 3 months now and is very painful when eating and talking and when my month falls to the side is quiet uncomfortable what should i do about it.. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7155-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7155_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:49:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/question/394092/48839</link><title>My husband is Bipolar, and everytime we talk he always tells me I;m attacking him. We can't talk</title><description>... My husband is Bipolar, we have been married for a 18 months. We had a great relationship when were dating. He was in a harry to get married,I told him lets wait at least a year.Well, he wouldn't have it so after 5 months we were married.With in a month are less I didn't know who he was. The next thing I know he tells me over and over I'm Bipolar so to make happy I had gone to a Mental Doctor. And they told me there was anything worry with me. Everytime I try  to talk to him,, he always tells me I attack him. Is this normal in a Bipolar ? I not sure to get a Divorce. He has beat me down so low I'm miserable. He blames me for the Bills I didn't run up he did. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7155-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7155_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 02:50:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/394875/97897</link><title>I would like to find a support group to talk about depression and to talk to other sufferers</title><description>... In Stratford Upon Avon please ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>