<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7161">dodge caliber</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:09:01" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7161-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7161_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:09:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/erectile-dysfunction/c/question/368009/139492</link><title>Dear Doctor, I am male 52, in cystoscopy large caliber stricture bulbous urethera noticed, cytology. micro hematuria urineylsis negative, dipstick urine shows blood fr last 1 year abd pelvic pain</title><description>... headache,throat pain, stiff ness in body, on diclofenac,taking omeprazole,sleep pills, CT,U/S comes normal. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7161-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7161_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:09:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/99633/checking-year</link><title>Dodging Depression: Surround Yourself With Behaviors That Make Depression Less Likely</title><description>...   ... Whatcha doing?  Watching parades perhaps? Did any of you ring in the New Year last night?  I must admit that I was asleep by that time.  I am not a big New Year's eve kinda person.  It is one of those holidays which I feel is over rated.  And not to mention if you are on the road you run the risk of being within proximity of a lot of drunk drivers.  I would much rather stay at home.  ...   ... Here is my promise to you...I am not...I repeat...not going to mention the words "New Year's resolution."   Shhh!  Be vewy vewy quiet and maybe the resolution hunters will not find us here. ...   ... Don't get me wrong, I do believe in setting goals but I don't believe in forced resolutions just because it is a certain day of the year.  ...   ... So let's just view today as a normal Friday and let me do my usual run down of questions. ...   ... 1.  On a scale of one to ten...rate this week in terms of your emotional well being...wi... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7161-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7161_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:09:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/57548/53725/alzheimer</link><title>Dodging the Alzheimer's Bullet</title><description>...   ... In the December 26 issue of the journal Neuron, Vassar and colleagues, report the discovery of a protein called elF2alpha. This protein changes in the absence of sufficient glucose within the brain. When this occurs, the protein releases an enzyme which results in the production of amyloid plaques, the sticky protein associated with Alzheimer's disease. "What we are talking about here is a slow, insidious process over many years where people have a low level of cardiovascular disease or atherosclerosis in the brain," said Vasser. ...   ... Although the development of amyloid placques is commonly associat... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7161-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7161_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:10:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/481837/133931</link><title>How can I order the Hydrocodone 10/325 asap?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7161-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7161_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:10:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/986143/136628</link><title>have just been on Prestiq 50 mg. for 5 days. Can you tell me about how long it takes to work? I a</title><description>... I have a lot of issues with my older boys who are 29 and 32.  They tell me lies to avoid confrontation with me.  there is alot more to this situation but I won't bore you.  I just want to feel like nothing matters and go on with my boring life.  I just love them so much and have tried to make them my life.  Please give me any suggestions. ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7161-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7161_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:11:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/749316/71444/fin</link><title>Finally Over!!</title><description>... Well I made it through the wedding with all smiles. Leading up to it was oh so eventful, but I wont bore you with that. What I will bore you with, is what I find so many on here saying, and that is a Rheumy with no heart! Come on now, why are these guys even in business. I went for my check up with my Rheumy, i have a horrible rash, i asked him about it and he said are you taking pain pills, i said yes, he said that is what it is from. Come on , really now, all that with out even looking at it, I am in the WRONG field that is for sure!!! Then I asked about my test results. He got smart, and said, you dont have this you dont have that, i said listen, this is the first time, i have seen you since the tests were done, i would like the results, better yet, i would like a copy of them. Needless to say I wont be going back to him. But when i looked at my test results, i saw that my tsh for my thyroid is barely registering, it is suppose to be atleast .45 and i was at .01. NOW that is not no... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7161-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7161_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:12:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabeteens/c/41603/17550/12-things</link><title>12 Things I Want for Christmas :)</title><description>... D e s s e r t D e p r i v e d   Sorry for the extremely long shortage in posts. I was preparing for my term exams, which finished on Friday! Woot woot, but really, not trying to bore you with my life, I decided that since, it's the lovely season of Christmas. (don't you just love the christmas feeling?) I would do a 12 Things I Want for Christmas . It'd be kinda cool if all of a sudden everyone on DiabeTeens started doing their own '12 things I want for Christmas'. I'm not saying you should, but it'd be kinda cool, you know? Well, in my mind anyways, it'd be cool. So...here we go :)   ~12 Things I Want for Christmas~   1) I want it to snow in Malaysia Yeah, this is as likely to happen as...well, it's never gonna happen, but I figured since this was all a fantasy list - it's only what I want to happen, then..you know, might as well add it to the list.   2) I wish there was a little button that could switch off your diabetes anytime you w... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7161-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7161_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:12:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/240285/129559/feel</link><title>sometimes i feel like doing nothing</title><description>... sometimes,or rather most of the times i have things to do but i end up doing nothing ,i  look online for stuff but dont get any ,sometimes i get bored ,i get bored with everything ,with sleeping ,watch tv and i just dont knw wat to do.i just wait for night to come,i knwthen i wil go to sleep if i feel sleepy.i dont knw y i feel like this.in such times i look for people to speak to,then i realise i dont have anybody at all to speak.i call friends but u can clearly guess from their tone that im disturbing them and well i feel more lonely than ever.worse im actually at uni and im not working ,i should b aply for jobs soon and this is scaring me coz now i wil go on job market and will b victim to all sorts of injustices and also i wont hide the fact that i wil b jeolous of those who wil get jobs b4 me.i dont knw how to react .it seems my life hasno value.i donthave any passion in life ,i feel like nothingness ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7161-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7161_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:12:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/question/231732/85554</link><title>Question about Ativan and Ambien</title><description>... I sometimes take 4mg of ativan and 10mg of ambien to go to sleep during the day because I am bored. Is that a good idea? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7161-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7161_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:13:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/185146/122872</link><title>If my problem is putting things off to the last minute, forgetting things i.e. wallet, keys, important dates. And low eneregy levels(not motivated) do I have add or adhd?</title><description>... I am a student in college. i find it hard to complete assignments. I get bored and rarely study or do my work at home or class. Do I have add or adhd? ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>