<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7165">vice president residence</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:28:00" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7165-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7165_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:28:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/community-26492-5.html</link><title>Meet Sue Bergeson, DBSA President</title><description>... Sue Bergeson became President of the Depression and Bipolar Support Alliance (DBSA), formerly the National Depressive and Manic-Depressive Association, in March of 2006, after serving as Vice President since August of 2000.   The Depression and Bipolar Support Alliance (DBSA) is the leading patient-directed national organization focusing on the most prevalent mental illnesses – depression and bipolar disorder.   DBSA has more than 1,000 peer-run support groups across the country and responds to the needs of over four million consumers who ask for help each year. Ms. Bergeson’s recent speaking engagements include the Library of Congress, the NIMH Women’s Health Initiative Lecture series, LEAD, the Managed Markets Depression Advisory Group, Alternatives Mental Health Conference, the Borderline Personality Disorder Conference, the Bipolar Options Summit, Mental Health Today, (National Public Radio), and the American Psychiatric Association Annual Meeting. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7165-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7165_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:28:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/156678/meditations-normal</link><title>Mood Disorders and the Presidency - Meditations on Crazy vs Normal</title><description>...   ... John Adams ...   ... David McCullogh in “John Adams” does not broach the topic of bipolar or mental illness, but in the book a clear picture emerges of a brilliant and temperamental revolutionary who knew how to seize the day, mobilize his countrymen, and change history. Nowhere was this more evident than the Second Continental Congress in Philadelphia, when Adams effectively floor-managed the break with Britain. ...   ... To Washington went all the glory and to Jefferson went all the credit. His brief moment in the sun - one term as the second President of the US - was u... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7165-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7165_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:29:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/215658/156274/healthcentral</link><title>The Presidency and Health: A HealthCentral Explainer</title><description>...   ... August 1, 1972: Eagleton withdraws from the ticket.    ...   ... According to the St. Louis Post-Dispatch , Eagleton had been hospitalized for mental health issues, including depression, three times between 1960 and 1966, and had undergone electro-convulsive therapy – also known as electroshock therapy – for " exhaustion and fatigue ." Eagleton was also taking Thorazine, a powerful anti-psychotic drug, information that had not been  disclosed to McGovern prior to his selection of Eagleton. ...   ... In a Time magazine poll conducted that summer,  76.7% of respondents said that Eagleton's mental health record would not influence their votes .  But there clearly was concern that given the pressures that come with being vice president and, potentially, the president, Eagleton was at risk for a recurrence of mental he... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7165-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7165_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:29:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/12995/36981/president-make</link><title>Tell the next U.S. President to make Alzheimer's a priority</title><description>... On January 20, 2009 - just a little more than five months from now - a new President of the United States will take office.No matter who you want to win the election, as supporters of the Alzheimer's Association, there is one thing on which we all agree: the next president must make the United States the world leader in Alzheimer care and research! ...   ... That's why, as part of our advocacy and awareness initiatives for World Alzheimer's Day, we're asking caring and compassionate individuals like you to sign the Alzheimer's Association Proclamation to the next President. ...   ... Make your voice heard in support of more Alzheimer care and research! We need at least 50,000 signatures to be delivered to the new president in January! ... Inauguration Day may seem far away, but we don't have any time to waste. We need to build a constituency to gather 50,000 sig... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7165-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7165_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:30:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/question/223834/138336</link><title>Dad wants to marry &amp; reside in same room in Alzheimer's facility. I have reservations, both emotional &amp; practical. The sibling of the other resident feels as I do...we want them to be happy but ???</title><description>... Should we allow a legal marriage so they can be in the same room? ... What concerns should we have? We want them to be happy. This has continued for over a month now &amp; the desire to marry persists because they want to be together all the time. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7165-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7165_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:30:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/290009/124934</link><title>i feel like a vice is gonna break my back into after thje short term of just takin a shower i have to bend over and sit for a few minutes to ease the pain ,,,, any suggestions as to whats wrong?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7165-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7165_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:31:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/copd/c/question/288700/56502</link><title>Does anxiety cause shortness of breath or vice versa? How can either be curtailed?</title><description>... I have been taking Effexor daily for anxiety and depression during a very trying period of time.  Now, I want to stop.  I have quit taking the medication for approximately 2 two weeks.  I feel less lethargic but have started having the anxiety where I feel like I can't breath.  Where do I go from here?  Do I need to continue the Effexor?  Am I dependent? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7165-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7165_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:31:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/622421/69641</link><title>Can anxiety cause depression and vice versa?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7165-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7165_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:32:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/9924/72471/hypertension-versa</link><title>Hypertension triggering Migraine and vice versa?</title><description>... ... Full Question: ...   ... Do you believe that (very) high blood pressure can trigger a migraine and/or do you believe that a migraine can trigger an episode of (very) high blood pressure? Andrea. ...   ...   ... Answer: ...   ... Dear Andrea; ...   ... Good question! The answer to both parts of your question is, "Yes." An added note is that, for some people, significant pain can increase blood pressure. ...   ... At times, this can create a question about how to best treat a Migraine when the Migraineur's blood pressure is high during the Migraine attack you're treating, but not at other times. Does one treat the Migraine or the high blood pressure? Whenever possible, it's important to know if the blood pressure triggered the Migraine, or if the Migraine is causing the high blood pressure. ...   ... As you are bound to know, if blood pressure runs high when you don't have a Migraine and aren't in pain, it's important that it be treated. It's quite helpful that many of the medications used to treat... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7165-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7165_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:32:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/894351/94698</link><title>Is it just normal when the ache's just in one side of my head .. vice versa . ?</title><description>... the headache that I am having is extremly hurts . Since my head is aching ,therefore, my eye and teeth also aches .. Its really painful as you imagine . The pain is in one side ,sometimes its on left or right . I also expericed Collapsing because of the pain . I had my head CT scan , luckily there is nothing wrong with my head .. but a migraine .. ... also had optical scanning nothing wrong . and tooth X-ray . I'll be entering college Level and Im worrying of the pain . ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>