<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7166">pita recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:33:12" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7166-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7166_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:33:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/7291/18969/eat-workout</link><title>What to eat before a Workout</title><description>... If you workout it's extremely important to eat well and have healthy snacks. Eating regularly throughout the day will help maintain energy levels, ensuring that your body has sufficient stores of energy to keep hunger at bay, and also helping you stay focused throughout your workout.   How much is too much? It's important to get the balance right, since eating too much prior to exercise can be counter effective. Why? Our bodies are not as efficient at digesting food during exercise since they are doing a number of different things at once: requiring blood supply, energy to digest the food, and also providing fuel to keep our muscles active. Therefore, overeating prior to a workout can make you feel sluggish, or can cause stomach cramps. At the opposite end of the scale however, not eating enough can also have undesirable consequences. If our blood sugar levels drop too low we can begin to feel weak, faint or tired, and this can also affect our mental ability, and reduce react... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7166-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7166_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:33:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/7291/28587/essential</link><title>Pantry Staples for a Heart Health Diet</title><description>...   ... However, if you’re trying to maintain a healthy heart you’ll know just how important eating well is. The good news is that with a little preparation, sitting down to a home cooked meal , even on the busiest of days, isn’t impossible. By making sure that your kitchen cupboards are well stocked with a few staples you’ll be able to put together a healthy meal in no time. Pantry essentials: ... ... Grains: whole wheat pasta, noodles, couscous, brown rice, oatmeal, whole grain cereal, unsalted/unbuttered popcorn, whole grain crackers, wholegrain bread (also pita pockets, tortillas, muffins). ... Wholewheat flour, sugar and other baking goods. ... No added salt canned tomatoes, and vegetables such as corn, peas, beans, and lentils. ... Dried beans and peas (pinto, kidney, black, chick). ... Tomato based spaghetti sauc... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7166-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7166_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:34:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002461fod.html</link><title>Cooking utensils and nutrition</title><description>... Food Sources Cooking utensils can affect any cooked foods. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7166-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7166_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:34:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002461.html</link><title>Cooking utensils and nutrition overview</title><description>... Definition Cooking utensils can have an effect on nutrition. Function Utensils that are used to cook food often do more than just hold the food. Molecules of substances can leach from the utensil into the food that is being cooked. Common materials used in cookware and utensils are: Aluminum Copper Iron Lead Stainless steel Teflon (polytetrafluoroethlyene) Both lead and copper have been linked to illness. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7166-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7166_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:34:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002461rec.html</link><title>Cooking utensils and nutrition</title><description>... Recommendations Metal cookware and bakeware should be designed to allow them to be easily cleaned. There should be no cracks or rough edges that can trap or hold food or bacteria. Avoid using metal or hard plastic utensils on cookware. These utensils can scratch surfaces, melt, or shorten the cookware's lifespan. Use wood, bamboo or silicone. Never use cookware if the coating has started to peel or wear away. ALUMINUM Aluminum cookware is very popular. Nonstick, scratch-resistant anodized aluminum cookware is a good choice. The hard surface is easy to clean. It is sealed so aluminum cannot get into food. Over the years there have been concerns that aluminum cookware increases the risk for Alzheimers disease . However, the Alzheimers Association reports that using aluminum cookware is not a major risk for the disease. A greater risk to health is uncoated aluminum cookware. This type of cookware can easily melt and increase the risk of burns if it gets too hot. Still, research has shown that t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7166-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7166_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:35:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/698/19487/recipe-barley</link><title>David Mendosa's Diabetes Breakfast Recipe: Better Barley</title><description>... Editor's note: A while back, we asked you to submit your favorite diabetes-friendly recipes. Our nutritionist, Heather Reese , checked them over and came up with the best in each category. Here's breakfast (note also the nutrition info at the bottom!), submitted by David Mendosa .   Better Barley Breakfast   Serves: 1   1/4 cup naked barley and 1 cup water in a small rice cooker for as long as it takes (about 40 minutes)   A little cinnamon   11 sliced or slivered almonds   A little non-nutrient sweetener (stevia or Splenda)   A little salt substitute (Sunny Paris or Mural of Flavor from Penzey's or Spike)   One tablespoon of freshly-ground golden flax seeds   25 fresh blueberries, blackberries, raspberries, or strawberries (washed just before adding them to the bowl)   2/3 cup plain unsweetened soy or almond milk (heated in microwave for 1 1/2 minutes)   Nutrition information: Calories: 287 Protein: 12 grams Carb... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7166-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7166_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:35:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/c/3120/8757/bone-month</link><title>Bone Friendly Recipes for Osteoporosis Awareness Month</title><description>... May is Osteoporosis Awareness and Prevention Month. This year's theme “Osteoporosis… it matters” emphasizes the importance for healthcare professionals and patients to talk about bone health. In addition to talking about bone health with our doctors, family members and friends, let’s also strive to have strong bones by eating healthy and nutritious food! In recognition of Osteoporosis Awareness and Prevention Month, try these delicious recipes from FoodFit.com and share them with your friends and family!  Do you ever forget about eating breakfast or just don’t have enough time to make a healthy breakfast before you leave the house? These recipes are great for those of you who may not have a lot of time, but want to maintain a diet rich in calcium. These recipes do not require a lot of preparation, so you can save time and reap the benefits of these calcium-rich foods! With just 10 minutes and a blender, anyone with a busy schedule can make the following recipe. This recipe... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7166-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7166_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:36:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/3900/17771/holiday-recipes</link><title>Gluten-Free Holiday Recipes</title><description>... I was invited to attend a gluten-free cooking event hosted by the Celiac Disease Center at Columbia University and held at Cooking by the Book here in New York City.   There was an intimate group of about 15 of us: some with celiac disease , some with wheat intolerance (like me), some spouses or parents of celiacs and some media and pharma folks thrown in for good measure. We were a happy, chatty bunch who got to know each other better over steaming pots of gluten-free ingredients. Yum!     What is gluten? What exactly is gluten and why would you NOT want to eat it? From the Celiac Disease Center : "Gluten is a protein found in wheat, and other grains and intolerance to it damages the small intestine, causing malabsorption of nutrients, which can lead to serious health consequences including Type 1 diabetes, thyroid disease, osteoporosis, cardiovascular disease, liver disease, infertility, depression and cancer." For more information on celiac disease... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7166-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7166_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:36:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/c/844/49154/thanksgiving</link><title>Thanksgiving Holiday Recipes: Pumpkin Bisque</title><description>...   ... Pumpkin Bisque ... This recipe serves 6 ...   ... Ingredients: ... 1 tbsp peanut oil ... 1/3 cup of finely chopped onions ... 1/3 cup of finely chopped celery ... 1 tsp fresh thyme ... 1 bay leaf ... 1 medium sized pumpkin (approx. 3 lbs) ... salt to taste ... freshly ground black pepper ... about 1 quart of low-sodium canned chicken stock (Try Pacific Organic Free Range Low-Sodium Chicken Broth; it has only 70 mg/sodium per cup) ... 2 tbsps toasted pumpkin seeds (optional) ...   ... Cooking Instructions: ... 1. Preheat the oven to 350 degrees F. ...   ... 2. Pierce the pumpkin several times and cook in the microwave until the shell softens using high power for approximately 3 to 5 minutes. ...   ... 3. Cut the pumpkin in half and scoop out the seeds. Save the seeds for toasting if desired. Place the pumpkin halves cut-side down on a baking sheet. Bake in the preheated oven about 40 minutes... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7166-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7166_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:37:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/c/844/47508/thanksgiving</link><title>Thanksgiving Holiday Recipes: Sweet Potato Soufflè</title><description>...   ... This week's recipe is sweet potatoe soufflè. Sweet potatoes are a popular Thanksgiving food, but you may want to consider adding them to your everyday diet. They are great sources of vitamin A and Vitamin C and good sources of copper, fiber, potassium and iron. ...   ... Sweet Potato Soufflè ... This recipe serves 10 ...   ... Ingredients ... 4 large sweet potatoes ... 2 tablespoons olive oil ... 1/2 cup skim milk ... 1/2 cup dry sherry ... 1/2 cup brown sugar ... 1/2 cup frozen orange juice from concentrate ... 1 teaspoon nutmeg ... 1 teaspoon cloves ... 1 teaspoon cinnamon ... 1 pinch salt ... 4 large egg whit... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>