<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7168">fabric glue</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:42:19" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7168-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7168_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:42:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/3900/47584/clothing-allergenic</link><title>Is there Milk in Your Clothing? Watch Out for Allergenic Fabrics</title><description>...   ... So I hit Uniqlo , a Japanese-based clothing store that has a big outlet here in downtown New York City. One of the defining features on Uniqlo is their very inexpensive cashmere sweaters and fashionable (if not overly tall and overly skinny) jeans. What I also discovered was they have a very inexpensive line of basic tee shirts, camis and turtlenecks . I bought a bunch of turtlenecks and camis for less than a NYC dinner at a nice restaurant and combined with my staples in my closet, I'm outfitted for the winter. ...   ... Cool right? ...   ... Well, the "Heat Tech" that Uniqlo's thin under-layer underthings sport has an added bonus: milk protein. Yes, milk protein is IN the fabric of the clo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7168-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7168_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:42:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/742375/59505/chemical-free</link><title>Protect Your Skin With Chemical Free Fabrics</title><description>...   ... But why would anyone put formaldehyde on clothing? There are several reasons that manufacturers use formaldehyde. It is believed that some of the chemicals help keep the fabrics stain free, wrinkle free and disinfected. But more importantly, it should be made clear that formaldehyde is considered a carcinogen, a cancer causing agent. ... Strangely enough, when clothes have a fresh, new scent to them, it's from the chemicals used during their manufacture. Some people have very sensitive skin and can break out in a rash from the formaldehyde and other chemical... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7168-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7168_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:43:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/25256/28554</link><title>How do I know if I am allergic to the chemicals and dyes in clothing/fabric?</title><description>... I work in a large department store and when I work with clothing for long periods of time my eyes get red and watery, the skin around my nose and mouth turns red and feels irritated and tongue has a funny taste on it somewhat metallic. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7168-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7168_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:43:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/question/919415/118196</link><title>why do I fabricate a response to a question just to show I know the answer? I'm bipolar</title><description>... I was explaining a process for using facebook to my wife and I told her because she uses her name from a previous marriage people will "stalk her" from her past. I do not like her using her name from a previous marriage and so I made up a situation that I thought would really prove my thought, which never really happened. This was involving an ex-girlfriend who I told her I had not had any contact from her in over a year. She accused me of being untrustworthy, so I told her that I made it up and she say's now she can't trust me. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7168-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7168_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:44:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/question/375122/64719</link><title>Is There any possibility that Morphea could be linked to the use of Formaldyhide in fabrics.</title><description>... I have been diagnosed with a rare skin disorder that looks a lot like the reactions that people are getting from wearing clothes that have been treated with formaldyhide.  I have checked into this skin problem and so far there nothing has been found that would determine a cause for this skin disorder. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7168-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7168_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:44:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002826.html</link><title>Household glue overview</title><description>... Definition Most household glues, such as Elmer's glue, are not poisonous. However, household glue poisoning can occur when someone intentionally breathes in glue fumes in an attempt to get "high." This is for information only and not for use in the treatment or management of an actual poison exposure. If you have an exposure, you should call your local emergency number (such as 911) or the National Poison Control Center at 1-800-222-1222. Alternative Names Glue poisoning Poisonous Ingredient Ethanol Xylene Light aliphatic naphtha N-hexane Toluene Where Found Glue Note: This list may not include all sources of household glue. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7168-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7168_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:45:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002826sym.html</link><title>Household glue symptoms</title><description>... Alternative Names Glue poisoning Symptoms Symptoms of breathing in ("huffing") glue fumes may include: Anxiety Convulsions (from breathing in large amounts) Drunk, dazed, or dizzy appearance Excitability Headache Irritability Loss of appetite Nausea Red, runny nose Severe poisonings caused by swallowing glue may cause: Gastric outlet obstruction Intestinal obstruction with abdominal pain ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7168-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7168_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:45:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002826trt.html</link><title>Household glue treatment</title><description>... Alternative Names Glue poisoning Home Treatment Seek immediate medical help. Do NOT make a person throw up unless told to do so by poison control or a health care professional. If the person breathed in the poison, immediately move him or her to fresh air. Before Calling Emergency Determine the following information: Patient's age, weight, and condition Name of the product (ingredients and strengths, if known) Time it was swallowed Amount swallowed Poison Control, or a local emergency number The National Poison Control Center (1-800-222-1222) can be called from anywhere in the United States. This national hotline number will let you talk to experts in poisoning. They will give you further instructions. This is a free and confidential service. All local poison control centers in the United States use this national number. You should call if you have any questions about poisoning or poison prevention. It does NOT need to be an emergency. You can call for any reason, 24 hours a day, 7 days a week. See... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7168-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7168_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:46:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/erectile-dysfunction/c/1653/7649/glue</link><title>postage stamps with GLUE???</title><description>... When is the last time anyone had stamps with glue that "had to dry" for the erectile stamp test? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7168-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7168_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:46:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/940179/75693</link><title>grommet causing me grief or is it my glue ear or something else????</title><description>... i got grommets 7 months ago and they are causing alot of problems wich are; ... - earache ... -multiple ear infections ... -discharge from the ear. ... - hearing loss ...   ... at the moment i wear two over the ear hearing aids because of my hearing loss. I also have been told that the grommets were not working 3 weeks after the operation wich was closely monitored. ... i am fed up with earache and high temperature. ...   ... is this my glue ear, grommets or something else ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>