<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7173"> severed spinal cord</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:59:25" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7173-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7173_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 03:59:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/71294/76385</link><title>Has anyone had strange/severe side effects from their spinal cord stimulator (scs)? Let me know pls.</title><description>... Has anyone had strange or severe side effects from a spinal cord stimulator implantation? My scs caused all sorts of debilitating side effects like arthritis, fibromyalgia, chronic fatigue syndrome, weakness and numbness in extremities, and chronic/severe chills and fevers...all of which I never ever had until the SCS. Let me know your experiences. I'd appreciate it. =) ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7173-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7173_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:00:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/288623/122417</link><title>What can be done for a person who has had severe sciatica for 25 years? She's had EVERY SINGLE THING done that can be done, including a Spinal cord stimulator, but that had to be removed. HELP.</title><description>... She's had epidurals, trigger points, Racz procedure, Rhizotomy, you name it ~ and still the sciatica is extremely painful. And because doctors are so afraid of the DEA, she's been continually UNDER medicated, so suffers terribly. Right now, she's on the Fentanyl patch 100mcg. Topamax 400mg per day, Cymbalta 130mg. per day, and MSIR 15mg every 2-4 hrs. but the doc doesn't give her enough of those to last. Any suggestions? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7173-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7173_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:00:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/eorthopod/faq/syndrome-delivers-baclofen-3732</link><title>I have been treated for severe pain from complex regional pain syndrome with a special pump that delivers a drug called baclofen to the spinal cord.</title><description>... I have been treated for severe pain from complex regional pain syndrome with a special pump that delivers a drug called baclofen to the spinal cord. Everything was going really well, and then all of a sudden, I stopped getting the good results I had hoped for. Now my pain is starting to come back. I can't do even the simple things I was doing like pick up a pot of coffee and pour. Have I reached some kind of plateau? Will I continue to get better with a little more time? Baclofen is a drug that has been used to reduce spasticity by stopping the messages that go from the muscles to the spine. They do this by inhibiting the GABA receptors in the nervous system. The result is to prevent the release of neurotransmitters . Neurotransmitters are chemicals that send and receive signals between a neuron (nerve cell) and the rest of the body. Baclofen can be delivered through a pump into the subarachnoid space of the spine. The subarachnoid space refers to an area between a layer of spongy tissue... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7173-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7173_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:01:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/</link><title>Spinal Cord Trauma</title><description>... The spinal cord carries nerve signals from the brain to the rest ... of the body. Trauma to the spinal cord can result from a number of ... injuries, most commonly from motor vehicle accidents, falls and ... violence. More than 80% of cases of spinal cord trauma occur in ... people between the ages of 15 and 35, and approximately 80% of ... those affected are male. Most spinal cord injuries occur in the ... area of the neck called the cervical region. Trauma can result from ... bruising to the spinal cord itself, loss of blood flow to the cord, ... or cuts in the cord. Cuts or a complete severing of the spinal cord ... are quite rare. Spinal cord injuries are serious and can cause ... diminished strength, coordination and sensation as well as other ... functions, such as bladder control. ... Symptoms ... The symptoms of spinal cord trauma vary, and depend on the ... location and severity of the injury. Complete spinal cord trauma ... - trauma that results in a total loss of sensation ... or the ability to move - occurs at about the sam... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7173-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7173_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:01:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/</link><title>Spinal Cord Trauma</title><description>... The possibility of spinal cord trauma should be considered in ... anyone who has been in a severe automobile accident or who has ... experienced significant injury to the head or neck. If you are ... conscious, you will be asked about neck pain and whether you can ... feel and move your arms and legs. You also will be assessed for ... recent use of drugs or alcohol, for whether you have other painful ... injuries that may be diverting attention from a neck injury, and ... for the presence of other signs of spinal cord injury. X-rays, ... computed tomography (CT) scans and magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) ... also may be used to evaluate your spine and the spinal cord. ... A cervical collar to keep your neck immobilized often will be ... left in place until the results of tests are available. If a spinal ... cord injury is suspected, the collar may be left in place for at ... least several days, even if tests are negative, in case an injury ... does exist but hasn't been detected because of swelling or muscle ... spasm. ... Complete spina... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7173-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7173_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:01:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001405trt.html</link><title>Spinal cord abscess treatment</title><description>... Alternative Names Abscess - spinal cord Treatment The goals of treatment are to relieve pressure on the spinal cord and cure the infection. Urgent surgery to relieve the pressure is sometimes recommended. The surgery is called laminectomy. It involves removing part of the spine bone and draining the abscess. Sometimes it is not possible to completely drain the abscess. Medicines are prescribed to get rid of the infection. This may include a combination of antibiotics. Corticosteroids may occasionally be prescribed to reduce swelling and pressure on the spinal cord. Support Groups Expectations (prognosis) How well a person does after treatment varies. Some people recover completely. An untreated spinal cord abscess can lead to spinal cord compression . It can cause permanent, severe paralysis and nerve loss. It may be life-threatening. If the abscess is not drained completely, it may return or cause scarring in the spinal cord. Complications The abscess can either injure the spinal cord from direct ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7173-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7173_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:02:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/fractures-11224-1.html</link><title>Symptoms of Spinal Cord Trauma</title><description>... Alternative Names Spinal cord injury; Compression of spinal cord; SCI; Cord compression Symptoms Symptoms vary somewhat depending on the location of the injury. Spinal cord injury causes weakness and sensory loss at and below the point of the injury. The severity of symptoms depends on whether the entire cord is severely injured (complete) or only partially injured (incomplete). The spinal cord doesn't go below the 1st lumbar vertebra, so injuries at and below this level do not cause spinal cord injury. However, they may cause "cauda equina syndrome" -- injury to the nerve roots in this area. CERVICAL (NECK) INJURIES When spinal cord injuries occur in the neck area, symptoms can affect the arms, legs, and middle of the body. The symptoms may occur on one or both sides of the body. Symptoms can include: Breathing difficulties (from paralysis of the breathing muscles, if the injury is high up in the neck) Loss of normal bowel and bladder control (may include constipation, incontinence, ... bladde... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7173-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7173_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:02:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/</link><title>Spinal Cord Trauma</title><description>... All cases of actual or possible spinal cord trauma should be ... evaluated by a doctor immediately. ... Prognosis ... Spinal cord trauma may heal over time without further problems, ... or it may result in permanent deficits, depending on the location ... and severity of the injury. ... Additional Info ... ... American Association of Neurological Surgeons 5550 ... Meadowbrook Drive Rolling Meadows, IL 60008 Phone: (847) 378-0500 ... info@aans.org ... http://www.neurosurgerytoday.org/ ... ... Christopher Reeve Paralysis Foundation 500 Morris Ave. ... http://www.apacure.org/ ... ... National Spinal Cord Injury Association 6701 Democracy Blvd. ... Suite 300-9 Bethesda, MD 20817 Phone: (301) 214-4006 Toll-Free: ... info@spinalcord.org ... http://www.spinalcord.org/ ... ... Think First National Injury Prevention Foundation 5550 ... Meadowbrook Drive Suite 110 Rolling Meadows, IL 60008 Phone: (847) ... 2... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7173-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7173_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:03:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001405sym.html</link><title>Spinal cord abscess symptoms</title><description>... Alternative Names Abscess - spinal cord Symptoms Chills Fever Loss of bladder or bowel control Loss of movement of an area of the body below the abscess Loss of sensation of an area of the body below the abscess Low backache, often mild but slowly gets worse ... Pain typically moves to the hip, leg, or feet Pain may spread to the shoulder, arm, or hand Male impotence Severe back pain Signs and tests A physical exam often shows tenderness over the spine. An exam may show signs of: Spinal cord compression Paralysis of the lower body (paraplegia) or of the entire trunk, arms, and legs (quadriplegia) Changes in sensation below the area of involvement The amount of nerve loss depends on where the lesion is located on the spine and how much it is compressing the spinal cord. Tests that may be done: CT scan of the spine Draining of abscess Gram stain and culture of abscess material Examination of cerebrospinal fluid MRI of the spine ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7173-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7173_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:03:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/27148/142803/stimulator</link><title>Spinal Cord Stimulator: A Possible Solution for Complex Regional Pain Syndrome</title><description>...   ... Spinal cord stimulation is used for many types of painful conditions including failed back syndrome , phantom limb pain, and arachnoiditis . The pain control is best in the buttocks down the leg using neurostimulation. The most dramatic results can be seen in those with CRPS. Upwards of 60 percent with CRPS will respond to a spinal cord stimulator. These results translate into returning to work, using less medication, and visiting the doc... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>