<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7174">seal team 6</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:04:19" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7174-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7174_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:04:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/1071/130508/seal-oil-approval</link><title>Will Seal Oil Win Your Seal of Approval?</title><description>...   ... We can learn a lot from these people who eat all the things that are blamed for heart disease and cancers (meat and fat) yet somehow had little to no diseases of modern man. ...   ... Seal oil has the choice for the three omega 3 EFA's and is an integral part of the heart prevention trio of necessary therapeutic nutrients. ... Seal Oil contains approximately DPA 23mg EPA 38mg DHA 45mg ...   ... Docosapentaenoic Acid (DPA) is not readily found in fish oils and is an important factor in preventing plaque and keeping the arteries soft and elastic. ...   ... ... DPA is an essential fatty acid containing 22 carbon bonds, but unlike its 'cousin' DHA it only has 5 (cis) double bonds. Not a great deal is known about how DPA contributes to the overall efficacy of Omega 3, but increase... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7174-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7174_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:04:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/medications/r/medications/golden-seal-goldenseal-oral-17309/uses</link><title>Golden seal (Goldenseal) Oral Uses and How to Use</title><description>... Generic Name: GOLDENSEAL (Hydrastis canadensis) - ORAL Golden seal (Goldenseal) Oral Uses ... Goldenseal has been used for infections. ... This product must not be used in newborns. ... Some herbal/diet supplement products have been found to ... contain possibly harmful impurities/additives. Check with your pharmacist for ... more details about the brand you use. ... The FDA has not reviewed this product for safety or ... effectiveness. Consult your doctor or pharmacist for more ... details. ... How To Use Golden seal (Goldenseal) Oral ... Take this product by mouth as directed. Follow all ... directions and warnings on the product package. This product is not recommended ... for long-term use (e.g., more than 2 to 3 weeks). If you are uncertain about ... any of the information, consult your doctor or pharmacist. ... Tell your doctor if your condition persists or worsens. If ... you think you may have a serious medical problem, seek immediate medical ... attention. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7174-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7174_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:05:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/medications/r/medications/golden-seal-root-oral-7387/uses</link><title>Golden seal Root Oral Uses and How to Use</title><description>... Generic Name: GOLDENSEAL (Hydrastis canadensis) - ORAL Golden seal Root Oral Uses ... Goldenseal has been used for infections. ... This product must not be used in newborns. ... Some herbal/diet supplement products have been found to ... contain possibly harmful impurities/additives. Check with your pharmacist for ... more details about the brand you use. ... The FDA has not reviewed this product for safety or ... effectiveness. Consult your doctor or pharmacist for more ... details. ... How To Use Golden seal Root Oral ... Take this product by mouth as directed. Follow all ... directions and warnings on the product package. This product is not recommended ... for long-term use (e.g., more than 2 to 3 weeks). If you are uncertain about ... any of the information, consult your doctor or pharmacist. ... Tell your doctor if your condition persists or worsens. If ... you think you may have a serious medical problem, seek immediate medical ... attention. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7174-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7174_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:05:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/medications/r/medications/golden-seal-goldenseal-oral-17309/images</link><title>Golden seal (Goldenseal) Oral Medication Images</title><description>... Generic Name: GOLDENSEAL (Hydrastis canadensis) - ORAL ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7174-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7174_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:06:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/medications/r/medications/golden-seal-root-oral-7387/images</link><title>Golden seal Root Oral Medication Images</title><description>... Generic Name: GOLDENSEAL (Hydrastis canadensis) - ORAL ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7174-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7174_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:06:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/2345/care-care-team</link><title>Teaming Up for Care: The Importance of Care Team Meetings</title><description>... When a loved one with Alzheimer’s Disease is living in a nursing home, how can caregivers ensure that their needs are being met? For instance when I visit Mom in the afternoon, I often ask Mom what she did that day, and she will reply “nothing.” Because of her short term memory loss, she rarely remembers what she had for lunch or whether she participated in bingo. ... ... That’s why I value the care team meetings that the nursing home holds on a quarterly basis. Similar to a parent/teacher conference that are held in schools, these meetings provide an opportunity for family members to hear from the professionals about what’s going on in their loved one’s life. These meetings also serve as a forum for concerns to be addressed. ... The care team at my mom’s nursing home includes a nursing staff member, the activity director, the dietician and the social worker. They’ll tell me about various issues, such as whether Mom’s weight is stable, whether she’s experiencing any new symptoms that they are ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7174-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7174_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:07:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/captain-goalie-high-hockey-2722</link><title>I am the captain and team goalie for our local high school ice hockey team.</title><description>... I am the captain and team goalie for our local high school ice hockey team. I just had surgery to reconstruct the ligament on the inside of my knee. It's the off season so I have some time to work on a rehab program but practice begins in another two months. Will I be able to get back on the ice by then? From the very start of recovery and rehab, patients who have had this type of surgery are warned to be patient. It can take up to nine months before they can get back to full speed on the field, ice, or court. But you will be busy all that time training and likely better than ever once you do rejoin the team. What will you be doing? After surgery, early motion and strengthening are the keys to a good result. A physical therapist will guide you through the necessary exercises and offer advice regarding precautions. A hinged brace is used right away that allows protected movement. The therapist supervises and progresses the rehab program on a week-by-week basis. Usually full weight-bearin... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7174-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7174_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:07:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/89/75424/challenges</link><title>Sealed Up Challenges With Arthritis</title><description>... Although many of our readers don't happen to live within the Continental U.S., I'm sure they are discovering many of the same "problems" that we are.  Packaging of a wide variety of things (everything from sliced cheeses and meats to medications to paintbrushes) has changed radically in the last few years.  Although I'm grateful for the concern toward good health, consumer safety and sanitation, I am just as frustrated by these  air-tight seals on many products! ...   ... At first, when this type of packaging was developed, I thought I'd just carry a small pair of scissors or a pocketknife with me in my car to open things like ketchup and mustard packets while on the road.  This was a good solution for awhile, but the challenge is intensifying! Like many of our readers, I do have some arthritis in my hands and my pincer grip just isn't what it should be (some friends like to say I lost my "grip" a long time ago!)  Those awesome packages where you're just suppos... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7174-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7174_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:08:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/medications/r/medications/golden-seal-goldenseal-oral-17309/side-effects</link><title>Golden seal (Goldenseal) Oral Precautions and Side Effects</title><description>... Generic Name: GOLDENSEAL (Hydrastis canadensis) - ORAL Golden seal (Goldenseal) Oral Precautions ... Before taking goldenseal, tell your doctor or pharmacist ... if you are allergic to it; or if you have any other allergies. This product may ... contain inactive ingredients, which can cause allergic reactions or other ... problems. Talk to your pharmacist for more details. ... This medication should not be used if you have certain ... medical conditions. Before using this medicine, consult your doctor or ... pharmacist if you have: ... ... high blood pressure ... heart disease ... ... If you have any of the following health problems, consult ... your doctor or pharmacist before using this product: ... ... bleeding/clotting disorders ... diabetes ... ... Before having surgery, tell your doctor or dentist that ... you are using this medication. ... Liquid forms of this product may contain sugar and/or ... alcohol. Caution is advised if you have diabetes, alcohol dependence, or liv... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7174-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7174_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:08:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/medications/r/medications/golden-seal-root-oral-7387/side-effects</link><title>Golden seal Root Oral Precautions and Side Effects</title><description>... Generic Name: GOLDENSEAL (Hydrastis canadensis) - ORAL Golden seal Root Oral Precautions ... Before taking goldenseal, tell your doctor or pharmacist ... if you are allergic to it; or if you have any other allergies. This product may ... contain inactive ingredients, which can cause allergic reactions or other ... problems. Talk to your pharmacist for more details. ... This medication should not be used if you have certain ... medical conditions. Before using this medicine, consult your doctor or ... pharmacist if you have: ... ... high blood pressure ... heart disease ... ... If you have any of the following health problems, consult ... your doctor or pharmacist before using this product: ... ... bleeding/clotting disorders ... diabetes ... ... Before having surgery, tell your doctor or dentist that ... you are using this medication. ... Liquid forms of this product may contain sugar and/or ... alcohol. Caution is advised if you have diabetes, alcohol dependence, or liver ... d... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>