<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7176"> weather in nyc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:13:00" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7176-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7176_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:13:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/83694/106765/weather</link><title>weather the weather</title><description>... how do you live moment to moment? ... I didn't sleep too well last night ... living in my apartment is nerve wracking. ... Jon ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7176-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7176_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:13:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/9924/9074/043007-6-trigger</link><title>04/30/07 #6 - Is weather a legitimate trigger?</title><description>... Full Question: I’m a 44 Year old Man, 6’ 185lbs. I live in New Jersey. I had graves disease about 7 years ago and was successfully treated with Radioactive Iodine. I have been experiencing migraines for about 11 years. I get the aura – Lightning bolts in the right eye, and then about 15 minutes to ½ hour late the pain comes, usually on the right side, but I have had it on both. I often loose my ability to comprehend things and to speak properly. When I first got them, I immediately though I had a brain tumor and had an MRI. The neurologist told me I had “Classic Migraines” and recommend Imitrex – It did not help.  I have tried various other medications also, having seen numerous doctors, but nothing really helps. I got in shape, watch what I eat and now have them down to about three a year – Interestingly it is almost always when the  seasons change- March April – October November. Unfortunately I have gotten 1 Migraine a month since October 2006. I assume it is because of t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7176-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7176_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:13:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/89/8863/weather</link><title>Whether the Weather...</title><description>...   ... Of course there are a lot of really “unique” suggestions from everyone—your next door neighbor, your friendly grocer, the mailman, even advice from Great Aunt Sue (who passed away from a different problem 12 years ago!)&amp;nbs... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7176-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7176_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:14:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/568286/139370/rh</link><title>Rain, Rain, Go Away: Rheumatoid Arthritis And The Weather</title><description>...   ... I had a headache all the time. It felt like someone was stabbing me between the eyes. My pain level was up, and for part of the time, I was just barely functional. I just didn’t feel good at all. ...   ... And since I’m not g-d, and can’t change the weather, what am I supposed to do at times like this? I guess function the best I can and hope the weather gets better pronto. ...   ... As the days cycled through rain, on and off, so did the way that I felt physically, and subsequently, impacted my mood, as well. ...   ... Some of us say that we are human barometers. I know that I feel the rain even before it comes. There is something about those low lying clouds that literally clog my brain. ...   ... And arthritics aren’t the only ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7176-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7176_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:14:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/915283/128440/forecast</link><title>Joint Pain Can Forecast the Weather</title><description>...   ... Ouch, it's cold outside. Just looking at temperature, one can easily conclude that l ow temperatures increase pain not only in a joint, but everywhere. Knee pain , rheumatoid pain, and osteoarthritis pain all show consistent increases in severity has the mercury plunges. The reason for this phenomenon probably has something to do with nerve conduction slowing in t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7176-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7176_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:15:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/5949/153965/fibromyalgia</link><title>Fibromyalgia Worse? Don't Blame the Weather</title><description>...   ... Study Design and Results ...   ... Because FM patients frequently complain of worsening symptoms due to the weather , scientists at Utrecht University in the Netherlands sought to find out how various weather conditions and patient characteristics might affect FM symptoms. ...   ... Study participants included 333 female fibromyalgia patients with a mean age of 47 who had been diagnosed an average of 3.5 years ago. Patient characteristics considered included age, education, marital status, time since symptoms began, and time since the diagnosis of fibromyalgia was made. ...   ... Participants kept a diary for 28 days, reporting on pain and fatigue levels as well as physical activity, sleep quality t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7176-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7176_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:15:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/1443/160215/seasonal-affective-disorder</link><title>Warm Weather Seasonal Affective Disorder</title><description>...   ... SAD is mostly known for the “ winter blues ” and is associated with feelings of sadness and depression during the cold months when there are less hours of sunlight each day. It can interfere with energy levels, behavior and sleep patterns. But although less, common, SAD can impact people during the spring and summer months. An article on South University’s website, “Spring Can Bring Showers of Depression,” symptoms of SAD during the warmer months include anxiety , insomnia and loss of appetite. [1] ...   ... Causes of Warm Weather SAD ... ... Cold weather SAD is thought to be linked to an increase in the prod... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7176-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7176_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:16:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/568286/152103/rh</link><title>With Stormy Weather Comes Rheumatoid Arthritis</title><description>...   ... But what about the more freak weather occurrences that seem to be happening as a result of global warming? ...   ... Last month, a tornado touched down about 10 miles from where I live. That's right. We had tornado activity in Michigan in March. It was also 80 degrees. The next week, it was 40 degrees. ...   ... In Michigan, tornado season usually occurs mainly in July and August. And the reality is that in most cases, we don't take the threat all that seriously. ...   ... I mean, even in the case of this latest storm, I stood by the window of my third-floor apartment and watched the sky turn green, and the pea-sized hail come and go. ...   ... Because these things don't happen in my (our) backyard, right? In some ways, that is just like illness. You never think it is going to happen to you, and when it does, you are powerless to stop it because you are caught tota... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7176-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7176_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:16:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002038.html</link><title>Dry skin and cold weather itch overview</title><description>... Definition ... ... ... ... Alternative Names ... ... Cold weather and itchy skin ... ... Information ... ... Here are some recommendations for dealing with dry skin : ... ... Take fewer and shorter baths. When you bathe, avoid hot water. ... Moisturize your skin immediately after bathing in order to prevent the skin from drying. ... Avoid overdrying wet skin. Try patting your skin dry. ... Avoid excessive use of soap. Try a soapless cleanser. ... Don't overheat your house, and use a humidifier if you live in a dry climate. ... ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7176-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7176_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:16:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/triggers-44407-5.html</link><title>Weather Changes as a Migraine Trigger</title><description>... Migraine sufferers may be able to avoid triggering some of the excruciating attacks by skipping the red wine with dinner and forgoing the chocolate mousse for dessert, but there's little they can do about one of the most common Migraine triggers : the weather. Half of Migraine sufferers were sensitive to weather variables, but most were wrong in their prediction of which climate variable was the culprit, according to findings of a study presented at the 46th Annual Scientific Meeting of the American Headache Society (AHS). Marcelo E. Bigal, M.D., Ph.D., director of research at the New England Center for Headache , Stamford, Connecticut, and assistant professor of neurology at Albert Einstein College of Medicine, Bronx, N.Y., explained: "Most people in the study thought they could predict which type of weather factor (temperature, snow, etc.) triggered their Migraines, but they really couldn't ... Ironically, we found the one constant in weather-triggered Mi... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>