<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7180">blink reflex</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:30:39" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7180-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7180_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:30:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/003292.html</link><title>Infantile reflexes overview</title><description>... Definition A reflex is an involuntary muscle reaction to a certain type of stimulation. Certain sensations or movements are known to produce specific muscular responses. Alternative Names Primitive reflexes; Reflexes in infants; Tonic neck reflex; Galant reflex; Truncal incurvation; Rooting reflex; Parachute reflex; Grasp reflex Considerations The presence and strength of a reflex is an important sign of neurological development and function. Many infant reflexes disappear as the child grows older, although some remain throughout adulthood. The presence of an infant reflex after the age at which the reflex normally disappears can be a sign of brain damage or damage to the nervous system. Infant reflexes are reflexes that are normal in infants, but abnormal in other age groups. Such reflexes include: Moro reflex Sucking reflex (sucks when area around mouth stimulated) Startle reflex (pulling arms and legs inward after loud noise) Step reflex (stepping motions when sole of foot touches hard surfac... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7180-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7180_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:31:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/24135/104796</link><title>I have excessive blinking and difficulty looking at people in the eyes</title><description>... I have been taking xanax .25mg for sleep for many years.  I recently have noticed this excessive blinking and facial distortment when I eat.  I started taking .25mg of xanax during the day and it helps slightly.  What is going on? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7180-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7180_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:31:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/770075/108859</link><title>I experienced momentary blackouts as though the lights blink. Could it be stress related?</title><description>... I have experienced momentary "blackouts" as though the lights suddenly blinked.  People that I have been with haven't noticed the blinking.  I've also had a dull headache.  I do have an allergy related sinus problem going on right now as well which may account for the headache.  Is it possible that the "blinking" sensation could be stress related as I have been under quite a lot of stress lately? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7180-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7180_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:32:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/54641/28329</link><title>what causes the sensation of constant hard blinking?</title><description>... I feel a constant hard blinking sensation that lasts for hours.  It affects my head. ears and keeps me from being able to concentrate on anything.  I have herniated discs in my neck, is this a sympton of that or is it something else entirely?  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7180-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7180_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:32:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/question/57184/26249</link><title>my 3 month old grandaughter stares without blinking for a long time just before falling asleep</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7180-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7180_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:32:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/764071/61885</link><title>EYE PAIN STINGING WHEN I BLINK</title><description>... EYE PAIN      ... what is wrong? my eye is stinging, it hurts when i close my eyelid, it feels like something is in it. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7180-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7180_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:33:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/764071/61884</link><title>EYE PAIN STINGING WHEN I BLINK</title><description>... EYE PAIN      ... what is wrong? my eye is stinging, it hurts when i close my eyelid, it feels like something is in it. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7180-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7180_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:33:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/question/751561/156797</link><title>what acid reflex? syptoms acid reflex?</title><description>... zarghani ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7180-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7180_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:33:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/question/877565/109625</link><title>ACID REFLEX: Are dried prunes a food that may cause acid reflex?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7180-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7180_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:34:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/encyclopedia/408/713.html</link><title>Reflex Sympathetic Dystrophy</title><description>... Reflex sympathetic dystrophy (RSD) is a term commonly used to describe severe pain and burning in an upper or lower limb following injury. S.W. Mitchell in 1864 described this symptom complex in great detail and provided the designation of causalgia (from the Greek "kausis" - burning, and "algos" - pain.) In 1947, it was argued that the causalgia and related syndromes were merely manifestations of one disease entity and the all-encompassing name of reflex sympathetic dystrophy was adopted. It is also known as algodystrophy, causalgia syndrome, post-traumatic dystrophy, reflex neurovascular dystrophy, and Steinbrocker syndrome. The cause is unclear but a number of factors may contribute, particularly changes in autonomic nervous system function. RSD may be associated with crush injuries, fractures, infections, burns , radiation therapy , and myocardial infarction. RSD appears to be more common among women than men, and among individuals over 50 years of age. It has also b... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>