<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7185">constitution of italy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:51:55" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7185-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7185_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:51:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/trip-italy-planned-months-2139</link><title>I have a trip to Italy planned in two months.</title><description>... I have a trip to Italy planned in two months. I also need a knee replacement before I go. The surgeon offered me the new minimally invasive "faster" surgery. Should I do it? It all depends on how important a quick recovery is to you...and how much it's worth in terms of risk. There's a chance that the implant won't last as long as the standard joint replacement. This risk of early failure is usually accompanied by persistent pain. On the other hand, most patients who have the mini-approach are back to their normal activities after only one to four weeks' time. This would certainly fit in with your travel plans. Studies done so far show no reason to think you shouldn't go ahead with this plan. So long as you know the potential problems, you'll know the worst that could happen. Bon voyage! Reference: Richard S. Laskin, MD. Minimally Invasive Total Knee Arthroplasty. In Clinical Orthopaedics and Related Research . November 2005. No. 440. Pp. 54-59.' ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7185-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7185_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:52:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/incontinence/c/question/499677/63722</link><title>Italy</title><description>...   ... I am going to Milano, Italy soon for a couple of days for a conferance. Does anyone know howe to find diapers there? Easy to find? Where to buy? Do I have to bring an extra case?  ...   ... Anxious ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7185-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7185_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:52:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/62131/32588</link><title>travel to Italy..what can diabetic eat?</title><description>... Diagnosed with Type 1 last year; grown woman who travels alot; need to find appropriate foods in foreign countries; this time...Italy   Thanks ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7185-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7185_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:53:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/782774/52089</link><title>I believe there were trials in Italy using just 1mg dose Tamoxifen do you have further info</title><description>... I have been taking 10mg Tamoxifen daily for nine months and suffer unacceptable hot flushes.   I took Arimidex for three months after my radiotherapy but the side effects of swollen joints and general tiredness made me change to Tamoxifen. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7185-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7185_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:53:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/5868/29802/constitutes-good</link><title>Diabetes Management: What Constitutes Good Enough?</title><description>... recognizes a need, say for new casual shoes, and then spend hours upon ... hours shopping for just the right pair? Do you obsess over finding the best ... shoes at a great price that fit perfectly and look stylish?  Then, ... after making a choice do you worry that you could have gotten a ... better pair or a cheaper price and thus don't ever truly enjoy the shoes.  ... Or, do you run into the store and find the first pair that fit your criteria ... and happily leave with your purchase?  ...   ... I've been reading a book, The ... Paradox of Choice that outlines the difference between maximizers and ... satisficers.  Maximizers are illustrated by the first ... scenario.  These individuals have a difficult time in modern society ... because they insist on only choosing the "best" option from the many ... hundreds they face each day.  Satisficers, on the other hand, recognize ... that "good enough" is good enough and quickly make choices regarding ... basic iss... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7185-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7185_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:54:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/9924/17586/121007-9-72-hours</link><title>12/10/07 #9 - 72 hours, what constitutes relief?</title><description>... Full Question: I've heard over and over that if a migraine lasts over 72 hours without 4 hours of relief that I should go to the ER because of the risk of migrainous stroke...but what constitutes relief? Do narcotics count? Do triptans count? If narcotics and other pain relievers count, why? Don't they just mask the pain and have no effect on the state of the blood vessels? Thanks, Tara.       Answer:   Dear Tara;   Everything in life counts. While your questions are far-reaching and thought provoking, on a practical level whatever relieves a Migraine is worth a try. Most Migraine-specific treatments such as triptans are vasoconstrictors, as well as blockers of central pain processing. Opiates enhance the pain reduction system in the brain (endorphins).   Although Migrainous stroke is fairly rare, it is far better to treat aggressively each Migraine episode.   What constitutes relief for the purposes of determining whether it's time to seek emerge... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7185-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7185_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:54:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/34978/cheating</link><title>Low Carb Diets: What Constitutes Cheating?</title><description>... I did have some food that was rather high in carbohydrates, including a ... samosa. And I enjoyed a couple of other yummy high-carb items. "Aren't you cheating on your low-carb diet?" asked my friend. I bridled at his remark. Cheating is dishonest. It's a word best reserved to its usual sense of copying the work of others. My diet is low-carb. It's not no carb, as I made a point to tell my friend. I'm sure that low-carbing the best way to control my diabetes and my weight. Each ... day I generally consume 40 to 50 grams of available carbohydrate. Since ... I'm a journalist rather than an engineer, I'm not as precise as some ... people, so I don't know exactly. I do admire the precision of engineers. That's one of the things that I like about Dr. Richard K. Bernstein , who was an engineer before he went back to school in his 40s to become a med... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7185-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7185_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:55:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/570617/87633</link><title>When you need to take a medication "with food", what constitutes "food": how much?</title><description>...   ... What's the minimum amount of "food" that should be taken with ibuprofen in order to protect my stomach? ...   ... Nancy Ray ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7185-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7185_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:55:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/question/945153/90245</link><title>Schiz - Gravely Impaired - What constitutes him being a threat to himself or others?</title><description>... My son has schizophrenia and becomes gravely impaired when he is off the medicine.  What type of behavior does he have to exhibit for me to get him in an in-patient unit against his will?  Our state requires they be a threat to themselves or someone else.  My son is not violent.  The illness causes him to lose weight and stop using soap or shampoo.  It is hard to tell when he is bad enough to force him into treatment and be kept.  I certainly don't want to have him taken in and they not keep him because he isn't "bad enough." ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7185-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7185_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 04:55:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/905445/49048</link><title>Does having sex outside of the marriage constitute as having an affair?</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>