<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7189">judiciary act 1789</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:08:05" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7189-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7189_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:08:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/news-289655-5.html</link><title>Safe Migraine Medications and New Laws in Effect</title><description>... Have you purchased or considered purchasing Migraine or other medications online, from a site that does not require you to have a prescription? If so, think about it again. There are some serious financial reasons behind the use of online pharmacies for some people, but there are other, safer possibilities that will be discussed later in this article. On April 13 (2009), the provisions of the Ryan Haight Online Pharmacy Consumer Protection Act 0f 2008 went into effect. This act, which amends the Controlled Substances Act to address online pharmacies, is named after 18-year-old Ryan Haight who died after overdosing on a prescription painkiller he obtained on the Internet. We've all heard stories such as Haight's. Stories about people who got something that looked like the medication they'd ordered, but wasn't... Stories of people who got ill from the medications they'd purchased online... and more. But the laws haven't been able to keep pace with ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7189-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7189_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:08:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/7399/43442/stabilization</link><title>Mental Health Parity Act Passed as Part of Economic Stabilization Act</title><description>...   ... Earlier this week, the Senate attached it to the Emergency Economic Stabilization Act (HR 1424). If you would like to read the section of HR 1424 that encompasses the Paul Wellstone-Pete Domenici Mental Health Parity and Addiction Equity Act 2008, you can find it HERE . ...   ... Below is a NAMI E-news alert I received this afternoon. ...   ...   ... Victory on Parity! ...   ... By a vote of 263-171, the House this afternoon gave final approval to the Paul Wellstone-Pete Domenici Mental Health Parity and Addiction Equity Act of 2008 as part of the Emergency Economic Stabilization Act (HR 1424). President Bush is expected to sign the legislation late today or early tomorrow. ...   ... A Triumph for Consumers and Families ...   ... This victory in the House ends a nearly 20 year effort to require grou... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7189-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7189_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:08:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/support-283147-5.html</link><title>The Americans with Disability Act and Your Anxiety</title><description>... The Americans With Disabilities Act and Anxiety The Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA) was enacted in 1990 as a way to protect people with either physical or mental disabilities from being discriminated against either in the hiring process or while working. The ADA requires employers to provide reasonable accommodations to a disabled employee, who has asked for the accommodation. Physical disabilities can be easier to determine than disabilities caused by mental illness. Limitations caused by diabetes, heart disease or a specific physical need such as needing a wheelchair are easy to determine and easy to document, certainly easier than disability caused by a mental disorder. What is a Mental Disability? The Diagnostic and Statistical Manual, 4th Edition, published by the American Psychiatric Association, is often used as recognized and authoritative information on mental illness. According to the DSM-IV, an individual with a mental disorder must exhibit at least one (if not more) of... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7189-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7189_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:09:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/159365/migraines-kindness</link><title>Migraines and Acts of Kindness - Migratude Monday</title><description>...   ... There's a lot of discussion these days about acts of kindness. Everyone is so busy that some of the little niceties of life seem to have slipped a bit. In that vein, I've been thinking of acts of kindness that could be especially helpful when we do them for people with Migraines. ...   ... You can find some of my suggested acts of kindness in our new slideshow, Acts of Kindness to Perform for People with Migraines . ...   ... Please take a few minutes to view the slideshow and share it with your friends. There are many, many more little kindnesses we can show toward people with Migraines and other problematic headache disorders. ...   ... What would YOU suggest? After you've looked at the slideshow, please come back here and post a comment with your suggestions. Pretty pl... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7189-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7189_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:09:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/19/20384/heart-day</link><title>Support Women's Heart Health: HEART for Women ACT</title><description>... To love or not to love, that is not the question. The question this week is to give or not to give in the name of love. Valentine's Day is already upon us. Actuallly it's been on us since right before the new year. Retailers can't wait to get people in the mood for love. Each year when this "Hallmark Holiday" (as I constantly hear it referred to) approaches, people debate whether or not to buy into cupid's day. I don't fault anyone either way, because I can see both sides. Some years, I've given cards to my husband, parents, niece, etc. and some years I haven't. I've always remembered my little boy though and will probably do the same for my little girl. But I don't overdo it. I usually just get them a box of candy and a card for the old scrapbook.   My son is 14 now and thinks the holiday should be like Christmas or his birthday. His requests get bigger and bigger each year, asking for video games and movies. I admit I did get him a mo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7189-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7189_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:10:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/10840/isnt-short-type-2s</link><title>"Short Acting" Medication May Last Longer in Obese Type II Patients</title><description>... If you forgot to test, you’re in good company. It seems that the scientific researchers whom you rely on for your professional guidance on diabetes made the same mistake. When they tested the short-acting insulins, they forgot that the great majority of us with type 2 diabetes carry around too much weight. This awful report just came out in a late-breaking abstract presented at the American Diabetes Association’s scientific sessions in Chicago . Dr. Jean L. Ardilouze, a professor of medicine at University of Sherbrooke in Quebec, Canada, and three colleagues presented “In Obese Subjects with Type 2 Diabetes, Are Short Acting Insulin Analogues That Short?” Their conclusion was this: In healthy normal weight subjects, our results reproduced data accepted and used in daily practice for insulin prescriptions. However, in a population of obese subjects with type 2 diabetes, we show for the first time that plasma levels of short-acting insulins are blunted, at low dosage, and severely delay... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7189-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7189_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:10:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/3025/17946/pain-act-law</link><title>Congress Considering Veterans Pain Act to Promote Research for Chronic Pain</title><description>... On November 14th the Senate Veteran's Affairs Committee passed the Veterans Pain Act of 2007. This is a critical step on the way to this bill becoming law. We all owe hearty thanks to Chairman Senator Daniel Akaka from Hawaii. He, along with Senator Brown from Ohio, recognized that pain is one of the most prevalent and persistent conditions that affect men and women who have served in the military. The Iraq war is resulting in thousands of injuries which are almost universally accompanied by pain, and which can lead to a lifetime of coping with pain.   The Veterans Pain Act, S.2160, will promote improved knowledge and skills in treating pain in veterans and will promote research to solve some of the mysteries that persist in our understanding of how to effectively treat painful conditions common to the military life. Please encourage your Senators to support S. 2160, the Veterans Pain Care Act of 2007. You can easily do so by going to the TAKE ACTION NOW section of t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7189-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7189_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:10:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/5949/154459/fda-announces</link><title>FDA Announces New Strategy for Long-Acting Opioids</title><description>...   ... According to the FDA, “The REMS is part of a federal initiative to address the prescription drug abuse, misuse, and overdose epidemic. The REMS introduces new safety measures designed to reduce risks and improve the safe use of ER/LA opioids, while ensuring access to needed medications for patients in pain.” ...   ... “Misprescribing, misuse, and abuse of extended-release and long-acting opioids are a critical and growing public health challenge,” said FDA Commissioner Margaret A. Hamburg, M.D. “The FDA’s goal with this REMS approval is to ensure that health ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7189-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7189_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:11:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/32873/156704/week</link><title>Americans with Disabilities Act and MS: Question of the Week</title><description>... The Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA) was signed into law more than 20 years ago. George H.W. Bush signed the bill in July of 1990. Do you think the ADA is a good law for those of us with disabilities? If yes, why? If no, why not? The ADA was written when disabilities rights groups shared drafts and edits for more than 20 years. After living with the law for awhile, it was clear amendments were needed, so it has been a living law with clarifications added. The ADA began as a way to add “disabilities” to the civil rights law that prohibits discrimination. It was supposed to increase employment opportunities and allow people with disabilities access to the same community that has been available to evearyone else, such as restaurants and shops. Then there is access, or lack of it. That means a wheelchair or a person with an awkward gait, balance problems, or fatigue must be able to cross a street, enter a room or use a bathroom. This is a lot to fit in a single act, which ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7189-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7189_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:11:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/11175/68921/disabilities-act</link><title>Working with Migraines: Rights under the Americans with Disabilities Act</title><description>...   ... *** This sharepost is legal education, not legal advice. No attorney-client relationship is created. *** ...   ... ... ... The ADA was passed in 1990 to prevent discrimination against disabled persons in employment, transportation, and public accommodation.  I will only be discussing the employment aspe... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>