<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7197">contraceptive diaphragm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:34:24" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7197-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7197_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:34:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/encyclopedia/408/771.html</link><title>Contraception</title><description>... Article updated and reviewed by Christina S. Chu, MD, Assistant Professor, Department of Obstetrics and Gynecology, Division of Gynecologic Oncology, University of Pennsylvania on May 10, 2005. Contraception is the use of artificial or natural means to prevent conception, or pregnancy . There are various contraceptive methods available today. The most common artificial methods are male/ female condoms , spermicides, sponge, diaphragm, cervical cap, oral contraceptives ( birth control pills), injectable contraceptives (Depo-Provera, Lunelle), vaginal rings, intrauterine devices (IUDs) and surgical sterilization. The natural methods include complete abstinence (no sexual intercourse), periodic abstinence and withdrawal. Emergency contraception is a method to prevent pregnancy after unprotected intercourse has occurred. Male/Female Condom The male condom (also known as a prophylactic or rubber) is a thin sheath, usually made of latex rubber, which covers the erect penis . When used correctly, a lat... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7197-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7197_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:34:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/007014.html</link><title>Emergency contraception overview</title><description>... Definition Emergency contraception is a method to prevent pregnancy in women who have had unprotected sex, or for whom a barrier method has failed (slipped condom, diaphragm, or cervical cap, or broken condom). Alternative Names Morning-after pill; Postcoital contraception; Birth control - emergency; Plan B Information Emergency contraception may be used following many different situations, including: After intercourse in which no birth control method is used Sexual assault or rape When a condom breaks or a diaphragm slips out of place When a woman forgets to take birth control pills Emergency contraception medicine is not the same as the "abortion pill." A woman who knows she is pregnant takes the abortion pill with the intent to end an early pregnancy (usually 4 to 7 weeks after conception). Emergency contraception pills are taken after unprotected sex to prevent pregnancy from occurring. TYPE OF EMERGENCY CONTRACEPTION Several types of emergency contraception drugs are available. Two emergency ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7197-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7197_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:35:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/guides/000091_6.html</link><title>Birth Control Options for Women - Spermicidal and Barrier Contraception</title><description>... Spermicidal and Barrier Contraceptives Barrier contraceptives are devices that provide a physical barrier between the sperm and the egg. Examples of barrier contraceptives include the male condom, female condom, diaphragm, cervical cap, and sponge. The condom is the only contraceptive method that helps prevent sexually transmitted diseases (STDs). Spermicides Vaginal spermicides are sperm-killing substances available as foams, creams, gels, films, or suppositories, and are often used in female contraception with barrier and other devices. Spermicides are usually available without a prescription or medical examination. The active ingredient in U.S.-made spermicides is usually nonoxynol-9, which attacks the surface of the sperm cell. Nonoxynol-9 does not provide any protection against sexually-transmitted diseases or HIV (the virus that causes AIDS). Research indicates that frequent use can cause vaginal and rectal irritation and abrasions that may actually increase the risk for HIV transmi... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7197-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7197_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:35:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/guides/000091_8.html</link><title>Birth Control Options for Women - Emergency Contraception</title><description>... Emergency Contraception Emergency contraception is available to prevent pregnancy in situations such as: After sexual assault After consensual intercourse in which contraception is not used When contraception is used but fails (for instance, when a condom breaks or a diaphragm dislodges) Emergency contraception is administered as a pill or, less commonly, as an IUD. Emergency contraception should not be used as a substitute for regular routine contraception. Emergency Contraceptive Pills The emergency contraceptive pill (ECP) is also called the morning-after pill. The emergency contraceptive pill is not the same thing as the "abortion pill." These pills should not be taken by a woman who is pregnant. There are two types of morning-after pills: One type uses the progestin levonorgestrel to prevent either fertilization or the implantation of a fertilized egg in the uterine lining. The other type uses the antiprogestin drug ulipristal, which appears to inhibit or delay ovulation. Levonorgestrel Mor... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7197-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7197_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:35:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/r/medications/norethindrone-contraceptive-oral-16321/uses</link><title>Norethindrone (Contraceptive) Oral Uses and How to Use</title><description>... Generic Name: NORETHINDRONE (CONTRACEPTIVE) - ORAL Pronounced: (nor-ETH-in-drone) Norethindrone (Contraceptive) Oral Uses ... This medication is used to prevent pregnancy. It is often ... referred to as the "mini-pill" because it does not contain any estrogen. ... Norethindrone (a form of progestin) is a hormone that prevents pregnancy by ... changing the womb and cervical mucus to make it more difficult for an egg to ... meet sperm (fertilization) or for the fertilized egg to attach to the wall of ... the womb (implantation). Regular use of the "mini-pill" prevents the release of ... an egg (ovulation) in about half of the women who use it. ... While the "mini-pill" is more effective than certain other ... methods of birth control (e.g., condoms, cervical cap, diaphragm), it is less ... effective than estrogen/progestin birth control because it does not ... consistently prevent ovulation. It is usually used by women who cannot take ... estrogen. For the most effective benefit, it is v... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7197-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7197_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:36:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/imagepages/17049.html</link><title>The diaphragm</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7197-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7197_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:36:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/19072-146.html</link><title>Diaphragm</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7197-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7197_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:36:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/19380-146.html</link><title>Diaphragm and lungs</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7197-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7197_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:37:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/incontinence/c/15224/107178/diaphragm</link><title>Pelvic Floor and Diaphragm: Floor and Ceiling of our Abdomen/Pelvis</title><description>... I want to look closely at the relationship between our diaphragm and our pelvic floor.  The diaphragm is the ceiling of our pelvis and abdomen, while our pelvic floor is just that...the floor of our pelvis and abdomen. Both of these structures are muscular tissue, both can descend down to a bowl shape, and both can draw up to a flattened, tighter position. Our diaphragm descends down to draw in every breath, taking up room in our abdominal and pelvic cavity. When our diaphragm takes up more space, we accommodate by expanding our lower rib cage and chest, and our pelvic floor descends ever so slightly with every breath. These are all components of the natural rhythm of our breathing pattern and pressure displacement. ... If our lower rib expansion and chest expansion are not functioning when we take in air, then the increased pressure in the abdominal/pelvic cavity has to find somewhere to go, and often puts increased pressure on our pelvic floor. Let me give some examples.  If w... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7197-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7197_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:37:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/question/761704/61233</link><title>spasms in the diaphragm.</title><description>... Can any one tell me if they have ever had a spasms in their diaphragm due to ms. I feel like some times I grunt out my words.  ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>