<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7200">uss stennis</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:47:27" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7200-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7200_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:47:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/84280/september-21-marks</link><title>September 21 Marks World Alzheimer's Day</title><description>... Often I’ve focused my shareposts on what’s happening concerning Alzheimer's disease around the United States. However, Alzheimer’s isn’t limited to the U.S.’s 50 states. In fact, September 21 has been proclaimed World Alzheimer's Day™ 2009 and will be commemorated across the globe. This year’s theme is “Diagnosing Dementia: See It Sooner” and the day’s purpose is to raise awareness around the world about this terrible disease. So what is Alzheimer's grasp around the globe? The website of Alzheimer’s Disease International (ADI) reports:          “There are an estimated 30 million people with dementia worldwide. By 2050, it is projected that this figure will have increased to over 100 million. Much of the increase will be in developing countries. Already more than 60% of people with dementia live in developing countries, but by 2040 this will rise to 71%. The fastest growth in t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7200-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7200_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:47:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/21076/study-group</link><title>Bipartisan Alzheimer's Study Group Announced</title><description>... In the United States, we're in the middle of our presidential election cycle. There are big plans on many issues, such as health care, being touted by candidates. However, away from the election fray, there also are smaller, quieter steps being taken by leaders at the national policy level concerning the fight against Alzheimer's disease.   Worried about the potential impact of Alzheimer's disease, U.S. congressional leaders named an independent, non-partisan Alzheimer's Study Group (ASG) in July 2007 . Former Speaker Newt Gingrich, founder of The Center for Health Transformation, and former Senator Bob Kerrey, president of The New School, are co-chairing this group, which is tasked with assessing the adequacy of the United States' current efforts to combat Alzheimer's. The taskforce is charged with recommending a National Alzheimer's Strategic Plan that will address identified opportunities and accelerate progress toward eliminating Alzheimer's... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7200-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7200_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:48:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/204/72882/art-versus-dying</link><title>Art Versus I Think I Am Dying?</title><description>... Tranquility's Quiet Strength" USS LCS Freedom Docked in Old Town, Alexandria, Virginia. Photograph by  ©  Michael John Coleman 2009 ... WASHINGTON, D.C.; FRIDAY MAY 29th, 2009--Spec ial By Michael John Coleman, MAGNUM Executive Director and Founder. If you ever wondered what a heart attack looks like through the eyes of an artist while it is happening, look no more!  So you missed that opening at Principle Gallery or maybe one in Soho , DC--New York--no matter, put your feet up and take a walk through MAGNUM's 'Little Galleries' (Someone out there got that reference I hope?!) and peruse some artwork created in the mist of an unwelcome cardiovascular event!  If you want to read more about the Migraine's three-fold increase risk of heart attack reported in a recent medical study-then check out MigraineBlog's Memorial Day Monday's article on MyMigraineConnection !  If you already read that article then walk into the next online room of our gallery, and learn a... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7200-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7200_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:48:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/9924/21009/3308-6-daily-pain</link><title>3/3/08 #6 - Help for sister in-law's daily pain?</title><description>... Full Question: Good morning sir, my name is Sgt.____; I am currently deployed aboard the USS ___. My wife is in Michigan taking care of her sister who, for the last 10 years has been suffering from chronic cluster headaches. I am not well informed on this topic but I do know a sad case when I see one. She has been treated in Michigan and in Ohio by multiple headache specialists and has been on very powerful narcotics to treat the pain. I’m not sure what has been done but I know she has had several surgeries and some kind of implant in her brain that is supposed to help. Nothing and I mean nothing has helped and she obviously feels like she doesn’t want to go on. The doctors seem to pass her around when they feel they have done everything. They have a passive aggressive attitude towards her and honestly don’t believe her about the pain she is in. I know she has been turned away as a "narcotic seeker" and she has to withdraw from these meds when they run out... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7200-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7200_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:48:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/204/72177/founder-migraineur</link><title>MAGNUM Nearly Loses Its Founder, A Life Long Migraineur, to a Major Heart Attack</title><description>...   ... "Attack On Freedom"   If you ever wondered what a heart attack looks like through the eyes of an artist, look no more!  In an effort to keep my cool while I was fighting to breath and stay calm--no small feat-so I deployed the only trick I knew - focus on my art and tried to get the perfect image of the new Littoral Combat Ship USS Freedom on her first Deployment, with the National's Capitol Dome in the far background or the right on the waterline horizon!      ...   ... While International News Agencies MSNBC &amp; Others Point Out Studies Support  Migraineurs have Twice the Chance of Heart Attacks &amp; Strokes! ...   ... WASHINGTON, D.C.; FRIDAY MAY 9th, 2009-Updated MAY 23 - Special By Michael John Coleman , MAGNUM Executive Director ...   ... When I was a young man I was employed as an Art Director working for Naval Sea Systems Command (NAVSEA) down the road from MAGNUM's current offices in a beautiful place called C... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7200-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7200_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:49:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/144743/brain-impairment</link><title>The Healthy Brain Initiative Focused on Research, Awareness of Cognitive Impairment</title><description>... THBI was established by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) as part of its Healthy Aging Program. This initiative, which was supported through appropriations by Congress in 2005, is the Alzheimer’s-specific portion of the Healthy Aging Program. As part of THBI, the CDC worked with a group of partners including the Alzheimer’s Association, National Institute on Aging, Administration on Aging, AARP, and private and public organizations to examine how cognitive health is promoted and protected and to identify knowledge gaps, and to identify ways that public health can contribute to this effort. ... First, let’s define what we’re talking about when we're talking about cognitive health. “Although standardized, widely accepted definitions of co... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7200-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7200_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:49:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/99817/system-association</link><title>Additional Facts and Figures on Caregiving, Medical System from the Alzheimer's Association</title><description>... In my last post, I shared some figures from the 2009 Alzheimer’s Disease Facts and Figures published by the Alzheimer’s Association. This week, I wanted to add some more pertinent information that can help inform those who have the disease as well as caregivers, policymakers and other interested parties. The information below is scary, not only for its impact on the individual and a family, but also the potential drag to the economy of the United States. ... Caregiving ... -           Women make up approximately 60 percent of family and other unpaid caregivers to those with dementia. ... -           A study found that 87 percent of caregivers of people with dementia were taking care of a relative, especially a parent or parent-in-law (57 percent), a grandparent (11 percent), or a spouse (6 percent). The other 13 percent were caring for a non-relative, such as a friend or relative. ... -   &amp;... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7200-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7200_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 05:50:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/77598/130630/depress-spouse</link><title>depressed spouse...</title><description>... ... My husband N i have been together for more than 14yrs,legaly married for more than 11yrs.We meet at our job I was 19 he was 21..it took him a a while for me to actually say yes to go on a date with him,he once told me that i became like a challenge for him because we got on a wrong start I compared him with another worker and he got really upset n I told him to go F*** himself...something no other girl had done I guess...well finally I agreed to go out and it just took of from that point shortly after 4 months of just dating I got pregos.. and well we decided to stick to it and moved in together our son was born in dec..shortly aftr he was born i turned 21 and well a couple yrs went by n decided to get legaly married from t... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>