<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7205">turkey leftover recipes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:07:33" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7205-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7205_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:07:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/646074/50094/leftover</link><title>Thanksgiving Leftover Extravaganza!</title><description>...   ... Sandwiches and Wraps ... Roast Turkey, Sun-Dried Tomato and Basil Wraps ...   ... Turkey Panini ...   ... Turkey Wraps with Cranberries ...   ... Turkey and Roasted Red Pepper Wraps with Tarragon Cream Cheese ...   ... Turkey and Roasted Red Pepper Sandwiches on Focaccia ...   ... Cranberry-Turkey Salad Sandwiches on Focaccia ...   ... Roast Turkey Sandwiches with Cranberry Sauce and Cream Cheese ...   ... Basic Turkey Tacos ...   ... Turkey and Corn Tortillas with Chipotle Salsa ...   ... Salads ... Baby Greens with Grilled Turkey, Cranberries and Roasted Shallot Vinaigrette ...   ... Fresh Greens with Grilled Turkey, Apples, Walnuts and Cranberry Vinaigrette ...   ... Charlie Trotter's Smoked Turkey a... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7205-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7205_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:07:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/968433/165494/depression</link><title>Holiday Leftovers: Dealing with Depression During the Holidays</title><description>...   ... ... When you are in the throes of an Auto Immune disease as we are, you know that one of the worst aspects of it to fight is that ever present feeling of fa... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7205-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7205_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:08:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/63553/42983/allergen-turkey</link><title>Allergen-Free Turkey Chili Recipe</title><description>... As mentioned in my previous blog, I really want to share some of my family's favorite allergen-free comfort foods for cold weather. I've always loved chili, and for years I only made it with ground beef. However, with turkey being so widely available (and it's a healthier option because it's a leaner meat), I've started using ground turkey for my chili instead. Of course, if you're a die-hard believer that chili should only be made with beef, by all means, feel free to substitute it for the turkey. ... This recipe is soy, milk, peanut, tree nut, fish and shellfish, and egg free. ...   ... Turkey Chili ... 3 tablespoons canola oil 1/2 cup white onion, diced 1 lb ground turkey 2 teaspoons kosher salt ½ teaspoon black pepper 2 tablespoons chili powder 1 1/2 teaspoons garlic powder 2 teaspoons cumin 2 teaspoons coriander 2 Tablspoons all-purpose flour* (Reference Wheat Free note if allergic) 1 small can tomato sauce 2 Tablespoons tomato paste 32 oz pinto beans, rinsed and ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7205-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7205_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:08:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/163775/escarole-meatballs-recipe</link><title>Navy Bean and Escarole Soup with Turkey Meatballs Recipe</title><description>...   ...   ...   ... I had been away from home for two-and-a-half weeks to undergo my second phase body contouring plastic surgery . I had been eating very little home-cooked meals during that time, aside from the delicious soup a dear friend made for me. I’ve been craving more homemade soup ever since. It is the ultimate comfort food, good for whatever ails you. ...   ... I am home now and already have made a simple delicious soup of my own creation. Little did I know that recipes abound on the web for escarole soup with beans and turkey meatballs. Well, I’ll throw my version into the mix because it is oh so yummy. Let me know what you think! ...   ... This is a full-of-flavor hearty soup that satisfies our need for warmth and coziness in Fall and Winter. My husband and I ate our soup cuddled up beside the fireplace last night and watched a video. I forgot about the coldness outside as the warmth enveloped me and nourished me in ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7205-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7205_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:08:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/5068/96333/cranberry-relish</link><title>A Diabetes Recipe: Cranberry Relish</title><description>... Cranberries. What would Thanksgiving be without them. It's delicious on the day itself, and it's also delicious with the leftover turkey we all eat for the next few days. ...   ... Unfortunately, the easy cranberry sauce, the stuff that comes in cans, is loaded with sugar. So what can we do? ...   ... Use our creativity, of course. If you have a family recipe for cranberry sauce, try making it with a sugar substitute. ...   ... Many people like the combination of cranberries and oranges ground together. So do I, but even whole oranges make my blood glucose go up. So when I make cranberry sauce, I use orange gelatin dessert. ...   ... It's simple: dissolve some sugarfree orange gelatin dessert in boiling water as usual, add some chopped cranberries, let it set, and that's all there is to it. ...   ... If you want to add other stuff, go ahead. Add walnuts. Try a little chopped ginger. Add some chopped onions. Or if you're really courageous, add a little horseradish. ...   ... You could even serve one ve... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7205-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7205_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:09:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/17824/133137/heartburn</link><title>Heartburn Friendly Cooking: Turkey Meatball Soup</title><description>...   ... Turkey Meatball Soup. Hopefully this soup will help to warm up your week. ...   ... Ingredients: - 1 pound ground turkey - 1/2 cup bread crumbs (I use rice bread) - 1/2 tsp. salt - 1 tsp. steak sauce (Ken's Marinade works great) - 1/4 cup rice milk - 1 celery stalk, thinly sliced - 2 medium carrots, thinly sliced - 2 cans chicken broth - 2 cups water - 2 cups cooked pasta (I use rice noodles) ...   ... Directions: In a large bowl, mix ground turkey, breadcrumbs, salt, steak sauce and rice milk. Mix well and set aside. In a large saucepan, bring broth and water to a boil, add celery and carrots, reduce ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7205-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7205_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:09:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/89/147535/painkillers</link><title>Cold Turkey: Quitting Painkillers for Osteoarthritis</title><description>... A few months ago, my orthopedic surgeon as well as my neurologist, diagnosed me with the biggest challenge so far - my back is "betraying" me! My lower back has deteriorating disks, I also have stenosis of the spinal column, bulging disks, exposed nerves, and a few other things.  Therefore causing excruciating pain. After a CT Scan, I was also told I needed to sell my house and buy one with no stairs. It was also recommended that I be sure to have wide doorways (they didn't need to explain that to me!). ... Yes, I was frightened about the future. My doctors also put me on a 24 hour a day regimen of strong narcotic paink... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7205-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7205_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:10:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/39/164208/tailgating-turkey-meatballs</link><title>Tailgating with Turkey Meatballs</title><description>... Reflux Friendly Cooking ...   ... Reflux Friendly Cooking is a weekly feature that will be full of quick and easy food ideas that are acid reflux friendly and can be easily modified to meet the needs of everyone in your family! Each week I’ll provide a simple menu that is designed for easy digestion. I’ll also give you suggestions on how to modify the same recipe for others in your family without acid reflux disease. Bon Appétit! ...   ... Tailgating with Turkey Bacon Meatballs . ... Tonight we are “tailgating” before the big game. It is important to find things to bring to events like these that are fun, but that will not make you regret your participation later. These meatballs look like the real deal, but the turkey bacon and ground turkey have a lot less fat than typical meatballs. ...   ... Cooking spray ... 1 lb. ground turkey ... 3 strips turkey bacon (cooked until crisp and cut into small pieces) ... 1 egg ... 1/2 cup breadcrumbs (rice bread works fine for a gluten f... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7205-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7205_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:10:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/17824/159404/friendly-casserole</link><title>Reflux Friendly Cooking: Turkey Noodle Casserole</title><description>...   ... Turkey Noodle Casserole ... I made two of these casseroles this evening. One was modified to be easy on the stomach and my kids said they both came out great! ...   ... Ingredients: ... 1/2 lb egg noodles (rice noodles also work great) ... 1 Tbs. extra virgin olive oil ... 3 slices of chopped bacon (turkey bacon also works well) ... 1 package of ground turkey ... 1 pound button mushrooms, sliced ... 1/2 medium onion, chopped ... 1 cup chicken stock ... 1/2 cup heavy cream (rice or almond milk also works) ... 2 Tbs. butter, softened ... 2 cups grated Gruyere cheese (shredded rice cheese also works) ... 1 cup Italian style bread cr... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7205-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7205_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:10:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/70966/163451/breakfast-casserole</link><title>Turkey Breakfast Casserole</title><description>...   ... This yummy breakfast casserole is reflux friendly, high protein and low calorie.  If you find that onion bothers your reflux you can remove it from this recipe. This can be made ahead of time and frozen in single serving sizes.  It is also great on a whole wheat english muffin. ...   ... Hope you enjoy! ...   ... ...   ... Turkey Breakfast Casserole ...   ... 1 package Lean Turkey Breakfast Sausage ... 2 cups of Egg Whites ... 4 large eggs ... 1 1/2 cup chopped fresh spinach (or use another non-starchy veggie if you hate spinach) ... 1/2- 3/4c chopped green onion ... 2/3 c. fiesta blend cheese ... Seasoning to taste (We like Cavanders Greek Seasoning with no salt) ...   ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>