<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7207">earthquake</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:16:00" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7207-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7207_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:16:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/454662/143519</link><title>First earthquake ever, nerves shot for over a week now, things I've been a little afraid of are really amplified now, can't sleep. help.</title><description>... Ever since we had our first earthquake a week ago my nerves have been shot. I am afraid to sleep and my anxiety has reached an all-time high. What can I do? I really don't want to be on medication because I can usually manage without it. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7207-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7207_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:16:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/266176/101145/earthquake</link><title>Helping Those With Diabetes In Earthquake-Ravaged Haiti</title><description>... The reports of the devastation from Haiti's 7.0 earthquake last Tuesda y are tough to watch, and tougher still to fathom. Harder to bear are the stories of those that lay suffering and dying, while supplies and aid sit on Port Au Prince's sole tarmac due to the country's destroyed physical and governmental infrastructure. Three million Haitians were impacted by the quake and the number of dead are expected to reach into the hundreds of thousands . It's hard to imagine that any one Haitian has been left untouched.  The outpouring of donations from around the world has been impressive, with the Red Cross alone saying that it had collected about $35 million already. Yet for those of us who live with diabetes - or have a family member who does -- can't help but wonder how do the Haitians who have diabetes manage? With the infrastructure of the nation in shambles, where can the more than 313,000 Haitians with diabetes receive the supplies, medicines, and medical attention that they need... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7207-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7207_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:16:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/19065/143766/future</link><title>Fear of the Future: Coping with the "Earthquakes" of MS</title><description>... You may have heard that central Virginia (and the entire East Coast) experienced an earthquake two weeks ago.  It rated 5.8 with aftershocks as large as 4.5 on the Richter scale .  One of my West Coast friends kindly did say that “a 5.8 earthquake is nothing to sneeze at.”  ... The intensity of the vibration was such that I stood frozen in my kitchen watching things bounce against the walls.  In fact, a few pictures did fall of the walls and several items fell off bookcase shelves.  Luckily not much broke, but I’m still noticing items which toppled over during the disruption. ... Most members of the household handled the earthquake well.  I was shaken-up for a little while and was quickly joined by my female cat, Musette, who wanted lots of pets and gave many meows.  My two boys were frightened and quickly hid.  I saw them scrambling downstairs into the basement to duck and cover. ... One ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7207-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7207_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:17:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/348553/134016</link><title>do earthquakes have anything to do with severe ringing in the brain and migrain?</title><description>... The more severe the wheather pattern, the more severe the ringing in my BRAIN and the worse the migraines get. Additionally I don't sleep for days. I recently was hospitalized and had not slept for 6 days prios and then did not sleep for the 5 days i was hospitalized. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7207-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7207_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:17:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/474024/123196/earthquake</link><title>Tidal wave, earthquake &amp; Featured Poet of the month all in one week</title><description>...   ... Just thought that now the internet is back on line I'd best send you a message to let you all know that all is well in the area of Indonesia where we live which is some distance away from the two devastated areas, the only problems it caused up until today was that the internet service went down and we kept having power cuts but things out here ‘Volcano wise' now seem to be settling down a bit many due to monsoon rains cooling the volcano but they have warned that its still rumbling and that things could change without warning, that's one of the problems of living in what's called (The ring of fire) ...   ... Now I must tell you about my own exciting news that's got me absolutely thrilled to bits, as many of you might know I enter a lot of poetry competitions run by Forward Press UK and have been successful with quiet a few of my poems, well I've just had an E-mail from them telling me that I've been selected as the "Forward Press" (Featured poet of th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7207-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7207_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:18:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/32873/138127/week</link><title>Q of the Week: MS Emergency Plan in Case of Catastrophe</title><description>...   ... Sometimes there is enough warning to respond. Sometimes there is little warning. What do you do now? After the bombing at the World Trade Center in 1993, they realized an evacuation plan was needed especially for people with disabilities. Many companies developed one. ...   ... Although many, probably most, plans were forgotten on 9/11, the entire 9th floor Associated Blind staff escaped. They were on a low floor (9th), but that is still amazing. People in a wheelchair, with an awkward gait, difficulty hearing or seeing, or  slow physical or mental capabilities have the right to be evacuated in case there is a reason. A plan should be in place, and I think practice would b... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7207-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7207_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:18:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/101529/disaster-haiti</link><title>Coping with Large-Scale Disasters</title><description>... Every new year I wonder what will happen in the world to bring us to our knees and cause us to mourn not as single individuals but as part of a global empathy for suffering in the world. It didn't take long for 2010 to be marked by tragedy on a grand scale. Last Tuesday on January 12, an earthquake with a 7.0 magnitude tore through Haiti with a force that has not been seen in 200 years. News reports   cite estimates of 200,000 dead with 80,000 buried in mass graves. There are also reports of about two million people homeless. We read these numbers and it seems incomprehensible. ... I am sure you have seen the news reports by now as well as the images. The injured are lying in the streets along with the dead. Children's bodies are stacked like cords of wood. Earth movers are being used to bury 10,000 people in a single day. Concrete and rubble litter the roads. There is looting, violence and chaos in the aftermath of this natural disaster. Yet it is so far away for most of ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7207-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7207_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:19:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/160135/prove-stranger-fiction-question</link><title>When Your Dreams Prove Stranger Than Fiction - The Bipolar Question of the Week</title><description>...   ... We all dream, but literary and cinematic heroes have a way of dreaming in fantastic ways. We go along with it because every once in a while we, too, have a weird and crazy dream. Case in point: Many years ago, I had a vivid dream involving an earthquake. It made such an impression that I told my then-wife about it. Early next morning, the house shook. This was the first earthquake (a very minor one) I ever experienced. ...   ... Don’t ask me to explain it. ...   ... Anyway, I’m throwing this topic wide open. Question: Your weird dreams. Go for it. ...   ... Feel free to write a book. Comments below ...  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7207-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7207_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:19:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/4182/161029/post-traumatic-stress</link><title>Self-Help for Post-Traumatic Stress</title><description>...   ... Traumatic experiences tend to come out of the blue. Their effects are shocking, outside of our normal everyday experiences and expectations, and they can often leave us feeling incapable as we struggle to find ways to cope and behave. Depending on the circumstances we may learn things about ourselves we don’t like therefore questions arise. Could we have been m... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7207-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7207_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:20:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/33722/33171/anxiety-hurricanes</link><title>Reducing Anxiety in the Aftermath of Hurricanes, Floods and Other Disasters</title><description>... disasters can turn lives upside down. The damage they leave behind often leads ... to serious anxiety and depression, as well as physical health problems. It's ... natural to feel sad, scared, anxious, nervous, or depressed following a ... traumatic event. Many survivors also experience headaches, muscle tension, ... insomnia, or nausea for days or even weeks afterward. ...   ... After a ... Traumatic Event ... If you've been exposed to a trauma and are having difficulty ... coping, try some of the following tips: ... ... Do something positive . Donate blood, prepare care packages, or ... volunteer to help others, all of which can provide a ... sense of purpose in a situation that feels out of your control. ... Follow your usual daily routine as much as possible. ... Limit your exposure to repeated news stories, which usually ... increases stress. ... Rest, ... get exercise, and eat properly. Seek out leisure and ... recreational activities that involve both mind and body. ... Spend time wit... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>