<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7212">mud pumps</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:38:45" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7212-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7212_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:38:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/215658/155889/standard</link><title>Tough Mudder: The Gold-Standard of Mud Runs</title><description>...   ... This past weekend I tackled the Tough Mudder: Mid-Atlantic in Frederick, Maryland.  Days later, I am sore in places I never knew I could be sore.  (My rib cage?  The palms of my hands?) ...   ... Last summer, I took on the Spartan Sprint, a 5k run with 18 obstacles.  It kicked my butt .  But since then I changed my training – it takes a lot more than just running to master one of these courses, I've learned – and I had a better idea of what to expect.  With that in mind, I signed up for the Tough Mudder, the 10+ mile gold-standard of mud runs. ...   ... On the bright side, I learned that supposedly 24,000 people would be embarking on the challenge with me, so I wouldn’t be suffering alone. Looking around the staging area, I was certainly not the caliber of athlete of some of the participants; on the other hand, I was definitely in better shape than quite a few as well.  ... &amp;... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7212-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7212_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:39:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/89/32655/osteoarthritis</link><title>Osteoarthritis On the Other Side of the World: Rice, Mud and an African Prison</title><description>... E. Africa) ...   ... My life continues to be a never-ending source of challenges ... and surprises. ...   ... I am working with 21 teenagers in a prison for Juveniles, ... ages about 9 to 17.  MY GUYS (yes, I ... REALLY care about them) have usually been arrested for such horrible crimes as ... stealing food or street prostitution, or, sometimes, their parents don't want ... them anymore.  They actually are just ... like the guys I dealt with when I taught behavior-disordered teens in America. But these ... kids usually have no shoes -- if they are really lucky they may have a shirt of ... some type, and of course raggedly torn pants! ...   ... The 19 boys are locked in one filthy cell and are allowed ... out ONLY when I get to work.  They sleep ... 3 kids to a bed.  My 2 girls have a ... luxurious private room with a single bed, and piles of rusted metal and other ... construction trash.  Toilet facilities ... consist of a small hole in the corner of each cell, and the kids, when they are ... lu... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7212-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7212_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:39:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/32481/41818/hurl</link><title>GET READY ALL YOU BIPOLARS TIME TO HURL MORE MUD AT THE HO!!!!!!!</title><description>...   ...   ...               OK GUYS SO WHATCHA GOT BUT THIS TIME YOU HAVE TO COME UP WITH SOMETHING MORE ORIGNAL THAN HO OR MATTRESS MAMBO COME ON GUYS!!!!   i THOUGHT ID GIVE YA THIS LIL TID BIT CONSIDERING SOME OF THE COMMENTS I GOT PRIMARILY FOCUSED ON MY SEXUAL TENDENCIES. YOU PERVERTS ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7212-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7212_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:40:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/question/167540/147610</link><title>i m 17 yrs girl i cant walk in mud because my legs from down are cracking and it is from last 5 yrs amd i m worried that it will me till my whole life i haved try all the things</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7212-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7212_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:40:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabeteens/c/71576/28631/pump-pump-pump</link><title>Pump, Pump, Pump, Pump it Up!</title><description>...   ... I guess I should start at the beginning of my pumping journey, which means we will be going back in time all the way to 2000. Insulin pumps were still very new at this time but I wanted one so badly. I got my wish and in October of that year I was distributed a beautiful blue H-tron. I loved it, for a while. It kept my blood sugars in wonderful control and I didn’t have to take shots anymore, but as the years wore on I got tired of it. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7212-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7212_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:41:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/651280/31465/pump-injections</link><title>Insulin Pump Therapy: To Pump or Not to Pump Part 2 - Pump vs. Multiple Injections</title><description>... hope after last week's blog that you are now in the position to make an ... educated decision about which form of basal/bolus therapy is or is not for you. ... Only you, your family, and diabetes team can make that decision. In all ... honesty, I believe that, in the end, it must be up to YOU to decide what will ... work best with your lifestyle, support network, and personality. Let's discuss ... the benefits and disadvantages of the pump and multiple injections. ...   ... PUMP ... POSITIVES: ... 1. No more shots (unless the ... pump malfunctions, which they do sometimes; or if you have ketones) ... 2. Less hypoglycemia ... 3. Gives insulin before and ... during meal as needed ... 4. More flexibility of ... different basal (background) insulin rates depending on the time of day (you ... may need more insulin between 3 and 7 am, for example) ... 5. Calculations of insulin can ... be programmed in your pump--you just tell it how many carbs you are eating and ... your current blood sugar ... 6. Ability to extend insulin ... over a period of time especially when ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7212-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7212_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:41:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/651280/31464/insulin-therapy</link><title>Insulin Pump Therapy: To Pump or Not to Pump Part I</title><description>... have done my research! After reading Health Central's DiabeTeens.com , along with ... questions and concerns from my own teen patients with diabetes , it appears that ... insulin pump therapy is a hot topic! As of June 14, the featured poll (how do you feel about the pump) results are: love it--51percent; ... hate it--9 percent; never tried it--40 percent. If 40 percent of our readers ... have no experience with the pump, then there are a lot of kids out there that ... need this information. ...   ... The ... key to making any important decision, especially regarding your insulin ... management, is to learn as much as possible before making a choice. Knowledge ... is power! So, let's talk about your choices. Keep in mind (and this is very important) that there is no one RIGHT way to do things-including diabetes ... management . My own practice is to offer choices, provide medically correct ... information, discuss positives and negatives of each form of therapy, and support ... the decision of my teens. (Along with offering my very... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7212-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7212_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:42:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/5868/29423/pump</link><title>Pumping Insulin and Pumping Breast Milk: Diabetes and Motherhood</title><description>... Descartes famously declared "I think, therefore I am."  Materialistic individuals have claimed, "I ... shop, therefore I am." But me, I pump, therefore I am.  ...   ... Lately, I have been feeling like my very existence is summed ... up by pumping.  Either I'm pumping ... insulin to sustain my life, or I'm pumping breast milk to nourish Sienna.  I have one or two pumps operating on my body ... at any given moment.  The fact that most ... people don't deal with pumping anything in their daily lives, while I have two ... pumps to manage, does make me feel like a robot at times. ...   ... After several confusing conversations with my husband, mom, ... and other acquaintances, I've learned to specify either my insulin pump or my breast pump whenever I discuss one or the other:  ... "No, I don't need to refill my breast pump; I meant I'm low on insulin ... in my regular pump."  Dennis only had to ... think about it for a second to realize th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7212-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7212_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:42:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/110/27342/worth-pile-beans</link><title>Insulin Pumps vs. Patient-Controlled Analgesic Pumps: A Need for Deeper Studies</title><description>... The American Academy of Pediatrics' journal, Pediatrics, recently published a review of adverse events reported in teens (ages 12-21 years) using insulin pumps ( Adolescent Use of Insulin and Patient-Controlled Analgesia Pump Technology: A 10-Year Food and Drug Administration Retrospective Study of Adverse Events ). The media picked it up, and announced Insulin pumps linked to injuries, deaths in teens . ... But the publication simply isn't worth a pile of beans. First, it's a summary of two entirely different subjects: insulin pumps, and a different device, patient-controlled analgesic (PCA) pumps. Sorry, but that's like reporting on apples and grapefruits, both of which can go into salads. Or auto accidents and gunshot wounds, both of which occur in teens. Insulin pumps and PCA pumps simply aren't the same device, the patients who using them aren't the same, and the number of reports isn't: 1594 for insulin pumps and 53 for PCA pumps. I'll ignore the PCA data for the rest of this discussion... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7212-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7212_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:42:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/erectile-dysfunction/c/4246/15918/ed</link><title>ED Treatment: The Vaccuum Tumescence Pump or "Penis Pump"</title><description>... One non-pharmacologic remedy for erectile dysfunction is the penile vacuum tumescence pump or "penis pump." This device is sold in pharmacies and by prescription from your doctor. The pump is a cylindrical tube that is closed at one end. A pumping device, sometimes similar to the pump of a blood pressure cuff, is attached to the cylinder. The tube is placed over the penis and held firmly to the base of the penis. Pumping the device creates suction within the tube, thus drawing blood into the penis. A constriction band (rubber-band-like ring) is then placed at the base of the penis to prevent the blood from leaving.   There are obvious limitations to this treatment option. First, the process does take time and may interrupt the natural sexual interaction between the couple. Most often this device is given to men in stable relationships whose partner has a knowledge and understanding of the man's problem. It does, however, allow the patient, if successful, ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>