<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7215">squamous cell carcinoma</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:52:06" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7215-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7215_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:52:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/encyclopedia/408/526.html</link><title>Squamous Cell Carcinoma of the Skin</title><description>... Squamous cell carcinoma is a type of skin cancer containing squamous cells. Squamous cell carcinomas can be found in many parts of the body including the lungs, skin, anus, esophagus, head and neck areas, and cervix . Squamous cell carcinoma (SCC) is the second most common form of skin cancer . It arises from the cells that make the protective keratin of the epidermis (keratinocytes). These cancers can be described based on how differentiated the cells are - well-differentiated, moderately differentiated, and poorly differentiated. The less differentiated the lesion, the least amount of normal tissue is preserved and the more aggressive the cancer . The appearance of squamous cell carcinoma is more varied than basal cell carcinoma . Squamous cell carcinoma also tends to grow more quickly and can, unlike basal cell, spread to other parts of the body, making it more dangerous than basal cell carcinoma . Those at greatest risk are: Those who have fair complexions and poor tanning capacity (burn eas... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7215-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7215_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:52:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/imagepages/2522.html</link><title>Squamous cell carcinoma - invasive</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7215-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7215_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:52:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/imagepages/18017.html</link><title>Squamous cell carcinoma</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7215-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7215_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:53:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-cancer/c/question/321041/118391</link><title>Metastatic squamous cell carcinoma</title><description>... Metastatic squamous cell carcinoma ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7215-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7215_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:53:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-cancer/c/question/92293/46495</link><title>squamous cell carcinoma</title><description>... I had squamous cell carcinoma surgery on my upper chest.  The biopsy was clean.   What does it mean? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7215-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7215_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:54:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-cancer/c/1443/166749/myths-squamous-carcinoma</link><title>Myths about Squamous Cell Carcinoma</title><description>...   ... The following are five myths surrounding squamous cell carcinoma: ...   ... It isn’t dangerous. ...   ... SCC is the most easily cured of all the skin cancers , however, when not treated is can cause disfigurement and death. It can spread quickly to other organs in the body. About 5 percent of people who develop SCC die from the disease. ...   ... SCC only occurs in the elderly. ...   ... The elderly have a higher risk of developing SCC, the same as many illnesses and diseases. It occurs most often in those over 40... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7215-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7215_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:54:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-cancer/c/1443/148172/cell-carcinoma</link><title>Ten Things You May Not Know About Squamous Cell Carcinoma</title><description>...   ... ... Bowen's disease is the earliest form of SCC. At this stage, it appears as a red, scaly patch, most often showing up on areas of the body most exposed to the sun. It can often be mistaken for a rash, eczema , fungus or psoriasis and is usually diagnosed with a biopsy. Bowen's disease is a surface form of skin cancer which has not spread to other areas of the body. ... While SCC, like other skin cancers, can be the result of years of over-exposure to the sun , those with light-colored skin, blue or green eyes or blond or red hair have a higher risk of developing SCC. ... This ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7215-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7215_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:55:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-cancer/c/question/355338/79117</link><title>Nasal squamous cell carcinoma</title><description>... What to put on a nasal squamous cell carcinoma to help with inflammation? My 11 year old pug was diagnosed with this in Jan.   It is now the size of a nickel and is very raw.  We're treating with anti cancer diet, etc. but I can't find any help as to what to use topically to help with inflammation &amp; bleeding.  We have been using chlorophyll powder made into a paste and it helps some but it is right under his nose &amp; above his mouth so he licks it off.  Thank you for any help or input. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7215-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7215_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:56:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-cancer/c/question/575773/75450</link><title>Scared! Just found out I have squamous cell carcinoma.</title><description>... A biopsy for a spot on my scalp came back as positive for squamous cell carcinoma. I have so many questions? Surgery is scheduled for 3 weeks from now. How do they know if it is mestatic and do I need to see an oncologist? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7215-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7215_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:56:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-cancer/c/question/465622/69282</link><title>How late is too late to treat squamous cell carcinoma</title><description>...   ... My best friend has had a growth on her face for about 10 mos. and just got diagnosed with squamous cell carcinoma after having a biopsy done. Her results came back literally in one day. She is going to be referred to a speacialist to have it scooped out and then she has to heal so that they can check and see if it has spread. I've read so far that if diagnosed early, then its 100% curable. What I would like to know is, is 10 mos. with this growth way too long for it to have been there, or is she still in a safe zone?  ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>