<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7216">salmonella</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:57:03" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7216-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7216_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:57:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/tomato-salmonella-outbreak-254118-5.html</link><title>The Salmonella Outbreak: How to Stay Safe</title><description>... The Food and Drug Administration has issued a warning that an uncommon form of salmonella has been linked to certain types of raw red tomatoes and foods containing raw red tomatoes. Here's how you can stay in the clear of salmonella: There have been 167 reported cases of salmonella caused by the rare form that has been found in raw red plum, and roma and round tomatoes. The bacteria CANNOT be eliminated by simply washing, so consumers are advised to avoid raw red plum, roma, and round tomatoes completely (and foods containing them) for the time being. However, you should wash ANY produce you buy at the store or your market, or grow in your own backyard. The following types of tomatoes have NOT been linked to the outbreak and are safe to eat: cherry tomatoes grape tomatoes tomatoes still on the vine tomatoes grown at home Furthermore, tomatoes in the following areas have NOT been linked to the outbreak: Alabama Arkansas California Georgia Hawaii Louisian... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7216-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7216_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:57:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/000294.html</link><title>Salmonella enterocolitis overview</title><description>... Definition Salmonella enterocolitis is an infection in the lining of the small intestine caused by Salmonella bacteria. Alternative Names Salmonellosis Causes, incidence, and risk factors Salmonella enterocolitis is one of the most common types of food poisoning. It occurs when you swallow food or water that is contaminated with the salmonella bacteria. Any food can become contaminated if food preparation conditions and equipment are unsanitary. You are more likely to get this type of infection if you have: Eaten improperly prepared or stored food (especially undercooked turkey or chicken, unrefrigerated turkey dressing, undercooked eggs) Family members with recent salmonella infection Had a recent family illness with gastroenteritis Been in an institution Eaten chicken recently A pet iguana or other lizards, turtles, or snakes (reptiles are carriers of salmonella) A weakened immune system Approximately 40,000 people develop salmonella infection in the United States each year. Most patients are yo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7216-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7216_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:58:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/000294prv.html</link><title>Salmonella enterocolitis prevention</title><description>... Alternative Names Salmonellosis Prevention Proper food handling and storage can help prevent Salmonella enterocolitis. Good hand washing is important, especially when handling eggs and poultry. If you own a reptile, wear gloves when handling the animal or its feces because animals can easily pass Salmonella to humans. References Pegues DA, Miller SI. Salmonella Species, including Salmonella Typhi. In: Mandell GL, Bennett JE, Dolin R, eds. Principles and Practice of Infectious Diseases . 7th ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Elsevier Churchill Livingstone; 2009:chap 223. Giannella RA. Infectious enteritis and proctocolitis and bacterial food poisoning. In: Feldman M, Friedman LS, Sleisenger MH, eds. Sleisenger &amp; Fordtran's Gastrointestinal and Liver Disease . 8th ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Saunders Elsevier; 2006: chap 104. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7216-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7216_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:58:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/000294sym.html</link><title>Salmonella enterocolitis symptoms</title><description>... Alternative Names Salmonellosis Symptoms The time between infection and symptom development is 8 - 48 hours. Symptoms include: Abdominal pain or cramping or tenderness Chills Diarrhea Fever Muscle pain Nausea Vomiting Signs and tests The doctor will perform a physical exam. You may have signs of a tender abdomen and tiny pink spots on the skin called rose spots. Tests that may be done include: Stool culture for salmonella Complete blood count with differential Blood culture Febrile/cold agglutinins (test for specific antibodies ) ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7216-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7216_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:59:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/000294trt.html</link><title>Salmonella enterocolitis treatment</title><description>... Alternative Names Salmonellosis Treatment The goal of treatment is to replace fluids and electrolytes lost by diarrhea. Electrolyte solutions are available without a prescription. Antidiarrheal medications are generally not given because they may prolong the infection. If you have severe symptoms, your doctor may prescribe antibiotics. People with diarrhea who are can't drink anything due to nausea may need medical attention and intravenous fluids. This is especially true for small children. Fever and aches can be treated with acetaminophen or ibuprofen. If you take diuretics, you may need to stop taking them during the acute episode, when diarrhea is present. Ask your health care provider for instructions. Changing your diet while you have diarrhea may help reduce symptoms. This may include avoiding milk products and following a BRAT diet. BRAT stands for bananas, rice, applesauce, and toast. These are binding foods that make the stools firmer. Infants should continue to breastfeed and rec... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7216-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7216_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 06:59:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/1048-146.html</link><title>Salmonella typhi organism</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7216-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7216_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:00:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/911306/105582/salmonella</link><title>Salmonella Found In Food Addatives</title><description>...   ... According to the FDA, the additive, hydrolyzed vegetable protein, is widely used in foods, but has not been directly linked to any illness. ...   ... Currently, the contamination presents a low risk to consumers, but the FDA has asked food producers to check inventories for items that use the recalled additive. ...   ... For more information, please visit www.foodsafety.gov. ...   ... For more information, please visit www.foodsafety.gov. ...   ... The Los Angeles Times , 3/5/10. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7216-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7216_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:00:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/1522/34626/salmonella</link><title>Breaking: FDA Lifts Ban on Tomatoes, Looks to Jalapeno Pepper as Salmonella Outbreak Culprit</title><description>...   ... Although the tainted Jalapeno, found in a Texas plant, was Mexican-grown, it was not necessarily contaminated in Mexico, inspectors say. ...   ... In light of recent investigations, the FDA has lifted its ban and warning on tomatoes . It was determined that fresh tomatoes now available in the domestic market were not responsible for the outbreak. ...   ... Enjoy these tomato recipes from FoodFit.com : ... ... Grilled Chicken with Tomato-Avocado Salsa ... Tomatoes with Fresh Grape Juice ... Tomato Bruschetta ... Spa-Style Chicken with Sun-Dried Tomatoes and Watercress ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7216-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7216_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:00:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/117/56058/recall-salmonella</link><title>Peanut Butter Snack Recall due to Salmonella!</title><description>... Peanut butter crackers have just the right amount of carbohydrate and protein for a quick diabetes snack.   Not to mention they are Josh’s favorite snack.   A nice pre-wrapped six pack of peanut butter crackers provides anywhere from 16 to 20 grams of carbohydrate and the protein and fat slows the absorption making it a great snack. ...   ... But now our favorite packaged food may harbor salmonella.   There is a nationwide peanut butter recall affecting peanut butter snacks.   The focus of the FDA investigation is the voluntary recall by Peanut Butter Corp of America in Blakely, Georgia .   Yesterday the FDA expanded their original January 13 th warning. See yesterday's press release here “ Because identification of products subject to recall is continuing, the FDA urges consumers to postpone eating commercially-prepared or manufactured peanut butter-containing products and institutionally-served peanut butter until further information becomes availa... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7216-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7216_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:01:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/common/images/image.html</link><title>Salmonella, germs</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>