<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7219">honda insight</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:10:31" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7219-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7219_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:10:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/genital-herpes/c/question/401188/83770</link><title>honda man in distress</title><description>... i recently noticed a small red sore on my penus,,, im 47,,and faithful  the sore on the side of shaft,,just under head,,,about the size of pencile eraser head,,,i only noticed the stinging feeling after sex,, after ejackulation,,,sorry on spelling,,anyway,, i told my wife,, we went to docter and awating blood test,,,my wife has cold sore , wich flare up time to time may 3 times a yr,,,during the docters visit i was prescibed a cream for the penus shaft,called   clotrimazole cream usp  1% wich ive been faithyfullly using some 8 days now,, aslo was prescibed a pill called  sulfameth trimethoprim  ,,,,, again  there ONLY one small sore in fact i thought it to be a mosito bite,,   its been 9 days now,,and all is well but ,, the area on the shaft is just red,, and wont go away,,, no problems urinating no open sores,,no blisters,,no and is not painful too the touch,, so i dont know whats up,,,my wife never gives oral,, but i give her oral,, this ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7219-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7219_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:10:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/32873/88703/walking</link><title>Mobility Aids and MS: The Future of Walking Aids</title><description>... Many types of walking aids do a good job of helping those of us who need it. Research has been responsible for many new advances to the long-lived foot braces, canes, crutches and walkers. Corporations and individual inventors continue to develop new and improved walking aids. The Twenty-first Century brought with it promises of an exciting high-tech future. The goal is for everyone to walk while remaining upright. Arjan Rensma of the Dutch innovation agency TNO* tells us research is underway on hip sensors that “help keep its wearer upright.” He also says there is great potential for “Intelligent...natural limb prosthetics controlled by the mind." It's beginning to sound a bit like science fiction, don't you think? One unique invention I talked about in the Walkers segment is the Segway. This scooter-like device depends on a gyroscope for balance and the rider's position for steering. Pretty clever. Dean Kamen, inventor of the Segway and head of DEKA, is developing... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7219-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7219_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:11:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/855506/72408</link><title>I am taking Topamax 100 mg's twice a day-for @ 6 years .Are other sufferers taking this drug?</title><description>... My neurologist prescribed  Topomax for my debilitating migraine headaches, which occured 2-4 times a week and forced me to call in sick as the headaches  caused me to be unable to carry out my duties as a perioperative registered nurse, at a very busy level 1 trauma center.  The neurologist warned me that this drug could make me a little bit dull, or a little bit forgetful.  I am now 68 years old and retired, and wonder how many other migraine sufferers have been on this drug.? I think it has been a godsend! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7219-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7219_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:11:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/55879/84128</link><title>Anyone on Simponi?</title><description>... I have tried Meth, was taken off that because my gums were swollen, bleeding and with the other side effects my Rheumy said I'm allergic to it. So we went to Humira. Been on that for several months and then noticed that everytime I give my injection I would break out with hives in my abdomen. So, again, I was told to get off it because I am showing signs of being allergic. I am supposed to start Simponi next week and wanted to know if anyone else is on it and their experience. I've not heard anything about it so I'm just curious. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7219-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7219_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:12:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/55879/60948</link><title>anyone on meth and presnidone?</title><description>... I just started meth on Friday. (below treatment dose b/c I am so scared lol I'm taking 3 pills once a week) My rheumatologist gave me presnidone also with it. Is this something that will continue once I'm on a regular dose of the meth? And if I'm on such a low dose of the meth, why am I so tired already? I've also noticed I've become a little crabby and less patient in the last couple days also. Anyone have experience or a story to share? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7219-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7219_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:12:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/55879/34845</link><title>Afraid to try meds anyone have advice?</title><description>... I am going on my 10th year with moderate RA. My rheumy has suggested meds many times and I have gotten injections once which did help tremendously. However, I am terrified to start Mtx or Enbrel b/c of the serious side effects. I can't help but think that living with RA prob isn't as bad as liver failure or worse! Was anyone else afraid to start meds too? Any suggestions about what meds I could try first that maybe aren't so scary? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7219-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7219_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:13:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/55879/84869/simp</link><title>anyone know anything about simponi?</title><description>... I have tried Meth, was taken off that because my gums were swollen, bleeding and with the other side effects my Rheumy said I'm allergic to it. So we went to Humira. Been on that for several months and then noticed that everytime I give my injection I would break out with hives in my abdomen. So, again, I was told to get off it because I am showing signs of being allergic. I am supposed to start Simponi next week and wanted to know if anyone else is on it and their experience. I've not heard anything about it so I'm just curious. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7219-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7219_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:13:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/55879/63930</link><title>Allergic to Meth, started Humira</title><description>... I tried Meth, had such bad reactions to it my Rheumatologist said to stop it immediately because it wasn't just side effects I was experiencing, but allergic reactions! I just did my first Humira shot. Still taking 5mg of prednisone. Is anyone doing the Humira and not the Meth with it? How is it working for you? How long before you noticed a difference? I didn't find any info about sun sensitivity and Humira and with summer coming I like to spend time at the pool and yes I admit, the tanning bed. Anyone have any experience with tanning while on Humira and any side effects? My rheumatologist seemed suprised when I asked about it but he just said that as a doctor I should know what he's going to say about tanning beds! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7219-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7219_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:14:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/63356/123151/diabetes-america</link><title>The Rising Cost of Diabetes in America</title><description>...   ... What I didn't share with you is how even with health insurance, the rising insurance premiums and co-pays are bankrupting patients like myself who are barely scraping by in this economy. ...   ... Yes, I'm one of the guilty parties who actually (gasp) uses their insurance policies so surely I'm to blame. It's kind of like how I have to pay a higher car insurance rate ever since another driver decided to run a red light and smash into another car that then crunched my car as it idled while waiting at a red light. I'm guilty because I was there. Right place. Wrong time. ...   ... So, too, in childhood. At eleven, I developed "juvenile" or Type 1 diabetes, an auto-immune disease that bankrupted my pancreas of in... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7219-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7219_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:14:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/copd/c/73139/25629/post-part</link><title>Meet Adam Frey: How I got here, part I</title><description>... Hello,   I hope to share with you all the story that plunged me first into a tree, an emergency room, and then into a fight with cancer.  This is a pretty long story and I hope to use these first two posts to bring it up to speed.  I hope you all enjoy and that maybe my fight will inspire or help you with yours, or at the least that you get maybe a little laugh, a little cry, or a little something.  Well, I guess the best way is to start from the top.   On March 26, I was on my way to school at Cornell University and was driving along eating McDonalds when I was forced off the road.  My '97 Honda CRV swerved right, then I cut it back left causing it to roll into a tree going 55 MPH.  When the dust settled, I found myself still in my front seat, sitting next to a tree in the bed of my SUV.  My whole body was numb, and I felt myself start to slip into unconsciousness.  I just told myself no.  My neck was really hurt, but upon gaining my moto... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>