<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7221">what is mittelschmerz</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:19:42" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7221-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7221_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:19:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001503.html</link><title>Mittelschmerz overview</title><description>... Definition ... ... Mittelschmerz is one-sided, lower abdominal pain that occurs in women at or around the time of an egg is released from the ovaries (ovulation). ... ... Alternative Names ... ... ... Ovulation pain; Midcycle pain ... ... ... Causes, incidence, and risk factors ... ... About 20% of women experience mittelschmerz, or pain associated with ovulation. The pain may occur just before, during, or after ovulation. ... There are several explanations for the cause of this pain. Just prior to ovulation, follicle growth may stretch the surface of the ovary, causing pain. At the time of ovulation, fluid or blood is released from the ruptured egg follicle and may cause irritation of the abdominal lining. Mittelschmerz may be felt on one side one month, then switch to the opposite side the next month, or it may be felt on the same side for several months in succession. ... The pain is not harmful and does not signify the presence of disease. In fact, women who feel this pain may be at an advantage ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7221-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7221_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:20:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001503trt.html</link><title>Mittelschmerz treatment</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Ovulation pain; Midcycle pain ... ... ... Treatment ... ... No treatment is usually necessary. Pain relievers (analgesics) may be needed in cases of prolonged or intense pain. ... ... Support Groups ... ... ... ... Expectations (prognosis) ... ... The outcome is expected to be excellent. ... ... Complications ... ... There are usually no complications. ... ... Calling your health care provider ... ... Call for an appointment with your health care provider if ovulation pain seems to change, lasts longer than usual, or occurs with vaginal bleeding. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7221-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7221_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:20:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001503prv.html</link><title>Mittelschmerz prevention</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Ovulation pain; Midcycle pain ... ... ... Prevention ... ... Hormonal forms of contraception can be taken to prevent ovulation -- and therefore ovulatory pain -- but otherwise there is no known prevention. ... ... References ... ... Rebar RW, Erickson GF. Menstrual cycle and fertility. In: Goldman L, Ausiello D, eds. Cecil Medicine . 23rd ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Saunders Elsevier; 2007:chap 256. ... Williams R, Elam G. Gynecology. In: Rakel RE, ed. Textbook of Family Medicine . 7th ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Saunders Elsevier; 2007:chap 36. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7221-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7221_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:21:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001503sym.html</link><title>Mittelschmerz symptoms</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Ovulation pain; Midcycle pain ... ... ... Symptoms ... ... Lower-abdominal pain that is: ... ... One-sided ... Recurrent or with similar pain in past ... Typically lasting minutes to a few hours, possibly as long as 24-48 hours ... Usually sharp, cramping, distinctive pain ... Severe (rare) ... May switch sides from month to month or from one episode to another ... Begins midway through the menstrual cycle ... ... ... Signs and tests ... ... A pelvic examination shows no abnormalities. Other diagnostic procedures (such as an abdominal ultrasound ) may be performed to rule out other causes of ovarian pain if ovulatory pain is prolonged. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7221-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7221_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:21:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/</link><title>Mid-Menstrual Cycle Pain (Mittelschmerz)</title><description>... Call your doctor if you have fever, pain with urination, ... abnormal bleeding or vomiting, even if your pain happens exactly at ... time of ovulation. Let your doctor know if mid-cycle pain lasts ... longer than a day. You also should contact your doctor if you ... missed your last menstrual period. ... Prognosis ... Pain during ovulation does not have any dangerous ... consequences. ... Additional Info ... ... American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists P.O. Box ... http://www.acog.org/ ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7221-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7221_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:22:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/</link><title>Mid-Menstrual Cycle Pain (Mittelschmerz)</title><description>... It usually is not necessary to prevent this mild, short-lived ... pain syndrome. Birth control pills prevent ovulation and can be ... used to prevent mid-cycle pain. ... Treatment ... Painful ovulation is generally brief, so using medication for ... pain relief usually is not necessary. Over-the-counter pain ... medicines, such as ibuprofen (Advil, Motrin and others), can be ... used as needed and are very effective at relieving mid-menstrual ... cycle pain. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7221-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7221_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:22:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/</link><title>Mid-Menstrual Cycle Pain (Mittelschmerz)</title><description>... Some women feel pain in the abdomen or pelvis during ovulation, ... when an egg is released from the ovary. This usually happens midway ... between menstrual cycles. The medical term for this is ... mittelschmerz, which comes from the German words for "middle" and ... "pain." Some women don't feel anything when an egg is being ... released from an ovary. Other women may feel intermittent or ... constant discomfort or pain during ovulation. ... Symptoms ... Ovulation usually occurs two weeks before the first day of each ... menstrual period, give or take a couple of days. During this time, ... you may feel pain in the pelvis that can range from a sense of ... discomfort or a mild twinge to severe pain that mimics ... appendicitis. It usually lasts a short period of time, from a few ... minutes to hours. It often is felt in the lower abdomen or pelvis, ... either in the middle or on one side. If the pain is severe, it may ... be accompanied by some mild nausea. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7221-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7221_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:23:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/</link><title>Mid-Menstrual Cycle Pain (Mittelschmerz)</title><description>... Pain during ovulation usually is easy to recognize because its ... timing is so characteristic. Your doctor will be able to determine ... that you are experiencing pain from ovulation based on your ... menstrual cycle, the location and description of your pain, and the ... results of an abdominal and pelvic exam. It is important to let ... your doctor know about any other symptoms you have, such as fever, ... vomiting, changes in urination or changes in your bowel movements ... or appetite. ... Additional blood tests, X-rays, a pelvic ultrasound or a ... computed tomography (CT) scan may be necessary if your pain is ... severe or if your doctor notices any unusual findings on your ... physical examination, such as a very tender abdomen or pelvis or an ... enlarged ovary. ... Expected Duration ... Ovulatory pain usually lasts from a few moments to several ... hours. The longer episodes of pain may be due to lingering ... irritation from a small amount of bleeding, which sometimes happens ... when the egg is released. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7221-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7221_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:23:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/askthegyno-256723-5.html</link><title>Pain Down There</title><description>... Women experience lots of moments that men can only experience as an observer. For starters, there's childbirth, breastfeeding, and multiple orgasms. But while the female body enjoys plenty of chromosomal perks, certain aspects of having a woman's anatomy aren't so hot. Mittelschmerz, menstrual cramps, and vulvodynia, just to name a few common aches and pains, plague the most sensitive female parts. But what exactly are they, and why won't they leave us the heck alone? Mittelschmerz It may sound like a type of German cookie, but it's actually a pain in the side. When a woman ovulates, about two weeks before menstruation, she may feel a slight pain on one side of her lower abdomen. Usually lasting a few hours, this pain, known as Mittelschmerz , is quite common. For most women, the pain is not severe enough to require treatment. It's simply a reminder that ovulation is taking place. According to Vivien Hanson, M.D., clinical investigator at the University of Wa... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7221-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7221_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:24:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/</link><title>Recurring Abdominal Pain - Recurring Abdominal Pain Symptoms - Acid Reflux Symptoms</title><description>... The timing of your pain may be specific enough to identify your diagnosis. ... Mid-Menstrual Cycle Pain ... (Mittelschmerz) ... Two weeks prior to the onset of bleeding each month, one of your ovaries releases a maturing egg. This normal event is "ovulation," and it can be painful. Pain caused by ovulation has a medical name, "Mittelschmerz." Mittelschmerz is not harmful, and it can be treated with over-the-counter pain medicines if symptoms linger for more than a few minutes. It is common for Mittelschmerz pain to last for several hours. ... Endometriosis ... Another condition that can cycle with a monthly pattern is endometriosis. For most women this condition is worst during the days immediately prior to the menses. It can cause pain that is more prolonged than is Mittelschmerz. The type of tissue that makes up the uterus lining is "endometrial tissue." Some women have small collections of endometrial tissue that are located outside of the uterus. This cond... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>