<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7222">route 666</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:24:30" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7222-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7222_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:24:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/742919/128171</link><title>yellow pill oval barr on one side 666 444 do you know what this could be thank you</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7222-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7222_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:25:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/copd/c/91092/52875/smoking-heart</link><title>Scary New Year en Route? Stop Smoking and Take Heart!</title><description>...   ... Like many nonprofits, we're in the red, especially in an economy that's currently "in the toilet." Our longtime benefactor and primary sponsor is hurting and holding a massive fund drive. They need to stay afloat. SOS, in turn, needs to survive as well. ... I share this to exemplify that smoking cigarettes and, in my case, as a longtime sober alcoholic, turning to the bottle, aren't options that come to my mind. Scary times pop up on occasion, i.e., the economy tanks, thus striking financial fear in the hearts and minds of many of us; friends and loved ones suffer grave illnesses, etc. ... Reintroducing addictive drugs and behaviors won't really quell fears, anxieties, concerns. Taking hypothetical scenarios to the extreme - speaking only for myself... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7222-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7222_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:25:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/80106/154975/alt</link><title>The Month Ahead: Alternate Routes</title><description>...   ... So much of living with RA is rolling a boulder up a hill over and over again. You try to find a medication that works, ways to live your life and you try and then try some more, and nothing works. When that happens, it is a reminder that you have to find an alternate route to your goal. This month, will focus on the theme of alternate routes to get to your goal and in the process, hopefully help you think about ways to get out of your Sisyphus dreams. ...   ... First, we need to send wi... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7222-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7222_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:25:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/343256/121349</link><title>Has anyone gone the route of the NTI-suppression system for the relief of TMJ migraines? What are your experiences with it?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7222-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7222_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:26:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/522757/80126</link><title>What are the Dr's. looking for in an ultrasound? What are the usual routes taken from there?</title><description>... What risks do nodules present? What makes a lymph node be something to keep an eye on? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7222-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7222_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:26:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/3387/10316/online-route</link><title>Buying Online Is Not the Best Route to Prescription Savings</title><description>...   ... But, if you're like me, and you don't have health insurance, then the cost of buying prescription medicines on your own can make you think twice about filling the prescription at all. ...   ... However, leaving your allergies and/or asthma untreated can be dangerous to your health. So, it's important to find a way to fill those prescriptions and keep refilling them too. Let's look at some options: ...   ... Filling Prescriptions Online ...   ... You've likely seen tons of ads online for filling prescriptions for various medicines, or even buying prescription medicines without a valid prescription. If you do this, it can be a dangerous practice. Here's why: ...   ... Some online medication vendors aren't ethical. You could end up with the wrong medicine, one of poor quality, or even a contaminated ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7222-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7222_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:26:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/c/question/535574/91206</link><title>what the price? what rout of injection? what the shape of pakage of preclass</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7222-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7222_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:27:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/prostate/c/question/924926/59020</link><title>Is radiation, with beads inserted, a normal route to take with elevated PSA levels?</title><description>... My boyfriend was recently told his PSA is elevated and as a precaution they inserted beads in him and he will be getting radiation for 6 weeks. This sounds very aggressive to me because no-one has mentioned anything about cancer. Should we get another opinion? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7222-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7222_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:27:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/953005/124834</link><title>Which route of administration results in the most severe allergic reactions</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7222-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7222_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:28:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/908758/113719</link><title>Has anyone ever tried a holistic route with their RA?</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>