<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7230">council bluffs</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:57:31" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7230-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7230_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:57:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/1407/peanut-butter-bluff</link><title>Reese's Peanut Butter Bluff</title><description>... ... For both of us Reese’s Peanut Butter Cups are our guilty pleasure. The combination of chocolate and peanuts is irresistible. ... ... Many people share our preference. The Snickers bar is the biggest selling candy bar, and Hershey’s Reese’s Peanut Butter Cup is number two, according to AskMen.com . ... ... I almost completely stopped eating any candy when I took my diabetes seriously- too much sugar. ... ... That’s why I was so excited to read in an article in diabetes magazine a few month’s ago that there is now a sugar-free version of Reese’s Peanut Butter Cups . But I looked in vain for it. ... ... Yesterday I finally found my favorite candy in my local drugstore. The first thing I noticed is that the label says it is low glycemic and has 5 grams of fiber. ... ... The second thing I noticed was that somehow one of the cups was in my mouth. It tasted great – every bit as goo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7230-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7230_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:57:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/259439/48622</link><title>online counciling??</title><description>... Hi..it's me again..I just wanted to add that I live on a remote island in the Bahamas where we have no access to regular counciling. Is there such a thing as online counciling ? Obviously we do have internet here. I also need to add that I ,myself suffer from ADD/depression and could use this myself. My teenage son with ADHD and I battle non-stop...In a fit or rage i yelled that i hate him once and I will never be able to forgive myself...I just feel soooo fustrated! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7230-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7230_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:58:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/854752/131658</link><title>im 17 and have severe depression. i dont want counciling and i dont want to take pills. how can i fix myself?</title><description>... ive been having bad swings where i get either angry to the point of fighting or just start crying. i cant think and i cant concentrate and i always feel tired and full of hate and guilt. i need help but i dont want counciling or medication. i just want to be happy again. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7230-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7230_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:59:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/7922/nutrition-magazines</link><title>Diabetes and Nutrition Recommendation Quality found in Popular Publications</title><description>... Back in the dawn of the Internet era, JAMA, the top American medical journal warned, “Let the reader and viewer beware” of the quality of medical information on the Internet. This month the American Medical Association reiterated the warning – on the web itself – “regarding the incomplete, misleading, or inaccurate medical information available on the web.” They aren’t, of course, talking about this blog or my website . Truly, I try my darnedest to be complete, leading, and accurate. I subscribe to the eight HONcode principles, as I state on my “ Diabetes Directory ”. The Health On the Net Foundation states in fact that, “Diabetes Directory is in compliance with the HONcode.” Not every medical writer on the web, however, subscribes to the HONcode. So I can understand the AMA’s frustration. Unfortunately, however, popular magazines don’t seem to do any better. The American Council on Science and Health has just issued its tenth annual report on the accuracy of nutrition information in pop... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7230-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7230_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:59:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/59238/138525/worried-weight</link><title>Are You Worried About Your Weight?</title><description>... ... Lose excess weight because of the health hazards it can cause. ... Watch salt intake because high levels can put you at risk of high blood pressure, a risk factor for heart disease. ... Beware eating too much saturated fat or trans fat because it can clog your arteries. ... Watch the calories you consume daily, because once you gain excess weight it can be very difficult to take off and keep off. ... Beware excess weight because it can increase your risk of developing certain cancers. ... ... According to researchers, though, the "weight alarm" continues to be rung by health experts, a recent survey shows that many Americans are ignoring the warnings or are simply confused by the information.  The survey, which began in 2006 by the non-profit IFIC, International Food Information Council, seems to showcase a downward trend in concern about weight .  Some experts feel that it is time for people to grasp the reality that regardless of what is causing the weig... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7230-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7230_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 07:59:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/84/30058/cadre-ing</link><title>CADRE Non-profit Working to Reduce Diabetes Complications</title><description>...   ... One could argue that despite all the big talk about combating the diabetes epidemic, lots of prominent organizations ... seem to be getting very little done. The field of diabetes education is ... facing a crisis , with so little professional support and funding to cope with the torrent of new patients coming their way. ...   ... For these reasons, I found it very encouraging to discover the Council for the Advancement of Diabetes Research and Education ( CADRE ), a non-profit organization "committed to ... reducing the devastating complications of both type 1 and type 2 ... diabetes through achievement of tight metabolic control. To achieve ... this goal, CADRE provides health care professionals with scientific ... information and educational programs to enable them to manage and ... empower their patients with diabetes." ...   ... Note the emphasis ... on REDUCING COMPLICATIONS. Note the focus on HELPING THE HEALTH PROS TO ... HELP PATIENTS. This seems pra... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7230-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7230_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:00:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/5949/137621/background</link><title>PACE Trial Results Misleading: Part I – Background</title><description>... In mid-February, the UK's Medical Research Council, with great fanfare, issued a press release announcing, “UK’s largest CFS/ME trial confirms safe and effective treatments for patients.”  The two treatments they claimed were so effective are Cognitive Behavioral Therapy and Graded Exercise Therapy.  Most of the national media, which prides itself on researching its stories and digging below the surface, did what they do with most announcements of medical research results – they dutifully repeated the information in the press release.  For the next couple of weeks, I saw dozens of headlines like these: “Psychotherapy Eases Chronic Fatigue, Study Finds” – New York Times “Study: 'Talking And Exercise Could Cure ME'” – Sky News “Study Says 2 Therapies Help Fight Chronic Fatigue Syndrome” – Newsday “Psychotherapy And Exercise Look Best To Treat Chronic Fatigue Syndrome” – NPR “P... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7230-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7230_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:00:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/790448/156192/medicated</link><title>Well and medicated right.</title><description>... I take latuda. I feel well on this med. it cost taxpayers though since I am disabled. Can the doctor make me take a cheaper medicine even if I tell her no? I'll end up refusing cheaper medicine and be locked up into submission to cheaper meds. Can I refuse cheaper meds? Can I bluff with the doctor and tell her I would pay the five hundred dollar med? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7230-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7230_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:01:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/question/59465/33590</link><title>how do i get help</title><description>... I have conversations with people in my head. At that moment I believe it is real and expect the other person to have remembered this conversation.I guess thru some physic supper power i been "blessed with". I mean I kinda know when I'm talking to myself and when i,m not. When  i am talking to people in person i have a hard time communicating with them because at the same time i am holding on the conversation in my head with them  and sometimes other people in the room I think my doctor is stupid because i expect her to understand my problem and symptoms in which i have told her in my head. I am 44 Years old and the few times i have been able to tell anyone no one seems to pay it any never mind.When i walk down the street i always here people yelling and calling me names where i am known and where i am not.i cope telling myself everyone hates me because i am quite.I very seldom confront any one but when i do i often bluff violence, and land in trouble by someone calling ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7230-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7230_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:01:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/22567/25645/tormenter</link><title>My Tormenter</title><description>... What ... rough beast is this, starting one more dull ... assault ... inside my brain stem, to compel ... a ... migraine to obliterate my skull ... 'cause ... I had cheese, or red wine, or rain fell? ...   ... Excruciating ... pain's not bad enough. ... This ... endless dread's the beast's most vicious curse. ... Will ... my boss think that this attack's a bluff? ... Will ... friends still love me? Will this one hurt worse? ...   ... Will ... side effects be worse than the disease? ... Then ... some new regimen prevents the pain ... and ... for one blessed moment, I think he's ... gone. ... But always will this rough beast remain, ... tormenting ... me with gleeful, patient scorn ... while ... he awaits the time to be reborn. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>