<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7234">347 ford engines</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:13:48" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7234-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7234_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:13:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/22705/36519/celebrities-public</link><title>Celebrities with Anxiety: Harrison Ford: Fear of Public Speaking</title><description>...   ... Harrison Ford was born in 1942 in Chicago, Illinois. After becoming discouraged by his lack of success in acting, he left the industry to pursue a career in carpentry. A number of years later, he was offered a role in American Graffiti (1973)and yet later, in Star Wars (1977). In 1981 he starred in Raiders of the Lost Ark as Indiana Jones. In 1965 he received nominations for both an Academy Award and Golden Globe award for his role in Witness . ...   ... Harrison Ford has appeared in countless movies and has received the Life Achievement Award of the American Film Institute. But even so, he is afraid to give a speech or talk in front of a group of people. According to Harrison Ford, public... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7234-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7234_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:14:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/44/2939/betty-ford</link><title>To President and Betty Ford: Good-Bye and Thanks</title><description>... For so long I’ve associated Betty Ford with her famous drug and alcohol recovery retreat—the Betty Ford Center —that until the recent flurry of news over her husband’s passing, I’d forgotten that her addiction was preceded by a diagnosis of breast cancer and a mastectomy . Betty Ford may have been the first celebrity—Gerald Ford, had just become president—to go public with a disease that in 1974 was something no one talked about. Dad often spoke of Gerald Ford—they’d gone to South High School together in Grand Rapids, Michigan, where they both grew up—and he certainly voted for him. And, despite the cultural taboo, in our family, breast cancer was a subject of frequent discussion. We talked about breast cancer because my father was a plastic surgeon who did many mastectomies and breasts reconstructions from the 1950s into the 1980s. He has an avid interest in helping women recover and did all he could to support them emotionally as well as surgically. Sometimes I worked for him, typing ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7234-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7234_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:14:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/9692/141257/betty-ford</link><title>Betty Ford and You</title><description>...   ... Sure there were some feminists who were starting to use words like "breast" and "vagina" in health books like Our Bodies Ourselves first published in 1973.  But for a first lady of an older generation to announce publicly that she had breast cancer and to allow herself to be photographed shortly after her mastectomy were unheard of. ...   ... Who knows how many women's lives were saved because the publicity surrounding Mrs. Ford's cancer sent them to the doctor?  The breakthrough she made led to the possibility of public awareness campaigns and more lives saved.  No... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7234-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7234_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:14:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/6148/136824/world</link><title>2011 Ford Ironman world championship, thanks for the gift RA</title><description>... It has still not set in as of yet however as time passes I know much training is still needed and it will set in. ... I don't have many words to say right now so I'll leave with this, In 2003 I was very sick, I had RA with a sed rate of over 250 the doctor had me on 14.5 of methotrexate. ...  It was hard to walk and also hard to do the simplest things that we all do every day like putting on socks and shoes or even going to the restroom and I remember asking myself why me? what did I do to deserve the illness I had. As years pass The answer is getting clearer, that RA illness was a great gift, without it I wouldn't be who I am today, eight full marathons, two half Ironman events and a entry to compete with the best in the world. ... That gift was packaged very painfully and it took many challenges to overcome to finally see what it really was. It was a FORD IRONMAN WORLD CHAM... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7234-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7234_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:15:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002432rec.html</link><title>Genetically engineered foods</title><description>... Alternative Names Bioengineered foods Recommendations Genetically engineered foods are generally regarded as safe. There has been no adequate testing, however, to ensure complete safety. There are no reports of illness or injury due to genetically engineered foods. Each new genetically engineered food will have to be judged individually. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7234-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7234_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:15:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002432fod.html</link><title>Genetically engineered foods</title><description>... Alternative Names Bioengineered foods Food Sources Tomatoes, potatoes, squash, corn, and soybeans have been genetically altered through biotechnology. Many more foods have engineered ingredients and more are being developed. Check with the Food and Drug Administration (FDA) for more information. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7234-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7234_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:16:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002432sid.html</link><title>Genetically engineered foods</title><description>... Alternative Names Bioengineered foods Side Effects The Food and Drug Administration (FDA) regulates production and labeling of genetically engineered foods. Some people have raised concerns that the genes from one food that are inserted into another food may cause an allergic reaction . For instance, if peanut genes are in tomatoes, could someone with a peanut allergy react to tomatoes? In January 2001, the FDA's Center for Food Safety and Applied Nutrition proposed that developers of bioengineered food submit scientific and safety information to the FDA at least 120 days before the food is marketed. Further details on these foods may be found on the FDA website. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7234-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7234_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:16:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002432.html</link><title>Genetically engineered foods overview</title><description>... Definition Genetically engineered foods have had foreign genes (genes from other plants or animals) inserted into their genetic codes. Genetic engineering can be done with plants, animals, or microorganisms. Historically, farmers bred plants and animals for thousands of years to produce the desired traits. For example, they produced dogs ranging from poodles to Great Danes, and roses from sweet-smelling miniatures to today's long-lasting, but scent-free reds. Selective breeding over time created these wide variations, but the process depended on nature to produce the desired gene. Humans then chose to mate individual animals or plants that carried the particular gene in order to make the desired characteristics more common or more pronounced. Genetic engineering allows scientists to speed this process up by moving desired genes from one plant into another -- or even from an animal to a plant or vice versa. Alternative Names Bioengineered foods Function Potential benefits of genetically engine... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7234-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7234_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:16:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/tissue-engineering-1746</link><title>What is tissue engineering?</title><description>... What is tissue engineering? Tissue engineering is a new area of science. It includes growing living human tissue for transplantation and other uses. Tissue engineering combines biology and engineering. It looks for ways to restore, maintain, or improve tissue function. One example of this is the use of cartilage cells to replace damaged or destroyed cartilage. Normal, healthy cartilage cells called chondrocytes are removed from the knee. These are grown and multiplied in a lab and then reinjected into the knee. The new cells are injected into the area of damaged cartilage. This allows the patient to regrow a smooth joint surface. The new, smooth weight-bearing surface is less likely to become arthritic. Many different types of tissue can be grown this way. This includes skin, bone, ligaments, and tendons. In the future, labs may be able to make donor tissue and organs for anyone who needs them. Living tissue and electronics may be combined to form new joints. These are only a few of the ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7234-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7234_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:17:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/146513/141156</link><title>I have been at a steel mill for 2 months working 50-60 hrs per week as a materials engineer and I feel like I cannot go in. I am homesick and depressed and I don't know why? Can you help me?</title><description>... I am a new graduate with a masters degree in Materials Engineering. My work and internships with the exception of 1 internship has been in nanotechnology. I left graduate school because I did not like the long hours of research and working on 1 project for 2 years. I have tried something new and I am working at a steel mill as a metallurgist (a professional) if you will and I am salaried. Its been nearly 2 months and I thought I was used to this job, but lately I have been feeling like I don't know why I am here; I am always anxious in the morning and though I get sleep; I dont want to go to work in the morning and I feel sad and depressed. My parents came to visit over the July 4th weekend and that made me homesick for the first time in my life. What is wrong with me? Also, I am working between 50-60 hrs per week which is normal at this job and I feel like I just made a mistake. Help me? ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>