<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7235">silicone roof coatings</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:17:40" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7235-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7235_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:17:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/9798/13780/pads</link><title>Silicone pads or silicon injectable</title><description>... Is there any one here that can tell me about an alternative to knee replacement envolving a sort f silicone injectable into the knee, if there is such thing?  Or is there a silicone pad that is slipped in between the joint to cushion the erroded joint?  I'd like to know A.S.A.P if possible.  You can contact me @  justdez727@yahoo.com with any answers you may have.   Thank you ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7235-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7235_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:17:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/636844/121461</link><title>tightness around the roof of my mouth and back of throat. Have you heard of this?</title><description>... I fight daily migraines with verapimil. Get sensitive to noise and light with oncoming mig. Oddly, I also get a tightness on roof of mouth and upper back of throat. Heard of this? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7235-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7235_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:18:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/genital-herpes/c/question/948721/105823</link><title>herpes on roof of my mouth very worried</title><description>... i keep getting infections on roof of my mouth my doc suggested herpes then referd me to oral sugeon there never there wen i c him they cum up as swollen lumps then seem to burst and go yellow then dissapear .my doc gave me acyclovir it helps iv been to oral surgeon today as i have outbreak again he wernt there so they are going to take a picture tommorow im very worried i have had blood tests hiv tests cos im so worried .no one i no has herpes on roof of mouth only on lips why am i getting this it started last yr and iv had about 7 outbreaks its relly getting me down my docs not sure if it is herpes ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7235-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7235_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:18:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/476675/105691</link><title>horrible pain of the roof of my mouth! pls help</title><description>...   ... thank you ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7235-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7235_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:19:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/85-father-cleaning-gutters-1415</link><title>My 85-year old father fell from his roof while cleaning out his gutters.</title><description>... My 85-year old father fell from his roof while cleaning out his gutters. The surgery for his hip fracture went well but the surgeon says he's not out of the woods yet. We're not sure what that means exactly. Can you enlighten us? Hip fractures in older adults can be complex and challenging to treat and manage well. Fractures from a high-energy injury such as your father's fall from a height can be accompanied by other injuries as well. Sometimes it takes some time for other problems to surface. Any hip fracture can be the catalyst that causes loss of independence. Serious complications such as pneumonia, infection, and blood clots can compromise return to health. Your father will be under close surveillance while in the hospital until his condition is stable. Most older adults have some form of osteoporosis. The bone loses mass and density and becomes more prone to fracture. This makes it difficult to stabilize the fracture with plates, screws, or pins inserted into or even through the b... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7235-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7235_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:19:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/c/question/359062/125071</link><title>what prescription medicine is top of the line that will keep high blood pressure at a normal reading? I take 5 different pills a day and it still goes up to the roof. Please help!</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7235-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7235_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:19:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/cold-flu/c/question/231488/126431</link><title>my age 64 66 inches tall weigh 200 have been taking simvastan 20 mg for 15yr and Zetia 10mg for 15 yr I do lots of ladder climbing for roofing work. For past 4-5 mo having difficulty with</title><description>... ladder up and down. Early in work day can go up down normally after several trips have to go one rung at a time but move right along, no stopping along way  Is this something I should be concerned with?  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7235-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7235_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:20:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/634435/69124</link><title>today i caught my 5 yr old who has adhd on the roof, she is okay. but how do explain to her that she</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7235-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7235_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:20:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/question/579279/95443</link><title>I have seen alot of questions in regards to lowering DHEA levels..how bout mine is through the roof!</title><description>... Anyone out there have HIGH levels of DHEA? Mine is double the # for my age. Was checked for polycistic ovary stuff...negative. No side affects or problems to report. The best thing about and really the only thing about it as far as I know thus far is......HIGH HIGH HIGH LABIDO!!!!!!! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7235-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7235_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:21:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/question/686360/111680</link><title>i have blisters on my upper thighs and stomach, and now one on the roof of my mouth help!?</title><description>... they started appearing about a week ago, and the blisters are not like bubbles though more like little spotts of open skin. ive already had the chicken poxs and the blisters arnt painful unless they are being rubbed somewhat hard on by my clothes. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>