<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7239">roundabout safety</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:33:23" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7239-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7239_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:33:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/96/112748/reflux-mom-head</link><title>Ask the Reflux Mom: Is It All in Her Head?</title><description>...   ... What if you talk to the school nurse, keep a symptoms diary and see the doctor and there is no diagnosis? It has been my experience that getting a diagnosis and treatment for Gastroesophageal Reflux Disease can be extremely quick or slow. Sometimes the symptoms are so common and classic that the doctor can diagnose the problem from a mile away. Other children, like mine for instance, don’t have the most typical symptoms and the road to diagnosis is rather slow and roundabout. It may take extra time and several visits to the pediatrician and specialists to figure it out. ...   ... In some instances, the doctor w... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7239-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7239_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:33:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/7008/9509/high-tech-bag</link><title>High Tech meets Hefty Bag</title><description>... Hi, I'm Karen, and I'm an almost-11-year survivor. I'm writing a book about the whole experience, with a humorous slant. Here is one of my pages: Radiation. Sounds sinister, doesn’t it? Like some KGB plot to eliminate James Bond. A foil-clad beauty cuddles up to 007, then Number One pushes a button and suddenly she’s a super-conductor. Voila! Fried secret agent! My appointment was for 9:00 a.m. Tuesday! So far, everything had been cutting-edge and state of the art. So when they talked about a custom-fitted mold, I expected them to take precise measurements and special-order the perfect, Karen-shaped radiation delivery system. Their ‘system’ turned out to be a can of Kwik Foam and a Hefty trash bag. The tech sprayed the foam in the bag and put it on the table. They positioned me to match up the beams to the dotted lines the techs had drawn on me earlier, with much twitching on my part and much complaining on theirs. (YOU try to stay still when someone is playing connect-the-... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7239-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7239_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:34:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/404482/72969/rhe</link><title>How I Travel With Rheumatoid Arthritis</title><description>...   ... I get that question a lot, especially from my mother, when I tell her about my upcoming travel itineraries. Then, as though she's saying it for the first time each time, she'll say "the youth is wasted on the young," as though I don't appreciate being young and full of stamina. But, when you have arthritis, "young" doesn't necessarily equate to having a lot of stamina. So keeping a game plan when traveling is essential, and someone to remind me (nag?) about that game plan gives me a chance to constantly refine it. My travels take me everywhere, most often to talk to groups of doctors, patients, families and others about arthritis, on behalf of the CreakyJoints community. I'm kind of like a (very hairy) mouthpiece for arthritis - always trying to raise awareness and draw attention to our collective needs. As a result of my hectic schedule, I find myself taking trains, planes and automobiles virtually every week, sometimes multiple times in the span of a few day... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7239-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7239_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:34:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/120/148003/schizophrenia</link><title>Schizophrenia and Meditation: An Aid To Recovery?</title><description>...   ... "A new study finds that people skilled at meditation seem able to turn off areas of the brain associated with daydreaming and psychiatric disorders such as autism and schizophrenia." ...   ... It is posited that people experienced at meditation continually monitor and suppress "me" thoughts and mind wandering. They are able to co-activate two brain regions to develop a present-centered mindset that is less self-centered. ...   ... In an unrelated study, even a brief amount of meditation can create an improved mood. It showed electrical activity in the left frontal region of the brain was significantly greater, a pattern linked to positive mood. In the study, brain patterns shifted in as little as seven hours among the new meditators. ... Extended meditation leads to neuroplasticity, the brain's ability to change, structurally and functionally, on the basis of environmental input. Experienced meditators are able to not get stuck on a particular stimulus, even long... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7239-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7239_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:35:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/16033/55181/friends</link><title>Hello friends!</title><description>... Here is my crazy story. Last Friday as in last friday not yesterday. So I am low on aderall I call the doctors office and I find that everyone is out of the office so no Aderall . Anyway so finally on Tuesday since I have no clue what took so long I get the perscription from the doctor. We take it to the pharmacy and they say that the Insurance place has to ok it. We started with a new place this year because in the middle of last year a new company  bought the company my husband works at so now it has a new name and they are out of AZ so they had to go with their company  for insurance. Anyway so its a big pain in the butt!!  Anyway so my doctors offices has to end up calling the MEDCO and  actually say they are wanting me to take the meds. So MEDCO has to send a form to my doctors and they have to fill it out and tell them why I am taking the meds and for how long  I have been taking them and if there is any other product that would work for me. Its just bec... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7239-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7239_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:35:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/34002/20733/times-science</link><title>Historical Times and the Blessings of Science</title><description>... Five long years have passed and I have come to know bipolar disorder and the mania experience quite well. Though not my friend ... it has not really been my enemy for a very long time. Through the years I have noticed more and more television commercials and print ads for medications of all types. And as I review my own writings, I am reminded that we are fortunate to live in such historical times. Manic-depression in the 1900's meant that if you were stricken, you were institutionalized with murderers and the like. It was madness and mayhem as women were often abused by the very "caregivers" that were to care for them. Patients were starved, or killed, they were considered worse than thieves ... they were the cast-offs of society. Science in those days included performing procedures like lobotomies on the mentally ill, it was another aspect of the horrific medical misjudgement and mismanagement of the day. Today researchers bring to consumers break-through science and as... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7239-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7239_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:36:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/37378/driver-seat</link><title>In the Driver's Seat</title><description>... In  a talk I used to give last year, I would joke: “I get road rage a lot and I don’t even drive.” No more. Yesterday, after 30 years, I”m finally back to being a licensed driver. The process was the most stressful event I can recall. More stressful, even, than the time I had to explain to Federal officials about the plutonium rods that airport security found on my carry-on luggage (okay, I just made that up). A brief history: 1976: I move to New Zealand with my fiancee Her uncle is at the airport to pick us up. I hop in the passenger side of the car. It comes equipped with steering wheel and pedals and control panel. There is only a glove box on the driver’s side. I never recover from the incident. New Zealanders drive on the left side of the road. They refuse to make an exception for me. Most of them display a total lack of understanding when I enter roundabouts on the side to which I am accustomed. Plus, speed limit signs are posted in kilograms, kiloby... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7239-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7239_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:36:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/568286/156676/ra</link><title>Kicking It: Kickboxing and RA</title><description>...   ... In that post, I focused on what I don’t do for exercise: yoga. ...   ... So I thought I would write a piece on what I do, do for exercise. ...   ... While yoga isn’t my thing, kickboxing is. ...   ... It took some trial and error to get there, though.  I attempted to do personal training through an adult education program in my area, but was told that the personal trainer did not feel comfortable training me because he did not have experience with my conditions.  I then did personal training through my school gym, but the person who trained me didn’t really work with me on things I could do that wouldn’t be really rough on my joints. ...   ... Finally, I started looking for other options. ...   ... As I said about yoga, I need something that is very active and engaging, something that stays interesting and allows me to mix it up. ...   ... So I found a martial arts pl... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7239-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7239_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:36:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/64018/38489/man-talk</link><title>Man Talk</title><description>... When you first look at a man and a woman, you are able to notice the subtle differences between the sexes.  It is when the two sexes communicate with each other, however, that the differences become truly glaring.  This is because one is speaking “he talk” while the other is speaking “she talk.”   Where this difference really becomes a problem is when you are in a relationship, and you need to know how to combine “he talk” and “she talk” into “we talk.”  So I feel like it's my job as a man and as a dating coach to help all the women learn how to understand “he talk” (or “man talk” as I like to call it), so that they won't need to hire a translator to understand what men are saying.   Women always want men to express their feelings.  They always complain “Why can't he just say he loves me?” or “I wish he would just compliment me more.”   What you ne... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7239-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7239_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:37:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/86453</link><title>Group Therapy for Eating Disorders</title><description>...   ... Normally, in any kind of group therapy I've attended, we've all had something in common.  Yes, in eating disorders I guess the commonality is food.  And maybe "those who know" (experts/professionals) would expound on a theory that all eating disorders have the same root problem.  I don't know.  I haven't examined the theories.  All I knew is that I had gained an amazin... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>