<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7241">flight simulators</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:42:15" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7241-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7241_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:42:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/149851/124541</link><title>acls simulator</title><description>... online simulator questions regarding acls ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7241-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7241_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:42:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/185415/79760</link><title>I have had a lumpectomy APril 8, 2009 and not yet simulated</title><description>... I went to a teaching hospital in New York City. Did not have to do chemo cause oncotype score was 11, however, the radiation oncologist keeps delaying my simulation and radiation treatments for the simple reason that she refuses to sign a consent form and refuses to assure me that she will do the mapping. She states that being that it is a teaching hospital she will oversee the resident.  The resident can sign the consent form. Is this proper? Should I fear that a resident is working on me? Should I also fear that radiation treatments may not be as effective since the lumpectomy was in APril 2009 and as of date I have not been simulated yet? Thank you for your responses. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7241-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7241_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:43:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/r/breast-cancer/article/planning-simulation-4530</link><title>The Planning Session (Simulation)</title><description>... Careful planning is necessary before your radiation treatment can begin. The planning ensures that you get the full benefit of radiation with minimal impact on other parts of your body. During the planning session, a radiation oncologist maps out the breast area that needs treatment. The oncologist or radiation technician uses a special X-ray machine called a simulator, and the process is called simulation because the treatment is being "simulated," or not really given. ... Because it is so important to position the angles of radiation accurately, the planning session can sometimes last up to an hour. The extra time and care during this session will make your future visits run more smoothly and help you get the most from your radiation therapy. You do not receive any treatment during the planning session. ... Here's what you can expect to happen during your planning session visit to the radiation oncology department: ... Before simulation ... At the beginning of your planning session, your doctor wi... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7241-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7241_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:43:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/1443/154242/improve-children</link><title>Using Avatars to Improve Social Anxiety in Children</title><description>...   ... Social anxiety disorder (SAD) is more than shyness. It impacts a child’s ability to make friends, answer questions in class or fit in with their classmates. They are often afraid of being criticized and feel no one likes them. They may be afraid to speak in front of others and some refuse to eat when other people are present. Children with SAD may have frequent headaches or stomach aches , wanting to stay home from school to avoid having to interact with others . ...   ... The new simulation, as reported by ScienceDaily, is designed to help children between 8 and 12 years old. Children sit at a computer while the clinician sits in a ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7241-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7241_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:44:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/658965/102932</link><title>I have had many preventive drugs;none worked. I then tried occipital nerve stimulation.</title><description>... The first nerve simulation worked for 3 months. No pain at all.  Then the leads fell off and the pain came back.  They took the leads off the nerves but left the wires and the stimulator in my back. At some point the wires poked through the skin and I got a pseudomonas infection and was in the hospital with IV antibiotics for aboout 5 days.  They tried to blame it on me.  They also told me they never heard of the term lead migraition (false).  A year later I was still in so much pain that I let them do it again with a different connection to the nerve. This one never worked and 4 years later it is still there (I lost my insurance at the same time).  I still feel that they have a duty to take it out at their expense because they lied to me in many ways.  They never told me it was not FDA approved.  They lied about "lead migration" and the staff was clearly on the defensive.  This is a well know Pain Clinic in SF but I have since read many re... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7241-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7241_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:44:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/incontinence/c/question/84971/28129</link><title>There is Femme Elite mashine for nerves stimulation with urge incontinens. Has it been succesful?</title><description>... This device claims to simulate the nerves and muscules of the bladder. Are there women who have positive experience with above? Forum? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7241-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7241_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:44:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/666807/100431/sp</link><title>There is no SPOON!!</title><description>...   ... Yeah.  Sci-Fi geek alert!!  ...   ... In the movie, The Matrix, Neo, a proto-messianic hacker, is trying to learn how to control the computer simulated reality he finds himself in.  His journey leads him to visit a Gandhi-like character who teaches him how to bend spoons with his mind.  Here is the dialogue that accompanies the scene: ...   ... Spoon boy: Do not try and bend the spoon. That's impossible. Instead... only try to realize the truth. Neo: What truth? Spoon boy: There is no spoon. Neo: There is no spoon? Spoon boy: Then you'll see, that it is not the spoon that bends, it is only yourself. ...   ... "This guy's about to talk about the Matrix on an RA site?  That's weird..." ...   ... Well, relax :)  This isn't about the Matrix.  It is about the philosphy that led (loosely) to the idea of the Matrix, however.  Plus, it's about ignoring spoons, and I hate spoons, so you see this is completely self-serving ...   ... In the context of the movie, Spo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7241-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7241_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:45:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/4182/168126/men-women-react-stress</link><title>How Men and Women React Under Stress</title><description>...   ... Little by little we’re finding out more about gender differences. In 2011, Nichole Lighthall, a USC doctoral student, reported her findings that men and women react differently to risky decision-making, and this is reflected in different brain activity patt... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7241-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7241_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:45:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/19/1508/lean</link><title>Finding Inspiration in Other Stroke Survivors</title><description>... ... ... My mother saw me looking out the window at her and told me that she had talked to her one... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7241-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7241_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:46:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/573318/93308</link><title>ACLS megacode sim access.</title><description>... where do I access the acls megacode simulator? Several site referred to this one but I can't find it.  Help please. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>