<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7242">hague convention</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:46:28" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7242-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7242_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:46:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/100/10012/convention</link><title>The Conventional Convention</title><description>...   During my business career, I’ve managed to avoid a great many conventions.   This was much more difficult when I was a featured speaker, but then I employed the ever popular “I must leave right after” tactic.   I would fly in just in time to give my speech and then fly out immediately thereafter.   The above aside, I have nevertheless attended numerous conventions.   Most of these have been what I call a “conventional convention,” tedious and boring.   A few of these have approached the bizarre.   For example, one convention in the mid-summer heat (90F plus) of New Orleans I was booked into a Bourbon Street hotel only to find it had no air conditioning.   About 4:00 a.m., after tossing and turning, and drenched in sweat, it occurred to me that it might be helpful if I rearranged the furniture.   I opened the refrigerator door and pushed the head of my bed up against the doorframe of the refrigerator (which made it impossible for the door to c... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7242-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7242_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:46:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/120/30811/orlando</link><title>NAMI Convention 2008 - Greetings From Orlando</title><description>... I flew out of Newark Liberty and there was a mix-up with my boarding pass, so security frisked me.  I had to stand there with my arms up in the air while she checked for contraband.  Then she opened and scanned my carry-on. ...   ... Aside from that, the flight was short and uneventful.  I ate a container of olives I'd bought in the Mediterranean store: Lebanese ones, kalamata, meaty olives, and plum-colored. ...   ... The Rosen Centre Hotel is a short drive from Orlando International airport.  After checking in, I was entranced with my Asian-inspired room: cinnamon-color and leaf pattern bedspread, dark cherry furniture and yellow tulips in a vase. ...   ... Here's what you can expect in terms of convention blog entries when I arrive home: an interview with Dr. Ken Duckworth, NAMI's medical director, who will share insights on schizophrenia in young people: treatment and hopes for the future; a roving reporter feature where I ask attendees to chime in with "how to b... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7242-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7242_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:47:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/100/11346/2007-nami</link><title>Observations about the 2007 NAMI National Convention</title><description>...   My annual pilgrimage to the NAMI National Convention has become for me, as it has for thousands, an opportunity to gather with friends, share personal experiences, and catch up on the latest information about mental illnesses and related issues.   Progress in the fight against serious brain diseases comes from numerous sources and often when we least expect it. Sometimes it is nothing less than a revolution. More often it is an accumulation of bits and pieces that, when fitted together, begin to make sense, to provide some answers. Even those of us that have the time rarely have the expertise to interpret and integrate all this information in a meaningful way. NAMI has rescued thousands of us.   The education program at the NAMI Annual Convention is superb. Enthusiastic presenters share the latest information in their fields of expertise, laboring hard to do so in a way that lay people will understand. They also make serious efforts to explain how their information relates... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7242-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7242_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:47:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/100/11960/nami-mike</link><title>NAMI Convention: A Discussion with Mike Fitzpatrick, Executive Director</title><description>... Mike Fitzpatrick This is number two in a series of seven blogs made possible by the encouragement and financial support of The Health Central Network. All represent interviews with senior officers of NAMI [National Alliance on Mental Illness] or other luminaries that attended the NAMI 2007 annual convention. These interviews cover a wide range of topics that should be of interest to everyone that is involved in one fashion or another with mental health issues. Mike Fitzpatrick, MSW, is the Executive Director of the National Alliance on Mental Illness (NAMI). Previously, he served as the Director of NAMI's Policy Research Institute and as NAMI's National Director of Policy. Prior to joining NAMI in 1999, Mike held senior management positions in state government, with non-profit agencies, and in the private sector. He served in the Maine State Legislature (his home state) and was House Chair of the Health and Human Services Committee from 1994 - 1996. Over the years, he has dev... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7242-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7242_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:47:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/ibd/c/2623/20094/treatments-ibd</link><title>Alternative &amp; Conventional Treatments for IBD</title><description>... Ten years ago when my IBD symptoms were at their absolute worst I was desperate. I'd been seeing a gastroenterologist, I'd had all the tests, gotten the diagnosis, and was taking my prescribed medications. But I wasn't really improving - I was still having 10, 20, 30 BMs per day, blood and mucus, and severe pain along with depleted energy, virtually no appetite, and rapid weight loss.   I wasn't angry at my doctor - I liked him, trusted him, and felt he really was doing for me what he knew best to do. But, I also felt that I had to try something else to get my health out of the hole it was in that was slowly getting bigger and deeper every day. At the time, I lived in California and a good friend lived in Prescott, Arizona, near Sedona. He had tried for months to convince me to go to Arizona to participate in "energy healing" that a friend of his did -to me, a girl who grew up in the Midwest, this sounded like a bunch of granola-crunchy-West-Coast-mumbo-j... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7242-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7242_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:48:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/148317/bipolar-conventional</link><title>Sex and Bipolar: Can Depression Lead to Over-Sexuality? Challenging the Conventional Wisdom</title><description>...   ... The authors cite a number of studies showing increased sexual interest and behavior during mania or hypomania, and the DSM makes it official by including “sexual indiscretions” in manic and hypomanic episodes. It also notes “decrease in sexual interests or drive” during depression. ...   ... Okay, time to challenge that notion. In our first installment, I alluded to a 2006 NIH-funded study of a large teen population which found that those who were depressed were far more likely to engage in risky behav... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7242-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7242_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:48:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/100/10477/defining</link><title>Unconventional Conventions: Some Defining Characteristics</title><description>...   ... Criterion #1 – ...   ... Most people attending a Conventional Convention do not appear to be happy about being there (boredom is contagious and insidious), unless they are enthusiastic about being away from home.   Some or even most may be happy, of course, but they show little exuberance.   The only exception seems to be at an open bar, which can generate a little too much... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7242-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7242_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:49:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/71019/power-prevention</link><title>American Association of Clinical Endocrinologists Annual Convention Coverage</title><description>... ... The convention took over the George R. Brown Convention Center in the downtown of America's fourth largest city. The convention center is so big that after Hurricane Katrina 7,000 refugees lived here. ... ... In the mob of today's convention you might imagine my surprise that the first person I made eye contact with asked if I was David Mendosa. The person who asked was Sarah Senn, who I had sent several photos for an article that she wrote about me. But we had never previously met in person. ... ... That article appeared in print this morning. It came out in Power of Prevention , the AACE's new magazine for doctors and their patients around the country. Sarah told me that they printed and distributed 600,000 copies. ... ... Dr. Donald Bergman, who chairs the Power of Prevention Committee for the Am... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7242-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7242_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:49:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/10655/live-nami-life-man</link><title>Live from The National NAMI Convention: My Life as Didge Man</title><description>...   ... Today I showed up with my didge. From early morning till about two in the afternoon I was Didge Man. If you never have experienced being Didge Man, you have missed out on a major life experience. ...   ... Basically, there are two types of Didge People, the coy type and the honk on demand type. Today, I discovered I fit into the latter group. Honk on demand. People literally stopped me in the parking area outside the hotel, and I obligingly honked on demand. ...   ... Going to get a coffee – honk on demand. Walking into the lobby – honk on demand. Walk in... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7242-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7242_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:49:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/159946/action-coalition-convention</link><title>Be Part of the Obesity Action Coalition’s Your Weight Matters Convention</title><description>...   ... ...   ... Do you have questions concerning your weight and overall health? Well, you may get all of those questions answered at the 2nd Annual Your Weight Matters National Convention (YWM 2013). Sponsored by the Obesity Action Coalition (OAC), YWM 2013 takes place August 15-18 in Phoenix, AZ. ...   ... Rise to the Challenge: YWM 2013 ...   ... Weight and health go hand-in-hand; however, individuals affected by excess weight or obesity are often exposed to a variety of misinformation. Last year, in an effort to help individuals understand how their weight impacts their health, the OAC hosted the Inaugural Your Weight Matters Convention. More than 275 attendees received evidence-based education on weight and health. This year, the OAC encourages individuals to “Rise to the Challenge” at YWM 2013. ...   ... YWM 2013 Agenda ...   ... Educational sessions will offer information on understanding your weight-loss options, weight man... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>