<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7249">largest alligator on record</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:10:30" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7249-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7249_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:10:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/89/2232/arthritis</link><title>Arthritis and Alligators</title><description>... ... My next hint was on a week-long canoe/camping trip in the Everglades, which was probably NOT the optimum activity for a patient with OA , but as a nature photographer, I was able to ignore much of the pain and literally focus on my surroundings. Incredible shorebirds, mystical frogs in the mangrove swamps, and bright-colored coral-mass colonies on the white sand beaches helped me ignore the twinges of pain. Walking on the warm white sand beach was like walking on warm snow. At night, I fell asleep in my tent to the hypnotic crashing of the waves on the beach nearby. ... ... The first night, I awakened suddenly to the piercing sound of quiet -... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7249-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7249_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:10:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/33200/food-diaries</link><title>Food Diaries: Recording What You Eat Helps Achieve Weight Loss</title><description>... simple as recording what you eat might make the biggest difference. ... Writing down what you eat can double your weight loss, according to a study ... that the American Journal of Preventative Medicine will publish next month. This ... finding comes from an analysis of the first phase of one of the largest ... weight loss maintenance trials every conducted. After about six ... months, the nearly 1,700 participants lost an average of 13 pounds. ... Kaiser Permanente's Center ... for Health Research in Portland, Oregon, which ran the study, asked journalists not to write about it until today. But Kaiser Permanente sent me a copy of the forthcoming report, " Weight Loss During the Intensive Intervention Phase of the Weight-Loss Maintenance Trial ." And last week one of the study's researchers spoke with me for an hour . The Kaiser Permanente investigators wanted to help a large ... proportion of people to lose weight and to keep that weight off ... long-term. The primary purpose ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7249-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7249_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:11:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/7712/55444/national-database</link><title>A National Database of Health Records: my first thoughts</title><description>...   ... The vision has received a broad welcome, but even its most ardent proponents are aware of the costs of implementing such a system. Perhaps of greater concern are the costs of such a system failing both in terms of its security and, more broadly, a systems failure. ...   ... I am immediately drawn to security and privacy issues. A cursory review of news stories during 2008 reminds me that a significant gulf exists between the technology underpinning data security and the people who use it. In a year when laptops containing sensitive and private data were left on trains and in taxis, some very real concerns are bound to be aired. The logistics of putting the health care records of an entire nation into a computerize... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7249-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7249_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:11:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/</link><title>Living With Quiggles: The Largest Minority</title><description>... Stigma: 1) the recognition of difference based on some distinguishing characteristic or mark; 2) a consequent devaluation of the person Quiggles: a made-up term (by the famous sociologist, Erving Goffman) to identify all of the variations and difference of the human body which occur either from birth, daily wear and tear, accident, or illness which can be, and will be, stigmatized. As you may already know, the United States population hit the 300 million mark recently. What many Americans may not know, or even be able to estimate, is how many of our citizens were living with a Quiggle when the day arrived. No, a Quiggle is not a fabulous new designer dog! In fact, since you had an interest or at least some curiosity which led you to read this column, there's a good chance that you may unknowingly own a Quiggle and thus are a member of America's largest minority. To most people's surprise our largest minority is not comprised of Hispanic or African Americans, but rather American... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7249-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7249_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:12:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/4182/13321/effect-health</link><title>Depression has the Largest Effect on Worsening Health</title><description>... A report published in the prestigious medical journal the Lancet , indicates that depression is more disabling than some chronic diseases. The authors of the study state that depression produces the greatest decrement in health compared with angina, arthritis, asthma and diabetes. Dr Moussavi and his team say that despite the evidence on the relationship between poor health and depression, there remains a lack of parity between mental health, physical disorders and access to treatment.   Very few studies have explored the effects of depression on overall health status and, until now, compared depression directly with other chronic diseases. Yet depression is a well known and commonly associated feature of many chronic diseases and conditions. When two or more diseases or conditions co-exist (in this case depression plus a chronic physical disease) the term ‘comorbidity’ is used. The comorbidity of depression with chronic physical diseases is well documented. V... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7249-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7249_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:12:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/727598/161144/largest-metropolitan</link><title>Index Identifies Health, Fitness Levels in Largest U.S. Metropolitan Areas</title><description>... Live in a major U.S. city? So how active and healthy is the population in your metropolitan area? ... A new report chronicling the American College of Sports Medicine’s American Fitness Index has just been released which analyses the health and fitness status of the 50 largest metropolitan areas in the United States. The fitness index started six years ago as a way to evaluate the health and fitness levels of America’s 50 largest metropolitan areas. The program provides reliable measures of health and community fitness to community leaders so they can understand the various influences on citizens’ physical activity and eating choices. Thus the leaders can develop strategies to encourage physical activity and mobilize the community to take part in best practices. The program also serves as a resource on research, education and application of sports medicine and exercise to the community. It also tries to help communities partner with existing organizations and other partn... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7249-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7249_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:12:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/30754/38750/top-networks</link><title>what are the top 5 schiz sights with the largest networks</title><description>... recently iv been relativly dissapointed at the lack of schiz sights there are. im mean u can find the defention of schiz everywere.....great, i think i have that down by now. but i find it hard to find sights like this. or schiz.com, and that sight is down like 50% of the time due to the crappy server they use supposedly. anyways i just want a reliable source of up to date schiz info or articles. is that to much to ask? hehe maby... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7249-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7249_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:13:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/369014/91079</link><title>what is the largest amount of these meds possible to take</title><description>... what is the most mg. you could take of ambien or morphin sulf you could take before it became fatal? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7249-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7249_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:13:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/434848/61986</link><title>can a dr that has your medical records talk bad about you to the new dr he is sending records to</title><description>... if a dr no longer wants to treat you and sends the new dr your medical records and suggest to the new dr not to treat me is that allowed ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7249-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7249_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:13:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/210222/146673</link><title>which records is a doctor allowed to release? Can primary care provider release records from specialists that do not originate in his office?</title><description>... I have a patient who has left the practice and wants all the records including notes and lab results from specialist. I understood that records can only be sent if they originate in this office. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>