<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7250">collagen vascular disease</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:14:07" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7250-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7250_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:14:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/161018/72741</link><title>How is collagenous vascular disease different than the build up inside the vascular system?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7250-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7250_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:14:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001223.html</link><title>Collagen vascular disease overview</title><description>... Definition Collagen vascular disease occurs when problems with the immune system affect collagen. Collagen is a tough, fiber-like protein that makes up 30% of body protein. It contributes to the structure of tendons, bones, and connective tissues. In a class of diseases known as autoimmune disorders , the body's immune system attacks its own tissues. Some of these diseases have similarities, including arthritis and inflammation of arteries in the tissues that connect joints and other tissues. These diseases are known as collagen vascular diseases. Collagen vascular diseases include: Ankylosing spondylitis Dermatomyositis Polyarteritis nodosa Psoriatic arthritis Rheumatoid arthritis Scleroderma Systemic lupus erythematosus Causes, incidence, and risk factors ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7250-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7250_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:14:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/question/510575/48148</link><title>what is the collagen vascular disease that causes asthma?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7250-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7250_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:15:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001226.html</link><title>Rheumatoid-collagen disease overview</title><description>... Definition ... ... Rheumatoid-collagen disease is any disorder affecting the connective tissue, with "rheumatic" symptoms including muscle stiffness, soreness and pain in the joints and associated structures. ... ... Causes, incidence, and risk factors ... ... ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7250-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7250_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:15:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/640702/120811</link><title>Hospital said I have "ulcerative colitis" MD who did colonoscopy said "No, it's collagenous colitis" Is this type a disease? Curable? I have an occasional "flare" &amp; often use padded underwear.</title><description>... I was 6 days on IVs - 24/7. I saw discharge paper which said "ulcerative colitis". The doctor said "No, it's collagenous colitis" She said colon was extremely inflamed &amp; that's why she sent me to the hospital. BMs were many...25 or more for a few days. Now I use Entocort or a powder (sulpha something) which controls diarrhea 95% of the time. Is collagenous colitis an incurable disease? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7250-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7250_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:16:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/vascular-disease-treatment.html-42582-5.html</link><title>Maintaining Vascular Health</title><description>... Baby Boomers need to understand how to maintain a healthy vascular system as they become seniors. By 2015, the U.S. Census reports an expected 87 million people aged 55 and older, up from 67 million in 2005. Since vascular disease primarily affects seniors, the number of vascular disease cases is expected to rise dramatically. The vascular system is made up of arteries and veins that carry oxygen-rich blood throughout the body to the vital organs, the brains, and the legs. As we age, our arteries tend to thicken with a buildup of plaque and cholesterol, get stiffer, and narrow. When blood flow is restricted, vascular disease like carotid artery disease can lead to stroke; peripheral artery disease can lead to problems walking and in the most advanced cases, foot ulcers, gangrene, and possible amputation; and abdominal aortic aneuryism can result in death if not treated early. These five practices are not new, but with so many people reaching senior status, it is important to reme... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7250-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7250_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:16:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/</link><title>Peripheral Vascular Disease</title><description>... Call your doctor if you consistently suffer from cramps, aching, ... numbness or disproportionate fatigue in your leg muscles or ... buttocks when you exercise. Call immediately if you have these ... symptoms at rest or when any part of your leg or foot suddenly ... turns numb, cold, pale or a bluish color. ... Prognosis ... In most people with peripheral vascular disease, leg symptoms ... remain stable. About 10% to15 % of patients improve, and about 15% ... to 20% get worse. Prognosis is better for people who are able to ... remain tobacco-free, stay on a healthy diet, keep their blood ... cholesterol under control, and exercise regularly. ... Additional Info ... ... National Heart, Lung and Blood Institute (NHLBI) P.O. Box ... http://www.nhlbi.nih.gov/ ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7250-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7250_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:16:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/</link><title>Peripheral Vascular Disease</title><description>... In peripheral vascular disease, not enough blood flows to the ... legs. It usually is caused by fatty deposits (called plaques) that ... build up along the walls of blood vessels. This buildup shrinks the ... size of the passageway and reduces the amount of blood that can ... flow through. Doctors call this atherosclerosis. The most common ... symptom is intermittent claudication, a cramping in the legs or ... buttocks when you exercise that goes away when you rest. The risk ... factors for getting peripheral vascular disease are the same as the ... risk factors for coronary heart disease, and include: ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7250-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7250_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:17:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/</link><title>Peripheral Vascular Disease</title><description>... You can help to prevent peripheral vascular disease by modifying ... your risk factors: ... ... ... Treatment ... Treatment for peripheral vascular disease includes: ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7250-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7250_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:17:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/encyclopedia/408/573.html</link><title>Peripheral Vascular Disease</title><description>... Peripheral Vascular Disease usually refers to atherosclerosis (development of fatty deposits that narrow arteries) in the peripheral arteries (often the legs). Mention blocked arteries and most people think of the heart. But blockages can affect other areas of the body as well - and certain types of leg or foot pain can be an important warning sign of potentially serious circulatory problems. When leg pain occurs with exercise and is relieved promptly by rest, chances are that blockage has invaded the vessels of the legs or feet. Doctors call this condition lower-extremity peripheral vascular disease. Leg pain severe enough to prevent a person from working, walking the golf course, or even crossing the street may be a symptom of advanced peripheral vascular disease, also known as atherosclerosis of the extremities. Late in life, fatty, fibrous plaques are likely to narrow the body's large and medium-sized arteries, impeding the flow of blood. As the plaques grow larger, the arteries ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>