<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7259">radish root</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:47:11" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7259-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7259_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:47:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/encyclopedia/408/749.html</link><title>Root Canal Therapy</title><description>... Root canal therapy consists of removal of the pulp tissue contained within the tubular root canals, and sealing them with an inert material to eliminate bacterial infection. Degeneration of the dental nerve is the primary reason for root canal treatment. It is most frequently caused by untreated bacterial decay that destroys the enamel and dentin and infects the pulp tissue. A sharp blow to the tooth can also precipitate nerve failure, sometimes years after the initial trauma. Nerves can degenerate long after teeth have been filled or capped, especially if the original decay was deep. Infection in a deep periodontal (pyorrhea) pocket may extend to the nerve, requiring a combination of endodontic and periodontic therapy to save the tooth. Nerve degeneration might also be due to poor dental treatment. Root canal therapy is sometimes necessary to eliminate hypersensitivity due to extreme attrition that has worn away one-third to one-half of the tooth's crown. For example, if a front toot... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7259-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7259_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:47:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/question/111583/102174</link><title>Where can I get Maca root from?</title><description>... I've read alot about Maca root and wondering where I can get in from? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7259-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7259_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:47:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/question/58849/53822</link><title>Cherry bark and Ginger root tea</title><description>... Why does Cherry Bark tea and Ginger root tea work for Asthma and COPS.  Does any of the drugs you recommend have anything with these properties in them. Do you recommend any Teas or have other advise for these disorders other then drugs. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7259-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7259_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:48:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/c/question/213913/114977</link><title>can i get a root canal while taking boniva</title><description>... Is it ok to get a root canal while getting a boniva shot every 3 months? After reading several bad comments on the drug, I want to stop. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7259-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7259_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:48:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/207878/82755</link><title>Painful root canal in pregnancy. What does baby feel?</title><description>... I just had a painful root canal in 34nd week of pregnancy. I would like to know what the baby experiences when I'm in excruciating pain. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7259-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7259_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:49:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/713921/110640</link><title>Marshmallow root and RA</title><description>... Has any body used a product called Intestinew wich contains many herbs such as marshmallow root and others to cure the leaky gut wich is responsible of RA? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7259-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7259_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:49:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/007275.html</link><title>Root canal overview</title><description>... Definition ... ... A root canal is a dental procedure to remove dead or dying nerve tissue and bacteria from inside a tooth. ... ... Alternative Names ... ... ... Endodontic therapy ... ... ... Description ... ... A dentist will use a needle to place numbing medicine (anesthetic) around the bad tooth. You may feel a slight prick when the needle is being inserted. ... Next, your dentist uses a tiny drill to remove the top part of your tooth and expose the pulp. Pulp is made up of nerves, blood vessels, and connective tissue. It is found inside the tooth and runs to the jaw bone. Pulp supplies blood to a tooth and allows you to feel sensations such as temperature. ... The infected pulp is removed with special tools called files. The canals (tiny pathways inside the tooth) are cleaned. Medicines may be placed into the area to make sure all the germs are gone and prevent further infection. ... The cleaned tooth area is sealed with a soft, temporary material. Once the tooth is filled, a permanent crown may ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7259-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7259_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:49:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/313334/138606</link><title>Maca Root and Effexor interaction?</title><description>... I'm thinking of trying the Maca root powder form (in my morning smoothie), but I was wondering if there would be a negative drug interaction since I'm on Effexor XR (37.5mg, once/day), and it's supposed to affect your mood and energy.  Has anyone tried this, or have any advice or suggestions?  Thanks! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7259-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7259_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:50:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/387699/116763</link><title>What Is Yellow Root Tea Good For</title><description>... Are there specific ailments that can be treated with yellow root tea?  What are some of the benefits of drinking the tea? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7259-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7259_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:50:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/389508/128450</link><title>what are the effects of root-meals on insulin levels of diabetic and non-diabetic conditions?</title><description>... root-meals like cassava,coco-yam,yam,potato.Their effects on insulin both in diabetic and non-diabetic conditions. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>