<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7260">iowa girls high school basketball</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:51:10" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7260-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7260_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:51:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/girls-school-basketball-2502</link><title>I'm the coach for a girls' high school basketball.</title><description>... I'm the coach for a girls' high school basketball. As we get ready for the next season, what's the latest on these ACL injuries girls seem susceptible to? Just as you already know, it's clear that knee injuries are problematic for female athletes. In particular, anterior cruciate ligament (ACL) tears are common. Rehab and recovery from such an injury can put a player on the bench for an entire season. Scientists at human movement and biomechanic research laboratories continue to study this problem. They start with cadavers (knees preserved after death for study) and examine the effect of load, torque, and alignment on movement of the knee. Then they study the spring , laxity , and stiffness qualities of human male versus female knees under different conditions. They know that there are differences in alignment. These are important factors. But they also know that there's a sex-difference in how stiff the joint is. This kind of stiffness isn't what we refer to as we get older. This quality... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7260-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7260_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:51:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/assistant-coach-basketball-2321</link><title>I am the assistant coach for our girls' high school basketball team.</title><description>... I am the assistant coach for our girls' high school basketball team. Our girls seem to have a high rate of ACL tears. My job is to find out if this is related to their menstrual cycle and come up with a policy for play based on this variable. What's the latest on this topic? Clearly, females have a higher incidence of anterior cruciate ligament (ACL) tears. The reasons for this may be multifactorial and not just one cause. For example, differences in male versus female anatomy may be a big part of the problem. The width of the pelvis and the angle at the knee are just a couple things to consider. Training techniques and training schedules may also be a factor. As a coach, you may have more to say about this variable than things you can't change like body type or hormone levels. Monthly fluctuations of hormones can affect ligaments. Exactly how the collagen fibers are affected hasn't been shown yet. It's possible the fibers relax more during certain times of the month, making them more vu... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7260-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7260_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:52:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/girls-basketball-school-2521</link><title>I am on the girls' basketball team for my high school.</title><description>... I am on the girls' basketball team for my high school. Last week, I worked out at the gym and then played a pick-up game on the court. An hour into play, I landed a jump and tore my ACL. I thought my work-out routine would protect me. What happened? Why didn't it work? Fatigue may be a factor -- at least according to several studies on the effect of fatigue on the knee. It appears that fatigue leads to a decreased sense of joint position called proprioception . The number of fibers that get activated is reduced with fatigue, too. When jumping, cutting, pivoting, and shifting weight suddenly through the foot and leg, the knee can get injured. Adding fatigue as a factor increases the risk of injury. With fatigue comes decreased neuromuscular control and a decreased ability to control movements. Landing forces can exceed the muscular control needed to slow the movement and avoid injury. This is just one of many possible explanations. Limited information on the status of the muscles and their... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7260-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7260_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:52:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/school-basketball-sponsor-2527</link><title>I live in a small town where I am both the high school basketball coach and the sponsor for the modern dance club.</title><description>... I live in a small town where I am both the high school basketball coach and the sponsor for the modern dance club. I notice the girls on the basketball team seem far more prone to knee injuries (especially ACL tears). The dancers rarely have ACL injuries and their movements are far more complex than the players. What's the take home message here? Studies show that athletes involved in noncontact jumping sports have the highest rate of anterior cruciate ligament (ACL) injuries. The main mechanism of injury is called plant-and-cut maneuvers. There is too much load on the knee with the foot planted on the ground while the player changes direction quickly. Dancers do have far fewer ACL injuries compared to athletes involved in jumping activities. The difference may be because dancers perform many more jumps in a daily 90-minute technique class compared to a 90-work-out on the basketball court. The rigorous dance training may be enough to prevent ACL injuries. This is true even though load o... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7260-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7260_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:52:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/teacher-school-volleyball-2024</link><title>I'm a teacher at the high school level with a chance to coach girl's volleyball.</title><description>... I'm a teacher at the high school level with a chance to coach girl's volleyball. I've heard that knee injuries are a big problem right now in girl's athletics. I don't remember that when I played. Just how common is this? Not all girls' sports are affected equally by knee injuries. Any activity with pivoting and jumping puts girls at increased risk for injury. This is especially true for basketball, soccer, and volleyball. Before adolescence, girls and boys have an equal amount of ligament sprains. Girls have a higher rate right after a growth spurt. Middle school and high school aged female athletes have four to six times the number of anterior cruciate ligament (ACL) injuries compared to boys of the same age. Untrained girls have the highest rates of ACL trauma. Since increases in growth can't be stopped, researchers say our focus should be on training. As you head into your new coaching position, learn all you can about this key feature in preventing knee injuries. Reference: Timothy E.... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7260-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7260_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:52:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/high-basketball-volleyball-1844</link><title>I'm a high school basketball and volleyball player.</title><description>... I'm a high school basketball and volleyball player. I go to training camps each summer. I always wonder if I'm making any improvements. Is there any way to show changes I'm making from my many hours of practice? Videotaping is an ideal tool to use as proof of "before" and "after" so-to-speak. During the school year or before heading off to camp, have a friend or family member videotape your form and skills as you play against an opposing team. Watch the video and choose one or two areas you'd like to work on during training. When you come back from camp, revideo yourself and compare the two. Use the slow motion feature available on most video cameras to study angles, joint motion, hand and foot position, or any other feature. You may even want to videotape the experts at the camps you attend (with their permission). This would give you a chance to review the movements throughout your training season. Try to set up two TV screens. You can watch yourself perform an action such as a jump, s... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7260-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7260_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:53:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/34071/46674/basketball</link><title>Weightlifting for girls basketball athletes.</title><description>... So my weightlifting program at school is designed with pushing your muscles to the limit. (Bigger Faster Stronger) As an exam we do a thing called survivor which is where you do three core lifts (bench, clean, and squat) for 9 minutes. You get as many reps as you can and you have quite a bit of weight on. I have recently heard from my orthopedic surgeon that that causes you to bulk up, and it will mess up your shot. He asked me how many reps we do for a regular routine and I said 3 sets of 5 reps. He couldnt believe that as a girl I was lifting like that escespially when I am in basketball. Does lifting like that really affect my game or shot in basketball? How should I be training? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7260-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7260_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:53:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/athlete-project-injuries-1949</link><title>I am a high school athlete doing a science project on ACL injuries in girls and women.</title><description>... I am a high school athlete doing a science project on ACL injuries in girls and women. So far I've found that females are at greater risk for ACL injury than males. Are they also\rmore likely to reinjure themselves later? Teasing this kind of information out of the literature can be difficult. Other variables must also be considered such as age and level of activity. Treatment of the torn ACL has also changed over the last 20 years, affecting the results for both men and women. In general, more ACL tears are repaired surgically early on. Early ACL repair allows young patients (especially athletes) to return to full activities. Several studies have been done looking at the rate of reinjury in two groups of patients: those who have an ACL repair and those who don't. The consensus at this time is that gender isn't a factor in reinjury. It looks like age is more of a predictive factor. The younger, active patients who don't have ACL repair reinjure the knee later. Meniscus and joint cartilage... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7260-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7260_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:53:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/school-soccer-championship-2506</link><title>Our high school girls' soccer team took the state championship last year.</title><description>... Our high school girls' soccer team took the state championship last year. We'd like to repeat that success this year. But several of our players are on the bench with knee problems. They've been told by the doctor they have patellofemoral pain syndrome. What causes this problem and what can we do to get them back in the game? The patella , or kneecap, can be a source of knee pain when it fails to function properly. Alignment or overuse problems of the patella can produce pain, weakness, and swelling of the knee joint. Several different problems can affect the patella and the groove it slides through over the femur (thigh bone). Patellofemoral pain syndrome (PFPS) is one of these problems. PFPS can affect people of all ages but is most common among young athletes. Physicians in sports medicine clinics report it accounts for up to 10 per cent of all visits. There are several possible reasons why PFPS develops. The first is overloading the patellofemoral joint. Heavy competition in sports ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7260-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7260_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:54:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/7737/march-common</link><title>Basketball, March Madness and Alzheimer's: Finding a Common Language</title><description>... Sometimes you just need to figure out what your loved one who has Alzheimer’s disease likes and then just be present while they do it. For instance, this is the time of year that March Madness of the NCAA men’s basketball finals consumes everyone. Thanks to Mom’s long love affair with basketball, we’ve found that sitting with Mom in the afternoons and over the weekends to watch basketball keeps her attention and gives us an opportunity to spend time with her in a meaningful way. Mom used to play basketball as a girl and then coached girls’ basketball when she worked in a high school. Ever since, she has remained a basketball fan. She used to trek many miles to watch me when I played the sport at the high school and college level, screaming at the top of her lungs to tell me to play defense or to celebrate a basket. In recent years, Mom has enjoyed working with me on making bracket picks for a tournament pool in which we participated. The deal was that Mom would make the picks (since ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>