<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7261">elvish language</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:54:48" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7261-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7261_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:54:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/700591/118425</link><title>how can my granddaughter be evaluated and diagnosed with adhd and language receptive disorder when the trained clinician did not know that English is her second language</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7261-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7261_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:55:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001544sym.html</link><title>Expressive language disorder - developmental symptoms</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Language disorder - expressive ... ... ... Symptoms ... ... ... Below-average vocabulary skills ... Improper use of tenses (past, present, future) ... Problems making complex sentences ... Problems remembering words ... ... ... Signs and tests ... ... Standardized expressive language and nonverbal intellectual tests should be conducted if an expressive language disorder is suspected. Testing for other learning disabilities may also be needed. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7261-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7261_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:55:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001544.html</link><title>Expressive language disorder - developmental overview</title><description>... Definition ... ... Developmental expressive language disorder is a condition in which a child has lower than normal ability in vocabulary, producing complex sentences, and remembering words. However, children with this disorder may have the normal language skills needed to understand verbal or written communication. ... ... Alternative Names ... ... ... Language disorder - expressive ... ... ... Causes, incidence, and risk factors ... ... Approximately 3 - 10% of all school-age children have expressive language disorder. It is a pretty common issue in children. ... The causes of this disorder are not well understood. Damage to the cerebrum of the brain and malnutrition may cause some cases. Genetic factors may also be involved. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7261-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7261_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:55:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001544prv.html</link><title>Expressive language disorder - developmental prevention</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Language disorder - expressive ... ... ... Prevention ... ... Good nutrition during pregnancy and early childhood and prenatal care may help. Other methods of prevention are unknown. ... ... References ... ... Simms MD. Language disorders in children: classification and clinical syndromes. Pediatr Clin North Am . 2007;54(3):437-467. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7261-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7261_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:56:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001544trt.html</link><title>Expressive language disorder - developmental treatment</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Language disorder - expressive ... ... ... Treatment ... ... Language therapy is the best method to treat this type of disorder. The goal of this therapy is to increase the number of phrases a child can use. This is done by using block-building techniques and speech therapy. ... ... Support Groups ... ... ... ... Expectations (prognosis) ... ... How much the child recovers depends on the severity of the disorder. With reversible factors, such as vitamin deficiencies, there may be nearly full recovery. ... Children who do not have any other developmental or motor coordination problems have the best outlook (prognosis). Often, such children have a family history of delays in language milestones, but eventually catch up. ... ... Complications ... ... ... Learning problems ... Low self-esteem ... Social problems ... ... ... Calling your health care provider ... ... If you are concerned about a child's language development, have the child tested. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7261-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7261_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:56:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001545.html</link><title>Mixed receptive-expressive language disorder overview</title><description>... Definition ... ... Language disorder in children refers to problems with either: ... ... Getting their meaning or message across to others (expressive language disorder), or ... Understanding the message coming from others (receptive language disorder) ... ... Some children only have an expressive language disorder. Others have a mixed receptive-expressive language disorder, meaning that they have symptoms of both conditions. ... Children with language disorders are able to produce sounds, and their speech can be understood. ... ... Alternative Names ... ... ... Developmental aphasia; Developmental dysphasia; Delayed language; Specific developmental language disorder; SLI; Communication disorder - language disorder ... ... ... Causes, incidence, and risk factors ... ... For most infants and children, language develops naturally beginning at birth. To develop language, a child must be able to hear, see, understand, and remember. Children must also have the physical ability to form speech. ... Up to 1 out ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7261-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7261_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:56:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001545sym.html</link><title>Mixed receptive-expressive language disorder symptoms</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Developmental aphasia; Developmental dysphasia; Delayed language; Specific developmental language disorder; SLI; Communication disorder - language disorder ... ... ... Symptoms ... ... A child with language disorder may have one or two of the symptoms listed below, or many of the symptoms. Symptoms can range from mild to severe. ... Children with a receptive language disorder have difficulty understanding langugae. They may have: ... ... A hard time understanding what other people have said ... Problems following directions that are spoken to them ... Problems organizing their thoughts ... ... Children with an expressive language disorder have problems using language to express what they are thinking or need. These children may: ... ... Have a hard time putting words together into sentences, or their sentences may be simple and short and the word order may be off ... Have difficulty finding the right words when talking, and often use placeholder words such as "um" ... ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7261-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7261_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:57:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001545trt.html</link><title>Mixed receptive-expressive language disorder treatment</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Developmental aphasia; Developmental dysphasia; Delayed language; Specific developmental language disorder; SLI; Communication disorder - language disorder ... ... ... Treatment ... ... Speech and language therapy is the best approach to treating this type of language disorder. ... Psychological therapy (psychotherapy, counseling, or cognitive behavioral therapy) is also recommended because of the possibility of related emotional or behavioral problems. ... ... Support Groups ... ... ... ... Expectations (prognosis) ... ... The outcome varies based on the cause. Brain injury or other structural problems generally have a poor outcome, in which the child will have long-term problems with language. Other, more reversible causes can be treated effectively. ... Many children who have language problems during the preschool years will also have some language problems or learning difficulty later in childhood. They may also have reading disorders. ... ... Complications ... ... Difficulty u... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7261-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7261_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:57:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/7930/36239/evaluation-disorders</link><title>The evaluation of Speech and Language Disorders</title><description>...   ... Early in the evaluation of a child suspected of a communication disorder, it is necessary to ensure that the child can hear correctly. If the ability to hear is seriously in question in a child, hearing testing with an audiologist could be considered. This may be the only way to identify a subtle deficit in hearing that is causing problems with communication. In addition to hearing deficits, a cleft palate may be the root of a problem with communication. Neurological problems like cerebral palsy, apraxia, and aphasia can also cause problems with speech or language. Mental retardation is also a condition that very commonly results in a problem with communication, and standard tests of intelligence can often be helpful. As ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7261-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7261_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:58:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/dating-256705-5.html</link><title>The Art of Female Body Language</title><description>... How is it that a guy can land an F-14 on a heaving aircraft carrier in the middle of the ocean by watching some dude wave a couple of flags, but still manage to totally screw things up when a hot girl is sending off vibes a mere 10 feet away at a party or local bar? They may not be wearing reflective vests and holding flashlights, but they're trying to get your attention all the same. In other words, they're sending signals! Sure, they're subtle, but at least they're trying. Read on, and you'll understand how to decipher the subtle art of body language -- female body language. The Drifter One minute, the girl you've been staring at is clustered in with her friends, then all of a sudden she steps away from them to order a drink or feed the jukebox quarters -- all by herself . That's probably no coincidence, especially since no woman on earth can even use a restroom unless another female accompanies her. "What she might be trying to do is set herself up in n... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>