<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7263">hospital acquired pneumonia</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:02:35" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7263-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7263_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:02:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/imagepages/17276.html</link><title>Hospital-acquired pneumonia</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7263-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7263_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:02:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/000146.html</link><title>Hospital-acquired pneumonia overview</title><description>... Definition Hospital-acquired pneumonia is an infection of the lungs that occurs during a hospital stay. Alternative Names Nosocomial pneumonia; Ventilator-associated pneumonia; Health-care associated pneumonia Causes, incidence, and risk factors Pneumonia is a very common illness. It is caused by many different germs, and the infection can range in seriousness from mild to life-threatening. Hospital-acquired pneumonia tends to be more serious than other lung infections, because: Patients in the hospital are often sicker and unable to fight off germs. The types of germs present in a hospital are often more dangerous than those encountered in the community. Hospital-acquired pneumonia occurs more often in patients who are using a respirator machine (also called a ventilator) to help them breathe. When pneumonia occurs in a patient who is on a ventilator, it is known as ventilator-associated pneumonia. Risk factors for hospital-acquired pneumonia include: Alcoholism Being on a breathing machine Brea... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7263-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7263_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:03:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/000146trt.html</link><title>Hospital-acquired pneumonia treatment</title><description>... Alternative Names Nosocomial pneumonia; Ventilator-associated pneumonia; Health-care associated pneumonia Treatment Treatment aims to cure the infection with antibiotics. An antibiotic is chosen based on the specific germ found by sputum culture. However, the bacteria cannot always be identified with tests. Antibiotic therapy is given to fight the most common bacteria that infect hospitalized patients, taking into account the most common bacteria in each hospital -- Staphylococcus aureus and gram-negative bacteria. Supportive treatment includes: Oxygen Lung treatments to loosen and remove thick mucus from the lungs Support Groups Expectations (prognosis) Most patients respond to treatment and improve within 2 weeks. However, hospital-acquired pneumonia can be very severe and sometimes life-threatening. Patients who also have many other serious conditions do not do as well. Complications Elderly or very weak patients who do not respond to treatment may die from acute respiratory failure caused by ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7263-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7263_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:03:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/000146prv.html</link><title>Hospital-acquired pneumonia prevention</title><description>... Alternative Names Nosocomial pneumonia; Ventilator-associated pneumonia; Health-care associated pneumonia Prevention Ongoing prevention programs to limit hospital-acquired infections are in place at most institutions. References American Thoracic Society. Guidelines for the management of adults with hospital-acquired, ventilator-associated, and healthcare-associated pneumonia. Am J Respir Crit Care Med . 2005 Feb 15;171(4):388-416. Craven DE, Chroneou A. Nosocomial pneumonia. In: Mandell GL, Bennett JE, Dolin R, eds. Principles and Practice of Infectious Diseases . 7th ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Elsevier Churchill Livingstone; 2009:chap 303. Chastre J, Luyt CE. Ventilator-associated pneumonia. In: Mason RJ, Broaddus VC, Martin TR, et al. Murray &amp; Nadel's Textbook of Respiratory Medicine . 5th ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Saunders Elsevier; 2010:chap 33. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7263-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7263_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:04:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/000146sym.html</link><title>Hospital-acquired pneumonia symptoms</title><description>... Alternative Names Nosocomial pneumonia; Ventilator-associated pneumonia; Health-care associated pneumonia Symptoms Cough that may produce mucus-like, greenish, or pus-like phlegm (sputum) Chills Easy fatigue Excessive sweating (rare) Fever General discomfort, uneasiness, or ill feeling ( malaise ) Headache Joint stiffness and pain (rare) Loss of appetite Muscle stiffness (rare) Nausea and vomiting Sharp or stabbing chest pain that gets worse with deep breathing or coughing Shortness of breath Signs and tests A physical examination shows: Crackles or decreased breath sounds when listening to the chest with a stethoscope Decreased oxygen Respiratory distress Tests performed may include: Arterial blood gases Blood cultures Chest x-ray or CT scan Complete blood count ( CBC ) Sputum culture Sputum gram stain ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7263-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7263_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:04:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/968433/159157/au</link><title>Pneumonia and Autoimmune Issues</title><description>...   ... Little did I know I would have real time, up close and personal facts to report to you on the subject. You may or may not know, depending on the length of time you have been treated for RA, that the main villain in RA is your immune system. It is mistaking your synovial linings around your joints as an enemy of your body. As it is programmed to do, your immune system attacks this lining and as it slowly erodes the lining you also begin to lose cartilage, and finally bone. (this is a VERY simplified explanation) There are many different parts of the immune system that may be at fault with RA, T cells, B cells, TNF, IL-6 and IL-1 are only a few.... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7263-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7263_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:04:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/copd/c/question/882378/96515</link><title>Is community acquired pneumonia contagious?</title><description>... Is community acquired pneumonia contagious? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7263-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7263_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:05:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/000145.html</link><title>Pneumonia overview</title><description>... Definition ... ... Pneumonia is a respiratory condition in which there is infection of the lung. ... Community-acquired pneumonia refers to pneumonia in people who have not recently been in the hospital or another health care facility (nursing home, rehabilitation facility). ... See also: Hospital-acquired pneumonia ... ... Alternative Names ... ... ... Bronchopneumonia; Community-acquired pneumonia ... ... ... Causes, incidence, and risk factors ... ... Pneumonia is a common illness that affects millions of people each year in the United States. Germs called bacteria, viruses, and fungi may cause pneumonia. ... Ways you can get pneumonia include: ... ... Bacteria and viruses living in your nose, sinuses, or mouth may spread to your lungs. ... You may breathe some of these germs directly into your lungs. ... You breathe in (inhale) food, liquids, vomit, or secretions from the mouth into your lungs ( aspiration pneumonia ) ... ... Pneumonia caused by bacteria tends to be the most serious. In adults, bacteria ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7263-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7263_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:05:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/000145trt.html</link><title>Pneumonia treatment</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Bronchopneumonia; Community-acquired pneumonia ... ... ... Treatment ... ... Your doctor must first decide whether you need to be in the hospital. If you are treated in the hospital, you will receive fluids and antibiotics in your veins, oxygen therapy, and possibly breathing treatments. It is very important that your antibiotics are started very soon after you are admitted. ... You are more likely to be admitted to the hospital if you: ... ... Have another serious medical problem ... Have severe symptoms ... Are unable to care for yourself at home, or are unable to eat or drink ... Are older than 65 or a young child ... Have been taking antibiotics at home and are not getting better ... ... However, many people can be treated at home. If bacteria are causing the pneumonia, the doctor will try to cure the infection with antibiotics. It may be hard for your health care provider to know whether you have a viral or bacterial pneumonia, so you may receive antibiotics. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7263-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7263_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:05:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/erectile-dysfunction/tepper-2177-143.html</link><title>Add an Acquired Disability</title><description>... What happens if we lose our ability to attain or maintain an ... erection, or to ejaculate as a result of an acquired disability? ... What happens if we lose sensation in our genitals, if we use a ... catheter, or if we have physical limitations? Whether resulting ... from Crohn's disease, SCI, or any other acquired disability or ... chronic illness, a medical impairment inevitably impacts male ... sexuality. Issues such as dependency, diminished body image, ... impaired sexual function, and loss of earning potential may ... threaten a man's gender identity or core sense of himself as a man ... and his ability to carry out established gender roles. ... Men arrive at rehabilitation with all the baggage society, ... culture, the media, parents, friends, and religion packed for us. ... We were socialized to be strong and self-reliant, successful, ... manly, and sexual performers. We learned the same myths and fantasy ... model of sex as our peers. What happens when we are faced with the ... loss of strength and self-rel... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>