<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7265">grassland plants</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:10:01" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7265-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7265_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:10:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/c/question/708116/150739</link><title>Does Almond Milk contain any plant sterols? If so, how much does it contain? (That is, 8 oz = X Mg of plant sterol).</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7265-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7265_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:10:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/common/images/image.html</link><title>herbs, dill, healthy food, plant, hanging plant, promo</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7265-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7265_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:10:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/reviews-434083-5.html</link><title>Planting Seeds Lavender Set: Aromatherapy for Migraines and Headaches</title><description>... Although fragrances can be a Migraine trigger for some Migraineurs, lavender aromatherapy is often recommended for Migraine. Lavender is soothing and relaxing, and for some Migraineurs, that's a big help while we wait for our medications to work and the Migraine to pass. Lavender has been cherished for centuries for its potent essential oil, which has soothing properties to ease tension, insomnia, stress, and headaches. Lavender oil is also known for its antibacterial and anti-inflammatory properties as well as its ability to balance dry or oily skin, making it excellent for all skin types. This Planting Seeds gift set contains three items: a four-ounce lavender aromatherapy candle, a four-ounce oatmeal lavender soap, and a packet of lavender seeds (pot not included). I tried both the soap and candle during a Migraine attack. The light scent was enough to enjoy, but not too heavy. It was apparent to me that both products are made with quality, natural aromatherapy ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7265-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7265_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:11:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002841.html</link><title>Fertilizers and household plant foods overview</title><description>... Definition ... ... Plant fertilizers and household plant foods are substances used to improve plant growth. Plant fertilizer and household plant food poisoning can occur if someone swallows these substances. ... Plant fertilizers are mildly poisonous if swallowed in small doses. Larger doses can be harmful to children. Touching large quantities of plant fertilizers may cause severe burns. ... This is for information only and not for use in the treatment or management of an actual poison exposure. If you have an exposure, you should call your local emergency number (such as 911) or the National Poison Control Center at 1-800-222-1222. ... ... Alternative Names ... ... ... Household plant food poisoning; Plant food - household - poisoning ... ... ... Poisonous Ingredient ... ... ... Nitrates ... Nitrites ... ... ... Where Found ... ... ... Various fertilizers ... ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7265-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7265_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:11:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002841sym.html</link><title>Fertilizers and household plant foods symptoms</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Household plant food poisoning; Plant food - household - poisoning ... ... ... Symptoms ... ... ... Blue-colored fingernails, lips, or palms of the hand ... Burning skin ... Burning of the throat, nose, and eyes ... Dizziness ... Fainting ... Itchy skin ... ... Low blood pressure ... ... ... Seizures ... ... Shortness of breath ... Skin redness ... Stomach pain ... Stomach upset ... ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7265-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7265_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:11:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002841trt.html</link><title>Fertilizers and household plant foods treatment</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Household plant food poisoning; Plant food - household - poisoning ... ... ... Home Treatment ... ... Seek immediate medical help. Do NOT make a person throw up unless told to do so by Poison Control or a health care professional. ... If the chemical is on the skin or in the eyes, flush with lots of water for at least 15 minutes. ... If the chemical was swallowed, immediately give the person water or milk, unless instructed otherwise by a health care provider. Do NOT give water or milk if the patient is having symptoms (such as vomiting, convulsions, or a decreased level of alertness) that make it hard to swallow. ... If the person breathed in the poison, immediately move him or her to fresh air. ... ... Before Calling Emergency ... ... Determine the following information: ... ... Patient's age, weight, and condition ... Name of the product (ingredients and strengths, if known) ... Time it was swallowed ... Amount swallowed ... ... ... Poison Control, or a local emergency numbe... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7265-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7265_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:12:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/98427/aromatherapy-review</link><title>Planting Seeds Aromatherapy Set: Migraine Product Review</title><description>... ... Lavender has been cherished for centuries for its potent essential oil, which has soothing properties to ease tension, insomnia, stress, and headaches. Lavender oil is also known for its antibacterial and anti-inflammatory properties as well as its ability to balance dry or oily skin, making it excellent for all skin types. ... ... This Planting Seeds gift set contains three items: ... ... a four-ounce lavender aromatherapy candle, ... a four-ounce oatmeal lavender soap, and ... a packet of lavender seeds (pot not included). ... ... I tried both the soap and candle during a Migraine attack... ... ... Continue reading this product review: Planting Seeds Lavender Set . ... ... Live well, ... ... ... ... ... ... Follow me on     or  ... ...   &amp;n... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7265-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7265_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:12:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/</link><title>Seeds of Greatness: Plant Small Changes to Grow Positive Results</title><description>... This time of year, we plant seeds so wonderful things will grow. It's the same with improving your lifestyle. Take a few small tips from below, plant them into your day, and grow great things such as better health, improved fitness, and a sunnier outlook! Rev Up With Breakfast When you eat breakfast, you fire up your metabolism after its rest from food the night before. Don't skip this important meal, even when you're on the go. Try This: Grab a nutritious shake, such as Ensure® High Protein, and a piece of fruit. With this breakfast, your metabolism will kick in and begin burning calories as it should. Take Small Bites — of Exercise Sometimes it's challenging to fit a workout into your day. Consider doing 10-minute chunks of exercise three times a day. Studies show it helps your heart as much as a straight 30-minute session. Try This: Walk in one direction for five minutes, then turn around and walk back the other way. You've just taken a 10-minute walk! Ease ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7265-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7265_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:12:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/prostate/c/question/251556/47617</link><title>why a cathedar for so long after seeds are planted</title><description>... why would a man have to wear a cathedar for so many month after having the seeds planted ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7265-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7265_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:13:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/question/879541/62576</link><title>veganism on just plants.</title><description>... how can a vegan like myself get all my minerals and vitamins from just plants ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>