<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7274">detroit riot</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:41:26" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7274-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7274_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:41:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/870242/145795</link><title>Hello My name is Kimara from Detroit Michigan my question Can men have multiple orgasms ? And Does sperm fluid still produce after one orgasm?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7274-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7274_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:41:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/996414/165274/liberial-write-detroit</link><title>need to fid a liberial Dr. to write script for 90 in warren, mi. detroit area</title><description>... As a painter for 24 yrs. and a back with 5 bad discs from arthrid. and old dr. past on. having had time finding dr. willing to write one now.Can someone help me find easygoing new one to do this. Thank-you ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7274-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7274_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:42:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/139160/154978</link><title>I Have a Prescription for Oxycodone 30 mg and I live in the Detroit,Mich area but I cannot find a pharmacy that has them ,doe anyone know the manufactures phone number (maybe They know where )?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7274-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7274_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:42:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/642852/88638</link><title>Closed head injury umeployed type 11diabetic looking for free insulin help in Detroit.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7274-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7274_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:42:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/166803/97096</link><title>Anyone in Detroit(MI) go to Dr Yahia??</title><description>... I am having a terrible time with this Dr. and wondered if anyone else might be too.  I cannot change because of the insurance.  I am thinking about filing a complaint with the state.   Anyone???? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7274-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7274_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:43:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/11175/68921/disabilities-act</link><title>Working with Migraines: Rights under the Americans with Disabilities Act</title><description>...   ... *** This sharepost is legal education, not legal advice. No attorney-client relationship is created. *** ...   ... ... ... The ADA was passed in 1990 to prevent discrimination against disabled persons in employment, transportation, and public accommodation.  I will only be discussing the employment aspe... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7274-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7274_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:43:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/10092/49770/interviews</link><title>Miss A Interviews Cathy Alter, Author of "Up For Renewal"</title><description>...   ... I met Cathy Alter in Georgetown a few months ago, and she is a riot! We really hit it off, but Cathy and I are very different. We're about the same age, but she strikes me more as an artsy intellectual chick who spent the 1980's following the Grateful Dead than a blonde girly girl like me who read Seventeen magazine religiously while listening to the Go Go's at the Country Club pool. I point this out because she doesn't seem like the type of woman who would look to women's magazines for advice--she's too cerebral. Well, several years ago Cathy Alter found herself divorced with all sorts of drama in her life when she decided she needed help. She decided to commit to reading about a dozen women's magazines for a year in hopes of getting her life back on track, and landing a good man. She did just that, and the whole story is told in her book Up For Renewal: What Magazines Taught Me About Love, Sex, and Starting Over. You wi... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7274-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7274_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:44:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/94790/18037/day-neurologist</link><title>My Day At The Neurologist</title><description>... Well my day went pretty well. I was a little nervous about meeting a new doctor but he was a riot! He was so funny and comical he set me at ease!!!! When he was walking me out he goes "walk this way" and started walking like a penguin ala Marx Brothers LOL. He was a hoot! He said the problems with my eyes weren't bothered by topamax, and he'd seen it help a lot of people. I go back to the eye doctor right after new years, so they will monitor my eyes very closely to make sure the meds don't hurt my eyes. He also gave me prednisone for a few days, he said he wants to break the cycle that my migraines have gotten into. Thinks it may be the midrin making it worse. He said the prednisone will help better than anything else till the topamax kicks in. I also got fiorcet, he wants me to try that instead of the midrin for bad ones. He said if I get a really bad one like last weekend, to call the office and they will give me some sort of "cocktail". LOL He said ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7274-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7274_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:44:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/71469/22223/good-week-job</link><title>A Good Week &amp; New Job</title><description>...                                                                                                  Thurs. 3-20-08   Hi everyone,      My new job that I started this past Monday is going very well, our trainer is a real riot and he's a really good trainer.  Our trainer has ADHD and a couple other people in my training class have ADD as well.  On our first day of class our trainer told us he had ADHD and that he would be the first one to admitt and he admitts it to ever o... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7274-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7274_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:44:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/question/430689/49685</link><title>What are the best exercises for putting on weight with out gainning to much muscle mass?</title><description>... I'm also a sprinter so i do alot of endurance exercises.Is there any percific exercises I should do that will help me put on weight but not effect my sprinting. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>