<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7293">basil recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:53:05" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7293-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7293_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:53:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/reviews-294584-5.html</link><title>Recipe: Veal Chops with Lemon-Basil Butter</title><description>... Veal Chops with Lemon-Basil Butter Serves 2 This simple dish has a light, lemony flavor that enhances the taste of the veal. 2 tablespoons butter, at room temperature 1 tablespoon finely chopped fresh basil or 1 teaspoon dried, crumbled 1/2 teaspoon finely grated lemon rind 1 tablespoon fresh lemon juice 2 1-inch-thick veal loin chops Preheat the broiler. Combine the butter, basil, lemon rind, and lemon juice in a small bowl. Hold each chop on its edge, fat side up. With a small, sharp knife, cut through the fat and halfway through the chop to create a small pocket. Stuff some of the butter mixture into each chop, then spread the remaining butter mixture on both sides of the chops. Place the chops on a broiler pan and broil about 4 inches from the heat, turning once, for 5 to 6 minutes per side, or until browned and tender. With a fork, pierce the chop, checking often for doneness; overcooking will toughen the veal. Serve immediately. Copyright © 2000 David R. Mar... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7293-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7293_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:53:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-cancer/c/question/580099/156374</link><title>I had a Basile cell removed over 2 weeks ago, it was just under my left eye tear duct &amp; next to my noise. I am still healing but it doesn't look as bad as it did a on day 10,</title><description>... I still have stitches that have not disolved. After reading many of these messages I am scared to death now to have the MOHS procedure &amp; reconstruction surgery.I didn't take the time to discuss other options with the eye surgeon. He probably doesn't want me to know the whole story so I won't back out of it. Oct 31 I have the Mohs &amp; then reconstruction. He told me I would be out of work 1 week for the upcoming procedures. I explained to him I have short &amp; long term disability insurance I have paid for years &amp; didn't use it as well as weeks of Paid time off saved.  He then said 2 wks I could be out. I also work in a hospital, non clinical but do see patients often. I don't want to go to work looking like a monster. The pictures also scar me. What other options are there since it is close to eye lids, &amp; maybe involves the lids? I am already on anti depressents &amp; anxiety meds due to a house fire &amp; other pit falls. I am worried how this will effect me menta... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7293-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7293_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:53:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-cancer/c/question/389926/126771</link><title>My husband is using Aldara to treat a small basil on the bottom of his eyelid. Some has slipped into his eye causing much discomfort. Is this dangerous. What should he do?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7293-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7293_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:54:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-cancer/c/question/213871/80229</link><title>Is basil cell cancer?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7293-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7293_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:54:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-cancer/c/question/226270/53365</link><title>line in neck thats itchy and below previous basil cell surgery</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7293-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7293_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:54:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-cancer/c/question/907792/124027</link><title>hello, i am 35 and have been recently diagnosed with basil cell carcinoma on my right upper arm.</title><description>... its about the size of a half dollar. i am having mohs surgery to remove it in 4 days. about how long does it take to heal, and am i going to be able to use my arm at all? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7293-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7293_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:55:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-cancer/c/question/516479/113436</link><title>basil cancer</title><description>... i have bcc,i have the medicine fluoruracil cream 5%,i lost the dosings directions,my bcc is on my nose,its about 3mm big.how much should i use a day plus for how long. my email is slackerbob3@yahoo.com. thanks.... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7293-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7293_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:55:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-cancer/c/question/434042/130438</link><title>Can an xray or scan of the basil cell area in question be done before surgery being done?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7293-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7293_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:56:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/157516/manhattan-recipe</link><title>Healthy Slow-Cooked Manhattan Clam Chowder Recipe (Paleo/Primal)</title><description>... The view from my window as I write this sharepost shows a dank and dismal day. I stepped outside earlier and the cold chilled me through to the bone. Yes, this is a good day to make a pot of soup. ...   ... My family is really good at making soup. My mother makes great soup. My father makes great soup. My brother makes great soup. And if I do say so myself, I make great soup. I don’t know why it is but, like our brown eyes, I think it’s something in our DNA. I say this because none of us has ever discussed soup-making or shared a recipe. Yet, we rock the soup pot. Surely it must be something in our genetic make-up. ...   ... Soup’s on… ...   ... I developed this hearty Manhattan Clam Chowder last year for my dad’s birthday. I served it as the first course, but truly it is a soup that eats like a meal. Instead of loading the chowder with the usual potatoes, I use a variety of organic fresh-from-the-farm root vegetables courtesy of my CSA (community supporte... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7293-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7293_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 11:56:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/prostate/c/question/90268/41020</link><title>What is effective treatment of ED following radical prostectomy?????</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>