<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7303">what causes itchy feet</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:29:39" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7303-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7303_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:29:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/195472/126064</link><title>Can Wellbutrin cause itchy palms and bottoms of feet?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7303-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7303_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:29:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/question/744482/148084</link><title>my 5 yr old son has small red itchy bumps on his sole of both feet.</title><description>... I have not been able to find an answer as to what is causing my 5 year olds itchy pain on the bottom of his feet. The bumps are under the skin and do not break the skin, also they are no where else on his body. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7303-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7303_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:30:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/867972/93655</link><title>itchy feet before penetration</title><description>... During foreplay and right before penetration, the bottom of my feet and lower part of my leg itch so bad that I can not enjoy sex.  Once my partner has penetrated, the itching subsides.  What can be causing this?  I have been married to my spouse for 11 years and this just started about 6 months ago.  It makes me not want to have sex. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7303-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7303_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:30:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/question/296654/143046</link><title>I have little bumps that are itchy on my feet/hands. Bottom of my feet are itchy, but my hands are not. Sensation is almost like pins and needles when I flex them but not quite. Tender to the touch.</title><description>...   ... They don't look like mosquito bites as they are not raised, but maybe bites of a gnat or spider or ant or so. I would think they are bites but they are only on feet and hands and it seems to be somewhat symmetrical patterns between left/right foot/hand: along points of contact (inner heel of foot, inner ball of foot, bottom of toes on the tip, palm side of hand along inner parts of fingers, protruding parts of palm, with tender fingertips). Also this is the third day I was sick. Day 0 my friend was coughing all over my food (had cold-like symptoms and works with 2-3 year olds at daycare). Day 1 I experienced a very slightly itchy throat but felt great, played sports at night time, and when I stopped playing immediately felt chills, feverish, short of breath with slight headache, thought possibly due to dehydration. Felt wor... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7303-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7303_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:31:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/714437/113301</link><title>What Is Causing Itching On Bottom Of Feet</title><description>...   ... Nma ... (Nig)W/A ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7303-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7303_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:31:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/594848/110886</link><title>What causes the feet to be sore and the toes to tingle and be sore?</title><description>... My feet are sore, burn and my toes are sore and partially numb with tingling sensations. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7303-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7303_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:31:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/850551/78193</link><title>How can I get rid of a itchy throat caused from a sinus infection?</title><description>... The infection seems to be gone but the itchy throat is not. ... I have been to doctors and specialist's and they say everything is clear, but I cough Constintly from a tickle in my throat. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7303-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7303_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:32:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/47703/35369</link><title>what causes itchy nipples</title><description>... i have recently missed a period, i am forty six, and have developed a very itchy left nipple. i also had a flat shaped lump there or should i say have a flat lump there, had mamogram. sometime ago, do i need to worry ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7303-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7303_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:32:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/154854/67848</link><title>Is itchiness causes breast cancer?</title><description>... I'm experiencing nipple itchiness severly. I noticed it a few weeks ago. At first it is still tolerable and once in a while but as days passed by I can't control to sctrach it and for the whole day it was very itchy. I can olnly feel it on my left breast. I'm not sure there is a mall lump but evrytime I press it I feel very pain until to my arms and back.Is this symptoms of breast cancer? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7303-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7303_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:33:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/718072/59461</link><title>i have had itchy breasts for years. what is the cause?</title><description>... The itching is not everyday, but it started at puberty, at least of what i remember. But recently i developed pain on one of my nipples and noticed that it was cut. almost as if a little slice had been taken off. and i have NO idea what it is from. it scabs, and itches like crazy. and a new devolpement is i looked in the mirror today and it looks like i have hickies on my breast, but that is impossible considering none of that activity has gone on there lately. Also for the first time today i noticed that that breast is smaller than the other. ... should i be concerned? ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>