<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7304">carmen electra video</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:33:45" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7304-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7304_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:33:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/headache-specialists/florida-39524-5.html</link><title>Maria-Carmen Wilson, MD - Florida Migraine and Headache Specialists</title><description>... Doctor: Maria-Carmen Wilson, MD Clinic/Facility: Address: 12901 BB Downs Blvd MDC 55 Tampa, FL 33612 Telephone: 813-974-4115 Recommendation: Patient Feedback ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7304-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7304_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:34:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/video-44020-47.html</link><title>Breast Reduction Surgery Video</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7304-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7304_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:34:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/find-44031-47.html</link><title>Menopause Video - Menopause Symptoms, Treatment</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7304-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7304_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:34:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/erectile-dysfunction/understanding-erectile-dysfunction-44026-47.html</link><title>Video - What Contributes to Erectile Dysfunction (Impotence)</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7304-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7304_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:35:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/videos-44022-47.html</link><title>Coronary Bypass Surgery Video</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7304-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7304_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:35:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/question/251950/154353</link><title>I want to see video of knee anterior cruciate ligament (ACL) replacement. What web site has videos of this kind of operation?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7304-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7304_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:35:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/common/images/image.html</link><title>Video Video Footage Image</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7304-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7304_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:36:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/9440/feel-head-explode</link><title>Feel as if Your Head Will Explode?</title><description>... How many of you have described your Migraines or headaches as feeling as if your head is going to explode? I have! This evening, I came across this video that I just have to share with you! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7304-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7304_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:36:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/458275/153760/video-games</link><title>Video Games: Myths vs. Facts</title><description>... ( click to enlarge) ...   ... For years now video games have been blamed for everything from learning disabilities to diminished social skills to heightened violent tendencies.  Researchers have been able to substantiate many claims about video games (especially regarding children), but there are still plenty of misconceptions out there about them. Let’s try to understand what’s going on by taking a look at some common video game myths.  ...   ... Myth: Video games are primarily influencing adolescent boys. ... Fact: Yes, video games are popular among children, but it may surprise you that only 25 percent of gamers are under 18 years old.  And perhaps even more surprising – 26 percent are over the age of 50.  The assumption that adults don’t play video games is probably as prevalent as the stereotype that most gamers are men.  While the latter is true overall, when you consider gamers under the age of 18, females outnumber males 33 to 20 percent.... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7304-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7304_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:36:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/80106/143482/con</link><title>"This Is Me" Health Video Contest</title><description>... Do you have a favorite charity you'd like to help? ... Want to do both? ...   ... HealthCentral is launching an exciting new contest of Health Videos . ...   ... Create a video telling us about yourself and your health journey. The next step is to submit your video anytime between September 1-30, 2011. ...   ... The Grand Prize winner will receive $200 to donate to their charity of choice. The 2 nd and 3 rd place winners receive $100 for their chairities. The Top 10 videos will be feature on the HealthCentral site and have an opportunity to become a regular video contributor.  ...   ... You can read more details about the contest on the Health Video page . When your video is ready, submit it here . ...   ... We're looking forward to watching! ...   ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>