<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7307">causes of the cold war</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:43:52" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7307-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7307_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:43:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/75934/19292/revamp-war</link><title>Can Revance - or Reloxin - Revamp the Wrinkle War?</title><description>... If you yearn for an unfurrowed brow but the thought of Botox injections leaves you cold, keep a lookout for a new, needle-free wrinkle-fighter that's currently under development.   Last month, Scottsdale-based Medicis Pharmaceutical Corporation - whose products include Restylane, the leading dermal filler worldwide - announced a strategic collaboration with Revance Therapeutics, a company headquartered in California that is developing a new botulinum toxin type A to relax wrinkles without injections [1 ]. Unlike the multitude of lotions and potions already out there that make unsubstantiated claims to be Botox alternatives, Revance has sound science behind it.   The idea is that this new form of botulinum toxin A, the active ingredient in Botox, can be applied to your skin, through which it is absorbed to target the overactive muscles that cause unwanted frown lines and other wrinkles. I spoke recently with Jonah Shacknai, the CEO of Medicis, who told me: "While the stu... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7307-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7307_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:44:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/c/question/47601/139827</link><title>I have purple fingernail beds do you know what this might be caused from? i stay cold most of the time and don't know if the finger purple finger nails and being cold are common.</title><description>... the lower part of my finger nails are purple in color the tops are normal pink in color. ALSO MY NAILS SPLIT AND TARE. I TAKE BIOTIN FOR HAIR AND NAILS. DOESN'T SEEM TO HELP ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7307-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7307_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:44:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/encyclopedia/408/320.html</link><title>Gulf War Syndrome</title><description>... Gulf War Syndrome is the name given to a variable combination of psychological and physical complaints experienced by veterans of the Persian Gulf War. It began in Indiana in early 1992, when soldiers in two reserve units that had fought in the Persian Gulf war began to suffer a puzzling array of symptoms. Some became unusually fatigued, and others said that their joints ached. They experienced headaches, rashes and hair loss , and their memories occasionally failed them. In some cases, the symptoms were severe enough to require hospitalization. Of the 697,000 veterans who served in the Gulf War hundreds, and then thousands, of veterans began showing up at hospitals run by the Department of Veterans Affairs with these and other symptoms. Eventually, 10,000 veterans asked for physical examinations to see if they had what has come to be called Gulf War Syndrome. The sequence of events leading to the identification of Gulf War Syndrome has occurred many times in recent years. First, there ar... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7307-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7307_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:44:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/5949/144420/prevalence</link><title>Prevalence of Gulf War Illness Varies by Deployment Area</title><description>... ... Fibromyalgia ... Chronic fatigue syndrome (ME/CFS) ... Functional gastrointestinal disorders ... Undiagnosed illnesses with symptoms that may include but are not limited to: abnormal weight loss, fatigue, cardiovascular disease, muscle and joint pain, headache, menstrual disorders, neurological and psychological problems, skin conditions, respiratory disorders, and sleep disturbances. ... ... For benefit purposes, the VA defines Gulf War Veterans as those who served on active duty in the Southwest Asia theater of military operations any time during the first Gulf War starting August 2, 1990 throu... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7307-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7307_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:45:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/16991/war-moms-mind</link><title>Refighting the Civil War in Mom's Mind</title><description>... In mid-August, I went to visit Mom at the nursing home right at the end of lunchtime. The dining room had emptied of residents, so Mom sat all alone, taking the final bites of her meal as the large television broadcast a soap opera.   "Hi, Mom! How are you doing today?" I asked as I approached the table where she sat. Looking up, I could see that Mom's face showed hints of distress. "I'm sad," she responded, her voice trailing off toward the end of the two-word sentence. "Why are you sad?" I questioned. Looking into my eyes, Mom slowly confided in me, "We lost the Civil War."   Startled, I asked Mom to tell me again why she was sad; Mom echoed the response that she had told me before. About that time, several of the nurse's aides were returning to the lunch room to enjoy their own meal. Not sure how our conversation would unfold, I thought it better to find a private spot in order to talk to Mom. "Hey, Mom," I replied... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7307-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7307_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:45:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/57548/139459/dementia-ptsd</link><title>Dementia and PTSD in Veterans and Victims of War</title><description>...   ... Many studies reveal how past traumas can haunt war veterans, victims of conflicts and holocaust survivors. As people age their previous exposure to trauma is adversely affecting them. For example there is a higher risk of dementia in veterans who suffered post traumatic stress disorder (PTSD) , altered brain structure associated with PTSD, and increased vulnerability to neuropsychiatric disorders caused by PTSD. ...   ... A study of 10,481 veterans over the age of 65 who attended the Michael E. DeBakey VA Medical Center in Texas found that about 30 percent of Vietnam War veterans and 12 to 20 percent of Iraq War veterans have dementia. Yaffe et al (2010) also found in a predominately male sample of 181,093 veterans that those who had suffered PTSD had... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7307-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7307_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:45:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/44/3435/car-wars</link><title>Car Wars</title><description>... ... Take my recent car purchase: Ever since that December trip to Florida, I have been spending as much energy on purchasing a car as I have facing my long January list of medical check-ups. That trip made me realize that it was time to replace my gas-guzzling (17-mpg highway), mechanically capricious 13-year-old van with something I could drive safely and afar. ... ... It started with a Chevy Malibu I rented in December. The renta... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7307-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7307_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:46:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/962/149238/arming-war-asthma</link><title>Arming Yourself for the War Against Asthma</title><description>...   ... There's an old saying that, "Knowledge is power!" and I am in total agreement with that sentiment. When you know and understand, you are in a much better position to take action, or to be more clear... actions that make sense and that will have positive benefits for you. ...   ... So, in today's post, I thought I would help you to find the most helpful sources of asthma knowledge. Beware! There is a lot of misinformation on the Web, and it's easy to get led down some crazy path, if you're not careful. ...   ... Start HERE! ...   ... HealthCentral.com was designed to provide reliable health information on ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7307-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7307_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:46:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/84/2302/wars-lantus-levemir</link><title>More Marketing Wars: Lantus vs. Levemir</title><description>... Reprinted with permission from Amy Tenderich of www.diabetesmine.com . Another larger-than-life Diabetes Marketing War , this time without the romantic names: I wrote a post introducing the first-ever competitor to Sanofi-Aventis' long-acting insulin, Lantus. The new product is called Levemir , from Novo Nordisk. What I missed more recently was that things turned ugly back in March. Sanofi filed suit against Novo Nordisk in a New Jersey U.S. District Court claiming that Novo was falsely promoting their drug as effective for 24 hours, which Sanofi claims is not true. The case was dropped on June 23 for lack of evidence, so Novo can go on making its long-lasting efficacy claim. Who's right here? Who knows? Novo's studies do seem to confirm its other two points of differentiation: that Levemir is well-absorbed by patients and causes less weight gain. Meanwhile a report released at the recent ADA Conference shows that a once-a-day dose of Lantus and Levemir have similar effects ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7307-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7307_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:46:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/49747/123671/rebels</link><title>How Gentle CCSVI Rebels will Win the MS Liberation War...7 reasons</title><description>...   ... Truth must be experienced rather than told because language fails to convey belief and is only the barest shadow of reality...Plato ...   ...   ... A Tale of Woe and Hope about a Profiteer's Conspiracy, Personal Health Freedom and a New Medical Paradigm ...   ... Who are these gentle CCSVI rebels? They are nurses, engineers, real estate developers, psychiatrists, teachers, farmers, accountants, business owners, lawyers, physiotherapists, and insurance brokers. They are mothers, fathers, wives, husbands, sons, daughters, sisters, brothers, and friends. They have said yes to health freedom against forces that would control them. They want to change to a more compassionate world that listens and cares. ...   ... They share a common bond...they are prisoners of a devastating disease called Multiple Sclerosis. It may relapse and remit or slowly progressively get worse to total disability. Who will be next? If you ar... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>