<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7320">cayenne pepper plants</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:25:58" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7320-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7320_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:25:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/200283/88213</link><title>Is Turmeric and Cayenne pepper good for prevention?</title><description>... Is there any Value and or truth in taking Cayenne Pepper and Turmeric to help prevent heart problems? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7320-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7320_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:26:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/question/461796/116800</link><title>does cayenne pepper pills work for acid reflux?</title><description>... do you think I am hurting myself or helping.. I just want a natural way to cure myself. I dont want to be on meds my whole life and I dont want to die from this. ... Thank you ... JC ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7320-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7320_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:26:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/c/question/37006/28287</link><title>is there a shot for the knee that comes from a pepper plant</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7320-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7320_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:26:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/1522/34626/salmonella</link><title>Breaking: FDA Lifts Ban on Tomatoes, Looks to Jalapeno Pepper as Salmonella Outbreak Culprit</title><description>...   ... Although the tainted Jalapeno, found in a Texas plant, was Mexican-grown, it was not necessarily contaminated in Mexico, inspectors say. ...   ... In light of recent investigations, the FDA has lifted its ban and warning on tomatoes . It was determined that fresh tomatoes now available in the domestic market were not responsible for the outbreak. ...   ... Enjoy these tomato recipes from FoodFit.com : ... ... Grilled Chicken with Tomato-Avocado Salsa ... Tomatoes with Fresh Grape Juice ... Tomato Bruschetta ... Spa-Style Chicken with Sun-Dried Tomatoes and Watercress ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7320-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7320_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:27:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/299905/130830/nightshade</link><title>Eliminating Nightshade Vegetables May Improve Health</title><description>... It’s hard to believe that eliminating any vegetable would be beneficial, but there is a botanical classification of plants called “nightshades” that may impact calcium metabolism, contribute to arthritis and/or joint pain and even have an adverse effect on overall health. The nightshade family includes tomatoes, eggplant, bell peppers, chili peppers, and spices such as paprika and cayenne pepper (black pepper is not considered a nightshade).  It also includes poisonous and/or addictive plants such as belladonna (deadly), mandrake and tobacco, which contain glycoalkaloids, substances that can be toxic and produce adverse effects that bring all plants within this category into question. Although our society’s heavy consumption of these foods in the form of pizza, french fries, baked potatoes, fried eggplant, tomato sauce and overall seasoning of foods make it difficult to isolate the effects of not consuming nightshades over the long term, researchers have fou... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7320-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7320_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:27:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/question/29437/31079</link><title>Dr. dean mentioned an injection based on cayenne but did not spel the name what is the name</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7320-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7320_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:28:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/334598/139665</link><title>are peppers harmfull for ra sufferers ? i eat alot of salad maybe to much onions peppers ect am i doing myself any favors ....</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7320-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7320_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:28:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/common/images/image.html</link><title>herbs, dill, healthy food, plant, hanging plant, promo</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7320-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7320_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:28:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/c/question/708116/150739</link><title>Does Almond Milk contain any plant sterols? If so, how much does it contain? (That is, 8 oz = X Mg of plant sterol).</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7320-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7320_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:29:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/headache-specialists/illinois-39538-5.html</link><title>Betsy J. Pepper, M.D. - Illinois Migraine and Headache Specialists</title><description>... Doctor: Betsy J. Pepper, M.D. Clinic/Facility: The Diamond Headache Clinic Address: 467 West Deming Place Chicago, IL 60614 Telephone: 773-388-6390, 800-432-3224 Recommendation: Patient Feedback ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>