<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7326">volcanoe eruption</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:47:48" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7326-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7326_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:47:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/56177/28705/eruption-coming</link><title>An Eruption is Coming</title><description>... My frustration and irritation flows and bubbles like the lava coming from a volcano. ... I feel an eruption coming. ... Soon the acidic elements of my life will come together to create an explosion. ... I am trying to prevent this natural occurrence due to the fact that I fear the destruction that is may cause. ... I feel it bubbling, inside of me... ... An eruption is coming. ... The question is "Is it preventable or is this destruction needed in order to create peace?"  ...   ... Bio ...   ... I am someone who is currently living with a number of mental illnesses including bipolar disorder.  This poem is an expression of how I often feel.  It is as if I have all these emotions inside of me, but am not free to determine when they express themselves.  All I can do is continue to do the things that I know will help me. ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7326-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7326_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:48:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/67935/162546</link><title>my son keeps having these eruptions on his skin and it keeps coming and going .we've tried deworming him and used hydocortisones but the eruptions keep recurring</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7326-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7326_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:48:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/2713-146.html</link><title>Fixed drug eruption on the cheek</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7326-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7326_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:48:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/2422-146.html</link><title>Fixed drug eruption, bullous</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7326-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7326_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:49:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/2421-146.html</link><title>Fixed drug eruption</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7326-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7326_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:49:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001454.html</link><title>Creeping eruption overview</title><description>... Definition Creeping eruption is an infection with dog or cat hookworm larvae. Alternative Names Cutaneous larvae migrans; Ancylostoma braziliense Causes, incidence, and risk factors Hookworm eggs are found in the stool of infected dogs and cats. When the eggs hatch, the larvae infest any contaminated soil and vegetation. When you come into contact with this infested soil, the larvae can burrow into your skin. They cause an intense inflammatory response that leads to a rash and severe itching. Creeping eruption is more common in countries with warm climates. In the U.S., the southeastern states have the highest rates of infection. The main risk factor for this disease is contact with damp, sandy soil that has been contaminated with infected cat or dog feces. More children than adults become infected. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7326-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7326_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:49:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001454trt.html</link><title>Creeping eruption treatment</title><description>... Alternative Names Cutaneous larvae migrans; Ancylostoma braziliense Treatment Anti-parasitic drugs such as thiabendazole, albendazole, or ivermectin may be used to treat the infection. Support Groups Expectations (prognosis) Creeping eruption may go away by itself over a period of weeks to months. Treatment helps the infection go away more quickly and is highly successful. Complications Secondary bacterial skin infections caused by scratching Spread of the infection through the bloodstream to the lungs or small intestine (rare) Calling your health care provider Make an appointment with your health care provider if you or your child have skin sores that are snakelike, itchy, or moving from one area to another. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7326-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7326_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:50:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001454sym.html</link><title>Creeping eruption symptoms</title><description>... Alternative Names Cutaneous larvae migrans; Ancylostoma braziliense Symptoms Blisters Itching , may be more severe at night Raised, snakelike tracks in the skin that may spread over time, usually about 1 cm per day (severe infections may cause several tracks) Signs and tests Your health care provider will usually diagnose this condition by looking at your skin. Rarely, a skin biopsy may be done to rule out other conditions. Rarely, a blood test may be done to see if you have increased eosinophils . ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7326-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7326_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:50:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001454prv.html</link><title>Creeping eruption prevention</title><description>... Alternative Names Cutaneous larvae migrans; Ancylostoma braziliense Prevention Public sanitation and de-worming of dogs and cats have decreased hookworm infestation in the United States. Hookworm larvae often enter the body through bare feet, so wearing shoes in areas where hookworm infestations are known to occur will help prevent infection. References Kazura JW. Nematode infections. In: Goldman L, Ausiello D, eds. Cecil Medicine . 23rd ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Saunders Elsevier; 2007:chap 378. Nash TE. Visceral larvae migrans and other unusual helminth infections. In: Mandell GL, Bennett JE, Dolan R, eds. Mandell, Douglas, and Bennett's Principles and Practice of Infectious Diseases . 7th ed. Orlando, FL: Saunders Elsevier;2009:chap 291. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7326-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7326_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:50:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/imagepages/2626.html</link><title>Strongyloidiasis, creeping eruption on the back</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>