<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7344">pampered chef</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:41:37" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7344-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7344_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:41:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/646074/48350/ready-bingo</link><title>Getting Ready for Top Chef: Top Chef Bingo!</title><description>...   ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7344-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7344_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:41:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/incontinence/c/question/336369/55177</link><title>whay doesn't pampers produce diapers in adult sizes</title><description>... I am a 23 year old bedwettter and i use to use pampers size  6 but as people every where know diaper sizes have seemed to shrink well the reason i ask is because the pampers size six were the best thing ever for me to find back when they would fit and now i am useing pull-ups goodnites and they are just not strong enough but the pampers size 6 was that is when it would fit ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7344-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7344_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:42:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/genital-herpes/c/question/114658/163770</link><title>can i give g herpes to my child by changing his pampers ?</title><description>... i had a herpes breakout genital area i touched so i have to change my toddler pamper but i believe i forget to wash my hands can i give g herpes this way ( also i rubbed diaper rash cream in his butt ) i change it a minute later after i touched i read The virus is fragile and dies when it leaves host cell should i worry ? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7344-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7344_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:42:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/question/734272/152078</link><title>I want to find an old person to pamper, to cherish and to spoil.</title><description>... I want to find an old person to pamper, to cherish and to spoil.  I am an out of work nurse in Radnor, Pennsylvania.  I volunteer along with my daughter and her friends at a local dementia unit at a nursing home.  I have worked at nursing homes for many years and do not like how dementia patients are handled.  I really love dementia patients.  I want to take care of a dementia patient or couple in their home but I have not had any luck finding one.  Is there anything you can do to help me? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7344-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7344_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:43:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/614008/137214/psoriasis-feel</link><title>Make-up and Psoriasis: You Can Still Feel Pretty and Pampered</title><description>...   ... For the longest time, I felt extremely frustrated any time I shopped for make-up, particularly concealer, foundation and face powder. I wanted to cover up the dry, red patches that appear near my hairline and on my face from time to time, but I didn't want to look too "made up." As any woman can attest, the caked-on look is not the desired effect of wearing make-up; on the contrary, we want the products we use to subtly complement our features, not draw attention to what we'd like to hide. ...   ... Problem was, I couldn't always find the right shade of make-up. Then there was the process of determining the best kind (sheer, cream, powder, etc.) for my fair, sensitive, dry skin. ...   ... I'm pretty sure I've had few hits and mostly misses through the years as I've tried to find the ri... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7344-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7344_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:43:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/question/48139/28618</link><title>does alzheimers patient take off their pampers that has faeces in it and put it on their heads ,do t</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7344-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7344_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:43:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/519810/73497</link><title>Do you always have to pamper your body so that your joints won't get swollen and painful?</title><description>...  I do a lot of lawn work because I enjoy it.  After a full day of enjoyment and taking care of Gods green earth.  I am in a lot of pain and swollen.  I do take small brakes at times. At the end I enjoy seeing what I've accumplished.  Everyone tell me that I am working myself to death. I am or should I just give up on cutting my grass? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7344-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7344_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:44:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/24582/138112/chef</link><title>In the Kitchen with Chef Seamus Mullen</title><description>... Photo Courtesy of Seamus Mullen ...   ... Anyone who knows me knows that I love food- cooking it, eating it, or watching shows about cooking it and eating it. If it has to do with food, chances are I’m going to enjoy it, so you can imagine my delight when Seamus Mullen, the talented chef from my favorite restaurant in New York City, appeared as a contestant battling it out on season two of the grueling Food Network show, The Next Iron Chef America. ... ... What made his participation on this show extra meaningful to me was the fact that Seamus has rheumatoid arthritis. I watched eagerly week after week as he succeeded at each of the cooking challenges on the show, knowing the additional challenges he must also overcome from RA in order to make it through to the next week. It felt exciting and inspiring to see someone with RA on TV, and as the season wore on, he spoke about the difficulties of rheumatoid arthritis on the show. ...   ... That was back in 2009; these days, Seamus is working o... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7344-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7344_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:44:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/7243/18666/chef-year</link><title>Chef Gale Gand: Starting the New Year Sweetly and Healthfully</title><description>...   Award winning pastry chef Gale Gand combines her artistic skills with a passion for good, healthy food. She is nationally recognized for her playful dessert creations that can be found in the Chicago area restaurants that she owns with partner chef Rick Tramonto. Her desserts are showcased at Tru, Cenitare and several other top restaurants. In addition, she hosts a TV show, Sweet Dreams on the Food Network and has written four books including her latest Chocolate and Vanilla (2006).   Gale is a devoted Mom and loves to cook for - and with - her 3 children. Gio (11), Ella and Ruby (3) are learning the joys of cooking from her. As a founding member of FoodFit's Chef Network, Gale has a strong commitment to nurturing her family with healthy, seasonal food.       Though she is so busy with so many projects, Gale values balance in her life and putting her family first. Her thoughts about how to begin 2008 with a healthy start are an inspiration to e... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7344-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7344_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:45:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/7243/18660/roasted</link><title>Chef Gale Gand's Roasted Pineapple Carpaccio</title><description>... Recipe courtesty Gale Gand     Roasted Pineapple yields 10-18 orders   1 pineapple, peeled 1 1/4 cups butter 1 3/4 cups organic light brown muscavado sugar 1 vanilla bean, split   Peel pineapple and leave whole. In a saute pan, melt the butter and add the brown sugar and vanilla beans. Cook to caramelize the sugar, then place the pineapple in and cook on all sides to brown. Add some water to the pan and continue cooking, turning the pineapple with tongs and basting occasionally until roasted through to the core. It may take 1 hour or more. Chill, then slice thin (either with an electric slicer or by hand).   Coconut-Cilantro Dressing yields 1 1/4 cups   1 cup simple syrup 1/4 cup coconut milk 1/2 tsp fresh ginger, grated 1 1/2 tsp cilantro leaves, chopped   Whisk ingredients together and chill.   Macadamia Nut Brittle yields 2 cups chopped   2 cups sugar 1/2 cup water to dissolve 2 Tbsp butter 1 cup macadamia nuts, toasted, cooled, and chopped   In a saucepan, bo... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>