<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7348">map of the united states</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:56:22" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7348-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7348_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:56:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/common/images/image.html</link><title>united states map</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7348-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7348_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:56:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/202/57619/migraine-medication</link><title>MAP0004 Acute Migraine Medication Trial</title><description>...   ... 850 Migraineurs are evaluating the effectiveness and safety of MAP0004 in the Phase 3 clinical trial which is a multi-center, double-blind, randomized, placebo-controlled trial. ...   ... The primary effectiveness goals are: ... ... pain relief at two hours after dosing ... suppression of nausea at two hours after dosing ... suppression of photophobia (sensitivity to light) at two hours after dosing ... suppression of phonophobia (sensitivity to sound) at two hours after dosing. ... ... This trial will also to evaluate: ... ... the earliest time of pain relief ... pain relief at 10 minutes ... sustained pain relief at 24 and 48 hours. ... ... In addition, patients in this study are being looked at for treatment of a single Migraine and may follow up on the long-term safety part of the trial ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7348-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7348_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:57:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/57548/148314/90-population</link><title>The over 90 Years Population is Growing Fast: Will The United States Cope?</title><description>...   ... The report published on November 17 th states that in 1980 there were 720,000 people aged 90 and above in the United States. By 2010, that number reached 1.9 million. It is estimated that by 2050 the numbers may reach nine million. The report suggests we need to adjust our terminology and as a result we should describe the oldest-old as people 90 years and over rather than the present 85 years. ...   ... It is no surprise that in many wealthy countries we are all living longer. But our wish for increased longevity comes at a cost; emotionally, sociologically and biologically. Most of us want more of life but it does have huge implications for the economy, for health services and for living arr... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7348-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7348_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:57:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/surgeries-hip-replacements-1312</link><title>I've heard that the United States has the highest cost for surgeries like total hip or total knee replacements.</title><description>... I've heard that the United States has the highest cost for surgeries like total hip or total knee replacements. Why is that? Comparing the cost of operations like joint replacement from country to country is truly like comparing apples to oranges. First of all, when costs are reported they may include all costs. This can include the surgeon, hospital, anesthesiology, drugs, and rehab. Other registries with collected data don't include the surgeon's fees. There is a difference in costs and billing between private and public systems. National health care is available in some countries, but not all. University hospitals may receive more funding to help offset the more complex patients they see. And finally, the cost of the implants used varies from country to country. Studies show that at a time when overall hospital costs have gone down, the price of the implants has gone up. Some hospitals are even buying implants by the case to help keep the cost down. As the number of adults needing join... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7348-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7348_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:57:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/5949/11238/beware-scam</link><title>Beware of the United States National Medical Association Scam</title><description>... I’ve been receiving e-mails from a group claiming to be the United States National Medical Association or US NMA. As soon as I saw that title, my red-flag alarm went off since there is no such organization. The group that provides medical oversight in the U.S. is the American Medical Association. The text of the e-mail begins, “Do you buy pharmaceuticals online? The US NMA was specifically established to protect the consumer. Our experts check every online shop for bogus medicines. The blacklist of unreliable or simply fraud shops is updated every week. We strongly recommend to visit our site before buying any medical products online.” It goes on to list several methods of online “cheating.” The poor syntax raised a second red flag, telling me that it most likely came from a foreign country. If there were any remaining doubts that something was not quite right, all I had to do was click on the link they provided claiming it would take me to a list o... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7348-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7348_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:58:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/3387/99551/great-united-asthma</link><title>5 Great Places to Live in the United States if You Have Allergies</title><description>... ... Pollen score ... Average medication use per patient ... Number of certified allergists ... ... There was quite a bit of movement on the list since last spring when the list was last compiled. Usually when I report on this, I talk about the worst places to live. This time I thought it might be fun to go the other direction and look at some of the better places to live in the United States if you have allergies. But I will tell you the absolute worst place at this time is McAllen, Texas, which rated worse than average in all 3 factors. ...   ... The Best Places to Live ...   ... So where are the places with a low pollen count, lots of allergists and not much need for medicating? Well, take a look: ... ... Portland. Doesn't matter whether you're talking east coast or west coast. If you live in Portland, Oregon (#100) or Portland... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7348-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7348_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:58:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/582316/129485</link><title>Which name of consultant prescribes adderall his prescription at united state?</title><description>... How can I get adderall with prescription in USA? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7348-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7348_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:58:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/tv-replacements-countries-1190</link><title>I saw a report on TV showing the high demand for joint replacements in Korea and other countries outside the United States.</title><description>... I saw a report on TV showing the high demand for joint replacements in Korea and other countries outside the United States. Are we the only ones making joint implants? Korea doesn't have any home-based supplier of joint implants. For this reason, they rely on five United States-based firms. There are other suppliers in Europe, but the UnitedStates supplies about 70 percent of the market for hips and 90 percent for the knee. Korea is only one country that relies completely on an imported supply of artificial joints. However this may be changing as these countries are preparing for their own production of joint implants. The demand for joint replacements is expected to go up even more. In Korea knee replacements are at an all time high. This may be because Koreans squat, which puts increased pressure on the knees. Korean women over age 60 with arthritis are a growing group in need of joint replacement. Reference: Jon Antoniou, MD, PhD, et al. In-Hospital Cost of Total Hip Arthroplasty in Ca... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7348-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7348_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:59:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/heard-replacement-compared-1188</link><title>I've heard it costs much less to have a hip replacement done in Canada compared to the United States.</title><description>... I've heard it costs much less to have a hip replacement done in Canada compared to the United States. Is this true? Yes it's true according to a new study just released by McGill University in Canada. They compared 940 Canadian and 739 American patients. All received a total hip replacement (THR). Costs were recorded. Canadian costs were converted into U.S. dollars for comparison. The researchers found the total cost of a THR in the U.S. is twice as much as the same operation done in Canada. It appears there are two major factors behind this difference. One is the cost of the joint implant itself. Prices can vary as much as 700 percent from one hospital to another. The second factor is the type of health care system. Canada has a national health system funded by the government. Services are rationed out. Follow-up and rehab after THR are not included as part of the services offered. Even though Canadians stay in the hospital longer, without these added services, the total cost is less. Re... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>