<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7401">yo mama jokes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:41:28" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7401-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7401_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:41:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/c/310478/152132/relcast</link><title>relcast what a joke and the jokes on me</title><description>... i reluctently and recently, probably 2 1/2 mths now, had the reclast infusion, my oncololgist suggested it last year , i was against it, once its in you, no turning back.  so then my rheumotologist suggested it and i gave in. now 2mths later, i developed HBP. i never had HBP my whole life, its always been normal low. my heartrate is eratic amoung other new symptoms, like muscular weaknes, short of breath. i mention these because i like to hike and never would be sooo out of breath as i was just recently. these symptoms, signs are all new. i am very disgusted and worried, hoping that in a years time and then some, will the reclast leave the body. too me, its like having a chemo treatment, not as toxic, but toxic enough to raise ones blood pressure to be in hytensive state. I started bp meds 3 wks ago, and bp is still in hypertension, that i'll address with doc. as far as the drug co's. i would love to infuse them and let them have things happen to their body.  the sudden&amp;nbsp... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7401-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7401_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:41:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/96/132845/tiger-mother</link><title>I am a Mama Lion-Not a Tiger Mother</title><description>... There has been a great deal of talk about Tiger Mothers, moms who set high educational and achievement standards for their children. I expect a lot of my children but I am not a Tiger Mom. Rather, I am a Mama Lion- fiercely protective of my cubs, ready to pounce if needed to keep them safe. You know the saying, “Don’t mess with the Mama Lion”. Well, that applies to me when it comes to the health and well being of my children. ...   ... When my reflux baby didn’t eat, sleep or grow like my other babies, I knew something was wrong. Yet there were many obstacles to getting her the care she needed. It took a long time to get a diagnosis and treatment plan in place. I went back and forth to the doctor, the specialist, the big city hospital and the specialty clinic. I did my own research and networking. I asked questions, lots of questions. I was persistent to the point of annoyance. I didn’t give up or let anyone stand in my way. I was the Mama Lion, protecting ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7401-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7401_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:42:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/3892/13354/mama</link><title>I Want My Mama!!!</title><description>... Having the support of family members is a key to dealing with a diagnosis of cancer in the family.   After I hung up from the phone call with my wife, when I first learned of her breast cancer, I was nearly overwhelmed with the new information I was processing. How was this going to affect our family. My wife homeschools our oldest son. How is that going to work if she is recuperating from surgery, or if she is enduring the ordeals of chemotherapy or radiation for months at a time? Your mind goes wild with speculation at a time like this. What if we were to lose her? I would lose my sweet companion that I hold so dear. I cannot imagine the void that I would feel in my heart, and the prospects of going on through life alone. The kids would be devastated to lose their mother. And how would I cope if I suddenly were to find myself in the role of a single father? You start getting a better appreciation of just how valuable your wife's contributions are to the family, when fac... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7401-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7401_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:42:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/136131/117019</link><title>Vyvanse and stuttering? Tourette's? Scared Mama!</title><description>... I am so worried about my 11 year old son, who happens to live with his father, who gives me very little information about our son and any treatments he receives. He began stuttering as a child and began speech therapy at the age of 3. We were told his speech problem was closer to "cluttering" rather than "stuttering". At  4 1/2 it was all but a forgotten problem, except when he was really excited or overly upset, and was completely manageable. Almost 2 years ago, his father and I separated and divorced. I moved out of the house and 3 days later, his father's girlfriend moved in! This upset my son to the point that the stuttering came back, quite significantly, but not near as bad as it is now! Last year, his father took him to a child psychiatrist, and he was diagnosed with ADD and was put on Vyvanse. I was never in agreement with the medication or the diagnosis, but had no say in the matter! My ex took our son off his medication for the summer and I noticed just yesterday, that ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7401-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7401_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:42:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/question/392399/132896</link><title>How do I forward this? I wish every mom knew that it was OK to be a MaMa lion! Thanks for the reminder!</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7401-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7401_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:43:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/6792/161748</link><title>DH re-did my computer for me, &amp; I'm now using Google, instead of ME. I can't get to the Forum anymore. HELP! Lowcountry Mama</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7401-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7401_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:43:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/question/199463/153449</link><title>should i go for job? mama ask me to leave my study and go for job 'cause i failed 4 time in 12th. I want to make my study but people and family say that I should go for job,what i have to do?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7401-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7401_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:43:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/110/14003/time-joke</link><title>Time for a joke!</title><description>... Things have been a bit serious around here. It's time to lighten up and retell an old joke... I've sure gotten old. I've had two by-pass surgeries. A hip replacement and new knees. Fought prostate cancer, and diabetes. I'm half blind and can't hear anything quieter than a jet engine. I take 40 different medications that make me dizzy, winded or subject to blackouts. I have bouts with dementia. I have poor circulation and can hardly feel my hands and feet. I can't remember if I'm 85 or 92, and I have lost all my friends. Thank God, I still have my Florida driver's license! Got any good ones that mention diabetes? Share them with everyone by adding the joke as a comment here. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7401-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7401_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:43:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/1070/82445/hat-joke</link><title>what a joke</title><description>...   ... as expected the MRI was normal.......... but the neurologist who i thought might actually help me turned out to be a joke. ...   ... he had a med student with him, and she was 10 times worse than he ever dard to be. he told her i had no known triggers... WHAT??? dude i told you at the frist appointment of at least 25. and those were just the ones i knew off the top of my head. i've done the elemination diet...... still in agony. keep taking you little preventative pills that are taking what little life i have left. and all he wants to do is up the dosages. just because aamatriptyline worked for 7 years 11 years ago doesn't mean that it will work now. and i've been on topamax for over 2 years now with NO relief! ...   ... i refuse to go back, and told my husband as much on the way home. hubby's response..... there is nothing wrong with you. my jaw nearly hit the floor. ...   ... so since my job could care less... and obviously my husb... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7401-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7401_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:44:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/5949/25060/pain-bad</link><title>Paula Abdul, Chronic Pain, and Bad Jokes</title><description>... Last week American Idol had their annual Idol Gives Back program.  If you haven’t seen it, they bring dozens of top celebrities together for a two-and-a-half hour live show to raise money for charities in the U.S. and Africa.  Later that night Jimmy Kimmel, on his late-night TV show, was talking about Idol Gives Back .  He said, “This year they estimate they raised $100 million, which will be divided between a variety of good causes: fighting malaria, Save the Children, and the search for a cure for whatever’s wrong with Paula.”  Of course he was referring to Paula Abdul. His “joke” got a big laugh from the audience, but not from me.  I’m tired of comedians and, even worse, serious journalists intimating that Ms. Abdul is whacked out on drugs because of one or two incidents (taken out of context) where she appeared to be acting a little strangely.  The fact is Paula Abdul has Reflex Sympathetic Dystrophy (also known... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>