<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7403">usc trojans</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:47:58" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7403-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7403_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:48:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/common/images/image.html</link><title>trojan condom</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7403-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7403_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:48:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/576614/83227</link><title>Vaginal burning</title><description>... I have had sex with my boyfriend roughly about a month ago and we used a Trojan-Enz latex condom. We have used condoms several occasions before (without any problems) but this time I had a strong burning sensation upon entry and a few centimeters inside of my vagina. I didn't have any pain during any deep penetration. The burning sensation did not hurt when I urinated and slowly went away after a few days. But I noticed recently that I had small linear pieces of skin (that were definitely not there before) that are sort of hanging off of the inner lining of my fabia minora. I am not sure if I have a latex allergy or if this is something more serious. Thanks. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7403-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7403_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:48:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/1443/154647/college</link><title>Sexual Health in College</title><description>...   ... The College Health Center ...   ... If you are sexually active, or planning on becoming sexually active, you want to find out what resources are available on your campus. The health center is the best place to start. Visit the center as soon as possible so you are prepared with the information you need, before you need... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7403-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7403_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:48:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/896502/148061/surprising</link><title>A Lower BMI or Improved Fitness? New Study Provides A Surprising Finding</title><description>... The term “ BMI ” seems to be thrown around a lot when talking about weight, especially in relation to extra pounds. So should you be paying close attention to your own BMI? And is it more important to lower your BMI or to improve your fitness level? ... So let’s start with the basics – what exactly is BMI? According to the Center for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), BMI stands for Body Mass Index and is a reliable indicator of most people’s body fat content.  Calculating a person’s BMI is inexpensive and easy to do, and can be used for determining weight categories that may be related to health problems (such as Type 2 diabetes). However, BMI should not be used as a diagnostic tool. “For example, a person may have a high BMI. However, to determine if excess weight is a health risk, a healthcare provider would need to perform further assessments,” the CDC website reported. “These assessments might include skinfold thickness meas... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7403-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7403_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:49:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/52325/157116/pregant-incentive</link><title>Pregnant and Smoke? Here's Your Incentive to Quit</title><description>...   ... Of the 21,600 children studied, those who were exposed to cigarette smoke  before birth  were 65 percent more likely to develop asthma.  This is a significant enough percentage for us to once again take this issue seriously.  Mom's should not smoke while pregnant. ...   ... This study was published in the American Journal of Respiratory and Critical Care Medicine. You can read more about it at  Medical News   Today  and   dailymail.co.uk .    An earlier study (you can read about at  USC News ) published in the same magazine discussed how smoking during pregnancy can cause DNA changes in the unborn child.   ... When you smoke you are putting, along with the highly addicting nicot... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7403-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7403_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:49:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/88918/51290/ground</link><title>Ground Yourself!</title><description>...   ... What is Grounding? ...   ... Grounding connects you with the very present moment using your five senses.  Let's talk about each of them: ...   ... Sight:  You can use your eyes and what you see in your surroundings to help ground yourself.  As you look at something, talk to yourself, either about what you see or what it means to you. ...   ... For example, I recently underwent Lasik surgery.  For those of you who are unfamiliar with the procedure, you essentially lie on your back, fully awake while your eye is held in pos... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7403-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7403_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:49:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/922587/138040/center</link><title>book, "The Center Cannot Hold" by Elyn Saks</title><description>... I know there was an interview of Elyn Saks (in 2007?) but I can't seem to access it.  And I know there are other posts about her book, but I'm going to start a new one.  I just read "The Center Cannot Hold."  The subject was something I'd had experience of, schizophrenia; the title was intriguing because I had felt just that way many times; and I knew it had something to do with success in the midst of mental illness, something to which I aspired.  It was pretty much what I expected -- a story of "rising above" the stultifying effects of schizophrenia and psychotropic meds and achieving success in academia.  It didn't inspire me to get another degree.  I already managed to get a degree despite severe depression, psychosis, paranoia, delusions, hallucinations, and a number of negative symptoms.  Ms. Saks relates some very harrowing experiences related to schizophrenia -- being put in restraints for 30 hrs at a time, walking across campuses wild-e... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7403-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7403_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:50:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/52053/iliad-heroes-losing</link><title>Homer's Iliad - Heroes One Day, Losing It the Next</title><description>... Homer is my favorite writer. Reading the first chapter to Thomas Cahill's "Sailing the Wine Dark Sea" last night reminded me why. "Rage - Goddess, sing the rage ... " reads the opening line to the Iliad. The Greeks are into their ninth year of a wearisome stalemate with Troy, but "the will of Zeus was moving toward its end." Spirits are low, tempers are frayed. Even the Gods and Goddesses are getting antsy. The Greek's greatest warrior, Achilles, is sulking in his tent and refusing to fight. Agamemnon, his comander-in-chief, has claimed his concubine - a legitimate prize of war - and Achilles is fit to kill. Only the intervention of Hera, wife of Zeus, and Athena, goddess of wisdom, keeps Achilles from giving into his emotions. The story gets complicated. Agamemnon, himself, had to give up HIS concubine, and fair is fair. It seems that Apollo, son of Zeus, had a personal interest in this particular concubine, and when Agamemnon wouldn't listen to reason, Apollo "came down furious from the... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7403-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7403_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:50:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/c/53591/89974/declared</link><title>Fosamax Mistrial Declared</title><description>... If you’re a fan of the television show "Law and Order," or grew up with Perry Mason, the following story is right up your alley. Filled with violence, intrigue, and conflicting versions of the truth – and with billions of dollars at stake – it ranks right up there with Judge Judy for entertainment value. What, O.J. Simpson’s in the news again? A federal lawmaker has been accused of accepting luxury Tahiti vacations? Maybe one of those Wall Street financiers has confessed implication in a money-laundering scheme? Nope, I’m talking a trial pitting over 700 osteoporosis patients against Big Pharma’s Merck &amp; Co., manufacturer of the osteoporosis drug Fosamax – a multi-billion dollar cash cow for Merck. The trial, the first of three “bellwether” lawsuits involving Fosamax, got underway in New York August 12. Presided over by U.S. District Judge John Keenan, it’s a consolidation of some 700 separate lawsuits against Merck &amp;... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7403-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7403_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:50:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/95378/food</link><title>"Food, Inc." Film Raises Questions for Diabetics About Food Industry</title><description>... American agriculture changed more in the past 50 years than it did in the previous 10,000 years since humans started cultivating grains and domesticating cattle, pigs, and poultry. This affects all Americans, but none more than those of us who have diabetes, which started its steep rise at about the same time that our farms became so much more efficient under the management of just a few huge multinational corporations. This correlation certainly isn't proof that modern agriculture caused the rise of diabetes. It remains, however, a likely suspect. Neither can we fairly claim that the giant corporations that control most of American agriculture are the cause of anything more than being efficient. These companies are doing what companies are supposed to do -- making a lot of money by doing what all companies try to do. The root of the problem is our government. The federal government of the United States of America set the conditions under which the great consolidation of American a... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>