<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7405">light therapy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:53:44" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7405-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7405_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:53:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/treatment-000008_9-145.html</link><title>Depression and Light Therapy, Electric Shock Treatment</title><description>... Psychotherapy Among the various psychotherapeutic "talk therapies," cognitive-behavioral therapy appears to be the most effective approach. If psychotherapy is used alone without medications, benefits should be evident within 8 weeks and symptoms should be fully resolved by 12 weeks. If these conditions are not met, then the patient should strongly consider antidepressant drugs. Cognitive Behavioral Therapy For many patients, cognitive behavioral therapy (CBT) works as well as antidepressants in treating severe depression. Like all psychotherapies, much of the success depends on the skill of the therapist. Many studies suggest that combining cognitive therapy with antidepressants offer the greatest benefits. Studies also indicate that the benefits of cognitive therapy persist after treatment has ended. Best Candidates . Although helpful for all patients with depression, CBT may be particularly helpful for the following patients: Patients with atypical depression or dysthemia Patients with a ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7405-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7405_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:54:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/18/149773/frequently-asked</link><title>Frequently Asked Questions about Light Therapy for Seasonal Affective Disorder</title><description>... 1\. Do I need to see a doctor to diagnose and treat my Seasonal Affective Disorder (SAD)? ... As with any mood disorder, a formal diagnosis is highly recommended. For one thing, it's essential to rule out any hidden conditions that might be causing the depression, like thyroid dysfunction. For another, you will need the SAD diagnosis to have your health insurance provider pay for treatment. ...   ... 2. Will replacing the existing light bulbs in my house with brighter or different bulbs work just as well as light therapy? ... Because of the importance of such factors such as positioning and dis... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7405-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7405_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:54:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/458275/155858/healthcentral</link><title>What is Light Therapy? A HealthCentral Explainer</title><description>... (istock image) ...   ... Shorter days are already upon us, which means less daylight and less time spent outdoors.  For those who suffer from seasonal affective disorder (SAD), a type of depression that occurs typically in the fall and winter months, the shorter days are especially rough.  Bright light therapy is best known as a method used to treat SAD, but is also highly effective in treating other conditions, and new research is expanding the potential for this simple healing method. ...   ... What is light therapy? ... During light therapy, also known as phototherapy or heliotherapy, a patient sits near a light therapy box that gives off a bright artificial light meant to mimic natural outdoor light.   Don’t worry, the amount of interior light being taken in by the eye is far less than what occurs outside, so relying on electric light doesn’t compare to the real thing.  Outdoor light on a sunny day is 500 to 1,000 times brighter than office or room ligh... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7405-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7405_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:54:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/496051/59567</link><title>Light therapy</title><description>... Has anyone had good results with light therapy? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7405-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7405_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:54:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/91/14127/low-laser-work</link><title>Does Low Intensity Laser Light Therapy Work?</title><description>... Dear Dr. Borigini:   My 85 year old step father has debilitating scoliosis and often acute pain that keeps him from sleeping. He sleeps in his Lazy Boy type chair because he cannot lie flat.   Recently he has seen a pain specialist and had cortisone injections which helped at first, but later injections gave little relief. The pain doctor has suggested LILT, Low Intensity Laser Light therapy for the pain, which insurance does not cover. The literature he gave us to read sounds too good to be true, saying that LILT affects the problem cells and doesn't affect the normal cells. I can't seem to find credible information online. For my stepfather this treatment would be expensive on his limited finances. Can you tell us if this is effective and safe?   A study was published in a 1995 issue of "Lasers Surgery Medicine" that concluded that monochromatic light/laser irradiation at low intensity did not provide pain relief. A German article... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7405-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7405_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:55:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/149044/92938/ultraviolet</link><title>Hope for Psoriasis Patients with Ultraviolet Light Therapy</title><description>...   ... The fact that this skin disease can drastically alter one's appearance as well as the persistence of symptoms despite repeated treatments can be psychologically damaging to the typical psoriasi... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7405-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7405_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:55:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/18/151866/therapy-affective</link><title>Light Therapy for "Indoor" Seasonal Affective Disorder</title><description>...   ... I was discouraged, as I'm on the maximum standard dose of Wellbutrin. Where do you go from there? And why had it stopped working? ...   ... As I was writing my series on light therapy for Seasonal Affective Disorder this past winter, I started thinking. Maybe my depression was a result of lack of light, and I had in essence developed SAD all year round. ...   ... A few years ago we moved from Connecticut, with its months of gray winter skies, to sunny California. Initially I wasn't working outside the home, so I spent a lot of time outside, even in the winter. Fifty degrees in the pale winter Connecticut sun is chilly; fifty degrees in the bright winter Californ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7405-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7405_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:55:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/21142/45417/light-therapyi</link><title>light therapyI</title><description>... i asked a question but i think i accidently erased it. i wonder if i should invest in a therapy light. i have major sometimes labeled treatment resistant depression and i noticed the site said that light therapy is for mild depression. any advice brendavo ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7405-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7405_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:56:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/18/148008/therapy-affective</link><title>Light Therapy for Seasonal Affective Disorder</title><description>...   ... Note: Although light therapy may sound like the ultimate do-it-yourself depression treatment, before doing anything, you should get a formal diagnosis of SAD from a doctor, and preferably have them guide your treatment. ...   ... Why Light Therapy? ...   ... It may be hard to believe that a dose of light every day could treat a mood disorder, but in the case of Seasonal Affective Disorder, it's far and away the most successful treatment. Light therapy replaces the light we are lacking during the ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7405-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7405_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:56:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/prostate/c/question/675662/110168</link><title>green light therapy</title><description>... Looking for information on retrograde ejaculation and this therapy,wondering if this is permanant after the surgery or temporary.thanks,,,mike ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>