<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7406">does my child have adhd</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:56:43" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7406-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7406_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:56:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/679447/167691</link><title>Does it help or hurt to tell your child you also have ADHD- child is 12 years old and it manifests differently in parent vs. child.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7406-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7406_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:57:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/question/924828/154843</link><title>if a person has a parent with bipolar disorder and then the child has adhd does that greater the chances of the child having bipolar disorder</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7406-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7406_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:57:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/133459/59176</link><title>What would you do, If your child has ADHD and the school constantly picks at you child ?</title><description>... more to my question. well picking like, always being agresive with words, saying things teachers should not say, or knowing the problem and instead of trying to help they take your child to court. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7406-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7406_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:57:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/849319/134500/supplements-treat</link><title>Supplements to Treat Your Child’s ADHD: GABA</title><description>...   ... When my son first got diagnosed with autism, we were sent a care package of supplements from a relative who is a pharmacist. I was grateful for the help but I wondered about the efficacy and safety of these products and especially for a child. So I began to research these supplements on-line and in the literature. In addition I listened to other parents about what worked and what didn’t work for their child. We even tried some of these natural remedies and slowly over the years I have come to some conclusions based upon our person... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7406-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7406_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:57:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/765162/118671</link><title>Can a child with ADHD control the way they act if they know there being watched to see if they have ADHD?</title><description>... My nephew went to the doctor's they gave his mother a paper for his teacher to fill out over a month period and he know's about it. The paper is to find out if he has ADHD. Will he be able to control his behavior in order not to be diagnosed with ADHD? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7406-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7406_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:58:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/734780/167175</link><title>Anyone have a child diagnosed ADHD and the child is medicated AND receiving counseling/therapy?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7406-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7406_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:58:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/1443/9943/child-adhd-months</link><title>Raising a Child With ADHD: Medication During the Summer Months</title><description>... From the time my son was just a toddler, as a mother, I had concerns over some of his behaviors.  I remember taking him to the doctor when he was not quite two and asking about hyperactivity.  The doctor felt my son was a “highly active child.”  From that point on, I questioned his activity level, his lack of sleeping patterns, his inability to sit still. Even when the other children in the day care seemed to be able to listen during story time, my son was wandering around, picking up toys, totally disinterested in what was going on in the room.  But over and over, physicians told me that his behaviors were within normal levels for his age and that there was nothing to worry about.   Throughout the next ten years, my son was referred to the school psychiatrist, the school psychologist, and the guidance counselor and yet none seemed to feel there was a problem, until, at 12 years old he was diagnosed with ADHD.  In some ways, the diagnosis helped, as it le... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7406-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7406_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:58:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/1443/114383/problems-parenting</link><title>Question of the Week: What Problems Do You Have Step Parenting a Child with ADHD?</title><description>...   ... "I need help! My step son has ADHD, and its BAD there are times we can not do anything with him... and I dont know what to do I'm too the point of leaveing can you help with advice on how to better handle this?" ...   ... "neither of his natural parents have ever picked up on the fact that there is truly a problem that needs to be addressed. I'm the step-mom who happened to be the first to raise a flag....." ...   ... "How do you go about trying to deal with an ADHD child and and keep to a routine etc when the natural mother absolutely refuses to accept ANY advice from professionals? She has the idea in her head that no one will tell her how to raise her child." ...   ... It seems this is a particularly difficult situation because the step parent may be struggling not only with the child's behavior but one or both of the natural parents fighting a diagnos... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7406-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7406_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:59:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/1443/152732/ts-talking-child-adhd</link><title>Dos and Don’ts for Talking to Your Child About ADHD</title><description>...   ... Each child is different and will have a different idea on what ADHD means. Depending on the age of your child, each will have a different level of understanding. Some, especially older children, will feel relieved that they are not "bad." Younger children will have a limited understanding of what this means to them. Many may already have low self-esteem from years of not being able to keep up with peers in scho... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7406-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7406_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:59:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/1443/11162/child-adhd-sleep</link><title>Helping a Child with ADHD Get to Sleep</title><description>... Children with ADD/ADHD sometimes have a hard time falling asleep. They may toss and turn or they may just not be able to shut down their thoughts long enough for sleep to come. In the summer months, when outside activity is higher and the sun stays out much longer, sleep may not come until well after parents are exhausted. The following are some tips to help your child fall asleep quicker. Stick to your bedtime routine, even during the summer months, as much as possible. Set a specific bedtime and keep with that bedtime, even if a child is allowed to sit in bed and quietly read or play. Create a buffer time to lower down the activity level for an hour or so before bedtime. Find quieter activities such as coloring, reading or playing quietly. Set up a quiet time before bedtime. Use this time to sit and read with your child or talk about the day's events. Make this a transitional time between active play and sleep. Use lavender... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>