<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7407">kim kardashian pregnant</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:59:32" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7407-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7407_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:59:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/149044/142056/kim-kardashian</link><title>Kim Kardashian Diagnosed with Psoriasis</title><description>...   ... Kim Kardashian is not the first celebrity to be diagnosed with psoriasis. Country music singer LeAnn Rimes has talked openly about her psoriasis in an interview with Health Central contributor, Heather Durocher. Other celebrities who have b... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7407-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7407_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 17:59:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/202/153901/karadashian-famous</link><title>Khloe Karadashian: Famous Migraineur</title><description>... Khloe Kardashian Odom, celebrity and entrepreneur, is a Migraineur who often tweets about her Migraines. Khloe Alexandra Kardashian was born on June 27, 1984 in Los Angeles, California to parents Robert and Kris Kardashian. Mr. Kardashian was a successful lawyer who helped defend O.J. Simpson during the murder trial of Simpson's ex-wife Nicole Brown and friend Ron Goldman. Mr. Kardashian passed away at the age of 59 from esophageal cancer in 2003. Ms. Kardashian's mother Kris is now married to Olympic winner Bruce Jenner. ...   ... Khloe Kardashian has a large, blended family including sisters Kim and Kourtney, brother Robert Kardashian, Jr., three step-brothers and a step-sister (Brody, Brandon, Bert and Casey, respectively), and half-sisters Kendall and Kylie Jenner. As a teen, Ms. Kardashian has admitted she was "a major trouble maker" and dropped out of the Catholic, all-girls school she attended after her older sisters had graduated. Referring to herself as a "shady kid," she later... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7407-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7407_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:00:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/blog-26560-5.html</link><title>Meet Kim Emmons-Benjet</title><description>... Kim Emmons-Benjet is a social worker by training but her passion is for her family. Kim, and her husband of ten years Brian, have two children - eight year old Josh and six year-old Hannah. She has worked as a child therapist and with families struggling with addiction.   In the mid-1990s Kim helped develop a comprehensive job training program that addressed the multiple challenges faced by people leaving welfare and government dependency. She has a bachelor’s degree from Colgate University and a Masters in Social Work from Howard University.   In addition to career accomplishments, Kim trained for and completed the 2002 Marine Corp Marathon, raising money for AIDS research in the process.   Kim’s son Josh was diagnosed with Type 1 diabetes in December 2002. Since then she has become an active member of the Juvenile Diabetes Research Foundation’s Capitol Chapter. Kim and her husband have served as the Chairs of the chapter’s annual Gala which r... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7407-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7407_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:00:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/blog-26572-5.html</link><title>Meet Kim Emmons-Benjet</title><description>... Kim Emmons-Benjet is a social worker by training but her passion is for her family. Kim, and her husband of ten years Brian, have two children - eight year old Josh and six year-old Hannah. She has worked as a child therapist and with families struggling with addiction.   In the mid-1990s Kim helped develop a comprehensive job training program that addressed the multiple challenges faced by people leaving welfare and government dependency. She has a bachelor’s degree from Colgate University and a Masters in Social Work from Howard University.   In addition to career accomplishments, Kim trained for and completed the 2002 Marine Corp Marathon, raising money for AIDS research in the process.   Kim’s son Josh was diagnosed with Type 1 diabetes in December 2002. Since then she has become an active member of the Juvenile Diabetes Research Foundation’s Capitol Chapter. Kim and her husband have served as the Chairs of the chapter’s annual Gala which r... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7407-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7407_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:00:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/720942/57986/kimcallag</link><title>KimCallag</title><description>... I've had EECP 3 times in the past.  It can really help, in my case, the 1st 2 times did wonders, the 3rd, not so much.  Apparently, if you have diabetes, it's not as effective. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7407-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7407_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:01:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/80106/162861/parenting-child</link><title>Parenting a Child with Juvenile Arthritis: A Review &amp; Interview with Kim P. Miller</title><description>...   ... Living with Juvenile Arthritis: A Parent's Guide is written in the reassuring voice of someone who's been through it all and come out on the other side. Kim is a former NFL wife and frames the book in sports metaphors, helping you to get a game plan to deal with your child's chronic illness. The book provides down-to-earth advice and tips on dealing with the challenges of life with JA, such as preparing for doctors’ visits, building a medical team, tips for "shot night," managing flares, dealing with the emotional impact on all members of the family and many more. Kim illustrates the practical sections with personal stories from: experience with her sons, Grant and Evan and stories provided by other p... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7407-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7407_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:01:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/question/734500/128866</link><title>Hi my name is Kim My husband is 47 has had progressive ms for 2 years now and has been told he is in final stages. What does this mean?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7407-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7407_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:01:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/661749/95908</link><title>Can you take cymbalta when you are pregnant?</title><description>... can you take cymbalta when you are pregnant ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7407-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7407_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:02:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/635702/159646</link><title>Pregnant @ 48?</title><description>... Although I'm 48 yrs old, I have been told by my Dr. that I have healthy eggs and I still have a chance of becoming pregnant. For a week and a half after my period, I have been having sharp pains in my breast and a heavy feeling in my lower stomach area. Is it possible that I may be pregnant? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7407-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7407_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:02:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/295656/61499</link><title>i went in for a vaginal scope surgery found out to be pregnant</title><description>...   ...  to unblock my tube so i could get pregnant.They never did a test to see if i was pregnant.When they were in thesurgery they saw the embrio 7 weeks old.They injected Methylene blue and finished the procedure.Now is this going to cause fetal brain damage ...   ...   ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>