<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7408">tom cruise</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:02:35" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7408-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7408_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:02:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/ibd/living-with-254527-5.html</link><title>Crohn's Disease Comic: Everything You Never Wanted to Know about Crohn's Disease</title><description>... Read more about Tom's comic and his creative process during the 24 Hour Comic Challenge ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7408-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7408_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:02:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/erectile-dysfunction/c/question/554884/69142</link><title>HI I AM 58YEARS OLD AND I STOP EJACULATION WHY IS THAT THANK YOU TOM.B.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7408-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7408_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:03:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/community-3405-143.html</link><title>Meet Tom Brown, Breast Cancer Husband</title><description>... Tom was born and raised in Leavenworth, Kansas. In 1992 Tom’s first wife, Barbara was diagnosed with breast cancer. After fighting the disease for nearly two years, Barbara died after a long and courageous struggle. In 1994 Tom met a wonderful woman in Carlisle, PA who also had just lost her spouse to death. Tom and Connie were married on September 30, 1995 and began a new life. Tom and Connie’s extended family includes three married sons and five grandchildren. Tom retired in the grade of Colonel from the United States Army in 1996. After retirement from the service, he and his wife Connie remained in Leavenworth, where they now reside. Tom began work on Men Bleed Too as a journal capturing the events that took place during Barbara’s battle with cancer. With Connie’s encouragement he decided to turn the journal into a book. Men Bleed Too is a heart touching story that will affect many lives. Tom is the author of numerous articles published by the U.S. Army. To... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7408-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7408_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:03:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/5949/162986/originator-awareness-day</link><title>Tom Hennessy – Originator of May 12 Awareness Day – Passes Away</title><description>... Thomas Michael Hennessy, Jr. passed away on September 9, 2013 in Boca Raton, Florida, following a 25-year battle with ME/CFS. He was a vocal and passionate advocate for people with chronic immunological and neurological diseases including, ME/CFS (myalgic encephalomyelitis/chronic fatigue syndrome), fibromyalgia, multiple chemical sensitivity, Lyme’s disease and Gulf War Syndrome. ...   ... Tom will probably be best remembered as the man who originally (21 years ago) designated May 12 as International Awareness Day for Fibromyalgia, ME/CFS and other neuroendrocine immune diseases. He also founded the advocacy organization R.E.S.C.I.N.D. – Repeal Existing Stereotypes for Chronic Immunological and Neurological Disorders . (R.E.S.C.I.N.D. is no longer online) ...   ... All of us who have fibromyalgia or ME/CFS owe Tom Hennessy a debt of gratitude. Awareness of these disorders has come a long way in the past two decades, but it was Tom who got the ball rolling and gave us a voice. ... &amp;... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7408-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7408_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:04:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/2299/live-tom-woottons</link><title>Reporting Live from Tom Wootton's Conference</title><description>... ... Very few people I talk to or communicate with see bipolar as an advantage, I know that a large chunk of my personality that I cherish – my creativity, my vision, my sensitivity, my mild craziness – can be attributed to some “good” bipolar genes, but this is a hard sell to people still struggling to find the right meds who are looking to pick up the pieces to their shattered lives. ... ... ... “There is no good or all bad,” Tom opened with, or words to that effect. Then he ran through the short version of the all-day or two-day seminar he gives. He started out by having us name all the bad things about mania. Well, that was easy. The list filled... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7408-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7408_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:04:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/ibd/living-with-254545-5.html</link><title>Everything you never wanted to know about crohn's disease: page 2</title><description>... Read more about Tom's comic and the creative process during the 24 Hour Comic Challenge ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7408-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7408_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:04:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/ibd/living-with-254557-5.html</link><title>24 Hour Comic Challenge: Everything You Never Wanted to Know about Crohn's Disease: Page 3</title><description>... Read more about Tom's comic and his creative process during the 24 Hour Comic Challenge.  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7408-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7408_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:05:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/ibd/living-with-254559-5.html</link><title>24 Hour Comic Challenge: Everything You Never Wanted to Know about Crohn's Disease: Page 4</title><description>... Read more about Tom's comic and his creative process during the 24 Hour Comic Challenge ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7408-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7408_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:05:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/ibd/living-with-254561-5.html</link><title>24 Hour Comic Challenge: Everything You Never Wanted to Know about Crohn's Disease: Page 5</title><description>... Read more about Tom's comic and his creative process during the 24 Hour Comic Challenge ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7408-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7408_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:05:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/ibd/living-with-255286-5.html</link><title>24 Hour Comic Challenge: Everything You Never Wanted to Know about Crohn's Disease: Page 6</title><description>... Read more about Tom's comic and his creative process during the 24 Hour Comic Challenge ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>