<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7409">rihanna chris brown</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:05:55" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7409-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7409_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:05:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/genital-herpes/c/18559/60554/celebrities</link><title>Oral Herpes, Genital Herpes, and Celebrities (Oh My!)</title><description>... There has been a lot of herpes talk in the media lately (and by “media” I mean gossip blogs and trashy online magazines) due to the recent allegations that R&amp;B singer Chris Brown beat up his former girlfriend, pop singer Rihanna. The incident reportedly took place after a pre-Grammy party, and while people speculate on what sparked the fight, many believe it was over herpes.  Rumors are flying that Rihanna not only gave genital herpes to Chris Brown, but that she got it from hip-hop mogul Jay-Z.   Why is this important?   It’s not.   At least not unless you’re one of those involved.   But the comments I’ve heard from people regarding this controversy tells me there’s still a lot of misunderstanding about herpes out there in the general population.   ...   ... No one knows for sure what caused the fight between the two celebrities.   My guess is that it had more to do with jealousy than an STD.   I would imagine th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7409-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7409_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:06:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/92183/60685/relationship</link><title>Are You In an Abusive Relationship?</title><description>...   ... It is so easy to allow evidence of these behaviors to happen and justify them - especially in the presence of tough economic times.  Certainly individuals who come from abusive homes may use those learned behaviors as their own yardsticks and assume the behavior is "normal."  But there is really no justification for relationship abuse.  And the longer you remain with a partner who shows signs of verbal coercive behaviors, the more at risk you are for escalation of those behaviors into more threatening and ev... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7409-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7409_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:06:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/571710/132970</link><title>I take a vegan (algae) omega 3 product but have been told I am getting NO EPA (unless at least taking Krill or another fish oil). Is this your understanding as well? Thanks, Chris</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7409-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7409_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:06:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/c/question/661653/127212</link><title>Hi my name is Chris my stepfather died of hypertenive and atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease what does this mean?</title><description>... What does this mean? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7409-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7409_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:07:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/254163/127149</link><title>Chris my stepfather died of hypertensive and atherosclerotic cardiovascular disase what is this?</title><description>... What does this mean? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7409-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7409_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:07:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/469110/99843/chris1967</link><title>To Chris1967</title><description>... I only write on this site occasionally I pass by and read what is important out here. I don't see the need of private messages when there's nothing private about them. This is how we all do it, we don't feel the need to share or to be here all the time. ... I'm glad you are feeling better, it's difficult to do it but eventually we manage to stabilize our mind and emotions. ... Take care Chris see you around. ... Alex ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7409-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7409_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:07:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/question/662398/65091</link><title>What do you think about alzheimer's and coconut oil as possible treatment? Chris</title><description>... My mother is 68 and is currently on Aricept and Namenda but until recent months, had not been taking it consistantly.  I am unsure at what stage she is.  I have recently read the article by the Dr whose husband had AD and she began to give him coconut oil and saw some improvement.  I just discovered this web site and I am finding it to be very helpful.  Thankyou. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7409-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7409_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:07:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/16367/21509/ms</link><title>Interview and discussion with Chris Tatevosian MS sufferer and author of Life Interrupted</title><description>... Interview and live discussion with Chris Tatevosian, MS sufferer and author of Life Interrupted, It's Not All About Me I'm going to be interviewed on the radio/internet on the interactive Blog Talk Radio Show, "Winning Life Through Pain" with coach Marla on Tuesday March 25th at 2 PM Eastern Standard Time. The topic: Multiple Sclerosis , a condition from which I have suffered for almost three decades and the resulting stress put on a relationship when life is interrupted by chronic illness. Marla and I will be discussing my book , Life Interrupted, It's Not About Me , which is my real life story written to help others avoid making the same relationship destroying mistakes that I did. If this self-help book helps just one person or saves one relationship it will have been well worth my literally making my life and open book. The story is not always pretty, but it's real. So, please join us on Tuesday March 25th at 2 PM EST by clicking the link below http://blogtalk... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7409-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7409_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:08:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/795915/136579/schroeder</link><title>A Message from Chris Schroeder, CEO of HealthCentral</title><description>...   ... -Chris Schroeder ...   ...   ... For those in the Washington D.C./Baltimore area, funeral arrangements for Jan are as follows: ...   ...   ... Hardesty Funeral Home ... 12 Ridgely Avenue, ... Annapolis 21401 ...   ... Visitation: Friday, Apr. 15, 2011 ... 2:00 pm - 4:00 pm &amp; 7:00 pm- 9:00 pm ...   ... Service: Saturday, Apr. 16, 2011 10:00 am ... Cemetery: St. Phillip the Apostle ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7409-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7409_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:08:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/160811/governor-christie-surgery</link><title>New Jersey Governor Chris Christie Has LAP-band Surgery</title><description>... I am very glad to learn that the governor of my home state of New Jersey, Chris Christie, is taking control of his health. Actually, I had considered trying to reach him to speak about obesity surgery. It turns out that I did not need to do so. Apparently Christie spoke with New York Jets coach  Rex Ryan about his weight loss surgery . Ryan had the LAP-band in 2010 and lost 100 pounds. In February, Christie secretly had bariatric surgery with the LAP-band. ...   ... I only can assume that being in the spotlight is difficult even under the best conditions. Christie has come under public fire about his obesity, more often than not he has been the brunt of fat jokes on national television. He is as imperfect as the rest of us although his obesity is open for public humiliation. ...   ... ... Chris Christie and David Letterman talk fat jokes. ...   ... The governor claims to be the healthiest fat person around. He has gone to lengths to chime in with the crowds who laugh at him at his e... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>