<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7411">lenin mausoleum open</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:12:27" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7411-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7411_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:12:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/videos-44017-47.html</link><title>Angioplasty Video</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7411-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7411_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:12:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/251764/68410</link><title>what do i do about having open cuts near the opening of my vagina that hurt and seem to not heal?</title><description>... i got three cuts near the opening of my vagina from shaving. i didnt even notice them until after i had sex with my boyfriend the next day. now the cuts hurt when i pee and wipe. they are like open cuts now..ive been washing it with soap and water and trying to dry it out sometimes. it doesnt seem like its getting better. im worried, what should i do? how long should it take to heal? how do i know its not something serious? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7411-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7411_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:13:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/802978/141690</link><title>7 month old girl with large vaginal opening can see inside large opening</title><description>... can see small bulb shaped balloon-looking ???piece ??? inside baby girl's too large looking ???vagina???opening???.have not explored much. afraid i'll injure. opening looks too big. when parting majora to clean can see what might be minora.?? and approx. 3/4 in. opening with above described bulb inside. no signs of uti or bowel problems.no discharge.please advise!!! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7411-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7411_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:13:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/959571/62130</link><title>When i open my mouth wide open, my jaws hurts. Is that a sign of a heart attack</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7411-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7411_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:13:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/968832/138722</link><title>inside my labia minora instead of having my urethra and then the vaginal opening underneath i have a huge piece of spongey flesh and then underneath that a tiny vaginal opening</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7411-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7411_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:14:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/866145/160791</link><title>I have 3 flat open sores on the opening lips of my vagina should I be worried, plus they itch like crazy</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7411-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7411_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:14:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/549290/127772</link><title>Yesterday I bit on my left side into a frozen cream puff. I felt something crack in my jaw. When I open my jaw wide, I feel and hear the "crack mid way, but not when my jaw is wide opened or closed.</title><description>... What can I do to remedy the problem. I had NEVER experienced anything similar before. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7411-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7411_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:14:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/233369/75286</link><title>After I have been asleep my eyes are difficult to open. I have to tub them to get them open.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7411-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7411_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:15:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/encyclopedia/408/66.html</link><title>Open Wounds</title><description>... A wound is an injury that causes either an internal or external break in body tissue. An open wound (as in a knife cut) is a break in the skin or mucous membrane. The most common accidents resulting in open wounds are falls, mishandling of sharp objects, accidents with tools or machinery, and car accidents. A closed wound (a contusion or internal bleeding ) is a bruise that damages the underlying tissue without breaking the skin (as in a black eye). There are at least five different types of open wounds: Abrasions An abrasion is a skin wound caused by rubbing or scraping the skin against a hard, rough surface. Bleeding in this type of wound is usually limited, but it is important that the skin be cleaned in order to guard against infection. Incisions An incision is a cut caused by a knife, the rough edge of metal, broken glass, a razor blade or some other sharp object. This type of wound generally bleeds rapidly and heavily. If the cut is deep, muscles, tendons and nerves may be damaged. Lacer... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7411-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7411_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:15:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002780.html</link><title>Drain opening agents overview</title><description>... Definition ... ... Drain opening agents are chemicals used to open clogged drains, often in homes. Drain opening agent poisoning can occur if a child accidentally drinks these chemicals, or if someone splashes the poison into the eyes when pouring it or breathes in the fumes of "foaming" drain openers. ... This is for information only and not for use in the treatment or management of an actual poison exposure. If you have an exposure, you should call your local emergency number (such as 911) or the National Poison Control Center at 1-800-222-1222. ... ... Poisonous Ingredient ... ... ... Hydrochloric acid ... Lye (sodium hydroxide or caustic soda) ... Potassium hydroxide ... Sulfuric acid ... ... ... Where Found ... ... ... ... Drain cleaners ... or openers ... ... Note: This list may not include all sources of drain opening agents. ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>