<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7412">when queen elisabeth</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:15:34" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7412-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7412_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:15:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/486637/102085</link><title>I am looking for an RA support group in Queens, New York or Nassau County, New York. help?</title><description>...   ... Thank you ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7412-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7412_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:15:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/973065/93161/migrainequeen</link><title>MigraineQueen</title><description>... Any longtime migraine sufferers out there who managed to get off ergotomines after years of use? I know, bite the bullet, but it's so painful. Lyrica once worked for a month, no headaches at all, but they returned. My self-diagnosis after 41 years of daily episodes is  "rebound headaches." Any suggestions appreciated. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7412-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7412_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:16:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/11096/awful-dont-queen</link><title>Yes, Migraines and headaches are awful, but don't be a whiner or drama queen!</title><description>... Now, before anyone jumps on me for the title of this SharePost and not being sympathetic toward my fellow Migraine and headache sufferers, hear me out, please. We all need to vent sometimes -- to complain about our headaches and Migraines and be heard by people who understand. If we didn't have that kind of outlet, we'd never be able to cope with our health issues. I fully understand and encourage healthy venting, and I'll gladly do anything I can to help someone who's venting and needs help and support. That begs the question of what's the difference between venting and whining. Here are some ways not to turn a vent into a whine... Seriously consider suggestions people make and information they share with you. Take whatever action you can to make things better for yourself. Don't misuse the 1 - 10 pain scale or exaggerate your level, even to make a point. A pain level of 10 should be reserved for pain beyond anything you've ever felt before. At a level 9... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7412-04"><link>http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/149721/resilience-pop</link><title>Madonna: What We Can Learn about Resilience from the Queen of Pop</title><description>...   ... Madonna, who is now in her fifties, was born Madonna Louise Veronica Ciccone in Bay City, Michigan to parents Silvio "Tony" Ciccone and Madonna Fortin. It was not long into Madonna’s childhood when s... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7412-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7412_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:16:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/55537/25948/gas-queen</link><title>gas queen</title><description>... Well I was better for abit, then had a stressful weekend &amp; now it's back. The EKG test last Wends. went  well, heart seems okay. Got married on Fri, it was beautiful. Falling out w/friend this Sun. (cause of stress)... so the gas is back. Mostly burping. Freaking out because there's like there's a balloon on my leftside, near the lower part of ribcage. Sometimes spreads out to belly, but not like last time when I felt full &amp; didn't eat. Mild burning in chest. I am burping all the time, has nothing to do w/what I ate. Tried Gas Relief... but it doesn't seem to help... I need help. The insurence kicks in on the 1st. I could go back to my doctor's &amp; spend like another $100... but I rather not. Should I be worried? ... Lissa ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7412-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7412_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:17:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/94143/31217/queen-heartache</link><title>I am the King of Pain and the Queen of Heartache.</title><description>...   ... All I said was to fucking tuck your pockets in and when you didn't I said I wouldn't go, just to see if you would do it. You didn't so I sighed and got up but you told me to not go if I didn't want to. ...   ... I was actually looking foreward to going on a walk, jog, or run or whatever the fuck you want to call it but instead you said you'd outrun me anyway. You basically just told me to go fuck off. ...   ... I may just be overly emotional or whatever but it really hurt. You don't even fucking care that I turned around and cried when you walked out the door. Or that you made me feel like complete shit. ...   ... Why do you keep doing this to me? How do you? If you ever tried to hurt me intentionally I don't know what I'd do with myself. Because if you can do this much damage without even trying I... ...   ... Whatever. I'm sorry that I was being difficult. I'm sorry that I was in a crappy mood. I'm sorry that I feel like shit when that happens. I'm sorry th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7412-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7412_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:17:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/question/107793/87085</link><title>Looking for a support group in Manhattan or Queens for a 21 year old with sz.</title><description>...   ... A very shy gentle boy, feelilng very lonely and isolated, and needs to be able to speak to and be in contact with people with some of the same challenges he faces. ...   ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7412-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7412_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:17:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/94755/26266/lithium-queen</link><title>lithium queen</title><description>... i have bipolar disorder, and was diagnosed early in life, and am now on ambilify, zoloft, depakote and xanax, my wife is my support group and my two boys.   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7412-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7412_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:18:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/c/9487/20235/royals</link><title>More British Royals Highlight Osteoporosis and Scanners for Detection</title><description>... While Camilla, the Duchess of Cornwall, is best known for her activism to raise awareness about osteoporosis, another member of Britain's royal family is bringing attention to the condition as well. Princess Anne -- daughter of Queen Elizabeth and known as the Princess Royal -- is slated to visit the new osteoporosis scanner at the Bradford Royal Infirmary next Tuesday.   The new device will replace an older model, increasing detail and reducing wait times to get a scan. It's great to see, once again, such a high-profile individual taking the time to help the public become more informed about osteoporosis and the importance of prevention and diagnosis.   Read more about the royal visit at www.thetelegraphandargus.co.uk/news/newsindex/display.var.2027320.0.princess_to_visit_scanner.php ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7412-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7412_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:18:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/sleep-disorders/c/5954/54410/sleeping</link><title>Sleeping Double in a Single Bed</title><description>... ... However, please consider the alternative. Snuggling together on a narrow bed may sound appealing to the newlyweds, but believe me, keep it up and the honeymoon will soon be over. Buy a bed large enough to give both people room to move around, stretch or roll over without disturbing his or her partner. Double is okay, but a queen or king size bed, if you have the room, is even better. ...   ... Think about it. You just doze off and your bed partner rolls over and slams you in the back with a hard knee. Or he or she may begin to snore , a most irritating sound to say the least. This one night time habit has been known to drive a spouse into a separate room to sleep. That's not good for a marriage. ...   ... To sleep well, people need comfort. A large bed, the right amount of blankets and a firm mattr... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>