<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7413">alkan piano</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:18:32" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7413-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7413_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:18:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/59238/158434/playing-practice</link><title>Losing Weight is Like Playing the Piano - Practice Makes Perfect</title><description>...   ... You go on a diet.  Particularly in January when the will to change is quite strong, you are convinced that this time you have the food and fitness equation all figured out.  I’ve been there myself, at a very young age (14), and I was convinced if I just do the cabbage soup diet, or the no grain carbohydrate diet or th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7413-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7413_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:18:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/1866/22858/hood</link><title>Visiting the Neurologist: The Importance of Check Ups</title><description>... Once again, I was reminded of the importance of MS maintenance. The value of not postponing doctor visits because "I feel fine".   Recently, I noticed a lingering burning smell in my basement by my water heater. My husband suggested that we get our home's chimney swept.   What I thought would be a twenty-minute, under a hundred-buck visit, turned into something much more...   When the chimney guys removed the water heater and gas venting tube, an avalanche of debris spilled out. There was 100 % blockage!!! The whole inside liner had collapsed. Gee, that was a surprise!   This utterly unexpected revelation struck a chord with me. Too often I feel like I want to postpone a doctors appointment until "something's up" or have my check up MRI's or blood work done when I have "extra" time.   You can't always see what's going on concerning MS, and I surely had no idea the peril that my family was in. Thank goodness that I caugh... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7413-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7413_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:19:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002825.html</link><title>Wood stains overview</title><description>... Definition Wood stains are products used for wood finishing. Wood stain poisoning occurs when someone swallows these substances. This is for information only and not for use in the treatment or management of an actual poison exposure. If you have an exposure, you should call your local emergency number (such as 911) or the National Poison Control Center at 1-800-222-1222. Poisonous Ingredient Hydrocarbons, or substances containing only carbon and hydrogen. Other ingredients may include: Alcohol Alkanes Cyclo alkanes Glycol ether Corrosives, such as sodium hydroxide (lye) Where Found Various wood stains Note: This list does not include all sources of wood stain. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7413-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7413_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:19:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002895.html</link><title>Fuel oil overview</title><description>... Definition Fuel oil poisoning occurs when someone swallows, breathes in (inhales), or touches fuel oil. This is for information only and not for use in the treatment or management of an actual poison exposure. If you have an exposure, you should call your local emergency number (such as 911) or the National Poison Control Center at 1-800-222-1222. Alternative Names Kerosene poisoning Poisonous Ingredient Hydrocarbons (alkanes, cycloalkanes, aromatics) Where Found Fuel oil Kerosene Note: This list may not include all sources of fuel oil. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7413-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7413_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:19:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/351552/144497</link><title>I have recently been diagnosed having RA. I have not seen a rheumatologist as of yet. I am experiencing muscle spasms in my whole body is this part and parcel of this disease?</title><description>... I play piano and last night at rehearsal, (after 2 and a half hours of sitting at the piano) I got up from the piano and my whole body felt locked, I could barely move, back, legs, arms, especially my legs. After a few steps, I was more relaxed. Is this supposed to be happening? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7413-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7413_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:20:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/574/14007/de-view-life</link><title>Vista de Vida [View of Life]</title><description>...   This is the first piece I composed for choir &amp; full orchestra. I wrote the horn section for my friend Cameron who played it with me. If you listen closely you can hear me playing the guitar &amp; piano. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7413-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7413_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:20:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/question/691325/163514</link><title>I've heard I can get finger joint replacement for disfiguring arthritis in a joint. Is that true?</title><description>... The affected joint is in the fourth finger on my right hand, and is the joint closer to the hand. It is currently deformed and painful, and prevents me from using that finger, particularly prevents me from playing piano. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7413-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7413_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:20:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/81712/32534</link><title>Is Duo-Anglucid a generic for Glucovance</title><description>... I am playing piano on a cruise ship and am getting my medicAtions in Mexico.  I have purchased Duo-Anglucid (Collins is the manufacturer).  How does it compare to Glucovance? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7413-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7413_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:21:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/370827/57922</link><title>are the miagranes I have .started making me wake up on the floor with stairs.</title><description>... My Miagrane is almost every 2 days to 4, The aura comes on fast and it's like a light bulb was turned on in the back of head. I have begun to finding mysel on the floor knocked out once a piano and the other times mostly stairs why? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7413-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7413_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:21:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/63219/21295/person</link><title>Creating Contentment for A Person With Alzheimer's</title><description>... I'll always remember sharing pumpernickle bread with honey on it with an 86 year old lady who had midstage Alzheimer's.  She was originally from Denmark.  Alzheimer's had not caused her words to be garbled, but part of the time she spoke in Danish.  When she did this I studied her face and eyes, and listened intently, trying to sense the feeling even if I could not understand the words.  Perhaps this was the more important part, because she would smile and I knew we were connecting.  We  shared some wonderful times.   Her relatives were far away and she was a widow.  When we met I asked about her favorite foods.  She smiled, and with her Danish accent said, "Pumpernickle and honey - OH, I always love that."   Thus began our midafternoon ritual of this special treat.  Other familiar foods associated with pleasant memories included Danish pastries.  For th... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>