<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7415">most anticipated games of 2013</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:24:48" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7415-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7415_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:24:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/82083/163932/migraine-patient-gratitude</link><title>You posted A Migraine Patient's 30 Days of Gratitude 2013 - "Ender's Game"</title><description>...   ... Last night, I was blessed to go see the movie my family has waited for approximately a decade, and thankfully, it was made in such a way that I was able to watch Ender's Game with my eyes open ! ...   ... I read the book the movie has been based on because my kids asked me to read it. I had no interest in a sci-fi story, but I did want to support my kids and have something in common to talk about. I was hooked. When my son played the audiobook version on a trip to the doctor (a four hour drive each way) my Hubs even became hooked on the story. When we heard there would be a movie, we got excited enough that even my Hubs who refuses to go to a movie, was ready to drop all and drive an hour to the nearest theater. ...   ... I love a good action movie, but I have terrible light triggers . I wear protective sunglasses most of the ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7415-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7415_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:25:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/158921/healthy-snacking</link><title>Healthy Game Day Snacking on a Diet</title><description>... Game day is here! Whether you’re watching the big game from your living room couch or are one of the lucky few who are tailgating at Super Bowl 2013, you will be rooting for your favorite team and chowing down snacks. Most traditional Super Bowl spreads are unhealthy pub grub: A buffet of easy-to-prepare appetizers and entrees that go well with beer. These foods are not healthy for the average person, and pose a greater threat for those of us on a diet. ...   ... I have eliminated refined foods, fast food, red meat, sugar, saturated fats, starches, and grains from my diet. I’ve worked hard to lose weight and educate myself on how to eat healthy. So, I am not about to let game day cramp my style. Neither will I allow my style (diet) to hamper my enjoyment today. Believe it or not, it is completely possible, dare I say easy, to make delicious and nutritious Super Bowl Party fare. ...   ... Since Super Bowl 2013 takes place in New Orleans, why not prepare some of the area's tradit... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7415-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7415_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:25:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/2573/game-table</link><title>The Significance of the Game Table</title><description>... After the first day of the sale, my dad called to share its success. He started to rattle off the things that had been sold. None of it caused a twinge on my part until he mentioned the game table. It’s strange to think that this game table would be the thing that would get to me. I didn’t have that reaction when Dad told me about the sale of Mom’s sewing machine, where she loved to create unusual clothes. And it wasn’t the iron table with the glass top that had had been part of my childhood memories. ... The game table wasn’t a family heirloom. Instead, it had been a part of our family’s lives after Mom had cust... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7415-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7415_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:25:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/1443/162238/video-addiction-children-autism</link><title>Video Game Addiction Possible for Children with ADHD and Autism</title><description>... ... Problematic Game Playing ... ... Video games offer relaxation and with the development of multi-player games, can offer socialization that children with ADHD and autism often miss out on - even if it is online and not in person. But playing video games can also become problematic. Problematic game playing is characterized by: ... ... ... Recurrent thoughts about playing, or the consistent urge to play, even when you are doing something else ... Restlessness or irritability when not able to play ... Attempts to reduce the amount of time spend on games or to stop without success ... Failing grades (or performance at work) because of time spent on ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7415-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7415_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:25:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/164617/great-weight-gain-addiction</link><title>Great Weight Gain Addiction Game, Part 8</title><description>...   ... In 1999, food company big wigs gathered in Minneapolis to hear a presentation about an alarming increase of obesity in the United States and how to best address it.  ... The meeting was held at the Pillsbury headquarters. One of the executives had become concerned after viewing  pictures of obese children who were struggling with diabetes and had early signs of heart disease and hypertension. ... This executive met with food science experts who warned that people were unable to withstand some of the concoctions being brewed by food companies. He felt it was time to sound the alarm to CEOs that their companies were making products that were contrary to the public well-being. ... The Minneapolis presentation was given, complete with 114 slides. The audience was told that half of American adults were overweight and that one-quarter were obese. They were also told that the number of obese children exceeded 12 million. Surely something must be done. ... The speaker went silent... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7415-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7415_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:26:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/164877/calorie-counts-game-changer</link><title>Are Calorie Counts On Menus A Game Changer?</title><description>... The premise seems sound enough. If consumers see a menu choice followed by a calorie count the length of an area code, they will shy away from the double bacon cheeseburger and make a more healthy choice. ... The idea has become popular enough and appears logical enough that restaurants are being forced to tack on calories counts to their menus . And so we are left with the big dollar question: Does any of this actually work? ... A Case of We Like What We Like ... As mandated by the Affordable Care Act, all restaurants that have 20 or more locations nationally are required to post the number of calories in food and drink items offered on their menus... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7415-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7415_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:26:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/82083/163929/days-gratitude-introduction</link><title>A Migraine Patient's 30 Days of Gratitude 2013 - Introduction &amp; Index</title><description>...   ... Looking for things to be thankful for can change how we see everyday life though. It can be an important part of our daily Migraine and headache management program and how we deal with our invisible illnesses . ...   ... I decided to share my journal for the 30 days of November because we often think of November as the month to be thankful. On the days I miss, Teri is going to share hers with you as well. ...   ... Most of you already know Teri, but since I am new here, I wanted this to be a chance for you not only to see a gratitude journal in action, but also to get to know me as a person and a patient - just like you. The HealthCentral Migraine community is your home, and I'm wanting to make it my home as well as fit in as a part of your online... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7415-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7415_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:26:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/727598/159856/highlights-alzheimer</link><title>2013 Facts &amp; Figures Report Highlights Latest Alzheimer's Numbers</title><description>... These sobering facts are just a few of the many provided in the Alzheimer’s Association’s 2013 Alzheimer’s  Disease Facts and Figures . And there are many more. For instance, it’s believed that 5.2 million Americans have Alzheimer’s disease in 2013. Of those, five million are estimated to be 65 years and older. Approximately 200,000 people who are under the age of 65 have early-onset Alzheimer’s.  The percentages by age group of people in the U.S. who have Alzheimer’s disease also are interesting: 4 percent are under the age of 65, 13 percent are between the ages of 65-74, 44 percent are between the ages of 75-84, and 38 percent are 85 years of age and above. ... Not surprisingly, the prevalence of Al... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7415-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7415_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:27:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/120/160458/schizophrenia-news-april</link><title>Schizophrenia News: April 2013</title><description>...   ... A report by the Work Foundation indicates only eight percent of the people diagnosed with schizophrenia are in paid employment compared with 71 percent of the general population. ...   ... Seven out of 10 people with this illness felt they were stigmatized because of a lack of understanding, stigma, fear and discrimination towards individuals with schizophrenia. ...   ... The report, Working with Schizophrenia, details that people with schizophrenia in paid employment are over five times more likely to achieve remission from this condition than those who are unemployed or in unpaid employment. ...   ... (Job applicants with schizophrenia facing  'discrimination,' retrieved on February 18, 2013 from http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/ . . .) ...   ... According to a new study: white European individuals with schizophreni... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7415-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7415_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:27:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/633468/162302/superheroes-ja</link><title>Superheroes and Friends for Life: The 2013 JA Conference</title><description>...   ... This was the Arthritis Foundation’s annual Juvenile Arthritis Conference held this year in Anaheim, California on July 20 th 2013, and I was fortunate to attend as RAHealthCentral’s special correspondent. ...   ... JA patients and their families were already tired from the previous day’s events, yet thrilled to be taking on another day of learning and camaraderie with their fellow rheumatic community. ...   ... Discussions of the deliciousness of bacon soon gave way to intr... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>