<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7416">release date bioshock infinite</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:27:48" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7416-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7416_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:27:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/4493/13575/relief</link><title>Relief and Release</title><description>... Hello,      My name Sarah and I am fortunate enough to not have to deal with pain 24/7, unlike my mother.  My mother and I have always had a very close relationship, closer than the typical mother-daughter relationship.  But my Mom has Lupus, and suffers from migraines frequently.  Sometimes her headaches are so bad she can't get out of bed and won't open her eyes because the light hurts to much.  I feel horrible when I get frusterated with her and her pain.  But having a family member in pain 24/7 is very hard and puts a stress on everyone.  I have found a way to positivly express myself though....Photography.  Photography has provided a great relief for me, and this picture is about people in pain seeking release, or relief, just like the title.       Thanks,          Sarah    ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7416-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7416_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:28:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/5949/154642/application</link><title>Zohydro ER (Extended-Release Hydrocodone) – FDA Accepts New Drug Application for Review</title><description>...   ... Hydrocodone is one of the most frequently prescribed opioid drugs for the management of moderate to severe chronic pain. There are, however, two features that set Zohydro ER apart from other hydrocodone products currently available: ... ... ... It does not contain acetaminophen. ... ... ... It is an extended-release medication. ... ... ...   ... Other hydrocodone medications currently available (like Vicodin and Lortab) all contain acetaminophen , which can be hard on the liver. They are also all immediate-release, meaning they have to be taken every four to six hours. Zohydro is intended to be administered every 12 hours to provide round-the-clock pain management for an extended period of time. ...   ... Under the Prescription Drug User Fee Act, the goal for a standard review of an NDA is 10 months from NDA subm... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7416-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7416_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:28:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/35832/15706/albums-15-ago</link><title>TWO NEW ALBUMS released as of 15 minutes ago! WWW.MYSPACE.COM/ANDREWMURA</title><description>... I'm happy to say that as of the first of November, I have released 2 new albums.  The first is the most topical and appropriate to this site, and is called VIEWS FROM THE ASYLUM.  It is a rock opera of sorts that catalogues the incredible journey i undertoook while being held for 16 weeks in an irish asylum. a little wizard of Oz, a bit Pink Floyd's The Wall, and a hefty slice of greek tragedy. and every word is true. from conversations with my soul, to talking to Jesus, to speaking with the devil, to being tested by God (and being found lacking)  the epic plot will  have you putting yourself in my place, wondering how it could get any grander, how it could get any worse.  The second album, which is my first to stray nearly totally from the themes of the first four (especially mental disease and trauma), entitled Stranger, is a half melodic alternative, half scalding blues album, and fun for the whole family.  You will be able to order t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7416-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7416_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:28:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/r/medications/bontril-slow-release-oral-57220/side-effects</link><title>Bontril Slow-Release Oral Precautions and Side Effects</title><description>... Generic Name: PHENDIMETRAZINE - ORAL Pronounced: (FEN-dye-meh-TRA-zeen) Bontril Slow-Release Oral Precautions ... Before taking phendimetrazine, tell your doctor or ... pharmacist if you are allergic to it; or to any other sympathomimetic amines ... (e.g., decongestants such as pseudoephedrine, stimulants such as amphetamine, ... appetite suppressants such as phentermine); or if you have any other allergies. ... This product may contain inactive ingredients, which can cause allergic ... reactions or other problems. Talk to your pharmacist for more ... details. ... This medication should not be used if you have certain ... medical conditions. Before using phendimetrazine, consult your doctor or ... pharmacist if you have: ... ... uncontrolled high blood pressure ... glaucoma ... history of alcohol/drug abuse ... vascular heart disease (e.g., chest pain, heart ... attack) ... mental/mood problems (e.g., severe anxiety, bipolar disorder, ... psychosis, schizophrenia) ... high blood pressu... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7416-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7416_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:29:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/18457/62977</link><title>Seeking information of better medication for chronic back pain while awaiting surgery date.</title><description>... Hi, My name is B, I have been on hydro for almost 3 years progressively having to take more to just help the pain, I was scheduled to have fusion in December one week prior to my surgery my neurosurgeon retired, leaving me hanging. I have finally found a new surgeon who I am comfortable with and will be rescheduling my surgery. My question is, I tak hydro 10mg 1 every 6 hours, if I don't and the pain gets severe they won't give me any relief.  So I do take them regularly,  I have asked my doctor if there isn't anything ... that is time released or that would work better, I feel like I am building up a resistance. She told me I am already taking the strongest medicine I can take.  I feel like she's just tired of my pain and would rather I didn't bother her anymore.  Any suggestions, they would be deeply appreciated.  Thanks litterally the pain in the butt!! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7416-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7416_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:29:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/55/50099/children-increase-risk</link><title>Children's Birth Date Can Increase Their Risk for Asthma</title><description>... In this entry, I would like to discuss some very recent research that has grabbed media attention: the effect of birth during the time of year on the development of asthma in infants . There has been a well-known association between viral infection (typically from cold viruses and related viruses) in infancy and the risk of developing asthma in childhood. Until now, we haven't known whether early viral infection contributes to the development of asthma or if young kids who will become asthmatic just get early viral infections more readily. ...   ... The current research suggests that viral infection in infancy ( ...   ... Risks of developing asthma in infants The study that was recently released looked at the time of year during which babies were born and the risk of developing asthma around ages 3-5. They were curious if being born 3-6 months be... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7416-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7416_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:29:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/breakup-256892-5.html</link><title>Mending a Broken Heart</title><description>... Everyone's been there. You're so in love with someone one week, and the next week your relationship is over. You've been hit by an emotional Hurricane Andrew, you're never getting back that Beastie Boys CD you left at your ex's house, and you can't even get out of bed. All you want to know is how long it's going to take before you're able to live your life like a normal person again. The conservative answer is that it takes up to six months to heal from a breakup. For those of you that don't like the sound of that, though, follow some simple steps. They should bring you closer to getting past this old relationship and prevent you from making the same mistakes in the future. Cry Me a River In the end, a breakup is a change , and big changes are difficult in almost any regard. Your ex knew you inside and out and it makes sense that breaking up with him or her could be overwhelming. Ending a relationship may also be the first time you experience a signif... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7416-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7416_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:29:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/sextechniques-256852-5.html</link><title>Speak Up for Better Sex</title><description>... Despite all the pop songs, TV shows, and movies about sex that would have you believe otherwise, a lot of us (or so we hear) are having sex that is average, even boring. For young people, particularly young women, sex can be something of a challenge because they're still discovering what turns them on. "One problem among people, particularly men, is that they learn about sex from watching porn," says Karen Gless, Ph.D., a marriage and family therapist in San Diego, CA. "In bed, they mimic the big, dramatic moves they see in porn films, but that's not necessarily what feels best for their partners," she says. What's the solution? Well, talking about what turns you on can go a long way towards better sex. If your partner's technique leaves you less than thrilled, or if his or her attitude could use some adjusting, perhaps the two of you should be talking more and boinking less. But beware: criticism directed towards a partner who's naked, insecure, ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7416-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7416_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:30:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/149661/trial-guidelines</link><title>New Migraine Medication Clinical Trial Guidelines Published</title><description>...   ... Just as health care professionals generally turn to the International Headache Society (IHS) for diagnosing Migraine and other headache disorders by using their International Classification of Headache Disorders, Second Edition (ICHD-II), researchers turn to IHS guidelines for setting up and conducting clinical trials for Migraine medications. ...   ... Yesterday, the IHS released " Guidelines for controlled trials of drugs in mig... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7416-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7416_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:30:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/news-159498-5.html</link><title>Doctors' Scores on Communication Predict Complaints to Authorities</title><description>... “We found that communication and clinical decision-making ability were important predictors of future complaints to regulatory authorities.” 1   Patients who feel that their relationship with their doctors is lacking two-way communication will be especially interested in a JAMA article released today. Tamblyn et al concluded, “Scores achieved in patient-physician communication and clinical decision making on a national licensing examination predicted complaints to medical regulatory authorities.” 1 Poor skills in patient communication is not a new issue. For decades, research has shown poor communication skills to be associated with: lower levels of patient satisfaction, more complaints, a higher risk of malpractice claims, and poorer health outcomes. Although medical schools responded to these issues by adding patient communication and clinical skills to their curriculum, there was neither any systematic evaluat... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>