<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7417">dota 2 heroes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:30:45" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7417-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7417_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:30:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/guide-210448-5.html</link><title>Diabetes Comics -- Diabetes heros in action</title><description>... See more of Kerri's story at SixUntilMe.com ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7417-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7417_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:31:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/sleep-disorders/c/5954/118776/guitar</link><title>Guitar Hero Study Shows Link Between Sleep and Test Scores</title><description>...   ... Guitar Hero requires complex motor skills. Dictionary.com describes motor skills as: "the ability to perform complex muscle-and-nerve acts that produce movement; fine motor skills are small movements like writing and tying shoes, gross motor skills are large movements like walking and kicking." ...   ... Students who learned a song in the evening followed by a good night's sleep were tested against students who learned a song in the morning followed by regular daytime activities. Those who learned the material before sleeping managed a better performance the next day than those who studied the material in the morning and were tested that evening. This is sometimes called sleep learning. ...   ... Th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7417-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7417_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:31:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/80106/140000/hero</link><title>Represent RA: Are You an Everyday Health Hero?</title><description>...   ... Are you and Everyday Hero? Do you know someone who is? If so, you may want to check this out. ...   ... The following is taken directly from the promotional material and does not constitute any endorsement or lack thereof  on behalf of MyRACentral. This is information only. What you do with it is up to you ...   ... The Producers behind  "The Biggest Loser" are in sea... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7417-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7417_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:31:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/156672/mcgovern-personal</link><title>George McGovern, Personal Hero and Personal Values: The Bipolar Question of the Week</title><description>...   ... In 1972 - the first Presidential campaign I was eligible to vote in - I proudly cast my ballot for McGovern. I knew he was going to lose in a landslide to Nixon, but at least I had the satisfaction of standing up and being counted. Being a natural born depressive inclined to manic flights of thinking, I naturally interpreted the election result as being the beginning of the end of America. ...   ... In just about every election since, I have come to the same conclusion. And, of course, with the brain I was born with, there is no way of convincing me I am wrong. But the craz... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7417-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7417_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:32:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/32873/105388/heroes</link><title>MS Heroes: Dr. W. Ian McDonald</title><description>...   ... I kept going to my doctor for various symptoms , and he sent me to various specialists who treated each problem. Sound familiar so far? There was something wrong that was bigger than the sum of all of these separate episodes, but I didn't know what it was. Then, I met Dr. McDonald through his work. The pattern of my symptoms was recognized as neurological, and I was introduced to the MRI. My particular symptoms over time with the results of my MRI gave the sum of these episodes a name. It was at the end of years of symptoms and seeing doctors but with no answers — I had MS. Dr. McDonald's work began as he studied neurology in New Zealand and later in the UK, focusing on multiple sclerosis . He was one of few neurologists... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7417-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7417_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:32:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/151926/bipolar-question</link><title>Your Heroes: The Bipolar Question of the Week</title><description>...   ... First, the newsman I always looked up to, who lived by the code: “To comfort the afflicted, to afflict the comfortable.” Seriously, what other public figure are you aware of that you could describe this way?  ...   ... Then there was Mike Wallace the mental health advocate, the man who surprised everyone in 1997 with his disclosures of severe depression. Suddenly, the issue was out in the open. Two years later, after a lifetime of denial, I was seeking help. I can’t help but wonder. ...   ... And of course Mike Wallace the role model, the man who kept going - going-going - as the star in the highest stress, most unforgiving occupation on earth all the way into his late eighties. ...   ... Not to mention his fearlessness; his fearlessness!   Everything he stood for - this was a man unafraid to look a dicta... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7417-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7417_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:32:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/116/19623/broken-places</link><title>Mental Health Heroes: Strong at the Broken Places</title><description>... Do you have a mental heath hero? I have a couple of them.   Pat Deegan, PhD, is one of my heroes. Check out her thought-provoking recovery journal on her website, at www.patdeegan.com . And read her story about the sea rose -it is so gorgeous, it just about makes me weep.   Another one of my heroes has to be Dr. Kay Redfield Jamison . The books she's written are so helpful and hopeful. And her authority as a researcher who lives with a mood disorder makes her that much more important to many of us-a researcher who knows how it feels to live with our illness!   Now, I'm one very lucky person because both Pat and Kay, along with my third hero, will all be co-keynoting with award-winning author Richard M. Cohen at the 2008 DBSA National Conference in Virginia in September. But that is not why I'm writing this. I'm writing this because I've been thinking a lot about my third hero, Larry Fricks, over the past few weeks.   Larry , as you may or m... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7417-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7417_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:32:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/7494/10985/todays-heroes</link><title>Alzheimer's Caregivers: Today's Heroes</title><description>... Recently, the Alzheimer's Foundation of America's Quilt to Remember was in Chicago as part of its 2007 national tour.  I was on site to participate in the opening ceremonies.  We laid out the Quilt to Remember on the ground in Grant Park—a task that often takes a few hours given the massive size of the panels and the enormous number of them (more than 100 at that time). People immediately started flowing by to experience it.  One family strikes my memory.  They had created and submitted a quilt panel, and had traveled to see it laid out here. They kneeled before it, and were in tears.  It was heartbreaking.    I walked over to introduce myself, and we spent some time discussing their experience of Alzheimer's disease with their mom.  "She was a wonderful woman," they pointed out repeatedly.  Apparently she had been sick for some time.  They remember back at the beginning.  Everyone knew something was wrong. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7417-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7417_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:33:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/330514/109504/resolution</link><title>New Year's Resolution Blogger: My Gym Hero</title><description>...   ... Sandy is my personal trainer at the gym. Before you go thinking that I must be pretty well off to afford a trainer, let me explain how our relationship came to be. I met Sandy at the first... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7417-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7417_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:33:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/160725/hero-journey-bipolar-question</link><title>Your Hero's Journey - The Bipolar Question of the Week</title><description>...   ... This is the part of the enterprise where the left brain takes over for a little while. In essence, if you’re sinking your boat in chapter thirty, you need to have iceberg warnings in chapter five. Your second draft is where you start making these adjustments. You’re also checking to make sure your heroes are sufficiently likable and villains despicable and a lot more. ...   ... You’ve probably heard about Joseph Campbell’s The Hero’s Journey. To vastly oversimplify: Hero sets off on a quest (or the quest imposes itself on the hero), hero enlists friends, deals with problem only to find himself involved in an even g... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>