<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7421">story magic flute</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:43:04" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7421-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7421_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:43:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/45116/57322/weight-revisited</link><title>Is There a Magic Pill for Weight Loss - Revisited</title><description>... About a year ago, I wrote a two part blog regarding whether or not there was a "magic pill" for people who suffer from obesity. I went down a laundry list of medications that have been approved for use to help people lose weight. Toward the end of the piece, I promised to keep readers updated about new drugs or interventions that appeared promising. There is some exciting research continuing in the obesity area. The most promising drug in at least a decade, known as rimonabant, has both raised and dashed hopes in a period of less than two years. It's an interesting story, but one that also continues, unfortunately, to prove my theory- no magic pill will ever substitute for good diet, exercise and plenty of sleep. ...   ... The old well known side effect of marijuana, extreme hunger, spurred interest in the cannabanoid blocking compound rimonabant. Sanofi-Aventis, the pharmaceutical company who was first to release and market the product in Europe in 2006 under the brand name Acomplia&amp;... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7421-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7421_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:43:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/45116/30705/magic-pill-weight</link><title>Is There A Magic Pill for Weight Loss?</title><description>... "there was something I could take" to "help me lose weight," I'd certainly be ... well off. I must have heard that more than I'd care to remember. The answer to ... that question is rather complicated. There are a few medicines out there that ... have been FDA approved for weight loss, but they are few and have some ... intolerable side effects for most of us. ...   ... The oldest weight loss concoctions on the market are in the ... sympathomimetic family, such as methamphetamine, phentermine and others. These ... are highly controlled substances that "rev up" your metabolism- which is why ... they were commonly called "uppers." Some unpleasant side effects include dry ... mouth, rapid heart rate, insomnia, anxiety and high blood pressure. Do they ... work? They sure do - in the short term. They're only approved for use for up to ... 12 weeks as part of a weight loss program. Often, however, they are used for ... longer periods and users become dependent on them. ...   ... Moreo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7421-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7421_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:43:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/666807/120936/in</link><title>Out with Magic Koolaid, in with waiting for the insurance company again</title><description>...   ... My rheumy says Orencia is next on the hit list, so I'm back to waiting on the insurance company to evaluate whether I can take Orencia or not and let me know.  I really love the "medical management" we Americans have the "benefit" of recieving from our insurance system. ...   ... In any case, I'm sticking with my routine and doing my research on Orencia.  What can I expect in terms of side effects?  I'll still be using the MXT with Orencia, but the goal is to get off the methylpred if I can.  Scratch that...  The goal is remission, of cour... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7421-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7421_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:44:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/44/2377/magic-web</link><title>The Magic of the Web</title><description>... ... I can’t. It took me hours on the Internet to begin to understand, say, the biopsy lab report that came in after my lumpectomy. I tracked down descriptions of my diagnosis until, after many hours, I understood that “invasive” breast cancer meant it had broken out of the milk duct where it began but did not necessarily mean that it had reached the nodes. A friend thousands of miles away spent hours with me on the phone while we tracked down the bottom lines of one study after another, each on our own computer, running down links. ... ... It was on the Internet that I found out that my arthritic reaction to Arimidex was shared by... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7421-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7421_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:44:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/all</link><title>Black magic babaji -Black Magic Specialist Baba Ji o9928576434</title><description>... Black magic babaji -Black Magic Specialist Baba Ji ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7421-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7421_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:44:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/all</link><title>Black magic babaji -Black Magic Specialist Baba Ji o9928576434</title><description>... Black magic babaji -Black Magic Specialist Baba Ji ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7421-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7421_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:44:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/copd/c/91092/37873/adventures</link><title>Smoke-free Adventures: Share Your Quit Story</title><description>...   ... A number of us continued our lively discourse in the adjacent university cafeteria following the event and some of these folks volunteered to start a new SOS addiction recovery support group meeting there on campus in the near future. I gave them some SOS group meeting start-up materials; they had purchased copies of my various addiction recovery books as well. Persons who'd quit smoking, drinking alcohol and using drugs sh... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7421-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7421_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:45:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/9539/10911/story</link><title>my story</title><description>... i feel releaved to have finally found a place in which others have similar experieces as my own.  my pain started in 2000.  i have had many different diagnoses over the years-including atypical trigeminal neuralgia, trigemianl neuropathic pain and occipital nerolagia.  it was not until last summer that i was told i have atypical migraines, chronic daily headaches and cervogenic headaches.  i have tried many medications and nonmedication treatments over the years.  in 12/03 with the help of my neurologist and a pain management doctor, who did nerve block injections, i became pain free.  i got pregnant in 1/04 (and had a beautiful little girl 10/04) and remained pain free until 8/05.  i had a great pregnancy.  then boom-in 8/05 the pain was back and none of the treatments i had in the past were working.  i was hospitalized last summer for 8 days and was again recently hsopitalized for 6 days.  fortuntely, i have a very supportive husband... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7421-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7421_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:45:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/genital-herpes/c/219901/105862/story</link><title>My Story</title><description>...   ... I am 26 years old. A few years ago, I met someone and fell for him hard. I was in a place at the time where I had already gone through some tramatic sexual experiences that left me feeling powerless when it came to sex: ...   ... My very first sexual experience was a with a boyfriend who became physically abusive and when I broke up with him, he raped me. I was 19. Determined not to let that carry over into my next relationship I tried to pretend it didnt happen. The first time I had sex in the next relationship, I started to cry and felt dirty. I decided to take time to heal. I abstained from anything sexual and avoided relationship after relationship for nearly 2 years. The next relationship I entered into was with a best friend. I figured I could trust a friend with my heart and my bod... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7421-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7421_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:45:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/115292/58479/paul-story</link><title>Paul's Story</title><description>...   ... Paul had a cousin in every port.  Seriously, no matter where we traveled he would run into "another cousin."  He was a Brooklyn boy transplanted with his wife to southern California.  He lived everyday with a passion and just some of his hobbies included reviewing mystery novels, collecting first editions, wine collecting, playing tennis, volunteering and giving lots of legal advice to family, friends, and clients.  My problem?  He didn't apply those same "taking advice/taking care" principles to himself.  Our ongoing friendly banter would include his giving me career advice (almost daily) and reviewing my media contracts, while r... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>