<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7423">postdoc jobs european university biotech</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:49:11" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7423-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7423_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:49:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/141334/occupations</link><title>Happy Jobs: Which Occupations Can Boost Your Mood?</title><description>...   ... The Least Stressful Occupations ...   ... Everyone experiences some stress on the job . But excessive stress can le... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7423-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7423_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:49:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/870042/95887</link><title>University Accomodations</title><description>... My 22 yr old daughter has just been diagnosed and now has the documentation of what she suspects has been going on for a long time. The problem: she has a 40 page undergraduate thesis to write--and 9 months into it (no job, leaving the university community in Chicago, and moving home) she has about 10 lines written--even though she's been on Adderall for about a month. What accomodations could she ask from the university to help her meet this final requirement for her bachelor degree? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7423-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7423_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:49:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/22537/30374/evaluation</link><title>Evaluation at University of Michigan.</title><description>...   ... Next was the intake nurse.  She's a RN that has special training.  After that, she goes and discusses you with the doctor.  Then you go sit with the RN and the doctor. ...   ... All of it was talking. No scans or anything.  It was kind of upsetting, though.  I don't know about you, but when I go to regular therapy, I ...   ... - identify the issues ... - identify my goals ... - create strategies to deal with my issues so that I can reach my goals. ...   ... This was more like, "tell me about how messed up you are".  I got to discuss my dysfunctional childhood, abusive first marriage, how I've managed to never hold a job for more than a year at a time.  I left feeling like a loser, quite frankly.  It took 2-3 days for me to start feeling better. ... &amp;nbsp... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7423-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7423_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:50:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/28496/45855/universality</link><title>The Universality of Breast Cancer</title><description>...   ... Many new voices in the community have been popping up over the past year and they've proven to be both insightful and universal. The first step to finding a cure to breast cancer, or any cancer for that matter, is to get people excited about it. ...   ... If only the directly effected care, then nothing will get done. However, when we can convince people who don't seem to be connected with the disease that it is important for them to care, then we will have a trampoline to boost us over that first major hurdle. ... Breast Cancer is devious, destructive, heart breaking, and beautiful. The moment a woman is able to step away from herself, and realize she has more life left in however many months, years or decades than in the rest of her life leading up to that point, is one of the most beauti... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7423-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7423_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:50:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/93/2841/universal-america</link><title>Universal Healthcare in America?</title><description>... It’s a big thing for anyone with a chronic illness—health insurance. Ask anyone who sees specialists, who has expensive medications, or who has not-so-great insurance what they would do to make things easier, and you will almost always hear "universal health care." I am one of the lucky ones—my husband is in a union. We have amazing insurance. I think it is roughly $90 a month for the four of us, and includes dental and some vision. The best part of our insurance are the spending caps. It goes like this—we have a $500 deductible. After that is met, we have a $1500 out-of-pocket spending cap per person, and it is a total of $3000 for the family before we do not have co-pays any longer. That means that I no longer have co-pays each year starting somewhere between May and late June. I take at least 5 different medications each day, the cost of each prescription ranges from $12 for generics to $24 for name-brand drugs. Everything that I take regularly is ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7423-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7423_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:50:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/746721/57001/job-bipolar</link><title>Getting a Job with Bipolar</title><description>...   ... Now I am facing the situation of not being able to get a job or get into grad school due to my past. My past performance academically is a blight on my record, and my past job history (or lack thereof) also counts against me. There was a bad period of about four years after a severe suicide attempt that led to temporary death and resuscitation. My brain was damaged, and I had to spend a long time doing many mental exercises to get it up to snuff. After tha... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7423-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7423_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:51:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/100/35219/job-critical</link><title>Finding a Job - Critical Answers</title><description>... The first step in finding and keeping a good job involves a little soul searching.  The best way to do this is to ask and answer a series of questions.  These questions may seem remarkably simple, almost silly.  But don't be mislead.  They're of the utmost importance. ...   ... Before we begin with the questions, however, let's discuss the nature of the answers you must give.  There are at least three reasons why the questions may be difficult to answer: ...   ... 1)  The answers you give must be your answers and your answers alone . . . ...   ... You must tease out and set aside the opinions and expectations of others.  This does not mean that you shouldn't seek the advice of others.  In fact, the advice of others can be very helpful, especially when you start for the first time to measure your functionality in absolute terms.  But, you must remember that their advice represents their opinions.  Their opinions may influence your thinkin... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7423-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7423_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:51:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/120/50397/working-worker</link><title>The Working Life on the Job: Library Worker</title><description>... This blog series continues with a look at the kinds of jobs people with schizophrenia have been successful working at. Stumbling through cyber-space years ago, I met someone from Israel who is a librarian, as I am, and after that, it seemed everywhere I went, I discovered librarians with SZ. I'll use my experiences as the springboard for you to consider making such an employment leap. ... In June 2000, I obtained my MLS-Masters in Library and Information Science-from Pratt Institute, which is, unfortunately, close to $1,000 per credit now so I couldn't do that today. When I worked at the last insurance brokerage, I was demoted and decided to see a therapist but the health insurance authorized only five visits because I had a pre-existing condition. When I told her I was in danger of losing my job, she said she was a career counselor by day in Manhattan, and would help me in that regard. She gave me the MBTI and some vocational tests, and at our last visit, she suggested I'd make a go... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7423-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7423_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:51:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/945814/118045</link><title>Job anxiety</title><description>... I'm a 48 year old ESL teacher who emigrated to America to a small town in the Mid-west where my husband had a job at a small school, - that was in 2001.  The first job I had was as a Nursing assistant, where I spent some of my time cleaning up poop off the shower floor.  I also worked for Wyndeham hotel services in a small telephone booth, privately, with an autistic child who ruptured my varicose vein, and then subbed a little for the school district, until told that they were not hiring people who were not 'local' and had not been trained at the local University.  I picked up a few months teaching two Spanish migrant workers at a school outside the district three years ago, then worked in retail a little and spent a month working for the Census bureau.  Then I learnt the ESL program was expanding at the local University, and suddenly have a $46 an hour job.....I've never earned more than $14 an hour since coming to America.  I'm utterly daunted by my luck an... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7423-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7423_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:51:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/896502/138445/critical</link><title>Regular Movement Critical to Your Health When You Have a Desk Job</title><description>... Physiologists have found that sitting stops the circulation of lipase, which is a fat-absorbing enzyme. In a 2008 story on ScienceDaily.com , these researchers found that “standing up engages muscles and promotes the distribution of lipase, which prompts the body to process fat and cholesterol, independent of the amount of time spent exercising. They also found that standing up uses blood glucose and may discourage the development of diabetes.” ... More recently, The New York Times ran a story by Jame Vlahos entitled, “Is Sitting a Lethal Activity?” . The story looked at the work of Dr. James Levine of the Mayo Clinic, who is a key figure in the emerging field of inactivity studies. His studies... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>