<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7424">best italian food Rome</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:52:06" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7424-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7424_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:52:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/159897/secrets-eating-italian-food</link><title>6 Secrets to Eating Italian Food on a Diet</title><description>... ...   ... 6 Secrets to Eating Italian Food on a Diet ... Whichever grain-free, gluten-free, low carb, Paleo, Primal, GAPS, SCD, or bariatric diet you follow, if you think that means giving up Italian food then I have good news for you. Sure, you will have to forgo the carb-heavy pasta dishes, but Italian cuisine offers so many more delicious possibilities. With a passion for the flavors of the Mediterranean, such as fish, vegetables, fruit, nuts, and espresso, it's possible to live large on Italian food without growing large. Here's what to order - and what to avoid: ... ... Main Course ... First and foremost,  lean proteins  and lightly-cooked   fresh vegetables  should be at the center of your meal. Choose from a variety of main courses of freshly prepared broiled, poached, baked, grilled, or roasted poultry, meat, and seafood, accompanied by unbelievably good farm-fresh-to-table vegetables that are lightly steamed and dressed with fresh lemon and herbs.  ... ... Next... ... ... Fir... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7424-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7424_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:52:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/234255/121264/italian</link><title>but butts and Italian food</title><description>...   ... As I've written many times this past week I was a mess. So where did I go to get my dose of "Italian food?" First I went to Margaret. She was very concerned and asked if I needed to the the crisis unit. I wasn't that bad. Her love and concern helped me see through to what I must do. I went to my pdoc. He was helpful and I am grateful that he was. That was the first course..salad. ...   ... The next course..the soup. I sought help from you. Many have stood by me and cared enough to try and help guide me. I am grateful for you. ...   ... The bread... I then sought help from a church leader. In my fury I ran out when he tried to help. Even though I ran out he still was willing to help. Which in fact he did. ...   ... Now for dessert. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7424-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7424_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:52:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/38597/36256</link><title>i'm having a hard time finding the right foods to eat is there a list of foods that are like ready t</title><description>... I have type 2 and I just can't get a grip on the right foods to eat. I need to find someone that can go over the foods that I can eat, Breakfast  I have a piece of wheat toast, lunch well thats always hard for me cause I'm out driving around and to be honest its always fastfood  I d eat alot of mcdonalds chicken salads but not all the time, and a diet coke, dinner the basics  hamburger hotdogs, mexican food ,italian, alot of chicken and rice, I do the once in a while donut OUCH  I just had my A1c and it the highest its been at 7.4 164 level I do take actosplus just one aday and now he wants to put me on amaryl, I really don't want anymore drugs  can some one help me out   Thanks Jeff in Indy ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7424-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7424_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:53:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/592811/99431</link><title>Does anyone know of any foods that cause flair ups?</title><description>... I was wondering if anyone knows what foods to stay away from? I know we are all different, and what might upset one, might not the other. My friend and ate at this great Italian place the other day, and the next morning I was miserable. Any info would be appreciated. Thanks ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7424-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7424_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:53:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/ibd/c/question/65913/47396</link><title>I need to know foods that IBS people can eat?</title><description>... I am taking a PSW course and need information, for a recipe for people with IBS. My assignment is on a 14 yr old italian boy with IBS. I need to look for a recipe and make it, and present it to my class. Could you please help? .... Kit ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7424-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7424_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:53:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/75934/26159/hema-botox-blog</link><title>Botox Blog Part IV: The Italian Rat Study</title><description>...   ... Botox is FDA-approved for the treatment of frown lines, as well as for numerous debilitating medical conditions for which it relieves significant suffering. As I've written before, it is vital that any cosmetic treatments should be stringently tested for safety. It's reassuring to note that Botox is... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7424-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7424_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:54:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/c/35150/53724/foods</link><title>Healthy and Tasty Food Ideas to Lower Your Blood Pressure</title><description>...   ... Throughout this article you will learn how to modify your eating without having to modify your taste buds. Your food has to lose unnecessary and unhealthy elements but the flavor can be brought out in other ways. Here are some tips to help make the change in lifestyle a little simpler. ... ... Take the salt shaker away from the table and put it in a cabinet. Out of sight is the best. However, if you must use salt when you cook add a smaller amount at the very end of the meal, just before it is finished. ... Instead of using salt in preparation use fresh herbs and spices. This will add flavor and not sodium. ... Increase the ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7424-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7424_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:54:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/191478/165410/national-traditions</link><title>Healthy Foods Help Ring in New Year in Many National Traditions</title><description>...   ... Here are some foods that are favorites in different parts of the world that also can provide a healthy alternative for your diet as you start 2014. They can also serve as a way to explore other cultures and a way to start your own New Year’s tradition. ...   ... Here goes: ... ... Grapes are a part of the celebration in Mexico and Spain. At midnight, Mexicans and Spaniards consume a grape, which represents a wish, on each strike of the clock at midnight. ... Children in Wales enjoy skewered apples covered with raisins and other fruit on New Year’s morning. ... Filipinos decorate their dining room tables with round fruit to mark the New Year. These shapes are believed to symbolize prosperity since they resemble coins. ... Eating lentils is believed to bring good luck and prosperity for Italians as they enter a New Year. ...   Beans are a staple ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7424-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7424_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:54:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/330514/125594/resolution</link><title>New Year's Resolution Blogger: Thanksgiving Day Parade...of Food</title><description>... Ah, the holidays. Treasured memories of time spent with friends and family, cheerful music and decorations, the fun of shopping for the perfect gifts...and the inevitable internal battle against the most delicious food available all year. We all say the same thing. "Well, it's the holidays.  I'll just start eating better on New Years."  This, my friends, is what has gotten me into so much trouble in the past and is already threatening my commitment this year. Not that I have been the best at watching my calories, especially since the wedding. But over the last couple of weeks I've actually been doing pretty well and (mostly) sticking to my promises. I've only had two cups of coffee in three weeks, and the dairy, although not entirely out of my diet, has been cut way down. I've had a couple slices of pizza here and there, but for the most part, the only dairy I'm eating (in moderation) is raw or goat's milk cheese. I've also been going to the gym, enjoying Tai Chi, and gettin... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7424-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7424_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:54:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/727598/161873/choices-control-acid</link><title>Food Choices Can Help Control Acid Reflux, GERD</title><description>... Acid reflux involves the stomach acid flowing backward into the esophagus, which is the tube that connects your throat to your stomach. When you have acid reflux, you may end up tasting food that you’ve regurgitated or sour liquid at the back of your mouth. You also may experience heartburn. GERD is a more severe form of reflux. Signs of GERD include frequent heartburn, regurgitation of food or sour liquid, coughing wheezing, difficulty swallowing and experiencing chest pain, especially when you’re in bed at night. ... One option is to make different dietary choices. Foods that have been scientifically proven to trigger GERD are chocolate, deep-fried foods, coffee, alcohol, and mint (including anything that contains mint oil). Fried food tends to be the biggest culprit since they a... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>