<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7425">coloring picture cars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:55:11" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7425-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7425_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:55:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/932594/94676/picture-trip</link><title>Picture from my trip</title><description>... ... I thought I might show you a picture of myself, Ben Browder and Claudia Black. I'm smitten by Ben so that's why I'm blushing so... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7425-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7425_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:55:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/5741/101622/picture</link><title>new picture</title><description>...   ... The reason I call it "Ugly" is  because the 1st time I made it, I didn't wait for the cake to cool before frosting. The top layer slid off and my attempt to fix went horribly wrong. Thus the name. ...   ... Bon apetit! ...   ... David the wayward baker. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7425-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7425_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:55:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/18/19405/studies-picture</link><title>Antidepressant Studies - Getting the Whole Picture</title><description>... You can stop feeling like it's your fault that you haven't found an antidepressant that works. Not that you should have ever felt that way anyway, but most depressed people blame themselves for everything that goes wrong in their lives. But this one is definitely not your fault, and probably not your doctor's either, for that matter. Last week a paper published in The New England Journal of Medicine showed that publication bias put antidepressants in a more positive light than was warranted by the evidence. To put that in plain English, when drug makers ask the FDA to approve a drug, they have to submit all studies that have been done for that drug, even the ones that show the drug to be less than successful. However, they are under no obligation to publish all the studies in medical journals. They can, and apparently did in this case, cherry-pick the studies and only submit the positive ones for publication. Not only that, some of the negative studies that were published ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7425-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7425_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:56:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/58426/63321/picture</link><title>What Is Wrong With This Picture</title><description>...   ... ...   ... Convenience is defined as anything that is intended to save time and energy and I look at the picture above and I'm beginning to think that the love of convenience and not money is the root of all evil. Indulge me for a second and really think about this, virtually all unhealthy weight gain is a result of convenience. ...   ... Many of the packaged foods we buy at the grocery stores have ingredients we cannot pronounce because of convenience.  We spend most of our days sitting and our waistlines are exploding because walking anywhere is just too much of a hassle, instead we just love driving all over the place and riding elevators &amp; escalators. ...   ... I remember hearing a story of aliens visiting earth for the very first time and being asked to report back to their planet about what they learned.  One of the things that really baffled them was the humans spent all day indoors and for exercise instead of choosing to use the vast outdoors they choose to ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7425-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7425_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:56:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/727598/160260/advancements-workings</link><title>Advancements Give New Picture of Brain's Inner Workings</title><description>... The Brain and Pain ... Researchers have found a way to see the effect of pain on brain scans for the first time, including measuring its intensity and determining whether a drug was easing it. “Although many studies have found brain areas that light up when pain is present, the new work is the first to develop a combined signature from all these signals that can be used to measure pain,” wrote Associated Press reporter Marilynn Marchione. ... This type of breakthrough is especially important in relation to Alzheimer’s and dementia, when it is really difficulty to determine whether the person who is in the later stages of these conditions is in pain but cannot talk or signal it. ... The study involved 114 healthy participants who volunteered to have heatin... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7425-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7425_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:56:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/404482/97177/car</link><title>Buying A Car Requires Special Considerations for Arthritis Patients</title><description>...   ... I'm going somewhere with this. ...   ... Yesterday, I borrowed a friend’s car to drive home to New York from Washington, DC. It's about 200 miles and takes a few hours. If you blink your eye you miss the part when you drive through Delaware, but that's beside the point. ...   ... About a half hour into the drive, I started noticing my lower back was bothering me. And then an hour or so later, it was to the point of being inexcusable. The car seat was actually hurting my back. How does this happen in the year 2010? ...   ... After trying to adjust it every which way, I chose instead to take my time up to New York, stopping three times to stretch my back. Which did help somewhat. But I've sat in lots of cars for a long period of time, and never had that kind of back-wrenching reaction. ...   ... Which begs the q... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7425-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7425_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:57:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/16361/26239</link><title>Headaches while riding in or driving a car!</title><description>...   ... We just went on a little trip, I actually put on blacked out glasses and put my seat back and just rode a lot of the time, but I missed a lot, and then I did have to look some to help hubby find our way when we came to turn offs and such.  I ended up with headaches most of the time.  I usually felt better in the morning after sleeping, then we would start out and soon I'd get a headache.  I took a lot of Tylenol but it didnt' seem to help much.  My headaches are not awful painful, just a nagging headache, and pressure in my head that makes it feel like it is going to explode.  And, I get grumpy!  Which I don't like.  Also, get symptoms in my face, and is on one side, kind ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7425-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7425_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:57:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/eorthopod/faq/husband-terrible-condition-3731</link><title>My husband banged his thumb in the car door and ended up with a terrible condition called CRPS.</title><description>... My husband banged his thumb in the car door and ended up with a terrible condition called CRPS. We can't figure out why this has happened. It wasn't nearly as bad as some of the past injuries he's had. Can you shed any light? Sometimes after trauma (even minor trauma) to human tissue, a chronic pain condition develops. Once called i&gt;reflex sympathetic dystrophy (RSD), this syndrome is now referred to as complex regional pain syndrome (CRPS). With CRPS, the pain generated is greater than expected for the degree of tissue trauma that has been sustained. The pain begins early on and spreads from a small, local area to a larger, regional distribution. Patients report a burning sensation that comes on suddenly for no apparent reason. It is intense. Usually, there are other symptoms such as sweating, hair growth, and changes in skin color and texture. No one knows for sure what causes this to happen. Lab studies of blood and tissue samples appear normal. There is no apparent inflammation o... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7425-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7425_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:57:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/32873/94380/owned</link><title>Mobility Aids: Wheelchairs and Car Adaptors</title><description>... Using a wheelchair, scooter or power chair enhances your mobility in and around the house. Suddenly you have control and you want to go further — across town or across the country. You'll have to transport your wheelchair, too, either with public transportation or private transportation. Today, I am talking about cars used to drive both you and your wheelchair within the city and beyond. It's funny how some people think. When I was first diagnosed with MS, friends and co-workers asked when I was going to get my van, as if there was no question. I drove a little sports car at the time and had no intention nor reason, as far as I could see, to need a van. I knew I didn't want one. I liked my little car and did not think my cane justified jumping from my small car to a large van. But with MS and time, things change. Drive in Cars Just because I cannot walk does not mean I cannot drive. Wheelchairs can go all kinds of places no one even imagined before.  Manual wheelchairs usually... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7425-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7425_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 18:58:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/question/548095/135559</link><title>Water filled flesh colored bumps that spread over body, what are they?</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>