<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7428">rainy afternoon kids craft</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:02:25" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7428-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7428_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:02:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/90847/65551/mondays</link><title>Rainy Days &amp; Mondays Always Get Me Down, Today is Wednesday!</title><description>... Today is Wednesday, and it is raining like crazy here in NC.  But that is all right because I am not down.  It is just the name of the song.  I was going outside with my camera, and came back in because personally I do not care for the rain. I prefer sunshine.  We MS'rs are dealing with a lot of issues right now especially with the changing of the guards, (seasons).  But have no fear, we will adjust.  Give our bodies a chance, they will rebound.  Funky things are going to happen to our bodies, until they adjust to the changing of the seasons, we are going to hurt in places that we did not know existed.  One morning I woke up and told my husband to put the bed down, and to stop spinning it around, and to stop trying to act like he was Popeye.  We both laughed.  Sometimes you have just got to laugh at yourself.  He even says that "honey you know we both are getting old, but hey, I don't mind if you don't."  You know what I real... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7428-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7428_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:02:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/372900/67751</link><title>I take concerta- a total of 72 mg. one in the morining, one in the afternoon.</title><description>... I am 29. I found out that I was add/adhd when I was 23? When should I stop taking these.. If I am planning on having kids within the near future? I also have a hard time with spending money, trying to make others that I work with happy.(ie: buying drinks for them in the morining). Also why do I have a hard time getting out what I need to say.. ? I know that this is alot of questions,but alot has been on my mind latley. thanks. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7428-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7428_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:03:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/2922/11839/sex</link><title>Sex in the Afternoon</title><description>... A lot of my patients find that as they get older, and by this I mean into their 40s and beyond, their sex life falls off some. It isn't lack of interest, though it is sometimes lack of the old degree of desire, but mostly it's that fatigue, lack of sleep, kids, and sometimes a couple of drinks with dinner, effectively drain the batteries.   For many couples one of the solutions is to have sex earlier, while you still have energy - either in the afternoon if it is on the weekends, (or you are retired) - or in the early evening, before dinner. It is a time of day when you have more natural energy, and where the desire to sleep, in our sleep deprived society, doesn't compete with sex.   Another trick that works well for couples with kids still around the house is to check into a motel or hotel for the evening, when you are going out on a date together. You don't have to stay the night, just spend an hour or two, and make it the prelude to a nice relaxed dinner or mo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7428-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7428_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:03:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/sleep-disorders/c/86903/40120/naps-kids</link><title>Naps Are Just Not for Kids....But</title><description>...   ... But many of us could simply use a " power nap " to re-charge.  Not a bad idea, as long as those naps only last about 20 minutes .  The downside?? Some people suffer from sleep inertia or excessive grogginess when they wake up.  Another problem?? You start not sleeping as well at night.  The upside ?? For some people it can really improve mood, alertness and even psychomotor performance.  ...   ... Want to try out this power nap theory personally? ... ... Take your nap between noon and 4 pm ... Keep ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7428-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7428_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:03:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/849319/94163/kid-clutter-holidays</link><title>How to Conquer Kid Clutter before the Holidays</title><description>...   ... Right now he is into taking toys apart.  He has many toy trains and he is fascinated with unscrewing all the screws.  I blame my husband for showing him how to use a screwdriver.  Needless to say, I am finding these parts of trains and screws all over the house.  He also loves to paint and do crafts so the items needed for these projects can also add to the great household clutter.  Toys, books, games, paper, art supplies, DVD's...the list goes on.  What do you do with all this stuff when you have a kid who likes to pull everything out at once?  And too, Max doesn't like to throw things away.  He has collections of things such as his train parts he cannot bear to part with... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7428-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7428_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:04:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/sleep-disorders/c/5954/21085/kids</link><title>Are Your Kids Having Trouble Sleeping?</title><description>... A recent study done in Helsinki, Finland, confirms that TV viewing does have an effect on children's sleep. Researchers sent surveys to over 300 families with young children asking about TV viewing habits and sleeping disturbances. The results showed: The majority of children watched TV one to two hours a day and were exposed to passive TV another hour or two. Both active and passive TV viewing led to shorter sleep duration and other sleep disturbances. The frequency of disturbances rose when children were exposed to adult content. Watching TV in any capacity caused sleep onset problems. Watching TV at bedtime caused a variety of sleep problems. Exposure to two or more hours a day of adult programming was strongly related to sleep disturbances. So how much TV do your children watch? Do they watch just before going to bed? This TV viewing can lead to disrupted sleep and other sleep problems that have a lasting effect on your children's health.   Even passive TV watching can... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7428-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7428_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:04:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/just-diagnosed-674-143.html</link><title>The First 48 Hours: Breaking the News to Your Children</title><description>... The only thing harder than learning you have cancer is having to tell your kids about it. My daughters were 5 and 8 when I was diagnosed, and I agonized over what to tell them. Learning you have breast cancer is a terrifying experience—you want to try not to pass that sense of overwhelming anxiety to them. Unfortunately, you do have to tell your children. Even if it were possible to hide it, doing so would forever erode their trust in you. As you and your family anticipate your treatment regimen, telling your children the truth about your illness can alleviate their anxiety and fear. While you may want to delay sharing the bad news, especially if school is about to start or there’s another important event coming up in your children’s lives, don’t wait more than a few days. They are likely to pick up that something is wrong, or overhear the alarming news from someone else, which will be a lot worse for them. When you sit down with your partner and your children,... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7428-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7428_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:04:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/149175/happiness</link><title>Happiness Through Nostalgia</title><description>...   ... My theory about sentimentality is that as we grow older we have more memories tucked away in the corners of our mind. Some are good memories and some are bad. For the person suffering from depression, the bad memories can seem to overshadow happier times. When we do discover a pleasant ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7428-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7428_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:05:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/39653/138348/things</link><title>The More Things Change The More They Stay The Same</title><description>...   ... As many of you know I am a Volunteer Advocate with the American Pain Foundation's Action Network, which has been very busy in many states advocating for legislation that would prevent insurance companies from requiring Fail First or other policies, in which insurance companies can require pharmacists to make patients take medications that are not as effective than what the  prescribing doctor has prescribed, leaving the patient ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7428-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7428_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:05:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/1402/12492/anxiety-attacks</link><title>anxiety attacks</title><description>... hello my name is Oleta.  I have been haveing this disorder since 1997. and i cant seem to get a gripe on it. Mine started one afternoon. When my husbend transferd our family to Virgina. When his Navy ship was going on A six month deployment. (i have never left alone before!).                          i awoke to haveing symtems as if i could not breath, my heart was hurtting and felt as if i was going to die.everytime i closed my eyes the room would spin and made me diszy. i felt like i had to move around. but at the same time i didnt want to move.                         I still get one  1 to 3 times a week. i sometimes feel like i am all alone in the world. and nobody seems to understand me. sometimes when my friends or family tell... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>