<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7430">conflict mali</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:08:29" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7430-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7430_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:08:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/70/9478/support-groups</link><title>Resolving Conflicts in Support Groups</title><description>... This week I got a call from a college student, let’s call her “Jane,” who wanted to observe our bipolar support group meeting in order to write a paper about it to fulfill a school assignment.  Jane was taking a class in Clinical Psychiatry and was to write about the format and process of our meeting rather than the content.  She assured me everything would be confidential and that she would use no names.  She asked if she could get our permission to observe a meeting. Well, our group is open in the sense that we put a notice in the local paper and our policy states everyone is welcome: “people who are bipolar, people who might be, people who don't want to be, people with family or friends with the condition, and people who want to learn more about it for whatever reason.”  Perhaps I should simply have pointed this information out to Jane and told her she was welcome any time.   Instead, since Jane had specifically asked for permission to come, I emailed ou... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7430-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7430_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:08:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/4182/156799/relationship</link><title>Expectant Parents, Relationship Conflicts and Stress</title><description>...   ... Chronic arguing seems to be a feature of some relationships but its effects differ in men and women for a variety of reasons. Researchers at Penn State have studied recovery from conflict in couples expecting their first baby. They found that the level of hostility expressed during conflict influences both stress reaction and recovery time differently in men and women, but that other factors, such as individual difficulties, anxiety and chronic relationship conflict also hav... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7430-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7430_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:08:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/2804/dealing-conflict</link><title>Dealing with Conflict</title><description>... ... For instance, Mom vehemently expressed that she wanted to leave the nursing home on a regular basis last fall. Taking a deep breath, I held her hand and explained to her that her lungs were bad and her memory was really bad. She listened to this news and tried to rationalize it away by describing it as “old age.” But I couldn’t let that explanation slide in this case. “Mom, do you realize that I come to visit you every day?” I asked her. “You do?” she ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7430-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7430_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:09:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/67816/conflict-mediation</link><title>Family conflict over elder care can be helped by mediation</title><description>...   ... Family problems can get sticky. Well, we all know that. But when our parents are getting to a point where it's evident that they can't make decisions for themselves, but they are too strong-willed or set on maintaining what they view as their independence, sometimes a trained third party can help wade through the pool of family dynamics that has remained stagnant for decades. ...   ... One resource that is being sought by families who disagree about the care of an elder is "elder mediation." NPR.org recently ran an informative article titled, " Mediators Help Families With Tough Choices Of Aging ." The article acknowledges that family dynamics enter into the pictur... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7430-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7430_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:09:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/26165/39528</link><title>Medication conflict..I think.</title><description>... I recently had a mole removed and now I am fighting infection.  So a Dr. gave me the Z - Pack(arithzimiacin) (sp)   I think it might be conflicting with the Neurontin I am on.  I am curious if it should.  Didn't think they would give it, if it would.  I am using the same pharmacy for all my meds.  I am getting very dizzy and weird dreams, grumpy, feel like I am drunk..LOL!  If you know anything please let me know.  I am suposed to take this for 5 days, but I know it stays in my sys. for 14 days. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7430-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7430_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:09:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/57548/137558/conflicts-care</link><title>How To Approach Conflicts in Patient Care With Doctors</title><description>...   ... The balance of ‘doing no harm' and doing what might be considered best for someone with a neurodegenerative disease such as Alzheimer's can be contentious. Giving treatments to people who are unable to consent to their involvement means we might have to protect them from the actions of others, who for many reasons could abuse that trust. ...   ... There are many examples of non-consensual treatments; making people do activities they say they do not want to be involved with, taking drugs with possible side effects they do not want to take, or being subjected to assessments and treatments ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7430-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7430_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:10:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/436900/64896</link><title>Fentanyl patch and conflicting information</title><description>... I have been prescribed the fentanyl patch 25 mg. After researching this drug on the internet, I have found conflicting information. I read that 100 mg of fentanyl equals 10 mg of morphine, and also that 360 mg day of oral morphine equals the 100 patch. Which is correct? ... Thanks ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7430-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7430_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:10:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/2757/dad-face-conflict</link><title>How Dad is Learning to Face Conflict</title><description>... More silver linings in my family's experience with caring for my Mom, who has Alzheimer’s Disease... Mom was the center of the Martin family. She was the pillar we all turned to in times of crisis, in times of celebration, and in times of need. Since her diagnosis in September 2005, each family member has stepped into new roles, and novel personality characteristics have emerged in each individual. This blog discusses another aspect of how my dad’s approach to life has been changed. Dad has always reacted adversely to familial conflict. I can remember being a teenager, confronting him with some problem (HUGE in my mind at the time), and his insistence on not talking about it. Now, 30 years later, he is having to learn how to handle conflict (truly huge this time around) due to Mom’s situation -- Alzheimer’s and her continual struggle with failing lungs due to Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease. The conflicts Dad now deals with can range from encountering problems with Mom’s care... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7430-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7430_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:10:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/7712/129556/expectations</link><title>Expectations, Conflicts &amp; Compromise</title><description>...   ... Sit with them and the issues start to emerge. He says his partner over-identifies with their disorder and uses it to excuse their actions. It results in a situation where he feels manipulated, confused and angry. His partner says this just isn't the case. She never consciously tries to use her situation to such an advantage. There are times however when her partner imposes unrealistic expectations and seems incapable of recognizing her symptoms for what they are. It's not an uncommon scenario. Without digging deeper into their personal situation and history many of the conflict issues with this particular couple, ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7430-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7430_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:11:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/91824/depression-week</link><title>Choice of Boredom or Conflicts &amp; Challenges in Depression: Slow or Chaotic Life?</title><description>...   ... It is time for a question.  Hope you all have doing okay.  This week has been up and downy for me...had a ton of Multiple Sclerosis symptoms yesterday.  I never know what to expect each day from either my physical disease or my mood.  ...   ... I remember a saying that is supposed to be a curse of, "May your life always be interesting."  ...   ...   ... My question today is, "Would you rather have a *boring* life with little to no conflicts or challenges or do you accept the *interesting* life you have now which happens to include some bouts of depression?"  ...   ... ... I must say that sometimes I do wish for a boring life, not so much boring but simple.  ...   ... What are your thoughts?  We want to hear them! ...   ...   ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>