<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7431">navalni trial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:11:26" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7431-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7431_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:11:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/erectile-dysfunction/c/question/14949/43184</link><title>Clinical Trial: New Drug for Hard-to-Treat ED Need midwest trial for professional;most closed.</title><description>... "Clinical Trial: New Drug for Hard-to-Treat ED" is perfect trial for me, but unavailable. Real problem after botched prostatectomy ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7431-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7431_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:11:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/161759/find-association-trialmatch</link><title>Find Clinical Trials through Alzheimer’s Association’s TrialMatch</title><description>...   ... How do people get involved in drug trials for Alzheimer’s? One efficient way is through the Alzheimer’s Association’s TrialMatch. Researchers are continually searching for qualified participants. As the TrialMatch website says, “We need your help. Without participation, finding a cure is virtually impossible…Recruiting and retaining clinical trial participants is now the greatest obstacle, other than funding, to developing the next ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7431-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7431_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:12:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/854063/81302</link><title>Re: Clinical Trial call" BETH TRIAL</title><description>...   ... I wrote one time here I am new in this site, I just had mastectomy five days ago and I will have chemo soon . I just wanted to ask anybody if they know about BETH Trial?? I am stage 1 6 lymph nodes negative ER/PR negative HER2 positive.. I am soo overwhelmed reading what's the best treatment for this case. Can anybody enlightened me regarding my BC.. thanks soo much  by the way, I have DCIS with IDC stage 1 high grade 3 , 6 lymph nodes negative, HER2 positive ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7431-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7431_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:12:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/360776/155918</link><title>while on the trials, do i have to cut back on my oral medications after my 3rd trial, and waiting for in implant</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7431-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7431_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:12:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/11407/162755/clinical-trials-faq</link><title>Clinical Trials: FAQ</title><description>... ... Answer: A group of people voluntarily agree to participate in a specific medical experiment by researchers. This can range from testing new prescription drugs to medical devices to procedures. ...   ... Q: How does a clinical trial work? ... ... A: Clinical trials compare new medical approaches to a standard approach or to a placebo, which has no active elements (such as a sugar or water pill) and acts as a constant for comparison. The goal of a clinical trial is to determine the effectiveness of the new approach when compared to standard care and/or current practices. ...   ... Q: Why are clinical trials important? ... ... A: Clinical trials are meant to increase knowledge and improve treatment, diagnosis, and prevention of diseases and conditions. One of the most important purposes of a clinical trial is to ensure the new drug or approach is safe and beneficial before selling it on the public market. ...   ... Q: Who conducts a clinical trial? ... ... A: Clinical trials have ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7431-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7431_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:13:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/78/12292/fast-faqs</link><title>Everything You Need to Know About Cancer Clinical Trials</title><description>... Q. I hear people at the cancer center talking about clinical trials. What are they? A. A clinical trial is an experiment designed to determine whether a new medical treatment is safe and effective. Clinical trials involve human patients. While the majority of research on any treatment happens prior to bringing in human subjects–pure research, plus trials involving animals–it’s a series of clinical trials that determines whether or not the drug or process will become an FDA-approved treatment. Q. Sometimes I’ve heard trials referred to Phase I, or Phase III. What’s that all about? A. A drug or treatment is subjected to three levels of trial before its effectiveness is proved or disproved. Here’s the explanation: • Phase I trials are the most basic; the most “raw,” if you will. The treatment hasn’t been tested on humans at all; this is the first chance researchers have to see its exact effects, both good and bad, on human patients.... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7431-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7431_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:13:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/202/99040/migraine-headache</link><title>Migraine and Headache Clinical Trials Update 12/24/09</title><description>... To obtain medically reliable data for a clinical trial, each study has to meet certain guidelines. Participants in these studies have to fit in certain criteria, called "inclusion/exclusion" criteria. "Inclusion" criteria are the requirements that allow someone to participate a trial and "exclusion" criteria means the reasons they are unable to take part in the trial. Clinical studies use participant's age, gender, type of disease and other medical conditions, while other studies use healthy participants in their study. If one is not accepted in a clinical trial they shouldn't take it personally - researchers are only making sure participants are safe. ...   ... It's interesting to note that not all cli... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7431-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7431_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:13:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/78/13507/trials-issues</link><title>Clinical Trials: Ethical Issues?</title><description>... Clinical trials, the process of putting new medical treatments through their paces in a real-life (human patient) setting, are conducted all the time. If the results of a trial are favorable, the treatment is introduced to the general public. If not, it's back to the drawing board for the research scientists. Sounds pretty straightforward, doesn't it? On the surface, yes. But when you really start to think about it, clinical trials can open up a medical-ethics can of worms.   Cancer research, like all science, relies on experimentation for results. Drugs, drug doses, hormone treatments, radiation, and other protocols are examined first as theory, on paper; then under the microscope, at the cellular level; then on non-human "volunteers" (white mice, anyone?), and finally, on human volunteers. While PETA activists (People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals) might claim otherwise, it's really only at the human level that this experimentation becomes an is... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7431-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7431_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:13:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/202/92841/migraine-headache</link><title>Migraine and Headache Clinical Trials Update 10/31/09</title><description>... Are you interested in clinical trials of new Migraine and headache treatments? ... ... Did you know that by participating in a clinical trial you can: ... ... •  Being proactive in your health care? ... •  Acquire access to new research treatments before they become public. ... •  Get specialized medical help from top notch health care facilities? ... •  And maybe most satisfying of all, helping others with your role in the trial. ... ... Clinical trials of medications and other treatments for Migraines, headaches, and other conditions are conducted for a variety of reasons. They gather data to determine if medications and other treatments are effective, if they're safe, what potential side effects they may have. Clinical trials also study particular symptoms, the effects of Migraine and other conditions on the body and various organs, and many other things. ... ... Participating in clinical trials can be one way to help add to the body of medical knowledge and... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7431-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7431_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:14:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/treatment-289899-5.html</link><title>Current Migraine and Headache Clinical Trials</title><description>... The number of visits to this page indicates that most of our members don't read or count on this information about Migraine and headache clinical trials, so the page will not continue to be updated. If you're interested in information about clinical trials, visit www.ClinicalTrials.gov . Clinical trials of medications and other treatments for Migraines, headaches, and other conditions are conducted for a variety of reasons. They gather data to determine if medications and other treatments are effective, if they're safe, what potential side effects they may have. Clinical trials also study particular symptoms, the effects of Migraine and other conditions on the body and various organs, and many other things. Participating in clinical trials can be one way to help add to the body of medical knowledge and evidence and to try medications and treatments not yet available. Below, is a list of clinical trials which are enrolling participants for various trials relate... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>