<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7432">ticket to mars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:14:23" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7432-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7432_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:14:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/114/17262/tickets-wrong</link><title>Getting out of speeding tickets via diabetes: Is it wrong?</title><description>... My friend told me a story about this kid with diabetes in his sixth grade class. Apparently, this student wasn't held responsible for any misbehavior because when his blood sugar was high, he wasn't able to control his actions.   Now, I think we can all mostly agree that this is kind of ridiculous, right?   He explained how he got in the fight with this kid one day (normal typical sixth grade fight) and while my friend was suspended for hitting the kid, the other kid received no punishment because he had diabetes and his blood sugar must've been high during the incident.   I don't know who decided this kid could get away with anything if his blood sugar was high, but I do know it's easy to abuse some of the "benefits" of having a chronic illness like diabetes.   A good friend of mine, a Type 1 diabetic woman in her mid-thirties, uses her diabetes regularly to get out of speeding tickets. She puts on a great hypoglycemic act-pan... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7432-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7432_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:14:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/120/157587/recovery-work</link><title>Recovery Options: The Ticket To Work Act</title><description>...   ... This first SharePost will talk about The Ticket To Work Act and the second one will talk about creating a PASS plan.  The last SharePost in the series will talk about the rules and guidelines for collecting a government disability check at the same time you work at a job. ...   ... This evidence refutes certain people's opinions that they trot out as facts. ...   ... The Mad in America crowd claims the medication causes disability, which accounts for the staggering number of people collecting government checks.  One person also claimed the medication causes people to sit home all day doing nothing. ...   ... Unfortunately, these are the prevaili... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7432-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7432_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:15:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/activity-osteoarthritis-2741</link><title>My doctor keeps telling me that the research shows activity and exercise is the ticket for early osteoarthritis of the knees.</title><description>... My doctor keeps telling me that the research shows activity and exercise is the ticket for early osteoarthritis of the knees. When I exercise it hurts more so how can this be helpful? Conservative care for the early stages of osteoarthritis does indeed include exercise. Before beginning a program of increased activity and exercise, efforts are made to reduce the pain and inflammation. Antiinflammatory drugs are used when painful knee symptoms first start. Once the symptoms are under control, then an exercise program is more manageable. As your physician has mentioned, many high-quality studies have confirmed that exercise is helpful in reducing pain and improving function. Muscle strengthening is especially helpful in reducing pain. So even before your pain is completely gone, exercise can begin. Aerobic exercise contributes to long-term improvements in function. Of course, these programs only work if the patient does them consistently. Once the exercises are stopped, the pain returns an... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7432-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7432_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:15:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/59238/97251/bigness-encroaches</link><title>Flying and Obesity: Buying the Extra Ticket for an Airplane Seat</title><description>...   ... The New York Post printed a photo in its December 3 rd edition that showed an extremely large person, it appears to be a man, sitting in an aisle seat.  He is so large that half of his body spills into the aisle, almost touching the seat across from him.  This appears to be a plane with 3 in a row, only 2 sections on either side of the plane (a 757).  The source of the photo is a stewardess who took the shot from the back of the plane, while still on the ground.  American Ai... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7432-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7432_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:15:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/451002/139601</link><title>I broke my back in 5 places &amp; cut the cord. I get hotter than someone else in a car even with the air on, so I had the windows tinted &amp; it help alot. Then after all these years, I got a ticket</title><description>... May I do this with the windows. ... It helps me so much with the tint on, my body stays a lot cooler even with the air on and how the sun keeps going to one side to the other it is much safer to keep the tint on, I'm 57 years old I really need the court to say it's OK. ... Thank you for your time, ... Kenny Baker ... e-mail:heyjudedec8@yahoo.com ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7432-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7432_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:15:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/r/medications/calcio-del-mar-oral-9051/images</link><title>Calcio Del Mar Oral Medication Images</title><description>... Calcio Del Mar Oral CALCIUM 600 MG TABLET ... Calcio Del Mar Oral CALCIUM 600 MG TABLET ... Calcio Del Mar Oral ELEMENTAL CALCIUM 600 MG TAB ... Calcio Del Mar Oral CALCIUM 600 MG TABLET ... Calcio Del Mar Oral CALCIUM 600 MG TABLET ... Calcio Del Mar Oral CALCIUM 600 MG TABLET ... Calcio Del Mar Oral CALCIUM 600 MG CAPLET ... Calcio Del Mar Oral CVS CALCIUM 600 MG TABLET ... Calcio Del Mar Oral CALTRATE-600 TABLET ... Calcio Del Mar Oral CALCIUM CARB 500 (1,250) MG TB ... Calcio Del Mar Oral CALCIUM CARBONATE 1.25 GM TAB ... Calcio Del Mar Oral OYST-CAL 500 TABLET ... Calcio Del Mar Oral OYSCO-500 TABLET ... Calcio Del Mar Oral CALCIUM 500 MG TABLET ... Calcio Del Mar Oral CVS CALCIUM 500 MG TABLET ... Calcio Del Mar Oral CVS CALCIUM 500 MG TABLET ... Calcio Del Mar Oral CVS CALCIUM 500 MG TABLET ... Calcio Del Mar Oral CALCIUM CARBONATE 650 MG TAB ... Calcio Del Mar Oral CALCIUM 500 MG TABLET ... Calcio Del Mar Oral CALCIUM CARB 1,250 MG/5 ML SUS ... Calcio Del Mar Oral CALCIUM CITRA... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7432-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7432_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:16:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/cold-flu/r/medications/mar-cof-bp-oral-153174/images</link><title>Mar-Cof BP Oral Medication Images</title><description>... Mar-Cof BP Oral PHENYLHISTINE DH LIQUID ... Mar-Cof BP Oral DIHYDRO-CP SYRUP ... Mar-Cof BP Oral COLDCOUGH PD SYRUP ... Mar-Cof BP Oral DIHYDRO-PE SYRUP ... Mar-Cof BP Oral POLY-TUSSIN DHC LIQUID ... Mar-Cof BP Oral DIHYDROCODEINE-BPM-PE LIQUID ... Mar-Cof BP Oral M-END WC LIQUID ... Mar-Cof BP Oral CAPCOF LIQUID ... Mar-Cof BP Oral ZUTRIPRO SOLUTION ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7432-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7432_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:16:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/cold-flu/r/medications/mar-cof-cg-oral-151645/images</link><title>Mar-Cof CG Oral Medication Images</title><description>... Mar-Cof CG Oral GUAIFENESIN-CODEINE SYRUP ... Mar-Cof CG Oral GUAIFENESIN-CODEINE SYRUP ... Mar-Cof CG Oral CHERATUSSIN AC SYRUP ... Mar-Cof CG Oral CHERATUSSIN AC SYRUP ... Mar-Cof CG Oral CHERATUSSIN AC SYRUP ... Mar-Cof CG Oral IOPHEN-C NR LIQUID ... Mar-Cof CG Oral GUAIATUSSIN AC LIQUID ... Mar-Cof CG Oral GUAIATUSSIN AC LIQUID ... Mar-Cof CG Oral GANI-TUSS NR LIQUID ... Mar-Cof CG Oral MYTUSSIN AC SYRUP ... Mar-Cof CG Oral MYTUSSIN AC SYRUP ... Mar-Cof CG Oral GUAIFENESIN-CODEINE SYRUP ... Mar-Cof CG Oral CODEINE 10 MG-GUAI 300 MG LIQ ... Mar-Cof CG Oral DEX-TUSS LIQUID ... Mar-Cof CG Oral TUSSI-ORGANIDIN NR LIQ ... Mar-Cof CG Oral TUSSI-ORGANIDIN-S NR LIQ ... Mar-Cof CG Oral M-CLEAR CAPSULE ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7432-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7432_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:16:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/question/all</link><title>I'm 27 years old marred girl. weight is 82 kg &amp; height is 5'5" my breast size is 40. plz help me out to reduce my breast size.</title><description>... I'm 27 years old marred girl. weight is 82 kg &amp; height is 5'5" my breast size is 40. plz help me out to reduce my breast size. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7432-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7432_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:17:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/cold-flu/r/medications/mar-cof-cg-oral-151645/dosage</link><title>Mar-Cof CG Oral Dosage and Storage</title><description>... Generic Name: GUAIFENESIN/CODEINE - ORAL Pronounced: (gweye-FEN-eh-sin/KO-deen) Mar-Cof CG Oral Overdose ... If overdose is suspected, contact your local poison ... control center or emergency room immediately. US residents can call the US ... National Poison Hotline at 1-800-222-1222. Canada residents can call a ... provincial poison control center. Symptoms of overdose may include: ... fast/slow/irregular heartbeat, slow/shallow breathing, cold/clammy skin, loss ... of consciousness. ... Mar-Cof CG Oral Missed Dose ... If you are prescribed this medication on a regular ... schedule and miss a dose, take it as soon as you remember. If it is near the ... time of the next dose, skip the missed dose and resume your usual dosing ... schedule. Do not double the dose to catch up. ... Mar-Cof CG Oral Notes ... Do not share this product with others. It is against the ... law. ... This medication has been prescribed for your current ... condition only. Do not use it later for another condition unles... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>