<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7433">747-8</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:17:25" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7433-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7433_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:17:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/5741/74454/fly</link><title>The why of the fly</title><description>...   ... I'm an addicted multi-tasker. I'm writing this journal, doing Suduko, chatting, listening to music and trying to catch that fly. ...   ... Voices are strong today. I turned on the voice eliminator..music. They say that music calms the savage beast. Who are THEY any way? It does help quell my voices. WDAVE radio wasn't playing when I woke up today. ...   ... I'm torn. I want to go back to the speakers group, but I don't wanna be called a circus. I more than likely won't go back. The anxiety I felt back then is still with me. Writing about it just now gave me a squirt of anxiety. ...   ... I feel good. No depression, or anxiety..the bit of anxiety I had earlier is gone. ...   ... Did someone say dessert? Maybe it was a voice in my head. Good idea though. We bought a dessert magazine with 135 recipes.... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7433-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7433_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:17:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/983302/109974</link><title>allergie medicine</title><description>... what products would be suitable for nasal and sinus congestion resluting from allergies ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7433-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7433_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:17:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/323062/99635</link><title>Does omeprazole protect me from the side effects of Motrin?</title><description>... I take 6 Motrin daily for pain control and I take omeprazole for GERD. My arthritis specialist said that as long as I am taking omeprazole I don't have to worry about the side effects of Motrin, but I thought omeprazole would protect only my stomach and not my duodenum. Will the omeprazole protect the duodenum also? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7433-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7433_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:18:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/prostate/c/question/450736/74221</link><title>Is Free PSA of 12.1 a sign of cancer spreading ?</title><description>... My father aged 84 years , under went scrotum removal operations in 2004 , when his PSA was at &gt;100 and after surgery it came to 0.05 after one year , again in 2007 end it started rising and now we tested his Total PSA last week ie june 1st 2009 it was at 14.1 and his FREE PSA iS AT 12.1 . What does this shows ? Is his prostate cancer spreading slowly or what please reply to my query . ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7433-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7433_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:18:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002418prv.html</link><title>Chromium in diet prevention</title><description>... Alternative Names Diet - chromium References Hamrick I, Counts SH. Vitamin and mineral supplements. Wellness and Prevention . December 2008:35(4);729-747. Rakel D, ed. Integrative Medicine . 2nd ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Saunders Elsevier; 2007. Goldman L, Ausiello D, eds. Cecil Medicine . 23rd ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Saunders Elsevier; 2007. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7433-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7433_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:18:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002400prv.html</link><title>Vitamin A prevention</title><description>... Alternative Names Retinol; Retinal; Retinoic acid; Carotenoids References Sarubin Fragaakis A, Thomson C. The Health Professional's Guide to Popular Dietary Supplements . 3rd ed. Chicago, IL: American Dietetic Association, 2007. Hamrick I, Counts SH. Vitamin and mineral supplements. Wellness and Prevention . December 2008:35(4);729-747. Mason JB. Vitamins, trace minerals, and other micronutrients. In: Goldman L, Ausiello D, eds. Cecil Medicine . 23rd ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Saunders Elsevier; 2007:chap 237. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7433-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7433_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:19:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002420prv.html</link><title>Fluoride in diet prevention</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Diet - fluoride ... ... ... References ... ... Hamrick I, Counts SH. Vitamin and mineral supplements. Wellness and Prevention . December 2008:35(4);729-747. ... ADA Division of Communications. For the dental patient: infants, formula and fluoride. J Am Dent Assoc . 2007; 138(1):132. ... Berg J, Gerweck C, Hujoel PP, King R, Krol DM, Kumar J, et al. American Dental Association Council on Scientific Affairs Expert Panel on Fluoride Intake. From infant formula and fluorisis. Evidence-based clinical recommendations regarding fluoride intake from reconstituted infant formula and enamel fluorosis: a report of the American Dental Association Council on Scientific Affairs. J Am Dent Assoc . 2011; 142(1):79-87. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7433-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7433_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:19:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002421prv.html</link><title>Iodine in diet prevention</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Diet - iodine ... ... ... References ... ... Hamrick I, Counts SH. Vitamin and mineral supplements. Wellness and Prevention . December 2008:35(4);729-747. ... Rakel D, ed. Integrative Medicine . 2nd ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Saunders Elsevier; 2007. ... Mason, MB. Vitamins, trace minerals, and other micronutrients. In: Goldman L, Ausiello D, eds. Cecil Medicine . 23rd ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Saunders Elsevier; 2007: chap 237. ... Institute of Medicine. Food and Nutrition Board. Dietary Reference Intakes for Vitamin A, Vitamin K, Arsenic, Boron, Chromium, Copper, Iodine, Iron, Manganese, Molybdenum, Nickel, Silicon, Vanadium, and Zinc. National Academy Press, Washington, DC, 2001. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7433-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7433_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:19:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002402prv.html</link><title>Vitamin B6 prevention</title><description>... Alternative Names Pyridoxal; Pyridoxine; Pyridoxamine References Escott-Stump S, ed. Nutrition and Diagnosis-Related Care . 6th ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Lippincott Williams &amp; Wilkins; 2008. Sarubin Fragaakis A, Thomson C. The Health Professionals' Guide to Popular Dietary Supplements . 3rd ed. Chicago, Il: American Dietetic Association; 2007. Institute of Medicine. Food and Nutrition Board. Dietary Reference Intakes for Thiamin, Riboflavin, Niacin, Vitamin B6, Folate, Vitamin B12, Pantothenic Acid, Biotin, and Choline. National Academy Press, Washington, DC, 1998. Hamrick I, Counts SH. Vitamin and mineral supplements. Wellness and Prevention . December 2008:35(4);729-747. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7433-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7433_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:20:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/002419prv.html</link><title>Copper in diet prevention</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Diet - copper ... ... ... References ... ... Trumbo P, Yates AA, Schlicker S, Poos M. Food and Nutrition Board, Institute of Medicine, The National Academies. Dietary reference intakes: vitamin A, vitamin K, arsenic, boron, chromium, copper, iodine, iron, manganese, molybdenum, nickel, silicon, vanadium, and zinc. J Am Diet Assoc . 2001 Mar;101(3):294-301. ... Hamrick I, Counts SH. Vitamin and mineral supplements. Wellness and Prevention . December 2008:35(4);729-747. ... Rakel D, ed. Integrative Medicine . 2nd ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Saunders Elsevier; 2007. ... Goldman L, Ausiello D, eds. Cecil Medicine . 23rd ed. Philadelphia, Pa: Saunders Elsevier; 2007. ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>