<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7437">free aldi meyola songs</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:28:57" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7437-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7437_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:28:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/678495/89755/diagnosed</link><title>Daughter records Song to Support Mom Who was Recently Diagnosed</title><description>... Hi: Below is a link to a FREE music download - a song written by Boston-area singer/songwriter Krysta Youngs to support her mother who was recently diagnosed with breast cancer. http://www.box.net/shared/static/sqbjj661gx.mp3 It's a beautiful, supporting song for anyone going through a difficult time. Joanne ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7437-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7437_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:29:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/120/21098/song-music</link><title>Singing My Own Song: Using Music as Therapy</title><description>... Music has always been a passion second only to writing for me. As a kid growing up in the 1970s, I listened to the AM radio, and later on, rock-n-roll. In college, I was a disc jockey at WSIA, 88.9 FM. My favorite bands were Sonic Youth, the Replacements, and Siouxsie and the Banshees.   As the schizophrenia slowly took over my brain, I listened to weirder music. On my radio show I dipped into the gloom: bands like Of a Mesh, Honeymoon Killers and Sleep Chamber. After I graduated with a BA in English, I had my breakdown. This was the day the music stopped. I couldn't go back to the way things were before.   At the second day program I attended, we had music therapy sessions, and my favorite instrument was the tambourine; it jangled and drowned out the symptoms.   When I was in my 20s, I loved to drive down the highway in my Mustang, listening to the FM radio. The Tom Cochrane song said it all, "Life is a highway/I want to ride it all night long." Google "t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7437-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7437_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:29:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/781360/66951/migraine-morning</link><title>Ode to a Migraine Free Morning</title><description>... Inventory taking time ... Will I need to lightly tread ... ice packs,heating pad,Relpax ... April's bird songs far too loud? ...   ... Will our rare spring sun be an insult, ... My teens' hairdryers and bursts of laughs ... like bullets to my wartorn skull ... Our little dogs' happy greetings brushed away? ...   ... Wait, no, it is quiet on my northwestern front ... Could it be a jewel , a diamond ... a treasure that I collect and prize? ... My body- neck to tip of skull is soft ... Not hard as granite , hot as embers. ...   ... Today I will not live in an iron mask ... made of pain and pretend that all ... is fine. Mothers, teachers, we have to be ... strong. My head in a vice I can still lead a class, ... drive a carpool...and try not to snap. ...   ... This mornng I say, "Sing birds!", ... "Come here, kids", "Shine sun!" ...  "Turn on some music and let's dance!" ... Quickly, quickly before the dark clouds ... roll in again and the curtains will be drawn. ...   ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7437-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7437_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:29:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/19065/52830/falling</link><title>Free Falling and other Silly Human Tricks</title><description>... Remember the Tom Petty &amp; The Heartbreakers song from 1989? 'Cuz I'm free!!! Free falling.... Yeah I'm freeeeeee.... freeeee falling! I’m not gonna talk about dumping a girl, feeling no regret, and driving around Los Angeles.  But today’s topic deals with balance and not of the philosophical kind. Balance which keeps you from falling.  Get it?  Free falling..... (lol) During a consultation with a neurologist in the summer 2005, the doctor put me through the hoops of silly human neurological tricks.  - follow my finger with your eyes, smile, how many fingers am I holding up? - hold you arms out, close your eyes, touch your finger to my finger &amp; touch your nose, close your eyes - don’t let me move your arms, sweeze my fingers ... - sharp needle test, tuning fork test, legs strength, check reflexes, etc. - walk normal, walk heel-to-toe, walk on your toes, walk on your heels - stand with your feet together, now arms out, now close your eyes Whoa, baby!!!!&amp;... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7437-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7437_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:30:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/157934/weight-christmas</link><title>Avoiding Holiday Weight Gain: Strategy 3 A Super Good Grain-free, Low Carb Christmas Menu</title><description>... When my daughter was a toddler, Christmas was a much more simple affair. Her handle on Santa Claus was fair at best, and anticipation of the big day was tepid. Decorated trees were nice, cheerful lights were nice, and merry songs were nice as well. Santa was still being deliberated. My daughter was told he was a grand old fellow who delivered gifts to all the children who had been good, and she was assured that she had made the grade. Her take on the whole thing was, well…Santa was a loud fellow who adhered to an odd dress code. He was rotund and older gent who laughed manically at pretty much everything and seemed a bit out of sorts about twenty-five percent of the time. If she were pressed for the truth, I’m sure the word terrifying would be used at least once. Then again, if he was the source of all those gifts he would have to be tolerated. As she grew older Santa rose to his traditional level of reverence. My husband believed in volume, so the tree would be buried in he... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7437-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7437_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:30:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/cold-flu/c/82437/18503/ways-kids-habit</link><title>Nag-Free Ways to Get Kids into the Hand-Washing Habit</title><description>...   ... * First make sure your sink area is kid-friendly by having a stepstool; if your toddler or preschooler still can't reach the faucet, consider purchasing a faucet extender at www.sinkpal.com . ...   ... * Squid Soap is "hands down" one of the most fun ways to get your kids to wash properly. The company manufactures a dispenser soap that looks like an orange squid. Kids squirt the "ink," or soap, on their hands and the ink doesn't rub off unless they wash for the recommended twenty seconds.  ...   ... * Since pump dispenser soaps are better than hand soaps for cutting down on germ trans... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7437-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7437_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:30:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/148381/depression</link><title>The Twelve Days of Christmas: Anxiety and Depression Free</title><description>...   ... On the first day of Christmas I gave a gift to me: A stress free holidayeee! (A poet I am not so forgive my attempt to rhyme). How you ask? Let us help with a couple of articles on how to take the stress and anxiety out of your holiday plans. ...   ... • Coping with Social Anxiety and Depression During the Holidays ... • 10 Tips to Reduce Holiday Stress ...   ...   ... On the second day of Christmas I gave a gift to me: Two (potentially) Mood Enhancing Supplements (Please note that you should always ask your doctor about any supplements or herbal remedies you wish to take to avoid adv... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7437-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7437_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:31:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/17047/managing-bad-times</link><title>Managing the Bad Times</title><description>... Life doesn’t come with a trouble-free warranty. A year ago exactly, I was stuffing my personal belongings into six or seven shipping cartons. My marriage of three years had just broken up, and I was taking a leap of faith by moving in with a friend on the opposite coast. My one-way ticket was booked. No time for sentiment. The clock was running. I had affairs to settle, things to pack.   Mercifully, the gods were smiling on me. I landed in a situation that was uniquely suited to my recovery and healing.   Now, a year later, I’m pulling out of the funk from the break-up of a short-lived relationship. Our illness doesn’t appreciate dimensions or proportionality. One ton of bricks dropped on my head is as good as ten tons of bricks so far as this illness is concerned. Often, it doesn’t take much. We feel something subtle shifting in the brain, and next thing we’re thinking, oh no, here we go again.   Time to man battle stations.   Late in... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7437-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7437_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:31:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/271731/98922/caged-bird-sings</link><title>I, too, Know Why the Caged Bird Sings</title><description>... I Know Why the Caged Bird Sings by Maya Angelou (with Audacious Liberties by Toby) The free bird leaps on the back of the wind and floats downstream till the current ends and dips his wings in the orange sun rays and dares to claim the sky. But a bird that stalks down his narrow cage can seldom see through his bars of rage his wings are clipped and his feet are tied so he opens his throat to sing. The caged bird sings with fearful trill of the things unknown but longed for still and is tune is heard on the distant hill for the caged bird sings of freedom The free bird thinks of another breeze and the trade winds soft through the sighing trees and the fat worms waiting on a dawn-bright lawn and he names the sky his own. But a caged bird stands on the grave of dreams his shadow shouts on a nightmare scream his wings are clipped and his feet are tied so he opens his throat to sing The caged bird sings with a fearful trill of things unknown but longed for still and his tune is heard on the... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7437-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7437_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:31:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/77040/35161/mental-health-21st</link><title>Mental Health Humor : Weekly Review July 21st to 26th</title><description>... Saturday! Where did the week go? Time sure got away from me this ... week. Some unexpected stuff with which to deal. That’s life! Did your ... week go as planned? Or did you have to deal with some unexpected ... happening as well? In the words of a Prince song, “We got 2 go through ... it 2 get 2 it!” We made it through the week, now on to our Weekly ... Review. Did you have a good week?? Hope it was filled with a laugh or ... two?! Our Weekly Review gives me the opportunity to acknowledge all of ... your great comments and to express appreciation for your continuing ... support! This coming week, I hope to be getting into some topics I ... wanted to last week but couldn’t…due to circumstances. Please Subscribe ... to our blog via e-mail ( MentalHealthHumor.com ) and ... Stay “Tooned” ...   ... ... ... ... ...   ...   ... ... ...   ...   ... ... ... Sunday ... Sunday - Mid-night ... Madness, I shared a little story about my son. He keeps my wife and I... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>