<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7438">facebook privacy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:31:55" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7438-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7438_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:31:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/148108/facebook-chat</link><title>Facebook Chat for Suicidal People? The Question of the Week</title><description>...   ... I find this news especially interesting in light of the fact that so much bullying does occur through social network sites.  The case of Megan Meier comes to mind, a young teen who committed suicide due to cyber-bullying on MySpace.  ...   ... In 2010 another teen named Phoebe Prince was bullied and tormented on Facebook and hung herself. ...   ... In 2011 a 16-year old girl attempted suicide by jumping off a bridge .  In this case she survived.  The cause of her attempt?  Facebook bullying. ...   ... In yet another story a teen-age girl was harassed by peers on facebook before her suicide and after.   It seems some bullies like to keep sending hateful messages on a memorial site even after the person has died. ...   ... Fed up with bullying which can be so prominent on facebook and other social networking sites, th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7438-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7438_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:32:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/135718/bariatric-weight</link><title>My Bariatric Life living life after weight-loss surgery: Facebook &amp; Easy Tricks to Sneak-in Exercise</title><description>...   ... I don't think this is natural, to work in an office all day and then purchase everything that you consume - from factory-farmed and overly-processed food to mass-produced clothing. It comes as no surprise to me that we as a nation are over weight, fat, obese. To me, the hunter and gatherer way of life or family farming seem the natural way that we were intended to live. The reality, for better or worse, is that sitting behind a computer is our system of lifestyle - used for both work and "edutainment" -- for most of us in the 21 st ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7438-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7438_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:32:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/956385/136346</link><title>I want to share my stuff. But I do not know how to use facebook, nor do I want to learn. Is there any other way to be able to SHARE without facebook being involved. All I know how to do is email!</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7438-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7438_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:32:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/80106/136870/myr</link><title>Rheumatoid Arthritis Support Comes to Twitter and Facebook</title><description>...   ... You can find us on Facebook and follow us on Twitter , and don't forget to join our twibbon campaign for RA Awareness. ...   ... We look forward to talking to you in both places! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7438-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7438_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:33:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/21949/137669/facebook-young</link><title>Facebook-a New "Wave" To Keeping Your Brain Young</title><description>...   ... Who would have thought that 40 years after the first email was successfully sent that we would be creating virtual spaces to connect with our friends, family and community via "the net!"  Not only has it become a modern phenomenon but it is a way of life.  I'm talking about Facebook.  Yes, the noun, the verb and the adverb-- Facebook.  ...   ... Something that started as a way to rate girls on college campuses in the early 2000s has essentially become THE hub to reconnect, invite, like, friend and chat with folks from all over the world.  And it doesn't just stop there - social media tools such as Twitter, LinkedIn, MySpace, Skype have also joined the ranks. ...   ... A recent study involving two senior resident facilities in Italy gave their participants laptops with wireless connections, along with tutorials on how to maneuver on the internet.  The men and women were sch... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7438-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7438_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:33:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/153458/migraine-awareness</link><title>Migraine Awareness - A Ribbon on Facebook</title><description>... There are so many ways to build awareness about Migraine disease. Some of them take a fair amount of effort, but some of them take almost none. During Awareness Month, I'll be sharing a wide range of these with you, and I hope you'll share your ideas with me and our readers. ...   ... Today, I want to share a very simple method for those of you who use Facebook, adding a puple ribbon to your profile picture. You can see an example of it here on my Facebook profile picture. This is very easy to do. You don't have to modify your picture yourself. To add a purple ribbon to your Facebook profile picture to help build awareness of Migraines, just use this PicBadges badge . ...   ... Live well, ... ... ...   ...   ... ... Get the latest Migraine and headache news, informational articles, tips for living well, and more in my free weekly newsletter. To subscribe, CLICK HERE . ... ... ...   ...   ... Follow me on     or  ... ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7438-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7438_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:33:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/4182/154438/time-depression</link><title>Facebook Time Not Linked to Depression</title><description>...   ... At the time the report drew some fairly prompt responses from several experts who immediately disputed the notion of a ‘Facebook depression’. For example, Tristan Gorrindo, MD and Eugene V. Beresin, MD stated that, “as child psychiatrists, what concerns us is that there is no scientific study of this diagnosis, nor are there criteria for how this diagnosis is made.” ...   ... Various other studies... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7438-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7438_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:34:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/8534/168036/unfriended-facebook</link><title>Why I Unfriended Facebook</title><description>...   ... I'm in my 40s; I figured this kind of thing was for "the kids" who are much more tech-savvy than I am. (I know, that may be offensive to some, but let me explain: I am a tech-unsavvy kind of girl. Atari was my kind of video game, OK?). ...   ... But then my older sister started using it, and she loved it. She was having tons of fun connecting with all kinds of people with whom we grew up. If I had a couple dollars for every person who has said, "I'm friends with your sister on Facebook," well, I'd be able to buy a new computer to Facebook on. ...   ... So I joined it too. And it was like what I imagine hitting the crack pipe would be like. I immediately had to have more of it. Needed to have more friends, needed to edit my profile (again), needed to come up with clever things to post. I was... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7438-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7438_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:34:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/4182/162707/happiness-perspectives</link><title>Facebook Usage Effects on Happiness and Other Perspectives</title><description>...   ... It’s probably useful to put social media site usage, and Facebook in particular, into perspective. Social media is now the number one activity for online time and Facebook tops the list of most-visited sites. According to a report by Nielsen, “In the U.S. alone, total minutes spent on social networking sites has increased 83 percent year-over-year. In fact, total minutes spent on Facebook increased nearly 700 percent year-over-year, growing from 1.7 billion minutes in April 2008 to 13.9 billion in April 2009, making it the No. 1 social networking site for the month.  And, in a Business Horizons article, the authors mention over 152 milli... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7438-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7438_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:34:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/22705/100281/anxietyconnection</link><title>Join AnxietyConnection on Facebook</title><description>...   ... AnxietyConnection on facebook ...   ... Please also remember to look me up on facebook . ...   ... Thanks ...   ... Eileen Bailey ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>