<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7441">barcelona real madrid goal messi</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:41:19" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7441-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7441_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:41:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/902491/110583/resolution</link><title>New Year's Resolution Blogger: Real Houswives and Real Dieting</title><description>...   ... Now as quiet as it's kept (a few close friends know) I really only like the Real Housewives of New York. Here's why -- they're really fit and really funny.  Bethenny is my superhero.  Not only is she the spokesperson for Pepperidge Farm but she is the author of the Skinny Girl craze.  You know, if not perhaps you've been hiding in a tent on a campground somewhere in West Virginia. No, no I'm not saying anything negative about West Virginia, I hear they've got super campgrounds and hiking there... try Spruce Knob in Seneca Rocks or Holly River in Morgantown. ...   ... Back to Bethenny, well, throughout every season of the Real Housewives of New York (RHNY) we see the Natural Foods chef surfing, eating healthy, walking, sharing healthy recipes even drinking low calorie liquor! Low calori... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7441-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7441_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:41:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/100/25623/coping-skill-6</link><title>Coping Skill #6 - Set Your Own Goals</title><description>... Goals!  Goals!  Goals! ...   ... Has anyone else noticed that, sooner or later, once we become stabilized on our medications, therapists start talking about goals ?  They stress that goals are important to recovery.  Then, if we don't pick a goal or two for ourselves, they select one or more for us.  Although therapists clearly have our recovery in mind and are well intentioned, sometimes the goals they select seem trivial or even irrelevant. ...   ... Schizophrenia, as we know all too well, is devastating.  One of the worst consequences of this condition can be that our relationships with others suffer.  Relationships, even those most dear to us, such as our ties to family and/or best friends, can be damaged simply because these others don't understand, or refuse to accept, the fact that we are ill.  In all fairness, our behavior often does change dramatically in the throes of this brain disease, which makes it much more difficult to maintain t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7441-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7441_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:41:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/80106/162734/perspective</link><title>Meeting Your Goals with Chronic Pain: A Shift in Perspective</title><description>...   ... The short answer is that it depends, and not exactly. If your dream is to become a trapeze artist and you live with chronic pain due to RA or another chronic illness or injury, you may want to consider revising your goal. Perhaps you'll still be able to work in the circus, but in a less physically demanding position. This is an example of reassessing your goals and shifting them slightly to accommodate your pain. There are several steps involved in shifting your plan so you can still live your life, even with chronic pain. ...   ... Get a Pain Management Plan ... According to a report by the Institute of Medicine, about 116 million America... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7441-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7441_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:42:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/45112/53769/resolutions</link><title>Set Realistic, Measurable Goals to Maximize New Years Resolutions for Heart Health</title><description>...   ... The statistics are not very encouraging.  Most people give up on their New Year resolutions within three weeks.  According to one discouraging study, only 8% of American's actually achieve their New Year resolutions! ...   ... How will you keep yourself motivated and make this the year you achieve your goals? ...   ... Here are five key strategies to stay motivated: ...   ... 1. Set realistic goals. ...   ... Set a goal you know you can achieve.  If you are currently inactive, it's unrealistic to set a goal to run 5 miles three times a week.  Instead, set a goal you can achieve, such as "I will... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7441-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7441_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:42:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/59238/165538/swap-resolutions-goals</link><title>Swap out Resolutions for Goals</title><description>...   ...   ... Since I write shareposts on nutrition, fitness, weight and lifestyle, not surprisingly, the goals I suggest this month will focus on those areas of life.  I might also add an observation I have made over the better part of three decades….when you are organized wi... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7441-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7441_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:42:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/80106/101281/year</link><title>Goals for Coping with Rheumatoid Arthritis</title><description>...   ... 2. Become informed about RA When you have a chronic illness like rheumatoid arthritis, it can feel as if you don't have any control of your life, making you feel helpless and depressed. The first step to taking back control is to make yourself somewhat of an expert on your disease and how it may affect your life. M.E.A. McNeil's The First Year Was Rheumatoid Arthritis is an excellent resource to help you get started. ...   ... 3. Discov... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7441-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7441_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:43:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/28524/92753/mastering-day-2</link><title>Mastering Diabetes: A1c Goals, Dual Wave with Insulin Pumps, Alcohol, Basal Logs</title><description>... Every morning before we started our class we had to check in and go for our vitals, which included blood pressure and pulse. The only day that my blood pressure was on the higher side was on the first day at 120/90, but the rest of the time it was around 101/70. ... After vitals, we started our first session of the day. Kellie and Jane, our CDEs, asked each one of us what our goals and wishes were as part of the mastering your diabetes program, as well as some background information on our diabetes history. Some of the questions included what our last A1C was, how long we have had diabetes, if we had any complications due to diabetes, any hospitalizations, what our current insulin regimen was, and what our hobbies were other than diabetes related. They wrote all of our responses up on colored pieces of paper on ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7441-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7441_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:43:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/82083/161486/video-startling-statistics</link><title>New "Faces of Migraine" Video Makes Startling Statistics Real</title><description>... One way to get appropriate information is to stack the deck in your favor – choose videos that are created or promoted by Migraine specialists and advocate/educators who use current, physician created or reviewed material to make their productions. ... I’m not a person that likes to be in front of a camera, but last year I got an idea for a video I felt really NEEDED to be available to the community. Its goal: to educate and create awareness among those who do not have Migraine themselv... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7441-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7441_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:43:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/c/727598/119470/shortly-middle</link><title>"Someone Will Be With You Shortly" Paints A Funny and Real Picture of Middle-Age Life</title><description>...   ... Hopefully, my aches, pains and meds won’t be a big part of my conversation. Instead, I hope to keep a sense of humor and perspective on the challenges of aging, but to be involved fully in the world. To reach that goal means starting now. ...   ... Which brings me to my book group’s lastest read, “Someone Will Be with You Shortly: Notes From  A Perfectly Imperfect Life” by Lisa Kogan . You may know Lisa from her regular column in O Magazine where she has developed a keen eye and descriptive style that provides a unique take on the world. In one of ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7441-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7441_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:44:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/c/440269/101602/time-real</link><title>This Time It's for Real</title><description>...   ... You see, I have this image that keeps flashing in my mind again and again - thanks to a little gift my sister gave my father. During the holidays I went home to visit my family and there it was, a digital photo album --- the kind you upload a gazillion photos to and then it runs them in a constant loop. While it was sentimental to see "the old family photos" of nine kids lined up in row like squished ducks, all dressed up, pushing each other and vying for attention...... it's when we got to the current photos that I glazed over! There I was flashing up over and over and over and OVER ag... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>