<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7445">marathon training</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:53:30" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7445-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7445_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:53:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/20192/41891/marathon-abs</link><title>marathon training/weight loss &amp; gain/abs</title><description>... Hi, I am a recently turned 28 year old male. I am 6'0 and weigh roughly 150lbs (I don't own a scale). I spent a lot of my summer training for the half marathon that I just completed 8 days ago. I've always been pretty thin, but have recently gotten thinner due to the training. I don't really think I lossed a ton of weight (I'm not really trying to), but I have definitely noticed that my clothes fit a lot looser than normal (especially in the chest and arms) and I'm a bit more tone, with the exception of my stomach. I guess I really have 2 questions: ... 1.) Now that the half-marathon is over, I am going to continue to run this fall and winter, but just not as much. So, 2-4 miles a few times a week compared to the 8-12 mile runs I was doing while training. Will I gain some of the weight/mass back to my body? I have also started doing push-ups and sit-ups 3-4 times a week too since the race ended and have noticed a little bit more tone and bulk, but not much. Will continuing ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7445-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7445_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:53:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/train-marathon-1661</link><title>I want to train for a marathon.</title><description>... I want to train for a marathon. I've heard that long-distance runners can get shin splints from the constant strain on the leg muscles. How do I know if I'm at risk? It's true that injuries are fairly common among distance runners. Up to 57 percent of recreational runners get injured over the course of a year. Most of these injuries (up to 75 percent) are from overuse. A recent study identified gender and foot posture as risk factors for medial tibial stress syndrome (MTSS), commonly known as shin splints. In a group of 125 high school cross-country runners, 12 percent showed signs of MTSS. Injured runners were overwhelmingly female. They also tended to be pronators. How do you know if you're a pronator? A doctor or sports trainer can do tests to find out. If pronating seems to be a problem in your case, you may want to look into orthotics. These shoe inserts can be designed to support your feet against pronation as you run. Preventive measures like these can improve your chances of avoi... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7445-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7445_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:54:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/training-marathon-hurting-2540</link><title>I was training for a marathon when my right knee started hurting pretty bad.</title><description>... I was training for a marathon when my right knee started hurting pretty bad. X-rays were negative, so I went to a physical therapist for help. She found the problem was in my hip, not my knee. Does this seem right to you? Pain or other symptoms experienced at a site remote from the cause of the problem is called referred pain. It is a fairly common problem that physical therapists are trained to watch out for. For example, knee pain can occur as a result of low back, hip, sacroiliac, or ankle impairments. With any musculoskeletal problem, therapists conduct a thorough screening exam to make sure the problem has a musculoskeletal origin and is within the scope of their practice. To do this, they use a screening model that includes past medical history , risk factors , clinical presentation , and associated signs and symptoms . An understanding of the clinical presentation comes from a broad exam referred to as a regional interdependence exam. By expanding the exam to include a broad region (n... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7445-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7445_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:54:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/question/419998/86768</link><title>As a Type II diabetic, how many carbs do I need to train for a marathon?</title><description>... I'm a 67- year old marathon runner who runs about 40 miles per week and have been diagnosed with Type II diabetes. My dietician said I should consume no more than 60-70 carbs per meal with snacks in between of no more than 15 carbs. That does not seem to be enough carbs to provide the energy I need to train and run properly. What do you recommend? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7445-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7445_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:54:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/c/727598/129607/women-marathon</link><title>Middle-Age Women Can Embrace Sense of Purpose, Exercise through Training for Half-Marathon</title><description>... Take my friends, Jan (age 59) and Pat (age 67).  After Pat moved into Jan’s neighborhood in May 2009, they two began getting together. “We both enjoy walking so my exercise got a jump start because of her commitment to meet and walk every morning before work for her at 5:30 a.m.,” Pat said. “I thought that was way too early for me truthfully. It worked perfectly however.” Fast forward a year and the two decided to graduate to a running program. And not just any old running program, but one that would allow them to run and complete a half-marathon. ...  It turns out the two came from different running backgrounds. Pat had never run a half-marathon, while Jan was a veteran. “I wanted to renew my interest in running,” Jan explained. “From the age 35 to 51, I ran on a weekly b... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7445-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7445_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:54:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/question/560290/139583</link><title>I recently started training for a half marathon. How does the body breakdown fat and change as the body replaces fat with muscle? My "fat rolls" seem to be more fluid or flabby instead of just firm.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7445-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7445_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:55:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/6148/44573/5-ra-0</link><title>Staying possitive, Marathons (5) RA (0)</title><description>... Training for marathon #6  Dec 7 2008 Had RA in 2003. Be a fighter and fight ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7445-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7445_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:55:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/896502/129601/succeeding</link><title>Succeeding at Completing a Half-Marathon at Middle Age</title><description>... Some people are born to run – and some just want to learn how to do it well. And some people want to learn how to run long distances. Which brings me to two friends,  Jan and Pat. Together, these middle-age women trained and completed the White Rock Half-Marathon in late 2010. ...  The pair’s exercise partnership started since they were neighbors who would walk most mornings together. “We both enjoy walking so my exercise got a jump start because of her commitment to meet and walk every morning before work for her at 5:30 a.m.,” Pat said. “I thought that was too early for me truthfully. It worked perfectly however.” That’s because having a routine as well as having a loyal training partner helped Pat, age 67, run her first half-marathon and Jan, age 59, get back into running. ... Jan had always enjoyed running when she was younger. “From the age of 35 to 51, I ran on a weekly basis. I ran numerous half-marathons, trained for sev... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7445-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7445_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:55:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/c/440269/116499/marathon</link><title>From Couch Potato to Marathon Runner</title><description>... As part of our recommitment to losing weight, my sisters and I decided, in addition to being each other's support, it would be good to train for a common goal and then carry it out together. So we decided to train to do a 5K run. Now, really, how bad could that be?  A 5K sounds like a long way to run, especially for someone like me who has never run any kind of race before! But after you do the conversion, a 5K run is only about 3 miles.  That's not TOO bad! And I was thinking, if Oprah can train to run a (26 mile) marathon, I can train to do a 5K! ...   ... So we turned to a training website for guidance, The Couch-to-5K Running Plan . This is a website that is suppose to help people transform from couch potatoes to being able to run a 5K in just two months. Perfect for me! Though I don't consider myself to be a total "couch potato," I have afterall been jogging on my own and riding my bicycle, I think the pace of the overall plan is good for me - something that gets you... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7445-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7445_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:55:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/52325/64948/breathin-asthmatic</link><title>Meet Breathin' Stephen, the Hard Luck Asthmatic On His Way to the Boston Marathon</title><description>...   ... He is the perfect example of the  Hard Luck Asthmatic , the asthmatic who does everything right, like Jake Gallant , only he and his doctor still have trouble managing his asthma.  ...   ... Stephen, age 54, said he's been hospitalized 92 times admits, many of those in critical care (his most recent was in Sept. 2008), and 14 times on a ventilator.  ...   ... "My asthma has gotten progressively worse since the age of 5," he wrote in an email to me.  "My first time on a ventilator was at the age of 16.  I had a respiratory arrest in the elevator while being taken to radiology for a chest x-ray. I coded, but it's unclear if my heart stopped. I did however suffer 2 fractured ri... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>