<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7446">cycling on the mont ventoux</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:56:10" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7446-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7446_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:56:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/275113/61173</link><title>four monts out of treatment and still feel bad</title><description>... or there any five year survial people out there that had invasive lobular brest cancer. ... tumor 2.5 with one node that had a little cancer in it. they took out 10 lump nodes. ... Now i have fluid in my chest and a little in my arem. Shoulders hurts and back.My legs ... have pain in them. My hole body has pain in it at times. When I get up I be stiff. ... Is this the way it make you feel. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7446-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7446_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:56:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/624028/121689</link><title>Hi my wife barbara has been diabetic for about 8 years now, and her prescribed medication has gradually increased, in the last 12 - 18 mont</title><description>... month she was rushed into hospital with symptoms akin to Lactic Acidosis, hospital not confirmed this but have reduced her metformin to 3 per day, she has been released and tests are still ongoing, she is still suffering from shortness of breath and severe exaustion, should her metformin be reduced further? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7446-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7446_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:56:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/421888/138027</link><title>I have 2 different chemo regimens between which to choose: dose dense AC every 2 weeks for 4 cycles, followed by T (4 cycles) VS. TAC every 3 weeks for 6 cycles. How do i decide which is better?</title><description>... Stage 2 breast cancer; 2 negative sentinel nodes, 1 positive node; ER+ PR- Her 2 neu -. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7446-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7446_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:57:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/956963/135919</link><title>I had my tubes tied almost 6 years ago and have had regular cycles. I finished my last cycle less than 2 weeks ago and startedanother cycle today. I was told it could mean a tubal pregnancy, True??</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7446-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7446_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:57:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/question/606523/136995</link><title>i not having my period about 1years &amp; 2mths. my last cycle was 10 march 2010. i was not doing sex nearly 1 months. my aunty had a same prob when she was young but her cycle back normal after married</title><description>... january until june - no period at all.. ... June until december - normal period... 7 days n every months until december.. ... but suddenly, years 2010, im having my period from june 2009 until march 2010... then im not having period back until now... ... wen i stop taking the medication, suddenly the blood also stop. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7446-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7446_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:57:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/99374/46587</link><title>Effectiveness of 4 cycles of TC vs 6 cycles of TC (Taxotere + Cyclophosphamide)</title><description>... The profile is as follows: ... Tumor size : 0.7cm ... ER/PR : Positive ... HER 2 : Negative ... Grade : 2 ... Age : 41 ...   ... Would like to know if chemo regimen of TC x 4 cycles or TC x 6 cycles is effective for this profile? Please advise. Thank you. ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7446-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7446_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:57:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/120793/76082</link><title>which is better? Taxol or Taxotere and why? 3 weekly cycle of Taxotere or weekly cycle of Taxol?</title><description>...   ... Her doctor said, go for Taxol weekly dose but another doctor having the same qualifications says, she can go for 3 weekly Taxotere dose. Both medicines have the same results. So, we are confused!!! ...   ... Any help??? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7446-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7446_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:58:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/160512/120029</link><title>if you neutropenic after one of the cycles of adriamycin &amp; cytoxan for breast ca do the dr.'s reduce the lifetime dose or increase it for the next cycle?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7446-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7446_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:58:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/124839/124097</link><title>I have a 25-26 day cycle and my husband and I are trying for our second child, I was wondering if implantation occurs earlier in shorter cycles?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7446-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7446_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 19:58:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/971899/89886</link><title>can i only have four cycles of fac chemotherapy instead of 6 cycles?</title><description>... 3.2 cm tumor, lymph nodes negative, vascular invasion present. er pr positive. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>