<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7448">running shoes boston</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:02:12" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7448-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7448_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:02:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/255251/168139/buying-running-shoes</link><title>Buying Your First Pair of Running Shoes: How to Make It Out Alive</title><description>...   ... Buying your first pair of running shoes can either be an exciting endeavor or your worst nightmare. Upon entering the strange world that is the running store, you see billions of brightly-colored, psychedelically-patterned shoes lining the walls that offer up other curious gizmos like anti-chafing sticks, tubes of edible goo and belts made out of water bottles. More than you bargained for. You snap out of your daze as the perky salesperson approaches. “What can I help you find?” Um…shoes…that fit…? ...   ... The walls and walls of shoes is a result of more and more people having gotten into running over the past decade. Athletic shoe companies have responded to the increasing demand by supplying the consumer with unlimited options, but for the novice runner, it’s almost impossible to know where to start. As someone who’s taken quite a few friends to buy their first pair of running shoes, I know this situation all too well. Fortunately,... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7448-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7448_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:02:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/question/491586/61834</link><title>Please help me support the National MS Society as I run the 2009 Boston Marathon</title><description>... or mail a check (made payable to "Run MS NYC") to: ... National MS Society-NYC Chapter Attn: Run MS 733 Third Avenue, 3rd Floor New York, NY 10017 ... Please make sure to put my name and the Boston Ma... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7448-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7448_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:02:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/311516/134576/rh</link><title>Rheumatoid Arthritis and Shoes: No Love Affair with Shoes</title><description>...   ... Although not necessarily my friends, I have found a few pairs of shoes that have become companions that I can rely on.  These simple pairs of shoes can be worn knowing that the pain won't be as extreme as with other shoes.   I found my first pair in 2008 after my husband found me crying at the computer.  I was sure I was destined for a life of "grandma" shoes.  His search found something different.  He found a shoe store in the Chicago area that specializes in or... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7448-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7448_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:03:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/32129/migraine-headache</link><title>Live from Boston -- What's new in the Migraine and Headache World?</title><description>...   ... ... ... ... ... ...   ... OK, that was our amusing video for this trip. Some of the video I shot today will be put up after we get home because it needs clipped and edited. Still, we'll have plenty of information and some superb still photos for you, still to come this week. ...   ... Tomorrow, I want to share an exciting letter and other news from Boston. ...   ... Until tomorrow! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7448-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7448_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:03:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/568286/136420/put</link><title>Put A Little Spring In Your Step: RA And Shoes</title><description>...   ... Yesterday was an absolutely beautiful day in southeastern Michigan. It was sunny and almost 80 degrees. I decided to go for a run, which really means that ... I would run one block and then walk two or three. ...   ... Today it is cooler and rainy, and my hips are killing me. Not the smartest thing. ...   ... But I will say, I bought a pair of Skechers Shape Ups and I love them. I was just wearing regular gym shoes yesterday, but I usually wear the Skechers when I do my workout DVD. Not only do I feel that they improve my posture, but I feel like my joint mobility is better, like I kick higher. They are very cushy, and they distribute my weight more evenly than regular shoes. ...   ... This isn't meant to be an advertisement. I am not getting anything for dropping the brand name. ...   ... Honestly, one of... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7448-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7448_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:03:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/important-people-arthritis-2268</link><title>How important are shoes for people like me with knee arthritis?</title><description>... How important are shoes for people like me with knee arthritis? Is there a best shoe you can recommend? Proper shoe wear has always been touted as being important by the experts. Our experience is that good shoe wear makes good sense but some people seem to benefit more than others. In some cases, people with worn out shoes that offer little to no support have no symptoms and no problems. Others have to replace their shoes as soon as any wear causes an uneven support base. It's unclear why there is such a wide range of responses. Some people may just have a more sensitive sense of proprioception (sense of joint position) that signals change immediately. In a recent study from Canada two groups of adults with knee osteoarthritis were compared wearing two different kinds of shoes. The first group had on a high-end walking shoe by New Balance. The second group had a special medical training device called Masai Barefoot Technology ® (MBT®). The MBT is designed to increase muscle activity in t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7448-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7448_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:04:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/special-shoe-insert-knee-2031</link><title>I'm going to get a special shoe insert to help my knee pain.</title><description>... Ask your therapist, podiatrist, or orthotist to look at your current shoe wear to see if a new shoe is needed. If your current pair is worn out, ripped, or run down on one side then it's time for a new pair anyway. ... Reference: ... Lisa B.... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7448-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7448_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:04:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/82397/47149/shoes</link><title>New Shoes</title><description>...   ... My doctor immediately sent me to a neurologist.  The Neurologist put me on Tianzidine and sent me for an MRI.  Meanwhile, I almost fall down crossing the street, I purchased a walking cane, the muscle spasms woke me up throughout the night and I continued to go to work exhausted and loopey from Tianzidine.  I have th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7448-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7448_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:04:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/896502/117755/research</link><title>New Research Indicates That Claims About Toning Shoes May Not Toe the Fitness Line</title><description>...     However, a new study by the American Council on Exercise has caused me to reevaluate this potential purchase. ACE is dedicated to promoting the benefits of physical activity and protecting consumers against unsafe and ineffective health and fitness products, programs and trends. ACE accomplishes this through ongoing extensive research and studies in all areas of health and fitness, as well as public education regarding scientifically sound health and fitness practices. ...   ... Dubbed the "workout watchdog" by The Wall Street Journal in ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7448-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7448_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:04:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/804021/149234/day-wandering</link><title>Walk a Day in Her Shoes: Wandering in Alzheimer's Patients</title><description>...   ... Most people will tell you that the worst day for a person with Alzheimer's disease is the day they are asked to give up their keys because it is no longer safe for them to drive.  I remember the day vividly because I was the one who had to ask my mom for her keys.  Normally,... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>