<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7449">Asics GT 2000</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:05:16" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7449-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7449_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:05:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/cholesterol/c/question/295581/137981</link><title>My Dr wanted to put me on lovaza but I could not afford it so he told me to take 1000 mg of omega 3's. I take 2000 mg in the am and 2000 mg in the pm. Is this too much? trying to lower triglycerides.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7449-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7449_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:05:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/836461/48078</link><title>Diabetic 2000 KCal ADA Diet</title><description>... What is the definition of a 2000 KCal ADA Diet ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7449-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7449_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:05:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/question/944154/78808</link><title>I have developed a Chronic Cough, do I go to my Gastro Dr. or Surgeon who operated in 2000.</title><description>... I had a successful Laproscopic Nissan Fundiplication in 2000.  I have had no problems, other than what everyone has after surgery.  I now have developed a chronic cough, at first I assumed it was allergies, after over a year, it is getting worse.  I have gained 30 pounds within the last year and wonder if that could be the problem.  My question is do I go to the doctor who performed the surgery or my gastro doctor? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7449-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7449_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:06:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/76871/44648</link><title>Can I get a Venus 2000 on the Web?</title><description>... I have ED.  I'm looking for a Venus 2000 which I understand is a masturbating machine. Is it safe to use?  Where on the web can I obtain one at the best price? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7449-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7449_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:06:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/205662/90099</link><title>Should I use Hot tub? Had open heart surgery in 2000, am 85 years old. Noticed my heel is swollen</title><description>...   ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7449-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7449_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:06:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/313707/147361</link><title>Based on blood test my doc advises I need to take 2000 IU Vitamin D daily. I currently take a 1200 liquid calcium capsule with 1000 IU Vitamin D. Your recommendaton please for other 1000 IUs.</title><description>... Based on blood test my doc advises I need to take 2000 IU Vitamin D daily. I currently take a 1200 liquid calcium capsule with 1000 IU Vitamin D. Your recommendaton please for other 1000 IUs. Should I take an additional dose of my current vitamin (4 capsules instead of 2) or look for more fortified with Vitamin D food products?   All my other labs were good. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7449-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7449_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:07:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/416950/58070</link><title>i have been remain anxious from 2000 to 2009 and now i m getting anti anxious medicines, I had many</title><description>...   ... Suleman ... Rabel143143@yahoo.com ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7449-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7449_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:07:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/question/46392/38597</link><title>gastric-bypass 02/02/2000, lost 200 of the 450lbs, first year in had skin removal, it was horrible</title><description>...   ... My surgery was in 2000, I weighed in at 450lbs and I have lost more than 200lbs. The first year after my bypass the Dr. did some kind of skin removal but didn't do a very good job at all and all he could say about it was "what did I expect being on government insurance". and now I am so unhappy with the way I look. It has given me very low self-esteem to where I have not wanted to have any kind of relationship. Is there something that I can do now, I do not live in the same state anymore and wouldn't let that Dr. do another surgery anyway. I should be proud of the weight I have lossed that I have had but because of the Dr. leaving me the way he did I am embarrassed and ashamed to have people see me. I do not feel like a women most of the time, I have to wear baggy clothes and I sometimes feel why did I even have the surgery if this is what I am going to feel like. What can I do, where can I go. Will this kind of surgery be considered cosmetic or would it be consi... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7449-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7449_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:07:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/845383/54234/lifetimegirl</link><title>Lifetimegirl_2000's Story</title><description>...   Hello to everyone. My name is Janice and I am living with migraine. I started seeing my family physician back in the early 80's for headaches that were so horrible that I couldn't find the right words to describe them.I had been riding in my car when another car hit me from behind and jarred me really hard. No damage to the old car so we just agreeded to let it go.Very shortly after that is when the headaches started with fury. ... My doctors were great and immediently knew they were migraines. I started the regimine of a preventative, a med to kill an oncoming headache and then a back up med in case that didn't work. Then, if all else failed go to the ER.This has now been going on 3 decades. I've been to a neurologist and I am now at a Headache Wellness Center where they day I have genetic, chronic migraine.As of the last 122 days from today (01-02-09) I have had 38 migraines. I keep a diairy for them to keep track of my progress. I hope to meet other people with this horrible... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7449-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7449_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:08:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/8855/13926/painting-2000</link><title>A painting from 2000</title><description>... This painting is done in oils in 2000 when I was living in Portland OR and having a very hard time. I studied at a college of fine art instead of for a lucrative career so don't have a lot of income, and was doing an office job that barely covered my rent let alone medical, food, clothing, housing etc expenses. I couldn't afford to miss work and the doctors I saw dismissed my problems as they were difficult to figure out under the rules imposed by the insurance companies. So I worked with daily problems leaving permanent damage from not treating them. Most of my paintings are based on landscapes drawn from internal experience mixed with memory and impressions of places from my past. I didn't do this painting to illustrate a situation or make a point, it was more an explosion of a lot of pain and frustration over time. I don't really like to talk about meaning or symbolism in my work, I feel if it doesn't speak for itself then it's not done... meaning is in the ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>