<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7450">thailand individual travel</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:08:36" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7450-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7450_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:08:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/guides/000001_2.html</link><title>Travel to Developing Countries - Traveler's Diarrhea</title><description>... Traveler's Diarrhea Traveler's diarrhea (TD) is the most common health problem a traveler encounters. It is almost always caused by ingesting certain organisms in contaminated food or water. Diarrhea can also be caused -- particularly in children -- by anxiety, stress, allergies, fatigue, and dietary changes. Symptoms and Course Diarrhea frequently occurs within the first week of travel, but may develop at any point, even after returning home. Traveler's diarrhea causes four or five loose or watery stools per day. Vomiting may also occur. It usually lasts 3 or 4 days, but about 14% of cases last longer. In rare cases, the diarrhea lasts more than 3 months. When TD lasts a long time, it can cause post-infectious irritable bowel syndrome. Traveler's diarrhea is rarely life threatening, although it can be severely debilitating, especially in children. Weakness, reduced urine output, lightheadedness, and mental changes require immediate medical attention, especially in children. Life-threate... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7450-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7450_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:08:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/guides/000001_4.html</link><title>Travel to Developing Countries - Travel Precautions</title><description>... Travel Precautions Vector-borne diseases are infections transmitted by insects and animals that harbor parasites, viruses, or bacteria. Common vector-borne diseases include yellow fever and malaria, but there are many others in every country in the world. The risk for malaria and other mosquito-born infections is highest when mosquitoes feed, between dusk and dawn. Insect Repellents DEET. Most insect repellents contain the chemical DEET (N,N-diethyl-meta-toluamide), which remains the gold standard of currently available mosquito and tick repellents. DEET has been used for more than 40 years and is safe for most children when used as directed. Comparison studies suggest that DEET preparations are the most effective insect repellents now available. DEET concentrations range from 4 - 100%. The concentration determines the duration of protection. Experts recommend that most adults and children over 12 years old use preparations containing a DEET concentration of 20 - 35% (such as Ultrathon), w... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7450-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7450_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:09:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/guides/000001_5.html</link><title>Travel to Developing Countries - Traveling with Health Problems</title><description>... Traveling with Health Problems or While Pregnant Diabetes People with diabetes who do not require insulin injections do very well during international travel, provided they monitor diet and exercise. Insulin-dependent patients should remember that if they are traveling eastward the first day is shortened, and they will need less insulin. Westward travel means a longer day, thus will require additional insulin. Patients who travel by aircraft and need to carry syringes or needles now require medical documents. Heart and Lung Diseases People with any serious medical conditions should check with their doctor before travel. Of note, cabin pressure in aircraft is typically equal to about 5,000 - 8,000 feet above sea level. This can produce a 4% reduction of oxygen in the blood, which can affect patients with heart or lung problems. Recommendations for Patients with Heart Risks. One study reported that over half the deaths that occurred in overseas travelers were due to heart disease. Generally,... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7450-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7450_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:09:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/40203/151145/week</link><title>MS and Travelling: Question of the Week</title><description>...   ... I’ve always loved to travel.   As children, we read books that carry our imagination away to different times and far off places.   In movies, we are drawn into sometimes dreamy or even scary places, transporting us to places we may never have the chance to visit.   (As an aside, I highly recommend renting any film by Director/Producer/Editor David Lean and his epics Lawrence of Arabia , Doctor Zhivago or Bridge on the River Kwai , as well as the gorgeous romance   “Summertime” that took place in the city of Venice.   They are each a feast for the eyes.) ...   ... When you have a chronic illness like MS, it’s not alw... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7450-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7450_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:09:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/guides/000001.html</link><title>Travel to Developing Countries - Highlights</title><description>... Highlights More than 50 million people from industrialized nations travel to developing countries each year. Since many doctors find it hard to keep abreast of medical trends in foreign countries, a local travel clinic may be especially helpful to prepare you for travel to developing countries. Travelers to developing countries should have a thorough checkup and prepare for any health situation at least 4 - 6 weeks before the trip. Be sure to get a checkup, even if this much advance time is not available. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention maintains a Traveler's Health web site ( wwwn.cdc.gov/travel ). The site carries news about dangerous disease outbreaks around the world, safety guidelines, and detailed disease information about diseases of particular concerns to travelers. Immunocompromised patients may need to take extra precautions in addition to the recommendations in this report. Patients with impaired immune systems should discuss their travel plans with their physicians... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7450-06"><link>http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/110/6935/medical-record</link><title>Traveling With Diabetes: A Diabetic's Survival Kit</title><description>...   ... Here's how to do it: ...   ...        1. Contact your p ersonal p hysician, and show him/her this commentary. ...        2. Ask the staff to give you co p ies of the following p ages from your chart: ...               * Any recent lab results (within the p ast six months or so) ...               * The most recent co p y of your: ...               &amp;... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7450-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7450_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:10:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/330514/152629/birthday</link><title>Celebrating my Birthday with Culinary "Travels"</title><description>... I celebrated my 33rd birthday recently. For those of you that have been following this blog, you know that I am a person who likes to celebrate practically anything; I barely need an excuse. And celebration always entails some kind of food and beverage. So when my birthday arrives, I make no exception and generally go over-the-top in my celebratory practices. This year, I have been overwhelmed by my friends' and family's generosity, and feel completely and decadently spoiled. But I also feel incredibly full and heavy! In the two weeks leading up to my birthday, I have totally blown my gluten and dairy-free diet experiment, and have been unable to get back on track. And when I say I blew it, boy do I mean it. I haven't held back one bit, and the five pounds I've put back on are sad, sorry proof. I'm going to make a safe bet and guess that this week will be the culmination of off-limits edibles, and come Monday I'll be peeling myself away from the restaurants and placing my butt firmly ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7450-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7450_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:10:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/72218/154154/ped</link><title>Trains, Trams, and Walking Canes: Pedestrian Travel in Europe</title><description>... One thing that I truly enjoy about European cities is the ease of public transportation.  Trains and trams connect neighborhoods and districts in a way which is not common in the US.  Other than cobblestone streets in old neighborhoods, it is very easy to get from point A to point B, that is, if you are ambulatory. ... In the train station, on the streets, every which way I looked in Zurich, I watched people of various ages using canes and crutches.  Only once did I spot a wheelchair.  The occupant was a youth who appeared to be permanently disabled and the chair was motorized.   It did make me wonder if wheelchairs are not as common in Switzerland.  Not even once did I spot an... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7450-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7450_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:11:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/manage-31662-5.html</link><title>Traveling with Asthma</title><description>... Summer vacation. It conjures up visions of relaxation, sports, sunny days, perhaps sand and water or woodlands. For individuals and families with asthma and allergies though, it means extra thought and preparation before "the good times roll." As we head full tilt into summer, here is a list of some common sense—but commonly missed—suggestions for a healthy vacation. Medications Take with you a detailed list of medications showing prescription refill number, prescribing physician and dosage. (Each medication's original label should have all the needed information.) Pack the needed quantities of medications and, if possible, also pack a backup quantity to avoid being caught short. Be sure to pack your medication in your carry-on luggage in case checked luggage is lost. Be sure to bring an emergency, insect-sting epinephrine injection kit if you or someone in your family has this form of hypersensitivity. Include with your medications a topical hydrocortisone cream a... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7450-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7450_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:11:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/cold-flu/c/82437/16611/dont-germs-travel</link><title>Don’t Let Germs Be Your Travel Companions</title><description>... As the holidays approach, you may want to stop making fun of these people, and start following their lead, especially if you are one of the millions of people who are planning on flying this season. ...   ... In fact, a recent study in the Journal of Environmental Health Research shows that you are 100% more likely to catch a cold while flying than when going about your normal routine. So, what's the intrepid traveler to do to avoid arriving at Aunt Ida's with the flu ? Here are some tips: ... ... Exit, stage left . Ask for a seat in the exit row. Not only will you have more leg room, but a sneeze can travel up to three feet, and the exit row will provide a safe zone. The second best option is to choose a seat up front in the plane because the air is fresher ( not much fresher, but inside of a... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>