<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7451">buy animal farm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:11:38" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7451-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7451_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:11:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/89/14387/flat-eggs</link><title>Flat Tires and Farm Fresh Eggs</title><description>... As I write this morning, I feel a definite hush in the air, and I KNOW it's not just me. A few short years ago around this time, the United States was hit with the most horrible disaster that destroyed not only buildings and shattered peoples' lives, but also changed the way we will think about many things forever. The blessing I felt in spite of this disaster was the outpouring of love and concern I experienced as I continued my travels through Sicily. The handwritten signs in store windows and the quiet smiles from people when they found we were Americans. People DO care for others, it's too bad that we had to find it out this way!   As usual, I'm rushing around trying to get the laundry done and my camera gear packed for another trip, this time it's to take on the role of "Daddyma" since one of my granddaughters is turning 3. I really couldn't quite understand what she was saying to me on the phone, so I had to ask her dad for a translat... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7451-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7451_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:11:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/145746/ohio-community</link><title>Ohio Man Kills Himself After Releasing 50 Exotic Animals Into Nearby Community</title><description>...   ... USA Today and other new sources are showing the horrifying scenes in Zanesville Ohio where Terry Thompson, owner of a wild animal farm, has set free exotic animals including bears, giraffes, tigers, cougars, leopards, wolves, and monkeys.  After setting the animals free Thompson shot himself.  ...   ... As a result of Thompson's apparent suicide, 49 of these animals have been killed so far.  The explanation given for shooting to kill instead of using a tranquilizer gun was to protect the people who live in the surrounding community.  Evidently they did not have tranquilizer guns.  ...   ... My personal response is horror.  Many of these animals are endangered species. ...   ... For example they killed 18 tigers, some at close range. ...   ... Here is another piece of this story. According to the Chicago Tribune Thompson had been charged with animal cruelty 11 times since 2004.  ...   ... How could this have happened? ... &amp;n... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7451-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7451_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:12:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/1443/115213/buy-adhd-child-pet</link><title>Should I Buy My ADHD Child a Pet?</title><description>...   ... Choosing whether to have a pet is a decision each family must make on their own, based on their lifestyle. For families that spend large blocks out each day away from the house, it may not be practical to have a dog. Allergies may need to be taken into consideration.   ...   ... There are, however, some benefits to having a family pet: ...   ... Pets teach about schedules . ... Every pet, whether it is a fish or a dog, must be fed each day. Some pets, such as dogs, are even more schedule intensive: feeding, walking, brushing, bathing. Children can learn to create basic schedules each day to help care for the pet. Creating the schedule also helps a child learn to plan ahead. He or she will need to plan for bath days, m... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7451-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7451_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:12:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/59238/160511/obesity-person-environment</link><title>For Obesity – Learn From the Animals…Says Expert</title><description>...   ... Highlighted in the discussion, was the 2012 book Zoobiquity, co-authored by Barbara Natterson-Horowitz, a researcher currently involved in a project that looks at the connection between the health of humans and the animal kingdom.  Ms. Horowitz discussed the prevalence of obesity in the patient population in her practice and like most practitioners, would typically discuss the foods they were choosing, how much or little exercise they were engaged in, their emotional state and how it guided... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7451-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7451_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:12:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/7243/15167/start-local</link><title>Three Reasons You Need to Start Buying Local</title><description>... The movement to buy local, healthy food is spreading across the country and gaining momentum - and that is a very good thing.   It is driven by several factors - one, the taste of fresh, local food is just so much better than food that has traveled far. Two, it often costs less because it is seasonally produced and the food is generally abundant and there are few transportation costs. And third is the state of our planet and global warming. As we know, driving food across the country and using gallons of gasoline to do it contributes to our climate conditions and the damages the planet.     This week I attended a meeting that dealt with the need for reducing our demand for oil. There was a lot of discussion about Middle East tensions and global warming and how we all needed to "do something" to make a change. Of course, there were suggestions for driving less, flying less and avoiding petroleum-based plastics. I began to think that if we became active in the l... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7451-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7451_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:13:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/92639/50693/cosmaceuticals</link><title>Are You Buying Cosmaceuticals as if They Are Hope in a Jar??</title><description>...   ... The biggest sellers are creams that have antioxidant s, followed by creams that have peptides, growth factor, retinols (vitamin A), fruit acids , hyalaronic acid , and even collagen .  Combination products or regimens, containing several of these ingredients are extremely popular.  The most important thing to consider is - ... ... (a) Is there enough active ingredient to have an impact? ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7451-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7451_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:13:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/7243/13273/2007-bill</link><title>Get Involved with the 2007 Healthy Farm Bill!</title><description>... This year the Farm Bill is up for renewal by Congress. The bill is comprehensive legislation that affects farmers and consumers alike, and I have been so pleased how consumers and public health advocates have been actively involved in its process all across the country. Here in Washington, I have been working with other coalition members who are calling for a Healthy Farm Bill that promotes and supports local,healthy food.   For example, Senators Sherrod Brown and Hillary Clinton have introduced a bill that would bring local, fresh fruits and vegetables to schools and underserved communities and would expand the Farmers Market Promotion program.   The Farm Bill is legislation that sets the direction of the American food system for years to come. In September, the Senate will be voting on these important issues. This year, by being involved, we can make it a "Good Food Bill." What are your ideas for supporting local agriculture? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7451-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7451_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:13:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/9182/7242/farm-show</link><title>Farm Show Pictures</title><description>... Here are pictures of the Farm show we went to. We had fun. It is the Largest Farm show in the world. And peopple from all over the world come by and shop there. Alan loved this big Truck This is Alans Fav. Picture as he loves NASCAR. We had fun. There are none of Michael as he was sleeping through most of it lol. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7451-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7451_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:14:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/gradually-taking-nebraska-2543</link><title>My son is gradually taking over the family farm in Nebraska.</title><description>... My son is gradually taking over the family farm in Nebraska. Last winter he got his leg caught in the auger and nearly lost it. Thanks to his physical therapist, he is back on his feet and working full-time again. I've seen other farmers who never got therapy and it shows. Why isn't this routinely recommended? Researchers have documented the beneficial effect of physical therapy after severe trauma such as your son experienced. A special study called the Lower Extremity Assessment Project (LEAP) project has collected data on patients at eight level I trauma centers in the United States. Analysis of the information collected shows that patients who are identified as needing physical therapy don't always get these services. Those who do, have better overall results as measured by range-of-motion, physical activities, daily self-care, and walking or climbing stairs. Why doesn't everyone get this kind of treatment? There may not be one single reason. First, there are always reimbursement iss... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7451-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7451_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:14:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/active-horsewoman-horse-1384</link><title>I am an active horsewoman with a busy horse farm.</title><description>... I am an active horsewoman with a busy horse farm. Because of my severe hip arthritis, I can't ride anymore. Would the new hip resurfacing surgery I saw advertised in the paper put me back in the saddle again? It's very possible. Younger adults with active lifestyles who are too young for a total hip replacement are turning to this new option. Instead of cutting off the head of the femur (thighbone), the surgeon puts a cap over the damaged bone. If and when you need a total hip replacement years from now, the bone will be undisturbed. At that time, the surgeon can remove the damaged bone and replace it with a complete implant. And you won't lose leg length from having a second hip surgery. Hip resurfacing isn't an option for everyone. An orthopedic surgeon will need to assess your situation. If you are a good candidate for this procedure, you may be able to start riding again two to three months after the operation. Rehab begins right away. A physical therapist will work with you to restor... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>