<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7452">arizona game and fish homepage</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:14:46" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7452-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7452_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:14:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/896502/139724/athletes</link><title>Senior Games Provide Competitive Opportunities for Athletes Who Are Older than 50</title><description>... For instance, Houston, Texas will host more than 10,000 athletes for the 2011 National Senior Games.  This event is the largest multisport competition for male and female athletes who are 50 years old and above. Events include track and field, swimming, bicycling, golf, racquetball, bowling, triathlon, archery, race walking and power walking, tennis, archery, basketball, and softball. These games are coordinated by the National Senior Games Association (NSGA) , which is a non-profit member of the United States Olympic Committee that is dedicated to motivating older men and women to lead a healthy lifestyle through these events. ... State chapters of NSGA also coordinate s... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7452-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7452_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:15:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/158921/healthy-snacking</link><title>Healthy Game Day Snacking on a Diet</title><description>... Game day is here! Whether you’re watching the big game from your living room couch or are one of the lucky few who are tailgating at Super Bowl 2013, you will be rooting for your favorite team and chowing down snacks. Most traditional Super Bowl spreads are unhealthy pub grub: A buffet of easy-to-prepare appetizers and entrees that go well with beer. These foods are not healthy for the average person, and pose a greater threat for those of us on a diet. ...   ... I have eliminated refined foods, fast food, red meat, sugar, saturated fats, starches, and grains from my diet. I’ve worked hard to lose weight and educate myself on how to eat healthy. So, I am not about to let game day cramp my style. Neither will I allow my style (diet) to hamper my enjoyment today. Believe it or not, it is completely possible, dare I say easy, to make delicious and nutritious Super Bowl Party fare. ...   ... Since Super Bowl 2013 takes place in New Orleans, why not prepare some of the area's tradit... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7452-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7452_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:15:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/95808/53881/mii</link><title>Playing Nintendo Wii Games as Multiple Sclerosis Therapy</title><description>... Right after Thanksgiving I wrote a piece titled " Wheeeee!!! " in which I stated that Mandy and I succumbed to Wii madness, purchased one of the video game consoles, and planned to delve into the world of Wii, Miis, and daily fitness tests. We guessed that perhaps, because of the physical nature of Wii gaming, playing Wii would actually prove beneficial to Mandy who, like so many others, suffers from Relapsing-Remitting MS . Now, after a month of playing, we believe that we were correct and that Wii is proving itself well worth the investment. At the risk of being a commercial for Nintendo, I'm going to plow ahead and talk about our experience to date. When you buy Wii it comes with a Sports Games disc. There are five games on the disc from which to choose: Tennis, Bowling, Boxing, Golf, and Baseball. Each game requires a level of physical and mental control over one's limbs. Mandy started slowly and, believe it or not, tired easily after playing just a few of the different games. I could... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7452-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7452_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:15:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/6509/69097/world</link><title>Video Games Improve Memory</title><description>...   ... The journal Psychology and Aging reports the findings of a study using the “Rise of Nations” video game.  Though the study is small (20 participants played the game, 20 did not), the results were quite remarkable.  The participants who played the game received rewards during their play time for successfully managing, building, and expanding empires.  ALL twenty game players showed improvement in working memory (short term memory), visual memory (memory of things seen such as lists), and other thinking abilities.  I have not seen the “Rise of Nations” video game, but I have put it on my “to do” list. ...   ... The website by ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7452-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7452_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:15:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/108270/preventing-brain</link><title>Preventing Alzheimer’s: Exercise, Diet and Brain Games Show Promise</title><description>...   ... Now, a Wall Street Journal article titled " How to Outsmart Alzheimer's: New Effort Tries to Fight Disease With Word, Math Games, even Wii for Exercise ," shines an even brighter light on this approach. ...   ... The article begins thus: "Doctors frustrated by a lack of a cure, or even an effective treatment, for Alzheimer's disease are trying a new approach: preventing the disease altogether. A new project, the Cognitive Fitness and Innovative Therapies, or CFIT, is trying to keep people at risk for Alzheimer's intellectually and physically fit with quizzes and other cognitive challenges to see if onset of the disease can be delayed, perhaps indefinitely." ...   ... This article brings together an array of approaches th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7452-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7452_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:16:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/113437/brain-food</link><title>Diabetes: Eating Fish Improves Omega 3 levels and Increase Brain Health</title><description>... Whether people with diabetes need bigger brains that other people is something that science hasn't studied yet. But some scientists who have studied our early ancestors have just discovered that we got our big brains originally from a diet that came in large part from fish and other aquatic animals. Until now, most of the scientists who study our early ancestors assumed that they lived on the plains of East Africa. This "savannah theory" seemed to point at a diet of roots, seeds and nuts, some green plants and the occasional small game -- the hunter-gatherer hypothesis. This is pretty far from the oceans where fish live. But fish also live in lakes and streams. And now we know that some of our earliest ancestors about 1.95 million years ago lived around such a wet environment.  Archeologists  working in northern Kenya found that our ancestors ate a lot of fish, turtles, and crocodiles. By analyzing the bones of the animals and the stone tools that our ancestors made the scientis... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7452-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7452_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:16:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/6509/54670/wii-success</link><title>Wii...What a Success!</title><description>...   ... The Wii was bought to challenge me physically and to encourage exercise.  My husband and I have just finished really getting into it, and I have learned how to turn it on by myself without anyone’s help.  Today, I spent my first half hour “working out” by myself with my Wii.  I was sweating about midway through.  Today was the first time I have run—actu... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7452-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7452_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:16:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/4182/112371/depressed-age-3</link><title>Parent Child Interaction Therapy and Young Children Clinically Depressed</title><description>...   ... Depression in children is a well established if still somewhat controversial concept. However, is the notion of a 3-year-old suffering with clinical depression convincing? If it is, what are we meant to do about it? ...   ... According to Luby the fact that depression is a brain disorder means it isn't restricted to older children and adults. Her view is that while preschool depression isn't common it exists in up to 2 percent of the population in that age range. Luby says a lack of disruptive behavior may also be a sign and that "good" children may... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7452-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7452_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:17:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/38780/49501</link><title>Expander Info (wish it came sooner for me)</title><description>... When I seen my PS last visit he said that they can now attach the expander to the tissue. I dont know about other ladies out there but my expanders move into spots that bug me. Sometimes its in my armpit, sittin high,sittin low,man it would have been nice to have em in one spot. So I hope they are doing this everywhere not just Arizona. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7452-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7452_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:17:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/5741/85298/quit-ya</link><title>Quit! Will ya?</title><description>...   ... I had two bad habits that needed to be addressed. Smoking and coffee. I wanted to quit smoking. It was slowly killing me and I wanted to live. I was up to four packs a day. I would wake up in the wee hours coughing so hard I thought my lungs would come flying out. I couldn't walk very far without losing my breath. My teeth were stained and my clothes smelled like smoke. ...   ...  I decided it was time to quit. First I needed a plan. I looked at when I smoked and what I was doing. I found out that I smoked and drank coffee at the same times. In order to stop smoking I had to stop drinking coffee. I drank gallons of coffee everyday. I quit coffee with the fear of how I was gonna wake up in the morning. Even with that fear I quit. After a few months I was waking up more refreshed than any cup of coffee could  ever do. ...   ... One year later I stopped smoking. I had just bought a carton of cigs. My son and I went to the park... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>