<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7453">pc 2 games reviews</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:17:37" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7453-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7453_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:17:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/37333/21462/game</link><title>review of automated game system</title><description>... Hi, i am an AS level student, i have just finished manufacturing an automated draughts board machine.     i would really appreciate it if you would email me so that i could send you an email with a Word document attachment that includes all the information about my design so that you could review it for me.   Typical student, i have left my coursework till the last minute, and would really appreciate it if people could get in contact me, and then review my project, for its practicality for a person suffering from arthritis.  my project is meant to limit the movement needed to play a game of draughts, this would be helpful to someone as i am sure it can be very painful movement in the joints sometimes.   i would also be very happy to be given a further understanding of the difficulties of arthritis.     my email is  - myles@smithsbarn.com i would really appreciate it if i could have feedback before the end of this weekend as i must hand my final piece of w... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7453-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7453_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:17:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/game-affected-hip-replaced-1501</link><title>Do you have any idea how my golf game might be affected by having my hip replaced?</title><description>... Do you have any idea how my golf game might be affected by having my hip replaced? Right now, the pain keeps me from going more than 9-holes once a week. And my drive falls way short of what it used to. Can I even play golf after this kind of surgery? Golf is a low-impact activity that can be resumed after rehab for total hip replacement. If you let your physical therapist know of your interest in getting back on the golf course, your rehab program can be advanced to include specific sports-training for golf. This is a good idea in order to prevent further injuries and to spare your implant excess torque or load. Studies show that of all the sports patients are involved in before joint replacement, golf is the one more people return to. There's some evidence that your handicap may increase as well as the your drive length. The average change in handicap is an increase of 1.1 strokes. The average drive length increases by 3.3 yards. Even though golfing can involve a fair amount of walking... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7453-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7453_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:18:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/164277/great-weight-gain-addiction</link><title>The Great Weight Gain Addiction Game, Part 4</title><description>... Photo by Stuart Miles ...   ... Read Part 1 ...   ... Before any of my friends share secrets with me they first want some assurance that I will keep the information that I am about to be given to myself. The conversation usually begins with the question, “Can you keep a secret?” ... I let them know that I certainly can, and when I give that same information to some other person I begin the conversation with that same question: “Can you keep a secret?” ...   ... I will be told by the person I am speaking to that he or she is cross-my-heart-and-hope-to-die capable. I’ll bet you know what happens next. Pretty soon there is not much secret left. This brings to mind the question as to why should there be secrets at all. ... The first reason is the hope to spare a person’s feelings as in “Don’t tell Mary that you saw her husband with another woman. It would hurt her too much.” Perhaps the judgment is bad but at least the intention is good. ... The second r... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7453-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7453_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:18:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/common/images/image.html</link><title>video game, gaming, tv, siblings, game</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7453-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7453_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:18:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/215658/157320/spartan</link><title>Spartan Race Fenway Park: A Review</title><description>...   ... One of the trademarks of the adventure run is mud.  They get messy.  Tough Mudder, Warrior Dash, Rogue Run, Spartan Race, Run for Your Lives – they all prominently feature slop and getting dirty is just as much a part of the experience as running.  Yet with the considerations of the venue, it didn't seem that mud was going to be in the mix. So the race’s designers got creative. ...   ... The race took place on Saturday, November 17, 2012 at Fenway Park in Boston, part of the centenni... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7453-06"><link>http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/89022/16757/review-managing</link><title>A REVIEW OF TECHNIQUES IN MANAGING YOUR DEPRESSION</title><description>... By Stanley Popovich   Some people have a difficult time in managing their depression. Sometimes, their depression and fears can get best of them. As a result, here is a short list of techniques that a person can use to help manage their depression.   One of the ways to manage your depression is to challenge your negative thinking with positive statements and realistic thinking. When encountering thoughts that make your fearful or depressed, challenge those thoughts by asking yourself questions that will maintain objectivity and common sense. For example, your afraid that if you do not get that job promotion then you will be stuck at your job forever. This depresses you, however your thinking in this situation is unrealistic. The fact of the matter is that there all are kinds of jobs available and just because you don't get this job promotion doesn't mean that you will never get one. In addition, people change jobs all the time, and you always have that option of going el... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7453-07"><link>http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/45204/17487/review</link><title>A REVIEW OF TECHNIQUES IN MANAGING YOUR DEPRESSION</title><description>...   Some people have a difficult time in managing their depression. Sometimes, their depression and fears can get best of them. As a result, here is a short list of techniques that a person can use to help manage their depression.   One of the ways to manage your depression is to challenge your negative thinking with positive statements and realistic thinking. When encountering thoughts that make your fearful or depressed, challenge those thoughts by asking yourself questions that will maintain objectivity and common sense. For example, your afraid that if you do not get that job promotion then you will be stuck at your job forever. This depresses you, however your thinking in this situation is unrealistic. The fact of the matter is that there all are kinds of jobs available and just because you don't get this job promotion doesn't mean that you will never get one. In addition, people change jobs all the time, and you always have that option of going elsewhere if you are ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7453-08"><link>http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/30889/17485/review-managing</link><title>A REVIEW OF TECHNIQUES IN MANAGING YOUR DEPRESSION</title><description>... By Stanley Popovich   Some people have a difficult time in managing their depression. Sometimes, their depression and fears can get best of them. As a result, here is a short list of techniques that a person can use to help manage their depression.   One of the ways to manage your depression is to challenge your negative thinking with positive statements and realistic thinking. When encountering thoughts that make your fearful or depressed, challenge those thoughts by asking yourself questions that will maintain objectivity and common sense. For example, your afraid that if you do not get that job promotion then you will be stuck at your job forever. This depresses you, however your thinking in this situation is unrealistic. The fact of the matter is that there all are kinds of jobs available and just because you don't get this job promotion doesn't mean that you will never get one. In addition, people change jobs all the time, and you always have that option of going el... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7453-09"><link>http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/89022/59701/review-depression</link><title>A REVIEW OF TECHNIQUES IN MANAGING YOUR DEPRESSION</title><description>... Some people have a difficult time in managing their depression.  Sometimes, their depression and fears can get the best of them.  As a result, here is a short list of techniques that a person can use to help manage their depression. ...   ... One of the ways to manage your depression is to challenge your negative thinking with positive statements and realistic thinking. When encountering thoughts that make your fearful or depressed, challenge those thoughts by asking yourself questions that will maintain objectivity and common sense. For example, your afraid that if you do not get that job promotion then you will be stuck at your job forever. This depresses you, however your thinking in this situation is unrealistic. The fact of the matter is that there all are kinds of jobs available and just because you don't get this job promotion doesn't mean that you will never get one. In addition, people change jobs all the time, and you always have that option of going elsewhere ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7453-10"><link>http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/45204/59700/depression</link><title>A REVIEW OF TECHNIQUES IN MANAGING YOUR DEPRESSION</title><description>... Some people have a difficult time in managing their depression.  Sometimes, their depression and fears can get the best of them.  As a result, here is a short list of techniques that a person can use to help manage their depression. ...   ... One of the ways to manage your depression is to challenge your negative thinking with positive statements and realistic thinking. When encountering thoughts that make your fearful or depressed, challenge those thoughts by asking yourself questions that will maintain objectivity and common sense. For example, your afraid that if you do not get that job promotion then you will be stuck at your job forever. This depresses you, however your thinking in this situation is unrealistic. The fact of the matter is that there all are kinds of jobs available and just because you don't get this job promotion doesn't mean that you will never get one. In addition, people change jobs all the time, and you always have that option of going elsewhere ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>