<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7456">gps reviews</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:27:01" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7456-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7456_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:27:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/question/398696/122373</link><title>Do ALL/MOST internist or GPs Know how to test for VIt D deficiency?</title><description>...   ...  What is TSH?  Why is it important?  How do you test for it? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7456-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7456_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:27:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/12995/36324/westchester-gps</link><title>Westchester County's Project Lifesaver --NY suburb gives GPS to Alzheimer's patients</title><description>...   ... Also see: Alzheimer's: Understand and control wandering Do you have the Silver Alert Program in your state? Probably not. ... NY suburb gives GPS to Alzheimer's patients ...   ... A county in New York's northern suburbs has a new program that will issue global positioning system tracki... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7456-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7456_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:27:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/question/466497/55014</link><title>Where can I buy a gps tracking bracelet?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7456-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7456_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:28:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/1443/147827/performance-review</link><title>Performance Review Anxiety: Tips to Help You Cope with an Upcoming Performance Review</title><description>...   ... The following tips can help you cope with an upcoming review: ...   ... Think about the purpose of the review. While many managers, unfortunately, focus on what the employee has done wrong throughout the year, a performance review is meant to provide you, the employee, with information to help you do your job better. While you are not able to control how your supervisor or manager acts during the review, you can control how you react to the information. For example, imagine your supervisor begins to discuss an error you made on a report you recently completed. Instead of becoming defensive and argumentative, thank the superv... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7456-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7456_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:28:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/21405/84696</link><title>Kolonipin. Med review @ med review N P recommended change from xanax to this med</title><description>... nurse practioner @ mental health med review. Recommending klonopin am conserned about this med.  I was conserned I may be getting addicted. as I have most times run out of the xanax before it is time for next script.  I and my Therapist feel that I should either increase my anti depressant and reducing the dosage of xanax.  Mt therapist indicated that kolonipin is very difficult to get off from once addicted.   I come from a family of drug and alcohol abusers and I don't want to become addicted to xanax or kolonipin.  My therapist recommended I stay on the xanax by reducing dosage and maybe increasing the dosage of anti depressant.  As I use the xanax not only for anxiety and to help me sleep. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7456-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7456_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:28:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/568286/159937/rheumatoid</link><title>Book Review: “Your Life With Rheumatoid Arthritis: Managing Treatment, Side Effects, and Pain”</title><description>...   ... Our fearless community leader here at HealthCentral, Lene Andersen, has written a book called, “Your Life With Rheumatoid Arthritis: Tools For Managing Treatment, Side Effects, and Pain.”  ...   ... The book, while more how-to than memoir, is a culmination of over 40 years of experience living with RA.  Lene began having symptoms of Juvenile Rheumatoid Arthritis at the age of 4, and she speaks from first-hand experience when she talks about treatments, managing pain, and dealing with side effects. ...   ... In the treatment section of the book, Lene explains the treatments that are currently available for RA, and how treatment has evolved over the years since she was diagnosed.  There are many more treatments available now than there were then. ...   ... In the side effects section of the book, Lene goes through the litany of side effects that can come from taking medication to treat RA.  If you have experience taking these medications, you are probably ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7456-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7456_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:29:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/92/20399/diets-la-loss</link><title>Popular Diets Reviewed: LA Weight Loss Program</title><description>... While I’m not as familiar with the LA Weight Loss plan as other diets, I do know many people who have experienced success on the program. This program has been around since 1994 and has more than 400 centers nationwide that promise weight loss success with individualized counseling. The LA Weight Loss program plan includes three phases: weight loss, stabilize and maintenance. The length of the weight loss phase is estimated according to the amount of weight you want to lose, based on a weight loss of 2 pounds per week. The final two phases are standard lengths, the stabilization phase is six weeks and maintenance is 52 weeks. While you are participating in the program, you will visit the center weekly for individualized counseling sessions. The Food The LA Weight Loss program is designed around your own food, and encourages a well-balanced diet that is rich in nutrients and includes all the food groups. The program teaches participants how to eat appropriate food portions using the... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7456-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7456_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:29:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/92/20194/popular-diets</link><title>Popular Diets Reviewed: NutriSystem</title><description>... The NutriSystem program has changed quite a bit over the years. When I first learned of this program back in high school, they had centers all over the country, now it is an online program. You’re probably familiar with NutriSystem from the many commercials on television, including the one’s targeting men with athletes like Dan Marino and Don Shula promoting the program. What will I eat? The NutriSystem program is much like the Jenny Craig program, in fact Jenny Craig, started out working for NutriSystem. This program is also designed around pre-packaged portion controlled meals that you purchase from NutriSystem and then supplement with foods from the grocery store. If you do the NutriSystem program you will receive breakfast, lunch and dinner entrees along with daily snacks. While you purchase a month’s worth of food at one time, they do provide guidelines for eating on your own. You can also delay your food shipment to use up leftover food. Do I need to exercise? Wh... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7456-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7456_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:29:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/92/17857/diets-diet</link><title>Popular Diets Reviewed: The Cheaters Diet</title><description>... I have a lot of friends who have a cheat day built into their eating plan. They watch what they eat six days of the week and then one day, usually a weekend day, they allow themselves to have whatever they want – within reason. Well, there’s actually a popular diet built around this principle, but with this plan you don’t get just one cheat day you get two! The Cheaters Diet by Dr. Paul Rivas says that the cheat diet helps dieters do the two things needed to help them lose weight: remain interested in the diet and keep their metabolism up. The idea behind this diet is that by building two cheat days into the plan, the body doesn’t go into starvation mode and weight loss continues even after people on other diets hit plateaus. It’s not uncommon for weight loss to slow after you’ve been on a diet, this is because the body has been consistently getting fewer calories than it’s used to and so your metabolism slows down to compensate. During the Week ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7456-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7456_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:30:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/reviews-161463-5.html</link><title>Living Well With Migraine Disease and Headaches - Review</title><description>... Teri Robert’s   “Living Well With Migraine Disease and Headaches- What Your Doctor Doesn’t Tell You… That You Need to Know” is just what the doctor ordered. Or- rather, is what the doctor actually didn’t order… which is why you must get a copy of this fantastic book! From definitions of types of Migraines and headaches to commonly used medications in the treatment of Migraines and headache diseases, to self-advocacy and dealing with family issues, this book has it all. The read is plain English with no “medicalese” used- even though this tome is written about medical issues. (Although there is an impressive glossary of medical terms included in the book)   The real life examples and cases cited in the book are wonderful tools, adding an element to a migraine book that is quite rare- an identification with the persons in the anecdotes, and a real life example of how things that you may be experiencing also affect others ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>