<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7457">the music man lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:30:25" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7457-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7457_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:30:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/444306/150069/dreamed-dream</link><title>I dreamed a dream lyrics</title><description>... There was a time, when men were kind And their voices were soft And their words were inviting There was a time, when love was blind And the world was a song And the song was exciting There was a time it all went wrong I dreamed a dream in time gone by When hope was high and life worth living I dreamed that love would never die I dreamed that God would be forgiving Then I was young and unafraid And dreams were made and used and wasted There was no ransom to be paid No song unsung, no wine untasted But the tigers come at night With their voices soft as thunder As they turn your hope apart As they turn your dreams to shame He slept a summer by my side He filled my dreams with endless wonder He took my childhood in his stride But he was gone when autumn came And still I dream he'd come to me That we would live the years together But there are dreams that cannot be And there are storms we cannot weather I had a dream my life would be So different from the hell I'm living So different... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7457-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7457_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:30:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/23153/34233/solution-pain</link><title>Solution for the Pain Pinch: Music Therapy</title><description>... Time for some music therapy. Music is a powerful healing force recognized around the world in many cultures. The beats, the lyrics, and the tones resonate within a person's soul. Even though personal preferences vary, the healing effects from music do not vary. Music evokes an emotional, calming feeling of positivity. Listening to music can actually lower heart rate and blood pressure. Plus, the beauty of music is that anyone (even those who can't hear it, but can feel it) can appreciate a melody, a harmony, and everything in between. ICU's, operating rooms, and nursing homes are all unleashing the power of music. Why don't you? ...   ... When I heard "Rocks in Your Shoes" by Emily West for the first time, I completely stopped what I was doing and turned up the volume. Go ahead and take a listen. ...   ...   ... ... ... ... ... ...   ...   ... Those living with pain know that there are "stones in the road" (More like an entire gravel truck dumped on you sometimes). Part of the keep-going attitud... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7457-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7457_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:30:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/5741/82419/music-play</link><title>Let the music play</title><description>...   ... My family is on fire. Not just my siblings but my parents,aunts and uncles and cousins.  Is it up to me to put out that fire? If it is I don't have the strength or the desire. ...   ... Its been a few frustrating days. I go see my pdoc for my Risperadol Consta shot. I'm racking my mind to have something to tell him. I got nothing. Besides the visit will only be 5 minutes. The shot will help. I feel like a derailed train. I go off path every now and again. ...   ... I'm waiting in the hall for the next door to open. I have been focusing on trying to close a door. I wait. Thankfully I'm a patient man. ...   ... Here they are! The voices have come to torture me. So they think. ...   ...  I sound cynical. I am. I have too much on my plate. I am a classic multitasker (old work habit). I am calm and I'm thinking clearly. Maybe i... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7457-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7457_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:31:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/129542/138653/music</link><title>Alternative MS Treatments: Music Therapy</title><description>...   ... But I know from my personal experience there is one alternative type of treatment and therapy that has made all the difference in helping to control MS and its effects on my attitude.  For me, it’s the music and lyrics of Bruce Springsteen that are helping me to rise above and stay mentally and emotionally ahead of each challenge MS poses each day. ...   ... It turns out this is about something that goes beyond The Boss and me. It’s about music therapy . ...   ... According to the American Music Therapy Association music therapy is, “… an established health service similar to occupational therapy and physical therapy and consists of using music therapeutically to address physical, psychological, cognitive and/or social functioning for patients of all ages.” ...   ... Dr. Al... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7457-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7457_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:31:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/1443/151176/relieve-anxiety</link><title>Music to Help Relieve Anxiety</title><description>...   ... Music Therapy ...   ... This study included a small group of people but most people have experienced these results at some time. During stressful moments, we can feel our bodies relax, at least a little, when listening to a song we love. At the Universit... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7457-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7457_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:31:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/19893/good-ol-days-mom</link><title>Music and Memory: Remembering the Good Ol' Days With Mom</title><description>... As I work through the process of mourning Mom 's death, I find that music - especially certain songs - tend to cause the tears to flow. Sometimes the songs are not surprising in their ability to tap into the well of grief, but other times a particular grouping of musical notes, a certain phrasing of words, an unusual inflection in the singer's voice will cause me to take a sharp inhale of breath and feel a twinge in my heart.   On a recent afternoon, I was watching television when Paul Anka came on, crooning "Times of Your Life," which at one time was Kodak's advertising jingle. Hearing him sing brought back mental images of me a young girl, following Mom's every move and wanting to grow up to be like her. And those memories quickly brought tears to my eyes.   (Thinking back on these memories, I find that I'm dreading the day when I unexpectedly hear "I Want to Hold Your Hand" by the Beatles; when it was initially popular, I was a you... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7457-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7457_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:31:53">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/120/21098/song-music</link><title>Singing My Own Song: Using Music as Therapy</title><description>... Music has always been a passion second only to writing for me. As a kid growing up in the 1970s, I listened to the AM radio, and later on, rock-n-roll. In college, I was a disc jockey at WSIA, 88.9 FM. My favorite bands were Sonic Youth, the Replacements, and Siouxsie and the Banshees.   As the schizophrenia slowly took over my brain, I listened to weirder music. On my radio show I dipped into the gloom: bands like Of a Mesh, Honeymoon Killers and Sleep Chamber. After I graduated with a BA in English, I had my breakdown. This was the day the music stopped. I couldn't go back to the way things were before.   At the second day program I attended, we had music therapy sessions, and my favorite instrument was the tambourine; it jangled and drowned out the symptoms.   When I was in my 20s, I loved to drive down the highway in my Mustang, listening to the FM radio. The Tom Cochrane song said it all, "Life is a highway/I want to ride it all night long." Google "t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7457-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7457_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:32:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/896502/149272/listening</link><title>Listening to Music Can Make Your Workouts Seem Easier</title><description>...   ... But one time when I attended one of these sessions, the power went off in the whole building. Fortunately, the classroom where we were lifting weights was really light since there was a bank of windows on one side so the teacher decided to keep the class going. Her decision felt like a ton of bricks, literally, because those weights that were so easy to lift to a bouncy musical number by Beyonce suddenly felt like dead weight. I never had attended a class that seemed to last longer (and it o... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7457-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7457_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:32:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/1443/117811/music-therapy-adhd</link><title>Music Therapy for ADHD</title><description>... Music has long been used to influence our moods, help us relax, lift our spirits or energize us. Chances are, your parents used music to sooth you as a baby. As a teen, music probably became even more important to you, and the music you chose to listen to showed who you were as an individual. You may listen to one type of music to help you relax or focus, another type to get you moving. As we grew up, we learned what we liked and how music could help us achieve our goals. Science is beginning to catch up to what we have instinctively known and is starting to incorporate music into education and treatment. What is Music Therapy? In simple terms, music therapy is the use of music to improve overall health. In recent years, music therapy has become more popular and according to Temple University , it is used in hospitals, psychiatric facilities, schools, prisons, community centers, training institutes, private practices, and universities. Music therapy works on the premise th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7457-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7457_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:32:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/154532/healing-question</link><title>Music and Healing: The Bipolar Question of the Week</title><description>...   ... Coincidentally, I will be talking with a lot of these people tomorrow. Let me explain: ...   ... I have been playing the didgeridoo for about five years. A couple of years ago, I began attending drum circles. A certain "Dr Jon" also attended. I first met up with Dr Jon at a NAMI walk, where he was playiing a metallic hang drum by a booth he was manning. I snuck up behind him with my didge and started honking along. Really, I'm not making this up. ...   ... I could write a book on the mental health benefits of drumming and didging, and someday maybe I will. Anyway, last year Dr Jon invited me to bring my didge to Stand Down. Dr Jon, it turns out, is Jon Nachison, a so... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>