<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7460">kobe bryant news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:39:03" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7460-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7460_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:39:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/57548/33720/detecting</link><title>Detecting Dementia in Highly Educated People</title><description>...   ... The most commonly administered screening test for cognitive dysfunction is the Mini-Mental State Examination (MMSE). The test itself lasts between five to ten minutes and consists of a series of questions that assess orientation, registration (i.e. name these three objects), attention, recall and language. Despite its simplicity the MMSE offers a relatively sensitive marker of overt dementia. However, it is known that people from certain cultural groups or low intelligence or low education may score poorly. However, people who are well ed... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7460-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7460_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:39:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/cold-flu/c/3989/166295/good-news-news-season-2013</link><title>The Good News and Bad News on Flu Season 2013-14</title><description>... ... Let’s start with the bad news: ... ... -The incidence of pneumonia, a potentially fatal complication of the flu has been rising since the second week of January. ... ... -Death rates have also increased over the same period of time. ...  Sadly, 20 pediatric deaths have been attributed to flu illnesses as of January 11th. ... ... -The majority of strains cultured from those sick from the flu have  the H1N1 type. This is the same virus from the pandemic of 2009  which was very lethal. ...     ... -More than 60 percent of the hospitalizations have been of people  between ages 18 and 64. Most other admissions have been children  under 5 years of age. This differs from past flu seasons which  reflected a predominance in hospitalizations of young children and  the elde... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7460-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7460_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:39:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/92163/31068/good</link><title>good news and bad news</title><description>... I have some good news I wanted to share! My blood test came back that my liver is good! In fact my count is beter then what it was! So I can stay on the Methotrexate! ... Bad news is my RA is not under control.. My inflammation is higher. So he said this is why I wanted to treat this more aggress then I did, because he didn't want this to happen. Since I do see him in the end of July and by then I go get another round of the same blood test he will wait and see what it says. Giving me a little more time of the Metho, but then he said we really need to start you on some of these other treatment. I told him about this group and how much help it has given me to be able to talk to others with RA. He was very happy to hear that. He said then when we talk about these drugs I would have a better understand of what I should start. He is really good with talking to you and not being so pushy. He has been slow going with me. He said you are not 100% and not able to do something is becasue wh... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7460-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7460_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:40:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/237590/102587</link><title>What is this news about radiation therapy being unregulated per World News Tonite?</title><description>... I was told that World News Tonite/ Diane Sawyer channel did a story on radiation therapy that was totally unregulated, ie...the doses?? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7460-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7460_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:40:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/19065/163535/opinion-reporting</link><title>Opinion: Reporting on the "Not So Much News" News</title><description>... Among various medically-related news sources, I do have a few favorites.  Some of these outfits have experienced medical reporters on staff who are sent to cover big events such as the ECTRIMS conference.  I tend to read these articles first. ... But earlier this week, I was disappointed to read a “news story” - presented by an author whose name I had come to recognize and published on a respected website - which was anything but enlightening.  The reporter seemed to give us the redacted version of a supposedly top secret, classified story in “Striking a Ne... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7460-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7460_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:40:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/3387/18531/good-news-allergy</link><title>Hookworms... Good News/Bad News for Allergy Sufferers</title><description>... There's a promising new allergy treatment on the horizon, but it's a bit yucky, to be perfectly frank (though not exactly scientific!). It seems that gutworms, or more specifically, hookworms, which are intestinal parasites, may offer protection from allergies, asthma, and other immune system disorders, including diabetes and MS.   I know what you're thinking, I've got to be kidding, right? Well, the truth is, researchers have been looking at why data gathered over the past 30 years shows that people infected with tropical hookworms hardly ever have allergies or asthma.   One theory is that hookworms may cause their host's immune system to be less active. Since overactive immune systems are at play in people with asthma and allergies, this possibility could be significant.   Scientists at the University of Nottingham in the UK are studying whether hookworms offer any kind of protection against immune system disorders. That's the possible good new... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7460-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7460_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:40:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/copd/c/19257/130183/news-news-good-copd</link><title>Bad News and Good News for COPD</title><description>... ... ... So, why are we not seeing the same type of decrease in mortality caused by COPD as we are in heart disease, cancer and stroke – but in fact, seeing a significant increase? It is due, in large part, to lack of awareness of COPD as well as a stunning lack of funding for research. Another reason is that the rate of COPD dia... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7460-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7460_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:41:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/1489/support-newsgroup</link><title>News Groups: A Source for Online Diabetes News, Research</title><description>... ... These newsgroups have been around for a lot longer than mailing lists and aren’t technically a part of the Internet at all. While anyone with an Internet account can read these newsgroups, they are the main part of the Usenet. ... ... Dr. Steve Bellovin , now a computer science professor at Columbia University, wrote the first version of software to distribute news within the Unix community in 1979 when he was a graduate student at the University of North Carolina. He worked with two Duke University graduate students, Jim Ellis, who died in 2001, and Tom Truscott, who hooked comp... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7460-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7460_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:41:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/9692/98179/mucinous-good</link><title>Mucinous Breast Cancer: Good News and New News</title><description>... Melody had never heard of mucinous breast cancer  when she received her diagnosis.  She says, "Of course I'd heard of breast cancer - I did not know there were specific types of breast cancer though.  Had never, ever heard of mucinous breast cancer and in fact found the term to be a little gross sounding.  I learned that I was lucky I had mucinous breast cancer as the prognosis for this is usually very, very good, and often better than other types of breast cancer because it's so slow growing." ...   ... Although most of us are familiar with the most common forms of breast cancer, ductal and lobular carcinoma, there are more than a dozen variations of the disease  with mucinous breast cancer making up about 2% of all breast cancer cases. ...   ... Mucinous breast cancer, also called colloid breast cancer, is different from other breast cancers because the cancer cells secrete mucin-a substance found in the digestive tract and other parts of the body.&amp;... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7460-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7460_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:41:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/news/when-no-news-is-good-news-the-surprise-benefits-of-knee-arthroscopy</link><title>When No News Is Good News: The Surprise Benefits of Knee Arthroscopy</title><description>... If you have pain in your knee, your doctor may suggest arthroscopy to find the problem. Arthroscopy is a surgical procedure that uses a special TV camera to see inside the joint. Arthroscopy of the knee has been shown to be highly safe and reliable, with few complications. It is also one of the most common orthopedic procedures done today. About 25 percent of all knee arthroscopies come out "normal," meaning no abnormalities are found. Because of this, some doctors have asked whether arthroscopy may in some cases be unnecessary or overdone. The authors of this study identified 42 patients (44 knees) who had "normal" knee arthroscopies. The authors contacted these patients about three and a half years later, to find out how they were doing. On average, the patients were 26 years old when they had knee arthroscopy. Three-quarters of them were men. At the time of the procedure, pain was their biggest symptom, followed by knee tenderness. Half of them had a history of knee injury. A few yea... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>