<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7461">navalni trial latest news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:42:00" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7461-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7461_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:42:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/325197/101502/news-foundation</link><title>The Latest News From The Migraine Research Foundation</title><description>...   ...   ...   ... J oi n M RF's mailing list to receive our newsletter and other updates via email. ... ...   ... MRF Funds New Investigator Award ... MRF is pleased to announce the second annual Thomas E. Heftler Migraine Research Award to honor the memory of a founding board member. The award furthers MRF's goal of attracting researchers to the field by encouraging researchers in the early stages of their careers to work in migraine science. A request for proposals has been posted here . If you'd like to make a donation for this award donate here and put "Heftler Award" in the comment field. ...   ... New Resources for Sufferers ... MRF continually strives to provide our friends with help and new information. Toward that end, we've added three new resources to the Resources and Links section of our website. We now have: ... ... Resources for people who need help paying for their medications ... A glossary of migraine and research terms ... Information about clinical trials from ClinicalTrials.gov ... ... MRF Suppor... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7461-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7461_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:42:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/120/148489/schizophrenia</link><title>Schizophrenia Latest News: December 2011</title><description>... EVP-62124 is a potent and highly selective agonist of alpha-7 neuronal nicotinic acetylcholine receptors (nAChRs). It works alone or in combination with donepezil to restore memory loss and improve memory function. ... EnVivo reported Phase 2B clinical data of EVP-6124 that indicate statistically significant and clinically meaningful effects on cognition and functional symptoms in schizophrenia. ... Their data for the Phase 2B study of EVP-6124 in Alzheimer's disease will be released in the first half of 2012. ... The Vanderbilt University School of Medicine staff and Jansssen Pharmaceuticals have teamed up to pioneer the use of "allosteric modulators" to adjust the activity of neurotransmitter receptors in the bra... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7461-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7461_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:42:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/120/122169/schizophrenia</link><title>Schizophrenia and Violence: Debating the Latest News</title><description>... The suspect boarded a plane to Israel and was apprehended after a ticket agent in the Ben Gurion Airport recognized him from media accounts and called the Israeli police. He was trying to get a ticket to Beijing and when his credit card was rejected he went to get cash from an ATM. That's when the ticket agent called the police. The man will be extradited to the U.S. to face charges of second degree murder. ... Eric Bellucci attended the prestigious Stuyvesant High School in Manhattan and graduated from Williams College. He was a football star on c... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7461-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7461_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:42:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/news/what-s-the-latest-news-on-meniscus-injuries</link><title>What's the Latest News on Meniscus Injuries?</title><description>... Five years ago, Dr. Goldblatt, orthopedic surgeon and professor at the University of Rochester School of Medicine (New York) wrote an article on meniscal (knee) injuries. It was published in the Journal of Musculoskeletal Medicine . Today, Dr. Goldblatt and two other orthopedic surgeons update that information here. More and more efforts are being made to save the damaged cartilage, first through conservative (nonoperative care) and when necessary, using surgery to repair the torn tissue whenever possible. There are multiple levels of protective cartilage and soft tissues in and around the knee. The meniscus is one of them. Shaped like a crescent or horseshoe-shape, there are two of these thick, stiff pieces of cartilage in each knee. They are designed to help separate the joint, assist with smooth motion, transfer load, and generally, protect the joint. Modern treatment no longer just removes a torn or damaged meniscus. Long-term studies have shown over and over that this type of aggre... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7461-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7461_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:43:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/120/143090/schizophrenia</link><title>Schizophrenia Drugs: The Latest Developments</title><description>...   ... Bioline RX enrolled its first patient in their Phase II/III Clarity Trial for BL-1020.  This compound is a first in class GABA-enhanced anti-psychotic treatment for schizophrenia. ...   ... The Clarity Trial is a randomized, double-blind, placebo-controlled study to be conducted in 15 sites in Romania and 19 sites in India.  A total of 435 patients experiencing an acute exacerbation of schizophrenia will be enrolled. ...   ... The goal of the trial is to determine the short-term cognitive benefit and anti-psychotic efficacy, safety and tolerability of BL-1020 in SZ patients over a period of six weeks compared with Risperidone (Risperdal) and a placebo. ...   ... Working memory, attention, verbal and visual learning, reasoning and social cognition are the most important neurocognitive functioning domains that are impaired in schizophrenic minds.  Clinical and non-clinical trials so far conducted s... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7461-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7461_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:43:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/154206/lorcaserin-loss</link><title>Lorcaserin: the Latest Weight-Loss Pill - My Bariatric Life</title><description>... For the first time in thirteen years, the Federal Food and Drug Administration (FDA), has approved a weight-loss pill . Belviq, which also goes by the generic name of lorcaserin, was given a FDA nod despite concerns about safety issues. The "diet pill" is to be taken in conjunction with a reduced calorie diet and a program of exercise. The drug works by activating a receptor in the brain that suppresses appetite by causing a person to eat less but feel full after doing so. Who Can Take Lorcaserin? Lorcaserin has been approved for use by obese adults with a body mass index (BMI) of 30 or more or overweight adults with a BMI of 27 or more if they have a co-morbidity of high blood pressure, type 2 diabetes, or high cholesterol. The drug was tested in placebo-controlled clinical trials including subjects with and without type 2 diabetes. The treatment extended from 52 to 104 weeks. Patients treated with lorcaserin lost an average of 3 to 3.7 percent of their body weight in a period of up... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7461-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7461_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:43:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/c/727598/167340/thoughts-mammograms-study</link><title>Some Thoughts about Mammograms Amid Latest Reported Study</title><description>... Now, news sources around the world are trumpeting a story that adds to the controversy of whether women who have reached middle age or older need to have regular mammograms. Or can we avoid this uncomfortable procedure? ... First, let’s look at the new study . The Canadian National Breast Screening Study followed 89,835 women who were between the ages of 40 and 59 years of age at the study’s start over the course of 25 years. During this time period, the researchers divided the participants by age &amp;nd... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7461-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7461_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:44:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/medications-277066-5.html</link><title>Migraine Abortive Telcagepant Performs Well In Trials</title><description>... Last year, we looked at Phase II clinical trials of MK-0974, an investigational oral calcitonin gene-related pepitide (CGRP) receptor antagonist, a new type of Migraine abortive. That medication has now been named telcagepant, and is showing great promise as a new Migraine abortive. When I spoke with lead researcher, Dr. Tony Ho, last year, he commented "MK-0974 has a novel new mechanism for relief. Nearly 70% get pain relief at two hours. The results are excellent for sustained relief at 24 hours. The adverse even rate is similar to placebo." In the latest Phase III study, telcagepant proved safe and effective in treating Migraines and caused fewer side effects than Zomig. Study details: Included 1,380 patients at 81 sites in the United States and Europe. Patients suffered from moderate to severe Migraine. Patients were given 150 or300 mg of telcagepant, 5 mg of Zomig, or placebo. Study results: Telcagepant 300 mg and Zomig 5 mg were similarly effective in ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7461-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7461_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:44:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/5645/12301/good-news-appt</link><title>Good News! &amp; Latest Therapy Appt</title><description>... Shall we start with the good news?  Always the most exciting to share and read? Since just before Thanksgiving 2006, I am down 50 pounds!  I still have a long road ahead of me, but it is a good start!  With my family history of medical problems, losing weight is important, as well as being a role model for my children!   Now, for my latest therapy appointment!  Have you ever walked out feeling just terrible and not sure why?  That was mine this morning.  A lot was said.  Many topics brought up (Or so I thought!).  She asked a lot of questions.  Then at the end she told/ask me...I am worried about you and the children!  You are asking for help, but as soon as someone is willing to help, you are pushing them away, like you do not want the help.  Do you feel this is what you are doing?   HUH?  What did I say today?  Did I say something to make her think I was throwing the past couple years of her time away?  ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7461-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7461_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:44:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/c/question/251246/75748</link><title>Latest news to get stronger bones?</title><description>...   ...   ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>