<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7463">hollywood actress</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:48:07" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7463-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7463_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:48:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/c/727598/118158/hollywood-role</link><title>Choose Hollywood Role Models Wisely As You Age</title><description>...   ... Recently, a Houston Chronicle article trumpeted “Glossy Covers Reflect New Definition of Youth.” Staff writer Greg Morago wrote, “But age is a huge factor in pop culture, especially in the cutthroat realms of entertainment, fashion and beauty. So it raised a few eyebrows when three well-known glossy magazines – Vogue, Harper’s Bazaar and Elle – all chose to put women older than 40 on their covers in September, traditionally the issue with the most ads of the year. Sure, the cover girls happen to be Halle Berry, Jennifer Aniston and Julia Roberts (none slouches in the beauty department), but it was enough for the Hollywood Reporter to suggest a seismic shift in the youthquake.” Berry is 44, Aniston is 40, and Rober... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7463-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7463_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:48:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/136675/creative-personality</link><title>Catherine Zeta-Jones and Hollywood: Bipolar Meets Creative Meets Personality</title><description>... Just a few quick observations on reports of Catherine Zeta-Jones being treated for bipolar II. I tend to avoid Hollywood stories, but it pays to jump in every once in awhile to clear up some confusion. As everyone knows, the film industry is over-populated with two types of individuals: 1) Those who are creative, and 2) Those who are A-holes (and I do not include Ms Zeta-Jones in this category). Bipolar may drive both phenomena, but not always. That’s where the confusion begins. Creativity Ronald Fieve is the author of “Bipolar II,” which includes in the subtitle “enhance your highs.” Many of the patients he sees in his Manhattan practice have high-profile careers in the media and business. These are your go-go types, highly energetic and creative who occasionally crash. But a brief time-out and they’re back in the game. Dr Fieve believes these individuals fall into a special subtype of bipolar II that should be called “beneficial.” Indeed,... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7463-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7463_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:48:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/migraineurs-543231-5.html</link><title>Famous Migraineurs: Marcia Cross. Wife, mother, actress, and Migraine sufferer.</title><description>... Marcia Cross, a wife and mother of twin daughters, has a thriving acting career despite Migraine disease . She was born in Marlborough, Massachusetts, on March 25, 1962, to Mark and Janet Cross and has two sisters, Susan and Ellen. She knew shortly after her first school play she wanted to be an actress and set out to do just, that graduating from The Julliard School in New York City. Ms. Cross began her acting career on the stage and an emerging day time television actress during the mid- 1980's. She could be found on daytime soap operas such as " The Edge of Night ", " Another World ", and " One Life to Live ". After a few years, she moved to Los Angeles, which afforded her plenty of work both in prime time television and movies. She has made appearances in " Cheers ", " Who's the Boss ", " Seinfeld " and " Quantum Leap ". In 1991 she played the role of Victoria Broyard in "Knots Landing," a very po... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7463-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7463_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:48:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/28496/45774/playwright</link><title>An Interview With Mia Perovetz: Actress, Playwright, and Daughter</title><description>...   ... Nikolai Hamel: When is the play opening? Where is it playing? Where can people get tickets? ...   ... Mia Perovetz: The Things I Wish My Mother Would Have Told Me... is opening at Center Stage NY located 48 West 21st fourth Floor, New York, NY 10010. October 22nd - November 2nd, 2008. You can purchase tickets at www.thethingsiwish.com follow the link to theater mania. Or call: 212-352-3101 ...   ... NH: How has the experience of writing a play over say, a book or an article, helped you express your story better? ...   ... MP: As an actor I'm constantly reminded to be truthful when I'm on stage, the challenge for me was to get up on stage and speak words that were only my own and to keep as much conviction in them as possible. The experience of writing a play was an opportunity for me to confront years of denial right in front of audience of people that had never heard me admit I was in pain. When you read an autobiography or an article although you are reading someone's perspective ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7463-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7463_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:49:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/cancerbasics-259109-5.html</link><title>Actress Christina Applegate Diagnosed with Breast Cancer</title><description>... Christina Applegate was just diagnosed with breast cancer.   I’m assuming she was under the close watchful eye of personal physicians since she has a strong family history of breast cancer.   Apparently she discovered the pea-sized mass during self- examination.   In general women are told to perform self- examinations every month because they know the geography and feel of their own breasts so they are more likely to notice “something that shouldn’t be there,” or something that has changed.   Over the years there has been a great deal of discussion with regards to the pros and cons of self-examination and frankly, I don’t get the “con” part.   If prevention is to become the cornerstone of our health system and the way we approach disease and our health – then noticing things is a key way for us to pick up abnormalities – whether or not they end up being true pathology.   Your eyes can take note of a mole... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7463-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7463_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:49:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/612055/77067</link><title>hollywood stars have no problem getting pain meds even when they have no chronic pain</title><description>... why is it a person with medical illness and chronic pain cannot get pain meds but hollywood stars can get pain meds when they have no medical illness or chronic pain ?? its s o unfair and unjust ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7463-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7463_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:49:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/5949/15601/pain-host-red</link><title>Hollywood Cure for Pain Hosts Star-Studded Awareness Gala</title><description>... Hollywood Cure for Pain has announced that it is holding a star-studded gala on November 7 to raise awareness for people suffering from chronic pain disorders. Hollywood Cure for Pain is a movement of people in the entertainment industry to help raise awareness and find a cure for people that suffer from various pain disorders. It’s founder, John Rue, suffers from RSD (the same disease that Paula Abdul has) and several other chronic pain disorders. This gala is the first of what they plan to be an annual red carpet event. The Hollywood Cure for Pain red carpet gala on November 7th features musical performances from award winning musicians: #1 Billboard dance/club artist Pepper Mashay, Grammy winner Val Watson (Club Nouveau), MTV Tila Tequila &amp; Janice Dickinson, reality TV star Marcus Foy (celebrity rap) with special guest, BT Chart toppers Fawn and Vincent Covello, Gigi Mackenzie (daughter of the famous Jazz singer Gisele Mackenzie, star Hollywood Walk of Fame), and an... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7463-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7463_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:49:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/222703/80143/hollywood</link><title>Los Angeles/Hollywood Chronic Pain Support Group Aug2nd Meetup</title><description>...   ... When: August 2nd, 2009 @ 6:30pm ... Where: Hollywood, California ... Who:  All are welcome - Visit meetup.com so we can easily get you info, etc. ... ... ... The Los Angeles / Hollywood Chronic Pain Support Group was established to get together once a month to talk intimately about life, love, and living with Chronic Pain. For us, it is important to have a safe monthly gathering place for anyone suffering from chronic pain... and with a specific focus on those living with a chronic disease such as one or more automimmune diseases. We share our triumphs, hurdles and pain, but we also offer resources such as alternate medicine pathways and non-Rx treatments to alleviate pain.  ...   ... The support group is organized by blogger Sasha of TypeAwithRA ( http://typeawithra.wordpress.com ) ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7463-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7463_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:50:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/887754/98832/hollywood</link><title>Does anyone find Hollywood movies about schizophrenia over the top</title><description>... Even "A beautiful mind" is not really accurate. I could not relate to it much at all. I realise it is different for everybody, but my experience was terrifying and if it were to be made in a movie, would be a horror movie. People's faces kept changing, I thought people were in disguise, other such psychotic things that would mess with people's heads were it to come out in a movie. I dream of writing a book about it, but do not know where to start. People say I have talent and always have had. I could read and write well when I was four. I am definitely not stupid. I learnt because my parents had many books and so did my grandparents. I basically taught myself. Anyway, I worked hard to overcome and on a recent review to mental health, because I was so well and had not been there for 12 years ( I went to a private G.P) they said I doubt you have schizophrenia it does not sound that bad. What a joke, just because I got better, they minimised what I had been through. Most people are not t... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7463-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7463_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:50:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/5741/61696/hollywood</link><title>Hollywood's wisdom of time</title><description>...   ... When I was younger, I didn't care about time. I told an older gentleman that I couldn't wait to be 18. I think I was about 13 at the time.  His response was 'You'll be 18 and then some before you know it." He was right. ...   ... Time was irrelevant. My thinking was I could skate through on my wits. I squandered many a year doing nothing to help myself mentally. ...   ... Now that I'm older I have a better appreciation of time. I look back and say  "wow, where did the time go?" ...   ... I spend alot of time writing journals. When I'm not writing I'm reading and thinking of stuff to write. That is time well spent. ...   ... The sands of time slip through my fingers. I'm not eager, or impatient for  time to come. I have loads of time. Time well spent. I have no need to rush it. ...   ... I sit here thinking about how I'm gonna spend time. I feel an urgency to decide how best to spe... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>