<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7465">xman sequel</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:54:05" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7465-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7465_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:54:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/medications/r/medications/diamox-sequels-oral-6754/uses</link><title>Diamox Sequels Oral Uses and How to Use</title><description>... Generic Name: ACETAZOLAMIDE - ORAL Pronounced: (a-SEET-a-ZOLE-a-mide) Diamox Sequels Oral Uses ... Acetazolamide is used to prevent and reduce the symptoms ... of altitude sickness. This medication can decrease headache, tiredness, nausea, ... dizziness, and shortness of breath that can occur when you climb quickly to ... high altitudes (generally above 10,000 feet/3,048 meters). It is particularly ... useful in situations when you cannot make a slow ascent. The best ways to ... prevent altitude sickness are climbing slowly, stopping for 24 hours during the ... climb to allow the body to adjust to the new height, and taking it easy the ... first 1 to 2 days. ... This drug is also used with other medications to treat a ... certain type of eye problem (open-angle glaucoma). Acetazolamide is a "water ... pill" (diuretic). It decreases the amount of fluid that can build up in the ... eye. It is also used to decrease a buildup of body fluids (edema) caused by ... congestive heart failure or... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7465-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7465_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:54:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/medications/r/medications/diamox-sequels-oral-6754/images</link><title>Diamox Sequels Oral Medication Images</title><description>... Diamox Sequels Oral DIAMOX SEQUELS ER 500 MG CAP ... Diamox Sequels Oral ACETAZOLAMIDE ER 500 MG CAP ... Diamox Sequels Oral ACETAZOLAMIDE 125 MG TABLET ... Diamox Sequels Oral ACETAZOLAMIDE 250 MG TABLET ... Diamox Sequels Oral ACETAZOLAMIDE 250 MG TABLET ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7465-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7465_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:54:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/medications/r/medications/diamox-sequels-oral-6754/dosage</link><title>Diamox Sequels Oral Dosage and Storage</title><description>... Generic Name: ACETAZOLAMIDE - ORAL Pronounced: (a-SEET-a-ZOLE-a-mide) Diamox Sequels Oral Overdose ... If overdose is suspected, contact your local poison ... control center or emergency room immediately. US residents can call the US ... national poison hotline at 1-800-222-1222. Canadian residents should call their ... local poison control center directly. ... Diamox Sequels Oral Missed Dose ... If you miss a dose, take it as soon as you remember. If it ... is near the time for your next dose, skip the missed dose and resume your usual ... dosing schedule. Do not double the dose to catch up. ... Diamox Sequels Oral Notes ... Do not change brands or dosage forms of this medication ... without consulting your doctor or pharmacist. Not all forms of this medication ... work the same way. ... Do not share this medication with others. ... Laboratory and/or medical tests (e.g., blood count, ... minerals such as potassium and sodium, liver function tests) may be performed ... from time to time to... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7465-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7465_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:54:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/medications/r/medications/diamox-sequels-oral-6754/interactions</link><title>Diamox Sequels Oral Medication Interactions</title><description>... Generic Name: ACETAZOLAMIDE - ORAL Pronounced: (a-SEET-a-ZOLE-a-mide) Diamox Sequels Oral Interactions ... Your healthcare professionals (e.g., doctor or pharmacist) ... may already be aware of any possible drug interactions and may be monitoring ... you for them. Do not start, stop or change the dosage of any medicine before ... checking with them first. ... This drug should not be used with the following ... medications because very serious interactions may occur: ... ... cisapride ... methenamine ... ... If you are currently using either of these medications ... listed above, tell your doctor or pharmacist before starting ... acetazolamide. ... Before using this medication, tell your doctor or ... pharmacist of all prescription and nonprescription/herbal products you may use, ... especially: ... ... anticonvulsants (e.g., phenytoin, primidone, phenobarbital, ... topiramate, zonisamide) ... other diuretics similar to this medication (carbonic ... anhydrase inhibitors such as brin... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7465-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7465_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:55:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/medications/r/medications/diamox-sequels-oral-6754/side-effects</link><title>Diamox Sequels Oral Precautions and Side Effects</title><description>... Generic Name: ACETAZOLAMIDE - ORAL Pronounced: (a-SEET-a-ZOLE-a-mide) Diamox Sequels Oral Precautions ... Before taking acetazolamide, tell your doctor or ... pharmacist if you are allergic to it; or if you have any other allergies. This ... product may contain inactive ingredients, which can cause allergic reactions or ... other problems. Talk to your pharmacist for more details. ... This medication should not be used if you have certain ... medical conditions. Before using this medicine, consult your doctor or ... pharmacist if you have: ... ... adrenal gland problems (e.g., Addison's disease) ... low blood levels of sodium or potassium ... severe kidney disease ... severe liver disease (e.g., cirrhosis) ... certain metabolic problems (e.g., hyperchloremic ... acidosis) ... ... Before using this medication, tell your doctor or ... pharmacist your medical history, especially of: ... ... breathing problems (e.g., emphysema, chronic ... bronchitis) ... high levels of calcium ... dehyd... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7465-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7465_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:55:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/erectile-dysfunction/c/question/702738/61700</link><title>when haing sex</title><description>... I'm a 40 years old male past 3 months and having trouble getting hard and keepping it hard also ajaculation too quickly can you help ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7465-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7465_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:55:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/question/421633/57591</link><title>in severe cases can the condition fight against the pills</title><description>... MY husband has been on sequel for a number or months and has had the dosage increased twice now, each time he is fine fror a week or so then the symptoms appear again. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7465-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7465_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:56:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/medications/r/medications/acetazolamide-oral-6755/images</link><title>Acetazolamide Oral Medication Images</title><description>... Acetazolamide Oral DIAMOX SEQUELS ER 500 MG CAP ... Acetazolamide Oral ACETAZOLAMIDE ER 500 MG CAP ... Acetazolamide Oral ACETAZOLAMIDE 125 MG TABLET ... Acetazolamide Oral ACETAZOLAMIDE 250 MG TABLET ... Acetazolamide Oral ACETAZOLAMIDE 250 MG TABLET ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7465-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7465_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:56:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/4216/108850/writing</link><title>Writing contest</title><description>... I have entered a writing contest for a possible slot in a movie being made. I would appreciate it if you would help by voting for me. Voting ends April 15th. Go to www.chancehappens.com and on the right and you will see Building a New Life Together. Click on it and it will take you to another link with the title. Click on it to read the story and vote on the yellow stars. The stars will turn red.The story is a condensed version of my book "She Taught Me To Laugh Again", which is a sequel to "Men Bleed Too", my story as a caregiver for my wife who had breast cancer.  I know that it would make a wonderful movie.  I hope you will support this effort, and keep in mind that you can vote daily. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7465-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7465_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 20:56:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/979654/55028/feel-quiting</link><title>I feel like quiting</title><description>... So I have been with my girlfriend for a year and a half now. A month into our relationship she has shared the fact that she suffers from seizures from time to time. She has about 1 every month, some times every 2 months. We have been to serveral nyc doctors and hospitals to hear the same thing over and over. They cant figure out why shes having seizures but here is this anti-depresent medication to take. The medication makes things alot worse so she doenst take them. I dont blame her, she had about 8 seizure in a month in a half since she started taking them, I would stop too. I dont know what to do anymore. Shes now pregnant with her first child, my second and we worry about the baby and what that will do to him. Since she has been pregnant shes only had 3 seizures. 1 in the begining, and 2 more on the saturday that just passed. We had a OBGYN apt yesterday where they told us it would be best to check her into the hp so they can monitor her. So they make her stay the night which is l... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>