<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7468">car change radiator fluid</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:02:49" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7468-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7468_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:02:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/417484/57293</link><title>I had a mastectomy for DCIS and radiation. During the radiation I noticed a change in my face.</title><description>... I wonder if this will have some side effects later on my overall health. What do you think? ... Thanks ...   ... Antou ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7468-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7468_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:03:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/651280/135969/transportation</link><title>Tips for a Successful Car Trip While Living with Diabetes</title><description>... ... Pack everything that you might need during your journey. ... ... Insulin (If there are temperature concerns, consider packing in a cooler to avoid the loss of potency. If there is air-conditioning this is of less concern). I would strongly recommend having all types of insulin you currently use (including the insulin you may use just at night). ... A... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7468-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7468_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:03:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/question/560290/139583</link><title>I recently started training for a half marathon. How does the body breakdown fat and change as the body replaces fat with muscle? My "fat rolls" seem to be more fluid or flabby instead of just firm.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7468-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7468_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:03:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/537192/154834</link><title>is there any corelletion between a car and development of polymyalgia rhematica which appeared after the accident?</title><description>... AFTER THE ACCIDENT AL MY MASCLES WERE IN PAIN CRP AND ESR WENT UP HIGH, AN INJECTION OF 2mg BETAMETHAZONE RELEASED MY PAIN FOR 10 DAYS AND I WAS DIAGNOSED AS PMR PATIENT. ... CAN IT BE A TRAUMATIC REACTION TO THE CAR ACCIDENT? ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7468-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7468_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:04:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/173270/123225</link><title>I have a male friend 19 years old who has just lost a best friend in a car accident, who also has some anger management issues</title><description>... He has come from a broken family, has shifted to melbourne in the past 12 months for work. One of his best mates died in a car accident 2 weeks ago, and has been drinking heavily and getting angry. I believe the anger has been building for years, but tends to rear its ugly head when drinking. Punching holes in walls after the funeral of his mate.I am hoping he can find someone to talk to in the Caulfield area. He is a low income earner, and cannot afford much. Is there help for him? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7468-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7468_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:04:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/migraineurs-434126-5.html</link><title>Famous Migraineurs: Carly Simon</title><description>... Migraine disease affects nearly 37million Americans. A large majority of sufferers, more than 28 million, are women. Migraines place an unusually difficult burden on women during the prime of their lives, while raising a family and having a career. Carly Simon, singer/songwriter, wife and mother, has been able to do both despite being a Migraineur. Ms. Simon began singing very early in life to help combat a stuttering issue. Her mother suggested she tap a beat rhythmically on her leg while she was speaking. This seemed to work so well that she started singing every time she spoke and hasn't stopped. She's won two Grammy Awards and an Academy Award and has recorded over 30 record albums. Some of her biggest hits include You're so Vain (my personal favorite), Anticipation , and Haven't Got Time For The Pain . Never Been Gone is a wonderful, yet painful result of a mishandled set of circumstances between Ms. Simon and Starbucks. They were to release her album, T... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7468-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7468_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:04:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/father-suffered-accident-2150</link><title>My father suffered serious burns in a car accident.</title><description>... My father suffered serious burns in a car accident. He's in stable condition but now they say he has compartment syndrome in his right leg. What happens next? What's the treatment for this? Acute compartment syndrome is a serious medical condition that occurs most often after a traumatic injury such as fracture, contusion, or burns. In the case of a burn the skin can't stretch and flex for swelling underneath. It starts to act like the outside covering of a sausage. There are serious consequences without proper treatment. The doctors may measure the compartment pressure several times before deciding on treatment. The measures will help them determine if the condition is getting better or worse. They may not take actual measurements but rather go on the basis of the history and clinical presentation. Sometimes all that's needed is proper positioning so the blood can flow to the area. For example, the leg should be kept down below the level of the heart. Movement and active contraction of ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7468-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7468_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:05:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/96/117870/reflux-sleep-car</link><title>Is It Safe For My Reflux Baby to Sleep In Her Car Seat?</title><description>... I know plenty of babies with reflux who play, digest and sleep in their car seat at home. My reflux baby was fairly content if I held her 24/7. There were times when I did put her down in the car seat because I just had to have my hands free. For example, I did need my hands free for my daily two minute shower. Most of the time, she was in my arms or in a sling/carrier or backpack. My arm muscles became hard as rock and my back ached from the constant bending and lifting. It sure was hard work holding her and I longed to put her down. ...   ... An article in the August issue of Pediatrics caught my attention. The article reported on car seat injuries that occurred outside of the car . It is estimated that approximately 43,000 infants were treated in the emergency department for a non transportation related car seat injury between 2003-2007. Approximately half of the injuries occurred at home and infants younger than four months of age were most likely to be injured. ...   ... I always th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7468-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7468_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:05:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/44/3435/car-wars</link><title>Car Wars</title><description>... ... Take my recent car purchase: Ever since that December trip to Florida, I have been spending as much energy on purchasing a car as I have facing my long January list of medical check-ups. That trip made me realize that it was time to replace my gas-guzzling (17-mpg highway), mechanically capricious 13-year-old van with something I could drive safely and afar. ... ... It started with a Chevy Malibu I rented in December. The renta... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7468-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7468_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:05:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/accident-dashboard-injury-2452</link><title>Back in high school I had a car accident and got a dashboard injury to both knees.</title><description>... Back in high school I had a car accident and got a dashboard injury to both knees. I never had surgery or anything, and I've gotten along fine. Now 30 years down the road, I'm starting to get arthritis in both knees. At 47, I'm pretty young for arthritis. So I'm wondering if this is the result of the accident. What do you think? A dashboard injury refers to damage of the posterior cruciate ligament (PCL) inside the knee. When a sudden impact from behind occurs, the passenger's knees are pushed forward into the dashboard. The force of the knees against the dash can cause the tibia (lower leg bone) to shift back far enough to rupture the PCL. We've known for a long time that the main function of the PCL is to keep the tibia from sliding too far back on the femur (thighbone). But more recent studies have shown us that the PCL has some other functions as well. It also keeps the tibia from shifting side-to-side during knee motion. And it prevents too much rotation of the tibia. Without an int... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>