<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7469">ibm thinkpad t43 change fan</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:05:51" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7469-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7469_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:05:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/196377/103647/fan</link><title>a bit of a vent... not a fan, RA... NOT a fan....</title><description>...   ... Well... its almost been two months since my official DX and wow - what an adventure!!! I have added Lyrica and Enbrel to my new RA meds. Very proud of doing my first injection today ALL BY myself!... Still on methotrexate and Im still on the LARGE prednisone dose and by my face/belly you can totally tell, and I am starting to get ?s about how I look-fun times. We tried to start to taper the predisone with the start of enbrel-- THAT DID NOT GO WELL, back up it went. I also have had steriod injections in my knees-which were soo nice, but those are wearing off... I just got knee braces for the knees as well, just those "basic" blue ones, my left brace is a little more invloved, where the right is just a pull on sleeve, becuase I need more support. My feet and hands continue to decline and my elbows recently deceided to jump on the RA bandwagaon about th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7469-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7469_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:06:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/6561/16591/im-fan</link><title>I'm not even a fan of Grapefruits...</title><description>... When I was really little, I used to climb my grandparents' grapefruit tree and get all of the ones that were at the top. I know now that of course they would have gotten them even if I hadn't been around, but the praise that I got for cleverly navigating the intertwining limbs of the tree and getting that perfect grapefruit was addicting. I loved that tree. It was perfect for reading a book in the afternoon sun down on those florida days of Christmas Vacation.   Every night, we'd each have a half (or more) a grapefruit- the ones that I pulled down from the tree. They were the sweetest ruby red grapefruits- the ones that sell for gobs of money at the store in winter.   We stopped making the voyage down to Florida yearly when I was 13. No grapefruit ever tasted as good as those from my grandparents' tree, and I stopped eating grapefruits.    Then I was put on meds- no grapefruit juice. (No loss, I said- and for another dozen years, to me, grapefruits were ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7469-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7469_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:06:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/150340/rushed-er-migraine</link><title>Sean "P. Diddy" Combs Rushed to ER with Migraine</title><description>... Rapper and music producer Sean "P. Diddy" Combs  was rushed to the UCLA emergency room by some of his staff members on Monday morning with what he later described as a "crazy Migraine." ...   ... His ER visit followed a pre-Grammy Awards party in Beverly Hills on Saturday hosted by Clive Davis as well as a party that Combs hosted at the Playboy Mansion following the Grammy Awards. ...   ... Combs was also among others in the music world who were mourning Whitney Houston's death. He told reporters: ... ... "Whenever you saw Whitney, she hit you with that beautiful smile... If we truly believe in God, then we should celebrate the life of Whitney Houston tonight." 3 ... ... Combs was treated in the emergency department and released. Later in the day, he was posting on Twitter to thank his fans for their support and let them know he was getting better. He Tweeted: ... ... "Thanks for all the twitter love! I'm fine. I just had the craziest Migraine. I'm just sleeping it off now. Thank you. Love yall." 2 ... ... Perhaps... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7469-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7469_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:06:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/477253/163702/migraines-weather</link><title>Migraines and Weather changes</title><description>... On Tuesday, there was a 16 percentage point increase in humidity, at the time my migraine peaked, and today a 15 point decrease. Also, at the time of onset, the humidity was in a state of flux. ... My first identified trigger was changes in weather. ... How does the weather effect your migraines? ... Do you also notice migraine onset during changes in humidity? ... J ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7469-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7469_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:07:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/living-with-203066-5.html</link><title>Home Accommodations for Multiple Sclerosis: Take Control and Make Changes</title><description>... Living with multiple sclerosis often means making lifestyle changes, big and small. While it is very difficult to take that first step and admit that you need some type of assistance, once you make the necessary accommodations for your disabilities you will find that it actually empowers you. You will be more in control and less dependent upon others. There are many things you can do to make life easier, some I've done, some I haven't needed to do yet. Take advantage of these and any other methods available to improve your quality of life. Cane Buying a cane was the first purchase I made after diagnosis . It really brought the reality of MS home. It was clear that I needed one, but I was reluctant to actually do it. My husband, watching me look at canes online said, “If you're going to get a cane, GET A CANE!”. That's how I ended up with a red paisley adjustable folding cane. It immediately improved my gait and allowed me to appear in public looking like I d... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7469-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7469_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:07:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/copd/copd-000070_11-145.html</link><title>Chronic Obstructive Lung Disease - Lifestyle Changes</title><description>... Lifestyle Changes Quitting Smoking and Avoiding Other Irritants Quitting smoking is the first and most essential step in treating COPD and slowing its progress. In many people who quit early, lung function stabilizes and eventually declines to about the rate of nonsmokers in the same age group. In some people, lung function may even improve slightly after quitting. As COPD progresses, quitting smoking can slow the rate of decline; however, lost lung function is never fully recovered. Most patients who smoke try to quit an average of seven times before they are successful. Using a combination of smoking cessation aids improves the likelihood of quitting. These include nicotine replacement products (such as patches, gum, nasal spray, and lozenges), counseling, and prescription medications such as bupropion (Zyban) and varenicline (Chantix). [See In-Depth Report #41 : Smoking.] Preventing Upper Respiratory Infections Good Hygiene. People should wash their hands with ordinary soap before eating ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7469-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7469_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:07:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/67078/19313/make</link><title>Multiple Sclerosis Disability Accommodations: Take Control and Make Changes</title><description>... Living with multiple sclerosis often means making lifestyle changes, big and small. While it is very difficult to take that first step and admit that you need some type of assistance, once you make the necessary accommodations for your disabilities you will find that it actually empowers you. You will be more in control and less dependent upon others. There are many things you can do to make life easier, some I've done, some I haven't needed to do yet. Take advantage of these and any other methods available to improve your quality of life. Cane   Buying a cane was the first purchase I made after diagnosis . It really brought the reality of MS home. It was clear that I needed one, but I was reluctant to actually do it. My husband, watching me look at canes online said, “If you're going to get a cane, GET A CANE!”. That's how I ended up with a red paisley adjustable folding cane. It immediately improved my gait and allowed me to appear in public looki... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7469-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7469_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:07:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/1950/160735/eating-anxieties</link><title>Eating Anxieties</title><description>...   ... Is there an adult out there who hasn’t been on a diet of some sort? Well, of course there is, but plenty more of us find ourselves standing on the scales and wondering where all the extra pounds have come from. Then there are the diet fads. Come on, what have you tried? The boiled egg diet, perhaps? Maybe you were a fan of the Atkins diet, or the South Beach, or Grapefruit diets? Losing a few pounds when you’re overweight is a good thing, although as most people know some dietary fads were too extreme to be healthy. Keeping a check on weight is one thing but some people get so anxious about their weight, shape an... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7469-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7469_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:08:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/c/46839/46959/hot-cold-sweaty</link><title>hot, cold and sweaty</title><description>... I started going through perimenopause several years ago after having major surgery that removed all my female anatomy.  I am now in major menopause. The worst part is at night!!!! ... Insomnia and body temperatures that vary from freezing to the sweat is pouring off especially around my neck and forehead.  So I battle with sheets,blankets and a fan on high all night long.  I recently started using a natural homeopathic cream that has sweet yams in it from New Mexico. It works fairly well for the hot flashes during the day but I have not noticed much of a change at night.  I was on premarin for a year,  but given that my family has a great cancer history, I stopped taking it.  Does anyone have any suggestions to get rid of the night sweats????  Stay cool and comfy...... KP ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7469-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7469_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:08:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/90847/132694/going</link><title>Going Through Again</title><description>... Before it was discovered that I had MS, I had started going through the change.  Now this is for the ladies so just smile .  Here recently I have been flashing again (hot flashing) one minute I am cool as a cucumber and the next I want to run through the street butt naked, such as I can.   I am sitting in church with my makeup flawlessly done, when all of a sudden water begins to run done my forehead, and out of my hair,  smoke is coming out from under my arm pits and I am using the church program to fan, then I am asking the church usher to please turn the air on.  It is 32 degrees outside.  But I am sweating like it is 90 degrees, but it only last about five minutes!   So embrassing, my makeup has started to run, I have black eyes, and my face is splotched, what a MESS!  OK I am beginning to cool down the water that was ruuning out of my hair has stopped, the tissue that I was wipping my face with has torn to bits, my eyes are totally black now... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>