<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7472">python re tutorial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:14:35" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7472-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7472_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:14:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/8621/16070/class</link><title>Next Class: Plastic Surgery Tutorial</title><description>... With Breast Cancer Comics by Dash Shaw     My next stop after Dr. Duggan was Dr. Yoon Chun, a highly-regarded plastic surgeon (referred to by several surgical nurses as ‘an artist') who couldn't be nicer or more lovely or more intensely intelligent and who spent almost two hours with me in her office explaining the various reconstruction surgery options available.   Dr. Chun also drew pictures, most of which I completely understood, and had I not been so absorbed in the decision-making process regarding the creation and construction of my new boobs - saline implants? silicone implants? TRAM flap? DIEP flap? - I probably also would have started thinking about how different my future might have been had Dr. Chun been one of my high school science or math teachers.   Deciding what kind of reconstructive surgery I was going to have was sort of like deciding everything else in my life - I usually start by figuring out what I don't want first and ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7472-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7472_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:15:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/110/10003/diabetes</link><title>Diabetes Terminology</title><description>... Sometimes the editor in me gets a bit irritated when I see non-standard versions of diabetes terminology. Here are some examples:   1) It's pretty standard now-a-days that the two types of diabetes should be rendered with an uncapitalized letter followed by an Arabic numeral (except at the beginning of a sentence, duuuh!). In the past, it was "Type I" and "Type II" but these usages are now considered outdated.     Correct uses:   At the FDA website : ...available treatment options for their type 2 diabetes .     and ADA : In one category, type 1 diabetes, the cause is...   and AACE :  The 41 million Americans who have pre-diabetes are at increased risk for developing type 2 diabetes   2) The use of HbA1c vs. A1C is unresolved. There's been a recent push to use "A1C", but us old-timers still like HbA1c. (I've also seen it as "HgbA1c" but that's a minority opinion.)     at ADA : An A1C (... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7472-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7472_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:15:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/109352/question-funniest</link><title>Question of the Week: Your Funniest</title><description>...   ... My quick funny list: Groucho Marx, Seinfeld, Oscar Wilde, Mark Twain, George Carlin, GB Shaw, Art Buchwald, Monty Python, Chris Rock, the Onion, John Stewart, Woody Allen, E*Trade babies, Warner Bros cartoons ... ...   ... Okay, you get the idea. One-word question: ...   ... Funny. ...   ... Go for it. Comments below ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7472-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7472_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:15:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/prostate/c/question/867147/123818</link><title>I'm 25 years old and have been experiencing symptoms listed for BPH/enlarged prostate and am a bit concerned that I may have a problem. I am on the medication wellbutrin which I read sometimes causes</title><description>... these symptoms. I never have had any blood or pain when urinating, mainly just the hesitation before being able to start fully urinating where I need to push... as well as the frequent urge to urinate. I'm only 25 years old and it's scaring me that I could have prostate issues so early. I have already scheduled a meet with a doctor but wanted additional feedback from others. Also I notice that anytime that I have an erection it makes it feel as though I need to urinate even more than normal, and even after urinating the urge to urinate still feels present, even during an orgasm it feels as though the semen thats coming out also contains urine as well even though I don't believe it does. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7472-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7472_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:15:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/240415/144245</link><title>Heart palpatations / skipped beats.</title><description>... Hello ... Recently it seems as if my heart is skipping beats. I went to the doctor about 4-5 weeks ago with a sinus infection that cleared up already. They checked my pulse and it was a bit high probably because I Was nervous. They did a EKG because they didn't want me leaving without double checking things. They did it for about 3-5minutes then let me leave. Recently the past few weeks I've been very conscious about my heart rate. My guess is I'm mentally causing myself to get heart palpatations / skipped beats (Almost heavy heart beats). It doesn't seem to do it when I have my mind focused on something else. I do notice it a lot when trying to sleep though because I'm laying there thinking a lot. Should I even be worrying at all? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7472-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7472_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:16:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/104764/midweek-stuff</link><title>How to Spot Spam on the Internet</title><description>...   ... Please know that this issue is being worked upon as we speak.  I am so sorry if any of your posts have comment spam.  I am hopeful that this problem will be resolved soon. ...   ... While I am on the topic of spam I did want to share a little story.  You will understand my meaning at the end.  I once moved to a new neighborhood when my boys were babies and I was eager to meet other moms and make friends.  I was at a playground one day and met this mom who seemed to want to talk with me and... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7472-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7472_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:16:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/104934/friday-health</link><title>Weekly Mental Health Checkup and Evaluation</title><description>...   ... It is time to review the week and see what we have to say about it.  My week was filled with medical appointments.  Somehow I managed to schedule three appointments in one week, got my annual physical done, saw my lovely dermatologist, and also saw my beloved physician assistant at the neurology hospital.  But guess what?  After sitting in all the doctor's offices I am sick.  "I have a told in my doze"  Translation for people who are not sick:  I have a cold in my nose.  I am feewing vewy vewy sick.  Okay so that was some Elmer Fudd.  I think I will get myself some soup.  But no spam.  Unless of course it is spam, eggs, sausage and spam which isn't a lot of spam.  Or a thin mint wafer (indulgent Monty Python reference). ...   ... Okay now!  Moving right along... ...   ... Enough about merely me...it is time to talk all about YOU! ...   ... How are you doing this week? ...   ... 1.  On a scale of one to... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7472-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7472_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:16:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/19065/115531/week</link><title>Leverage Your Multiple Sclerosis Diagnosis Into Great Experiences</title><description>...   ... Having just returned from a cruise which hosted over 300 people traveling with the Multiple Sclerosis Foundation , I have been thinking about all the individuals I met, observed, or got to know personally.  One of these individuals was seated at the same dinner table as I.  Let’s call her “Kay.” ...   ... Kay is a woman who was diagnosed with MS over 30 years ago (if I remember correctly).  She has a wonderful outlook on life and is a Monty Python fan, which provided some great laughs.  She said that she didn’t focus on MS at the beginning (nor during the many years since diagnosis) and simply went on with her life. ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7472-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7472_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:17:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/8621/15786/meets-toy</link><title>Laura Zigman Meets Her Breast Surgeon and Becomes a Bobble-Head Toy</title><description>... With Breast Cancer Comics by Dash Shaw   I was still under the impression that I had a pre-cancerous non-cancerous type of cancer that wasn't really cancer when I met with the head surgeon at the Sagoff Breast Center at the Faulkner Hospital in Boston.   Dr. Margaret Duggan - a tall, fiercely intelligent, completely approachable, extremely accomplished surgeon who wore scrubs and a white coat and adorably hip but not annoyingly hip black-rimmed squarish glasses, took me into her office and spoke to me for over an hour.   She gave me an incredibly detailed and easy-to-understand mini-course that covered oncology and biology and genetics and surgery and plastic surgery and statistics and probabilities and which included hand-drawn diagrams on a pad of paper which I actually understood.     Despite the fact that we were talking about my pre-cancerous type of non-cancerous cancer, I couldn't help wishing (since I have never quite gotten ove... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7472-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7472_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:17:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/73302/73058/dead-ms</link><title>Mortality and MS</title><description>...   ... I suppose you had to be there.  What does this have to do with anything?  Bear with me, I'm getting there. ...   ... I have this memory of when I was first telling others about my MS diagnosis.  There are just some people you don't want to share such information because they begin talking about the worst case scenarios.  One such individual began telling me right... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>