<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7473">noise canceling head phones</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:17:33" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7473-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7473_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:17:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/sleep-disorders/c/question/982434/59323</link><title>in M.V.A.motor vec.acc.12-29-08 with son also hit head i think loud noise or several sounds at once</title><description>... is causing me great distress even to act out,has improved somewhat also causes dizzyness &amp; nausa seems right side more sensative. pretty much whole body is sprained &amp; burning in limbs lower back feels shreaded have whiplash also bone bruiseing ect. now need info.@head help PLEASE ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7473-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7473_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:17:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/question/753725/125309</link><title>i hear noise in my head that no one else can hear like skeching</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7473-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7473_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:18:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/556010/79829</link><title>always being on edge, not feeling that way &amp; sudden noise startles me</title><description>... does anyone with fibro experience such as jumping when a phone rings or a sudden noise . Always being on edge but not feeling that way ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7473-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7473_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:18:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/003043trt.html</link><title>Ear noises or buzzing treatment</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Ringing in the ears; Noises or buzzing in the ears; Ear buzzing ... ... ... Home Care ... ... Tinnitus can be masked by competing sounds: ... ... Low-level music, ticking clocks, or other noises may help you not notice the tinnitus. ... Tinnitus is often more noticeable when you go to bed at night because your surroundings are quieter. Any noise in the room, like a humidifier, white noise machine, or dishwasher, can help mask tinnitus and make it less irritating. ... ... Learn ways to relax. Stress does not cause tinnitus, but feeling stressed or anxious can worsen it. ... Avoid caffeine, alcohol, and smoking. ... Get enough rest. Try sleeping with your head propped up in an elevated position. This lessens head congestion and noises may become less noticeable. ... Protect your ears and hearing from further damage. Avoid loud places and sounds. Use earplugs if you need them. ... ... Call your health care provider if ... ... Call your doctor if: ... ... Ear noises start after a h... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7473-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7473_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:19:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/003043.html</link><title>Ear noises or buzzing overview</title><description>... Definition ... ... Tinnitus is the medical term for "hearing" noises in your ears when there is no outside source of the sounds. ... The noises you hear can be soft or loud. They may sound like ringing, blowing, roaring, buzzing, hissing, humming, whistling, or sizzling. You may even think you are hearing air escaping, water running, the inside of a seashell, or musical notes. ... ... Alternative Names ... ... ... Ringing in the ears; Noises or buzzing in the ears; Ear buzzing ... ... ... Considerations ... ... Tinnitus is common. Almost everyone experiences a mild form of tinnitus once in awhile that only lasts a few minutes. However, constant or recurring tinnitus is stressful and can interfere with your ability to concentrate or sleep. ... ... Common Causes ... ... It is not known exactly what causes a person to "hear" sounds with no outside source of the noise. However, tinnitus can be a symptom of almost any ear problem, including: ... ... ... Ear infections ... ... Foreign objects or wax in the ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7473-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7473_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:19:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/87/12612/cancer-trial</link><title>An Oncologist's Thoughts on the Canceled Breast Cancer Prevention Trial</title><description>... Earlier this summer, the National Institutes of Health decided not to fund a breast cancer prevention trial to test Letrozole (Femara) , an aromatase inhibitor , vs. raloxifene (a tamoxifen-like drug) in the primary prevention of breast cancer. Expert Patient PJ Hamel first wrote about the canceled breast cancer chemoprevention study in June, when the story first became news. More recently, Tara Parker-Pope, a wonderful science writer for the Wall Street Journal , covered the issues surrounding the canceled National Surgical Adjuvant Breast and Bowel Project (NSABP) study brilliantly.   Chemoprevention and Clues from the ATAC Trial   In my eyes this is a minor tragedy. In one sense, I feel the answer may already be out there. In the ATAC trial of tamoxifen vs. Arimidex in the adjuvant setting, there were fewer new breast cancers in the women who received Arimidex than tamoxifen - a rate of about 0.31% per year in the arimidex group vs. 0.5% in the tamoxifen group. This woul... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7473-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7473_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:19:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/question/440231/150354</link><title>RA - high pitch noise - Plaquinil.</title><description>... RA symptom is coming back ( mainly, sleeplessness)What am I to do? Plaquenil works perfectly for how ever long it last. Is high pitch back ground noise in my head is one of the  the symptom of RA.? ... Yes, My RA doctor knows. She said she is never heard of such thing. I don't mind plaquenill,but not if it causing long term hearing loss.I am only 45 years old. Any other MED I shoud ask to try? ... Thanks folks ... Sleepless in Seattle ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7473-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7473_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:19:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/294853/54298</link><title>Is there any corelation between noise cancelling headphones, flying and acute onset of migraines?</title><description>... Twice, on long flights (greater than 4 hours) when wearing BOSE noise cancelling headphones I have had acute onset, splitting migraines - to the point of nausea and vomitting. Maxalt did help.  I am trying to figure out if the trigger is flying, long flight, or the headphones which seem to work by changing the pressure in my head.  Regular earplugs do not seem to cause the same headaches although I am nervous about truly figuring this out :)  Thank you for any help you can give me. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7473-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7473_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:20:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/604522/141157</link><title>Does loud voices/noises bother other people so badly?</title><description>... I've had depression since I was a child. I can't function when family gatherings are taking place. My wife, daughter and friends when they talk it's almost like a physical assault inside my head. I avoid Walmart 'cause it's so loud. They tease me and say I'm too sensitive but I can't deal with the loudness. It just makes me want to run and hide. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7473-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7473_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:20:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/444306/145218/depression</link><title>Noise Pollution, Depression, ... and Nature As Our Guide</title><description>...   ... We have nonstop noise these days in our lives.  How can we possibly have mental clarity and peace?  Our minds  are constantly being jolted and thrown violently back and forth by this sudden noise and then the next.  ...   ... Have you ever stood five minutes in a crowded city and listened?  It is amazing to me how loud it is.  But when you add all the noises together, it makes sense. The decibel levels and vibrations of all the noises combined. ...   ... Ten car engines, five stereos, two car alarms, a siren, our own radios, the chattering in our car, honking ahead of us, a loud muffler behind us, an airplane overhead....all this noise then blasts through our fragile minds and bodie... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>