<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7474">php convert special symbols to html</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:20:58" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7474-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7474_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:20:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/prostate/news-2819-143.html</link><title>Major League Baseball Raises Awareness of Prostate Cancer on Father's Day</title><description>... years ago, professional baseball games have been a quintessential ... opportunity for millions of American fathers to bond with their ... children. On June 16th, in commemoration of Fathers Day, ... Major League Baseball altered one of the games most storied ... traditionsthe seventh-inning stretchas a public service ... to these same fathers. To raise awareness for prostate cancer, fans ... in baseball stadiums across the country sang Take Me Out to ... the Ballgame last Sunday after the sixth inning, a symbolic ... gesture that refers to the fact that one in six American men will ... develop prostate cancer at some point in their life. A public ... service message, promoting regular prostate exams as well as ... general cancer awareness, was displayed on the big screen during ... the stretch. The players wore blue wristbands, and the ... uniforms of coaching staff, ball-boys, ball-girls, and grounds-crew ... featured the blue ribb... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7474-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7474_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:21:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/scheduled-special-test-2091</link><title>I'm scheduled to have a special test for my knee.</title><description>... I'm scheduled to have a special test for my knee. It's called a\rKT-1000. What is this exactly? The KT-1000 arthrometer is a small device that's strapped to the leg during knee examination. It's used when the doctor thinks there may be a tear in the anterior cruciate ligament (ACL). The examiner pulls on the uninjured knee and the gauge on the KT1000 shows how many millimeters of motion occur between the lowerleg bone (tibia) and the upper leg (femur). This motion is calleda drawer sign . The reading is compared between the injuredknee and the normal knee. If there's more than three millimeters difference between theknees, the ACL is torn. It's considered more accurate than anMRI. If you'd like to see a photo of this tool go to: http://www.medmetric.com/kt1.htm or http://www.ismoc.net/procedures/kt1000.html . Reference: Mininder S. Kocher, MD, MPH, et al. Relationships BetweenObjective Assessment of Ligament Stability and SubjectiveAssessment of Symptoms and Function after Anterior CruciateLig... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7474-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7474_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:21:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/42544/elders-digital-tv</link><title>Tips To Help Your Elders Get Ready for Digital TV Switch</title><description>...   ... I'm writing this to give readers information, but I'm most concerned about elders getting scammed. Older people are still more vulnerable to giving out private information over the phone or even in a store, thinking that this nice young woman who is asking must need it in order to help them. ...   ... So, to help your elder, please be aware by reading the tips, below, and then go to the government site, at www.dtv2009.gov , for more information. ...   ... At midnight of February 17, 2009, U.S. television will stop broadcasting in analog and switch to 100% digital broadcasting. People with cable or satellite TV access shouldn't even notice a hiccup. However, those with a TV antenna will no longer get reception, unless they have a converter box. ...   ... You can order coupons at the government site to offset the pr... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7474-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7474_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:22:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/type-I-diabetes-000009_10-145.html</link><title>Type 1 Diabetes</title><description>... Home Management Monitoring Glucose (Blood Sugar) Levels Both low blood sugar (hypoglycemia) and high blood sugar (hyperglycemia) are of concern for patients who take insulin. It is important, therefore, to carefully monitor blood glucose levels. In general, patients with type 1 diabetes need to take readings four or more times a day. Patients should aim for the following measurements: Pre-meal glucose levels of 70 - 130 mg/dL Post-meal glucose levels of less than 180 mg/dL Different goals may be required for specific individuals, including pregnant women, very old and very young people, and those with accompanying serious medical conditions. Finger-Prick Test. A typical blood sugar test includes the following: A drop of blood is obtained by pricking the finger. The blood is then applied to a chemically treated strip. Monitors read and provide results. Home monitors are about 10 - 15% less accurate than laboratory monitors, and many do not meet the standards of the American Diabetes Association.... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7474-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7474_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:22:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/167792/blood-medication-application</link><title>Blood Pressure Medication May Have Application for Alzheimer’s</title><description>... ... Multitudes of middle-aged and elderly people take ACE inhibitors to manage their blood pressure. The drug is considered safe when used as directed by the attending physician. This new study found that it is possible to genetically target certain immune blood cells to over produce the AC enzyme. This over production serves to break down defective proteins in the brain associated with Alzheimer’s disease. The process prevents cognitive decline in laboratory mice that are bred to model the disease, therefore the researchers are now convinced that high activity of the AC enzyme may, under the right ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7474-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7474_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:22:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/19034/pbss-forum-onset</link><title>PBS's "The McNeil Report" Features Segment, Forum on Early Onset Alzheimer's</title><description>... Yesterday evening, "The McNeil Report" on PBS featured a very interesting and informative segment on early onset Alzheimer's disease . The segment, which was reported by Susan Dentzer through a partnership between The McNeil Report and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, featured participants in the Early Memory Loss Forum, held in Los Angeles. A group of participants who have been diagnosed with early onset Alzheimer's were interviewed. Several had been corporate executives; some of those who were interviewed were in their late 40s.   I've provided links below to the transcript of the show as well as to the Insider's Forum, which offers you a chance to ask questions of some of those people interviewed. The answers to questions that are submitted will be posted on Wednesday, Jan. 16.   For the show's transcript: http://www.pbs.org/newshour/bb/health/jan-june08/alzheimers_01-10.html   For the Insider's Forum (through Wednesday, Jan 16, 2008): ht... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7474-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7474_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:23:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/c/76444/153118/osteoporosis</link><title>Osteoporosis Awareness Month with American Bone Health.org</title><description>...   ... Here is what we’d like to do, to show our commitment to our health, bones and lifestyle. ...   ... GET AMERICAN BONE HEALTH STRONG WITH US! ...   ... 1) Grab a camera or camera phone and go to a local landmark. In California , for example, you could take a picture by the Spanish Steps at Rodeo Drive or Greystone Park . Think big and small—the landmark could range from something nationally known like Santa Monica Boulevard to something more personal like a neighborhood park, a school, or your office. ... ... 2) Take a picture of yourself flexing your muscles in front of the landmark. ... ... 3) Dress it up: Write something to go along with the picture that says what you’re doing and where you’re doing it, such as... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7474-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7474_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:23:35">http://www.healthcentral.com/incontinence/c/4877/11956/bladder</link><title>A New Bladder?</title><description>... Scientists at the University of New York are studying special cells that line the bladder in hopes of being able to engineer new bladders and restore continence in people with serious bladder conditions, including those with bladder cancer. This new bio-engineering technology could allow those who've lost their bladder function or had all or part of their bladders removed to regain continence. Researchers predict that regenerating certain bladder cells, those that enable the bladder to retain urine, could produce usable bladder tissue for transplantation into people who need bladder replacement. More on this from EurekAlert! : http://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2007-07/babs-smc073007.php Best of health, Maria Maria Gifford Community Moderator IncontinenceNetwork.com ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7474-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7474_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:23:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/151010/coconut-saturated</link><title>Coconut Oil: A Different Kind of Saturated Fat</title><description>... Coconut oil is a special kind of saturated fat. The trouble with saturated fat in general, as I wrote here last week, is that our bodies find them harder to burn than other kinds of fat, like the monounsaturated fat in food like avocados, olive oil, and macadamia nuts. We manage our diabetes by controlling the spikes in our blood glucose levels. And nothing has a more dramatic affect on our levels than the starches and the sugars of high carbohydrate food. Therefore, many of us now follow a very low-carb diet. But when we start getting most of our energy from fat rather than from carbohydrates, our bodies are just beginning to learn how to convert fat to the energy we need. So we have to make it easier for ourselves, Ron Rosedale, M.D., told me. Dr. Rosedale is a physician and scientist who wrote The Rosedale Diet . Dr. Rosedale says to limit the amount of saturated fat during our first few weeks on a very low-carb diet. Otherwise, we will feel our lack of energy and tire easily. But this... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7474-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7474_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:24:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/42538/167509/omega-omega-6-balance</link><title>Omega-3 + Omega-6: Are you in balance?</title><description>...   ... Ashley believes better nutrition is simple and is on a mission to help people achieve their personal health goals by providing simple but highly effective tips and strategies. She emphasizes the value of quality nutrition choices in achieving optimal health. ...   ... Let’s jump into the Q&amp;A… ...   ... What are Omega-3 and Omega-6? ...   ... Ashley Koff: Omega-3 and Omega-6s are essential fatty acids (EFAs) . Both are essential to the structure and function of our cells, and regulate critical aspects of brain function, metabolism, and immune-system health. We cannot make omega-3 and omega-6 fatty acids in our bodies, so we have to get them from foods or supplements. ...   ... We need omega-3s in our diet to help prevent chronic inappropriate inflammation. Insufficient omega-3s ar... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>