<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7475">software consultant work at home</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:24:30" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7475-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7475_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:24:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/007249.html</link><title>NICU consultants and support staff overview</title><description>... Alternative Names Neonatal intensive care unit staff; NICU staff Information AUDIOLOGIST An audiologist is trained to test a baby's hearing and provide follow-up care to those with hearing problems. Most newborns have their hearing tested before leaving the hospital. Your health care providers will determine which hearing test is best. Hearing tests may be also be done after leaving the hospital. CARDIOLOGIST A cardiologist is a doctor that has special training in the diagnosis and treatment of heart and blood vessel disease. The cardiologist may examine the baby, order tests, and read test results. Tests to diagnose heart conditions may include: X-ray Electrocardiogram (EKG) Echocardiogram Cardiac catheterization If the structure of the heart is not normal due to a birth defect, a cardiologist might work with a cardiovascular surgeon to perform surgery on the heart. CARDIOVASCULAR SURGEON A cardiovascular (heart) surgeon is a doctor who has special training in doing surgery to correct or treat de... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7475-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7475_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:24:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/96/87260/consultant</link><title>Ask The Lactation Consultant</title><description>... Breast milk is often the ultimate "comfort food" for a baby with gastro-esophageal reflux since breast milk is easy to digest and well tolerated by many babies. At the same time, a baby with reflux may have difficulty nursing due to pain and discomfort. A Lactation Consultant may provide much needed information and support to help a mother and baby work together. I asked Melissa Nagin, Lactation Consultant and expert on http://breastfeeding.about.com to discuss nursing a baby with reflux. What does a Lactation Consultant do? A Lactation Consultant is a health professional who offers breastfeeding assistance and education. They provide a variety of services such as individual consultations, prenatal breastfeeding classes, postpartum support groups and assistance with breastfeeding products such as breast pumps. What type of training/certification does a Lactation Consultant have? To call yourself a "lactation consultant" you must carry the designation "IBCLC" (International Board... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7475-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7475_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:25:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/80106/70681/foe</link><title>Typing with Rheumatoid Arthritis: Use Voice Recognition Software</title><description>...   ... A few weeks ago, we posted about a study of computer use and its impact on pain for people living with RA, Osteoarthritis and Fibromyalgia. In this study, "84 percent of respondents reported a problem with computer use attributed to their underlying disorder and 77 percent reported some discomfort related to computer use." ...   ... For me, it's typing. Doing too much drag-and-drop with the mouse isn't good either, but typing takes my pain levels from 0 to 60 in no time. If I didn't have Dragon NaturallySpeaking, a voice recognition software that types what I dictate, I wouldn't be able to write more than maybe 200 words a day. Using the computer still hurts, but as long as I respect my limits (currently about 1200 words a day), it's manageable. Dragon gave me my voice ba... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7475-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7475_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:25:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/32591/40089</link><title>my consultant has prescribed alprazolam and if this does not work then Risperidone.</title><description>... I am also taking Dosulepin. The aim is too reduce the high level of anxiety.  I would like to know what each medication does and if either/both are addictive. ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7475-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7475_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:25:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/erectile-dysfunction/c/question/72586/117621</link><title>What Can I Do? he will not see a doctor but expects me to come home from work with solutions</title><description>...   ... He is constantly on me about sex. He tries at least 4 times a day. He has ED. I am frustrated and frankly tired. He will not consult a doctor and blames me for the problem. I don't know what to do at this time. ...   ... He knows what time I need to go to work, he wakes me and alerts me he is ready, when I brush my teeth he alerts me he is ready, when I walk in the door he alerts me he is ready, when I go to bed again he alerts me he is ready. Only problem is nothing is happening. He tries and tries and nothing. ...   ... This goes on day after day. Anyone have any ideas? I want more out of life and frankly I am not to blame and probably a bit cranky with him. What can I do? ...   ... I just don't know what to do, he will not consult with a doctor and expects me to come up with a solution.  ...   ... He thinks I should be able to come up with answers each day... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7475-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7475_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:26:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/question/523190/72399</link><title>I had symptoms of a heart attack today driving home from work,but when i got home and laid down for</title><description>... I was driving home and my arms got tingly,i got dizzy and started to sweat alot. Then when trying to push the gas pedal, I had a hard time because my leg wouldnt stop shaking. I got hame,laid down for ten minutes and felt better ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7475-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7475_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:26:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/806002/138279</link><title>hi.im 24.i go 2 work by two-wheeler.my work place is 15kms 4um my home.i almost travel more than 35kms/day.i heard tht-by riding bike(lots)girls might lose der virginity (break hymen).is it possible?</title><description>... started riding bike (with this far distance)some 1year back. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7475-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7475_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:26:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/question/142801/120411</link><title>Having consult tomorrow for nissan fundoplication surgery and looking for question to ask the doctor before hand.</title><description>... Taking several meds for gerd that have not worked.  I have  had H-pylori for over 6 years and no med work for that as well looking for help.  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7475-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7475_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:27:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/805089/98395</link><title>Periods are late, so whom should i consult? fmly dr or a gynecologist?</title><description>... My periods were due on 6th of dec, but its 10 days past and i havent got them yet. this is the first time its getting so late. i even had pregnancy test at home which resulted to negative. do i need to report this to a gynecologist or a family doctor? please help me. its very urgent. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7475-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7475_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:27:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/40368/45210</link><title>What kind of doctor should I consult if I have a red, itchy, rush in my breast (think not swollen)</title><description>... Two days ago I got a red rush in a small part of my left breast. It was only painful the first day, a bit red now it is itchy and bigger. I have travel insurance since I am in a business trip but I am not sure what kind of doctor to consult here or whether I should cancel my trip and consult back home. Could you advise? My trip should end of December I do not want to wait till that. I am from Mexico so I could go back and return but I am on a business trip so if I could consult here I could but I don't know where to start here. I only consulted the Multi Plan service yet ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>