<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7477">china bird flu</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:30:21" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7477-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7477_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:30:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/livingwithit-278640-5.html</link><title>CDC Expert Answers Questions About the Flu and Flu Vaccine</title><description>... Have a question or comment? Click here. Are there things you want to know about the flu and the flu vaccine? If so, you're going to love this article. I recently had the opportunity to speak one on one with Dr. Carolyn Bridges, the Associate Director for Science in the Influenza Division of the Centers for Disease Control (CDC) . This CDC unit is responsible for a number of tasks, including: Year-round influenza surveillance throughout the world Coordinating with state and local health departments Global decision-making with the World Health Organization (WHO) on flu vaccine content twice a year Influenza risk assessments Studies of the flu disease burden Antiviral resistance research and monitoring Improving community and public awareness of the flu and flu prevention As you can see, the Influenza Division has their hands full. They also maintain a comprehensive mini site about the flu and flu vaccine: http://www.cdc.gov/flu/protect/keyfacts.htm You'll find answers to most of your... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7477-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7477_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:30:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/c/280722/148605/govt</link><title>US GOVT does not want to reveal the blueprint of the Lab-bred Bird flu</title><description>...   ... The H5N1 virus has been truly creating panic all over the society due to its burgeoning nature. Today there are vast sections of populations that are afflicted with this virus. Initially, it was transmitted from the birds alone to the human beings. The transmission becomes more active when it got contagious spreading from human to human. There have been varied studies at present carried on the same by the National Science Advisory Board for Biosecurity (NSABB) and other associated bodies, sources from the NIH ( National Institute of Health ) say in its published article on 20thDecember. ...   ... Studies from Europe and US mention how the situation may worsen if they transmit from o... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7477-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7477_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:30:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/cold-flu/cold-flu-tools-quizzes-assessments-265213.html</link><title>Quiz: The Truth About the Flu Vaccine</title><description>... 302 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7477-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7477_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:31:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/77780/100365/feeder-beautiful</link><title>The birds at my bird feeder are beautiful...</title><description>...   ... What I had not mentioned, and is still happening, is that over the course of the last 2 weeks.. something within has been charging up daily into another frighteningly High Mixed Manic Episode likened to those that have placed me IP in the past. ...   ... You know... something that has rushed up behind, you did not ever see, and flung you head first into air at a alarmingly rate of speed.  You are flailing haphazardly, screaming, towards a ever increasing solid large black mass.  You know you are going to splatter all over that solid, ever increasing in size, black mass but... there is nothing to stop the speed of... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7477-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7477_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:31:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/disorder-types-273404-5.html</link><title>Animal and Bird Phobias</title><description>... Animal and bird phobias are quite common. People may be afraid of dogs, cats, mice, or rats. Someone may be afraid of birds in general, although fear of pigeons is also common. A phobia is an intense and irrational fear. Most people would be afraid of a growling dog standing in their path, however, it may be irrational or unreasonable to be afraid of your neighbor’s dog, especially if the dog is friendly and has never really provided a reason for you to be afraid. Phobias interfere with people’s daily life or functioning and most people suffering from phobias understand their fears are unreasonable but are not able to overcome their fear. Symptoms As with other specific phobias, symptoms of an animal or bird phobia include: Headache Stomachache Muscle tension Rapid heart beat Sweating Shortness of breath Irritability Trouble concentrating Causes Sometimes a person with a specific animal phobia can pinpoint how the phobia began. They m... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7477-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7477_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:31:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/271731/98922/caged-bird-sings</link><title>I, too, Know Why the Caged Bird Sings</title><description>... I Know Why the Caged Bird Sings by Maya Angelou (with Audacious Liberties by Toby) The free bird leaps on the back of the wind and floats downstream till the current ends and dips his wings in the orange sun rays and dares to claim the sky. But a bird that stalks down his narrow cage can seldom see through his bars of rage his wings are clipped and his feet are tied so he opens his throat to sing. The caged bird sings with fearful trill of the things unknown but longed for still and is tune is heard on the distant hill for the caged bird sings of freedom The free bird thinks of another breeze and the trade winds soft through the sighing trees and the fat worms waiting on a dawn-bright lawn and he names the sky his own. But a caged bird stands on the grave of dreams his shadow shouts on a nightmare scream his wings are clipped and his feet are tied so he opens his throat to sing The caged bird sings with a fearful trill of things unknown but longed for still and his tune is heard on the... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7477-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7477_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:32:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/444306/167393/birds-soothing-soul</link><title>birds soothing to the soul</title><description>...   ... If I get soundproof window, birds won't be there and ac will be on the other side, getting the vibrations and noise trapped back on me by the soundproof window, so I don't know. ...   ... Why are things so difficult? ...   ... No luck yet with finding a quieter car.  I want safe people around me.  I need quiet and help.  ...   ... Have to wait some for my tx so I don't bother my father too much, he is having difficulties too, can't stress him too much. ...   ... I don't want to complain anymore. ...   ... My boyfriend told me he got me a 2006 apple computer on ebay.  After the computer guy said don't get older than 2009.  The computer guy said I would have the same issue in a couple years with an older computer. ...   ...   ... I want a break.  At least a quiet car, that is hard too doing that.  Something to cover the ac noise, it is heating up. ...   ... I am very tired of all ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7477-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7477_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:32:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/850274/136971/birds-times</link><title>birds nest goes in the trash three times</title><description>...   ... My roommate just destroyed for the third time the little morning doves birds nest in the garage.  I am very upset.  They came to nest there and were very sweet and carried one twig at a time to build their nest. ...   ... She took the broom three times and knocked the nest into the garbage.  She thought it would harm her garage door. ...   ... Apparently we don't see eye to eye on animals.  I want my own home where birds can nest, animals can roam freely. ...   ... Of course, I guess if it was a rattlesnake, I would have gotten it out of the garage too, so maybe I need to calm down and another perspective too. ...   ... Marishka ...   ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7477-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7477_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:32:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/57909/28499</link><title>Am allergic to birds. Neighbor wants to keep 4 chickens in coop 20 yards from our house. Problems?</title><description>... I know I am allergic to birds in cages. My reactions have all occurred indoors and involve swollen eyes and sneezing. The city council has just passed an ordinance allowing a maximum of 4 chickens to be housed in backyards if the neighbors agree. My neighbor wants to keep chickens in a coop approximately 15-20 yards from our house and has asked for my approval. Is this liable to cause problems for me? Are there precautions I should ask her to take to reduce the production or spread of allergens? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7477-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7477_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:32:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/36354/49995/odd-bird</link><title>The odd bird out</title><description>... Its going to be a late night for me. I am trying to nurse a very scared, and hurt love bird back to health. At my job we had 6 love birds in a large cage toghether. One got sold so we had five. Four of the five paired up (married in the bird world) which left my little friend as the odd bird out. The other pairs in an effort to protect their mates nearly killed him this afternoon. Beating him within an inch of his life. They bit off a toe, opened up a dime sized wound just above his tail, and damaged his wing. I was able to rescue him, I just hope it wasn't to late. I stopped the bleeding, cleaned his wound and got him drinking gatorade and eating some millet. He seems to be resting comfortably but I am worried about him, he lost a lot of blood for such a little bird. ...   ... I cant be mad at the other birds, they were just doing what was natural. I am mad at myself at not noticing the two pairs earlier and getting them into seperate cages. But it did get me ... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>