<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7478">protect kids online</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:33:03" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7478-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7478_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:33:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/155373/teaching-healthy</link><title>Teaching Kids to Eat Healthy Using Online Games</title><description>... Gaming Childhood Obesity ...   ... Games targeting healthy behaviors are proliferating. A study published in the Archives of Pediatrics &amp; Adolescent Medicine found that children who played a health game were significantly more likely to select and eat healthier foods than kids who played a game without healthy-stimuli. ...   ... What else does gaming bring that might also be new and important in the fight against childhood obesity? Gaming may make it a little more fun. ...   ... ...   ... Food N’ Me  is an interactive website that aims to promote healthy eating among children. ...   ...   ... The Power of Play: ... Online Games Teach Kids to Eat Healthy ...   ... How can something as seemingly trivial as games improve children’s eating habits and, consequently, their health? Nutrition in and of itself is boring to children. While gaming is fun, exciting, and addicting. So applying gaming theory to nutrition education in the form of online games and mobile apps enables us to ca... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7478-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7478_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:33:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/news-289655-5.html</link><title>Safe Migraine Medications and New Laws in Effect</title><description>... Have you purchased or considered purchasing Migraine or other medications online, from a site that does not require you to have a prescription? If so, think about it again. There are some serious financial reasons behind the use of online pharmacies for some people, but there are other, safer possibilities that will be discussed later in this article. On April 13 (2009), the provisions of the Ryan Haight Online Pharmacy Consumer Protection Act 0f 2008 went into effect. This act, which amends the Controlled Substances Act to address online pharmacies, is named after 18-year-old Ryan Haight who died after overdosing on a prescription painkiller he obtained on the Internet. We've all heard stories such as Haight's. Stories about people who got something that looked like the medication they'd ordered, but wasn't... Stories of people who got ill from the medications they'd purchased online... and more. But the laws haven't been able to keep pace with ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7478-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7478_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:33:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/913874/80034</link><title>How can I protect my kids from my husband's depression?</title><description>... My husband is suffering from severe depression. We have four young children and I was wondering if anyone has any advice ... on protecting my children  from my husband's depression without scaring them? At this point they just know that he's not feeling well - nothing more. I just don't want them to be hurt by or learn from his anti-social and erratic behaviors. I also don't want them to think less of my husband - they think he's the greatest person in the whole world!           ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7478-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7478_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:34:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/867037/157846/monitoring</link><title>Monitoring program captures online video chats of other users on your computer</title><description>... Monitoring software tool traces other user’s internet activities on your pc and is easy to download or install from World Wide Web. Computer monitoring device traces changes made to your pc by different persons while running invisible in background. ... Software, monitor, activity, external, person, system, application, capture, typed, username, password, keyboard, unauthorized, user ... URL: http://www.digitalpccare.com ... Employee monitoring software captures personal online conversations of professionals with family or friends during office hours and sends report to managers. Monitoring activity tool traces tasks performed by employees on office computers while remains away from their view while running hidden in background and undetectable by users in all software applications. ... Monitoring mac device traces USB media insertion or removal operations on your system hardware such as pen drives, thumb drives, mem... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7478-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7478_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:34:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/6898/44721/mental-depressants</link><title>Kids and Mental Health…Kids and Anti-depressants</title><description>... ... (a) It requires communication so choose times that are organic like car pool rides home, family dinner, an impromptu snack stop on the road. ... (b) Walk a fine line between established rules and regulations and reasonable expectations. Yes, breaking rules does have consequences - but make them appropriate for the offense. Have reasonable expectations for your teen. ... (c) Get teens involved with after school activities - sports, philanthropic, whatever. Leave them with too much time and they will get into trouble. ... (d) Inspire them and motivate them. Be there for them when there is failure but let them know that failure is merely a learning lesson. Don't protect them from handling life, but do suppo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7478-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7478_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:34:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/504554/150385</link><title>CAN I TAKE AN ONLINE TEST TO CHECK ME FOR BI POLAR</title><description>... I AM A 59 YEAR OLD FEMALE! AFTER MANY YEARS OF TAKING RUDENESS AND DISREPECT FROM 2 OF MY 3 KIDS I FINALLY WENT OFF ON 2 OF THEM RIGHT BEFORE CHRISTMAS OF 2011. MY OLDEST SON TOLD ME I HAVE BIPOLAR ! I WENT TO THE DOCTOR BUT HE TOLD ME I DID NOT! HE HOWEVER PUT ME ON BUPROPION SINCE I FELT DEPRESSED. RIGHT BEFORE I WENT OFF ON 2 OF MY KIDS MY MOM DIED LIKE 3 MONTHS BEFORE ! THEY NEVER DISRESPECT THEIR DADDY BUT THEY HAVE DONE THINGS TO ME IN THE PAST 15-20 YEARS THAT I WANTED TO KEEP PEACE SO I WOULD NEVER SAY ANYTHING ! HOWEVER  A  FEW TIMES  I LET THEM  KNOW I  DID NOT LIKE THINGS AND THEY WENT WEEKS  NOT TALKING TO ME ! WELL I COULD NOT TAKE ANYMORE AND I LET THEM BOTH KNOW I HAD ENOUGH! THEY CAN SAY WHAT EVER THEY WANT AND WHEN THEY WANT TO BUT I AM NOT ALLOWED TO COME BACK WITH A WORD ! WHEN I DECIDE I HAD ENOUGH MY OLDEST ONE TELLS ME I AM BI POLAR !I  EVEN  WENT TALF TO MY PRIEST  AND HE TOLD  ME  TO  DO... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7478-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7478_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:35:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/123621/157255/share-online</link><title>Obama share a list of songs online</title><description>... Obama share a list of songs online, Romney features recipes submitted, while Obama released photos of their grandchildren with family and children in Instagram Romney in Facebook to interact with their constituents. According to the latest survey of the Pew Research Center shows that today's U. S. adults every 10 people in four political plate active in the social network, social networking applications have become one of the U. S. citizens to participate in political benchmark. Obama and Romney's campaign team has its main network's director cheap mulberry bags of digital technology. Teddy Goff, director of digital technology for the Obama campaign team, said his team efforts to design different information for different social media platforms. Goff said: "If our keynote appropriately, then all of these people have the power of work for us, but doing so also at risk, because untrue in those areas, it will not only no longer care about, and will send tweets say why they no longer care... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7478-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7478_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:35:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/genital-herpes/c/question/all</link><title>online.. vashikaran specialist guru+91-9829810409</title><description>... +91-9829810409 you don't worry my child i will solve your life all type problems world famous POWERFUL MOLVI +91-9829810409 ruhani ilmoo k badsha +91-9829810409 WORLD FAMOUS BEST INDIAN MOLVI JI INDIA / AMERICA / CANADA / AUSTRALIA / UK / USA INTERNATIONAL SERVICE WITH MOLVI JI 90 ilemo ke mahir molvi ji RUHANI DUNIYA ME naam HI KAFHI H. DUKHIYO KA EK HI SAHARA SAI NATH HAMARA. NIRASH MATA, BHANE, BHAI EK PHONE JARUR KARE. NURI HAJURI SIPLI, BLACK MAGIC 90 ILMO KE BADSHAH. HAJI SULTAN KHAN RETURN OF THE VASHIKARAN KING IN INDIA. mera ilem sari duniya me chalega. mera kam hi meri pahchan hai. your all problem solve by islami duaa MolviJi INTER CasT LovE MaRRiagE SpeciALisT +91-9829810409 world famous POWERFUL MOLVI +91-9829810409 astrologer har samsya ka samdhan with 101% guaranteed.vashikaran muth karni black magic Mohini Vashikaran, ruhani &amp; sifli ilam GUARANTED RESELT all problem tona totka,tantra mantra,jadu tona,kali kitab,kala ilam intercast love marriage love back love related p... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7478-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7478_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:35:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/1443/11900/online-tests-adhd</link><title>Online Screening Tests for ADHD</title><description>... If you are wondering if you, or your child have ADHD, there are a number of online screening tests available. It is important to note, however, that these screening tests should not be used for diagnostic purposes. They are helpful in deciding if you should see your doctor. In addition, they may provide a starting point for beginning a conversation with your medical provider about symptoms that you are experiencing or have experienced in the past.   1) The Amen Clinic ADD Test   This site provides a self-screening test for both adults and children. It has approximately 75 questions you rate between 0 and 5, with 0 being never and 5 being very frequently. After completing the questionnaire, your results will be displayed on the screen. You can print out the pages of the questionnaire to discuss with your doctor. You also can take an additional test, The Amen Brain System Test, which will help determine the subtype of ADHD.   2) Adult ADHD Self Report Scale   This test is f... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7478-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7478_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:36:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/266176/77845/finds-conference</link><title>Child Diabetes Management: Emotional Challenges, Protege Trial, Online Tools</title><description>...   ... After a dinner buffet that was a diabetic's dream -- every food offering, from the chicken wings to the chocolate-covered strawberries, were labeled with the number of carbohydrates they contained -- we checked out the much touted Exhibition Hall. Since we had two very different agendas on the exhibition floor, with me wanting to absorb as much information about anything diabetes and my thirteen-year-old son searching for fun, we decided to part ways. ...   ... I was not disappointed with the breadth of what I found. I wandered from booth to booth, discovering new resources I didn't know were available, hearing about up-and-coming technology, and seeing what's on the horizon for diabetes management and prevention. T... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>