<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7479">dunbar number social networks</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:36:25" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7479-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7479_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:36:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/1750/15062/iam-social-support</link><title>This is what I am doing to create a Social Support Network</title><description>... What I am doing to create a social support network, I recently looked up the meetings in my area for NAMI and I attend the meeting meet several members , the only thing is most all the people there are married so they discussed thier wifes and thier familes I left after one hour I just didnt connect with what they were talking about It was not my social network I will go back next time it may be different people But I think I need to be somewhere where I can meet women my age who are going through the same type of struggles and who are not married and not attached to someone in other words I would like to start dating and thats why I wanted to go to these support groups but I wanted to go also to make friends but with everyone married there I dont think thats the place for me to find someone else single my age to talk with there. I am also OnLine in Myspace and I am trying to meet someone thier but I havent meet anyone who is local here in Gainesville, Florida. The Brain Injury Suppor... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7479-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7479_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:36:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/incontinence/c/76594/78661/caringbridge</link><title>Social Networking in the Time of Crisis</title><description>... One of my best friends - a girlfriend in high school and later one of my roommates in college - recently learned that a rare but virulent cancer has returned and with a rage. Eager to offer Martha comfort and encouragement from afar as she underwent surgery at M. D. Anderson Hospital in Houston, I found myself escorted online to her personalized web site at www. CaringBridge.org. There, I found I can track the course of her treatment and remain in touch through her recovery. Through her site, I can feel intimately connected to Martha and her family through her posts to all of us visiting the site and leaving our prayers and good wishes for her. There's a journal section where Martha has entered background information on her cancer and now gives frequent updates on her condition. I can even choose to be alerted, as I have, by email every time she makes a new journal entry. This allows her to conserve her strength and energy for her health needs, while be sustained emotionally by all of... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7479-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7479_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:37:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/32873/150704/social</link><title>Social Networking and MS - Question of the Week</title><description>... Do you have a favorite social networking site? The concept of an online virtual community is not new, but still growing very fast. It offers valuable opportunities for sharing information on various specific interests. There is always Twitter (300M registered users) and Facebook (800M registered users). HealthCentral is on both of these sites. Another site HealthCentral is on is StlumbleUpon. ... In a post last month, Merely Me mentioned StumbleUpon . I commend her for bringing to our attention this innovative and unique website. It helps to enhance our social networking experience. Here are a couple others I have been looking at: LinkedIn Here is a professional site where you can connect to others including those related to MS. HealthCentral’s LinkedIn connection is here . Infographic List - Healthcare Then there is a site that illustrates information in the form of data visualization and infographics. While not exactly a networking site, they do share information in a very usable and crea... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7479-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7479_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:37:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/132835/diabetes-networking</link><title>Diabetes Social Networking</title><description>... The social network space for people with diabetes lags well behind the Internet's superb ability to provide information. Websites like HealthCentral far exceed the older sources of information that we have -- including our health care teams, our books, and our magazines -- in the quantity and often even the quality of information that we seek about diabetes. But the Internet hasn't been doing a good job in connecting the real people who have diabetes with other real people. Those of us who have diabetes often feel isolated from our communities because of the special need we have to control our condition. Many of us, particularly those who live in small towns or rural areas, don't have anyone with whom to discuss our dietary, activity, and medication requirements. Local support groups often fail to provide positive reinforcement when they exist at all. Many of us in fact lack that option within a reasonable driving distance. Support and communication are functions that the Internet can pr... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7479-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7479_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:37:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/651280/125120/networking</link><title>Diabetes and Social Networking</title><description>... Social networking is a relatively recent phenomenon that has become a part of our social lexicon. It seems that just about everyone has a Facebook account. Blogs have also become commonplace, and thus have become the source of an incredible amount of information, as well as providing "point of views." As such, not all information may be trusted as accurate and may just reflect the writer's interpretation. Websites such as HealthCentral clearly indicate the source of blogs posted, such as medical expert, community member, person with diabetes, etc., so that the reader is aware of who is posting information. Other online groups such as Children with Diabetes , and Permanent Neonatal Diabetes interest groups , serve to provide up-to-date information, along with commentary about diabetes specific concerns. There are several disease-specific information exchanges that exist on social networking sites such as Facebook. The authors, Greene, Choudry, Kilabuk, and Shrank recently published "Onli... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7479-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7479_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:38:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/59238/121298/reinforcement</link><title>Can Social Networks Influence Healthy Living?</title><description>...   ... ... Fat is catching - your friends, family and social network can make you fat (I've written extensively about this before) ... A college roommate who is overweight can actually help you to slim down (because they may chronically diet and exercise, trying to lose weight) ... You are what your mother ate during pregnancy - the food choices a pregnant woman makes can determine future obesity of offspring ... Heavy parents have heavy kids - it may be partially genetics and partially home environment plus lifestyle habits that the children see modeled by parents ... ...   ... So it's not a stretch to hypothesize and wonder - Can social networks also help us to improve our health?   This was a recent column in the New York Times and the information offered was quite compelling.  Sleeplessness, smoking and reckless behavior can be encouraged by your social network, according to studies.  We also know that when you decide to diet, joining a support gro... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7479-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7479_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:38:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/8534/157765/networking</link><title>Social Networking is Good for Your Health</title><description>...   ... This often-overlooked factor that can improve your health is spending time with people who care about you. Researchers have found that people with strong social networks, and those who just spend time with lots of other people, are more likely to live longer. On the other hand, living an isolated life is a major factor that puts you at risk of dying sooner (joining other better-known health threats like smoking). ...   ... How could good relationships with other people keep you healthy? The experts are still puzzling over this. One thought is that being social might affect your body’s internal processes. Perhaps being around people who care about you affects your brain in a way that lowers the level of inflammatory chemicals in your body (inflammation plays a role in many health problems... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7479-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7479_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:38:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/84404/33970/smaller-messaging</link><title>Twitter: The New Diabetes Social Network</title><description>... What I am talking about is Twitter . Twitter is a micro-blogging platform that saw the light of day in early 2006, starting to pick up steam over the following couple of years and starting to reach a critical mass the first quarter of 2008. ... They define themselves as "a global community of friends and strangers answering one simple question: What are you doing?" As simple as it sounds, it's powerful. No wonder more than one million people are using Twitter these days. ... In Twitter, you can post at most 140 charact... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7479-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7479_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:38:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/1750/16941/create-social</link><title>What can I do as a Disabled Person to create a Social support network</title><description>... My Case Manager came by today and we discuss my lack of a good suppoet network I do have a close friend She is my roomate But outside of the home I dont have any social contacts here in tjhe Gainsville Area I have been to the NAMI support meeting here and all the guys there were married and they all talked about how thier wifes support them in thier recovery and I felt so left out of the whole discussion that I left after an hour and went home. She told me I should go back and give it another try but I dont see how this will help in meeting anyone to date that has the same problems or finding new people to socilize with. There is also a Brain Injury support group that meets on the 3rd Tuesday of each month at 6:15 pm I missed the last one this month because I got the date and day of the group mixed up so I will try again next month. I hjave a myspace account and I have been trying to meet someone on there but so far I have talked to ladies on there but I have not meet anyone yet. I do... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7479-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7479_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:39:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/genital-herpes/c/question/465938/83249</link><title>HSV and HPV Social Network , Why don't you join to find friendship and support?</title><description>...   ... Best wishes, ...   ... M Sadavero ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>