<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7481">worms nexus 7</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:42:23" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7481-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7481_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:42:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/high-blood-pressure/c/question/260910/167568</link><title>My question is i have high blood pressure and take Bystolic spironolactone nexus. I would like to know what kind of diet pills can i take.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7481-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7481_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:42:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/879936/129047</link><title>some times i feel that there are some worms in my head and feel like sounds of worms.what is the reason?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7481-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7481_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:43:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/6639/23272/ms</link><title>Worms- They Might Help Your MS</title><description>... Having performed some medical work in Mexico in the 1970's, (I'm that ancient), it has always occurred to me that chronic parasitosis was a problem that quietly devastated the potential of so many Mexican children. Harboring intestinal worms for the long term remains a public health problem throughout the Americas. It results from the consumption of drinking water that mixes with sewage.   People with these creepy crawlers on board can be fatigued for the long term, suffer abdominal difficulties, and sustain lifetime malabsorption which causes vitamin deficiency states.   What in tarnation does this have to do with Multiple Sclerosis? Have I been out in the sun too long, seeking higher Vitamin D levels to help thwart future disease?   Doctors tend to talk in riddles. So I shoot back to you: "Crohn's disease, Ulcerative Colitis, Multiple Sclerosis, Rheumatoid Arthritis , Insulin-dependent (Type 1) Diabetes and Asthma."   "That's it", you s... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7481-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7481_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:43:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/ibd/c/2623/47391/bugs-worms-answer</link><title>Could Bugs or Worms Be the Answer?</title><description>...    ... In was in 2004 when I first read about drinking pig whipworms to treat IBD . Joel Weinstock, a gastroenterologist at the University of Iowa came up with the idea of ingesting the worms to treat IBD. Dr. Weinstock noted that ulcerative colitis and Crohn's are diseases of the 20 th century and are very rare in less developed countries where the GI tracts of nearly all children have worms in them. In countries like the US, though, where we have eradicated stomach parasites like roundworm and whipworm (there is a human variety) the theory is that our immune systems grow overactive without any parasites to fight against and voila! you get things like IBD. As far as I know, though, this doctor gave no reason why some people end up with IBD while other people don't. Trial studies using the pig whipworm - Trichuris suis - were conducted in 2004 and some good results were seen. But, the worms only live in the GI tract for a short period of time, perhaps two to three weeks. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7481-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7481_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:43:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/18335/42056</link><title>nose allergy a gainst worm and dirty weather.</title><description>... nose allergy a gainst worm and dirty weather. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7481-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7481_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:43:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/639480/67139</link><title>Worm on your site</title><description>...   ... Please clean this up , because I was really wanting to read the article!!! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7481-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7481_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:44:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/question/94894/34109</link><title>ring worm like rash but it feels hard and it's under the skin</title><description>... My son has ring worm like rashes on his arm that is hard and is under the skin. It doesn't itch, it doesn't hurt. it's not red or blistery. He does have eczema and asthma. I have never seen his skin like that.  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7481-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7481_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:44:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/ibd/c/question/337533/93756</link><title>What kind of worms are these and how to treat it?</title><description>... I saw black little worms in my toillette after a baowl movement. What could it be? I went to the pharmacy and mentioned this and they gave me vermox to take. I took the pill and the next day i saw the same thing in my toillette after flushing. I'm wondering if it is something else. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7481-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7481_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:44:52">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/776578/92343</link><title>is there an actual worm that is sexually transmitted other than trichmoniasis?</title><description>... is there an actual worm,  that is sexually transmitted, that attacks the spine, brain and nervous system?  I am curious about this because of a condition that i am suffering.  no one seems to know what it is, I am trying to distinguish whether it is something contracted from the drinking water at my house or something my ex-boyfriend passed on to me, considering that he had numerous problems that he had long before he met me.  i started having brain seizures for no apparent reason, nasty headaches, and nerve problems. I've been going through this for a couple of years, i've been to several doctors and no one knows what it is.  i'm positive that is a parasite of some kind, i can't tell however if its my nerves that make me feel like i have worms moving through my muscles, or whether i actually have worms. i wake up several times in the middle of the night because it feels like something is actually moving through my spine in my neck, th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7481-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7481_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:45:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/ibd/c/2623/150308/revisited-ibd-diseases</link><title>Bugs &amp; Worms, Revisited - They Really May Help Fight IBD and Other Diseases</title><description>...   ... Here we are more than three years later and this possibility is now being seen as a truly viable option for treating those of us with Crohn's, Ulcerative Colitis, Multiple  Sclerosis, and possibly rheumatoid arthritis and some allergies. ...   ... The Wall Street Journal (WSJ) has an article in the Feb. 14, 2012 edition titled, "In a Squeaky-Clean World, a Worm Might Help Fight Disease ." This article discusses the new clinical trials and tests that are being conducted by researches as several universities  and biotechnology companies using pig whipworms to modulate the immune system. ...   ... As we know by now, living in a super clean, germ-free environment may actually be harmful to our health. Why? Because, our immune systems are built by necessity of fighting off germy intruders. But whe... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>