<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7482">popular twitter stars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:45:25" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7482-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7482_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:45:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/92/19112/diets-diet</link><title>Popular Diets Reviewed: The 5-Factor Diet</title><description>... T he 5-Factor Diet is the newest craze in Hollywood. Harley Pasternak, a celebrity trainer who works with stars like Jessica Simpson, John Mayer, Alicia Keys and Halle Berry, created the plan to fit within the strict time constraints of a movie set and touring schedule. With relatively little time and space on a movie set to train clients, the plan was designed to be simple and effective. The five in 5-Factor comes from the foods you eat, the number of times you eat every day and the length and duration of your workouts. The five fives are: • 5-week plan • Five meals a day • Five ingredients • Five minute workouts • Five cheat days in 5 weeks. How the Diet Works People who follow this diet plan eat five meals every day. Each meal is a balanced mix of five ingredients: lean protein, complex carbohydrates, fiber, healthy fats and water or another sugar-free beverage. The diet plan focuses on lean meats, complex carbohydrates, high fiber fruits and vegetables and healthy m... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7482-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7482_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:45:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/7243/26577/celebrating</link><title>Celebrating Rockfish: A Sustainable Star of the Sea Returns</title><description>... this a wonderful time to celebrate the delicious taste of this outstanding fish. ... Rockfish, also known as striped bass, is found in the waters near where I live ... in Washington DC. It is a favorite local fish from the ... Carolinas to Maine. ... One of the rites of spring all around the Chesapeake Bay is  the charter boats  setting out to the sea  because catch restrictions have been lifted and ... they can now lure in this star of the sea again. ...   ... ... The popularity of rockfish is well known because of the ... sweet taste of its meaty white flesh. But in the 1970s the fishing pressure mounted ... and Rockfish became over fished and the stocks were being threatened for the ... future. So in a major conservation act, a group of states halted rockfish (striped ... bass) fishing in the 80s to rebuild the stock. This also happened in the ... Mediterranean in Europe where the same ... problems were occurring. These measures have been successful a... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7482-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7482_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:46:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/78/19585/fights</link><title>Desperate Housewives star fights for Breast Cancer Patient Protection Act of 2007</title><description>... Bree Hodge (who used to be Bree Van de Kamp before her husband was poisoned and she remarried) is fighting alcoholism and the growing estrangement of her son while trying to keep up appearances on Wisteria Lane. She’s also faking a pregnancy, and plans to raise her teenage daughter’s illegitimate baby as her own. Is this for real? Not unless you believe everything you see on TV. Bree is a character played by actress Marcia Cross on “Desperate Housewives,” one of the world’s most popular television shows, with an estimated audience of roughly 20 million viewers a week. Which is the same number of signatures–20 million–that women’s cable network Lifetime has gathered, in the past 12 years, on a petition to be presented to Capitol Hill lawmakers urging them to support the Breast Cancer Patient Protection Act of 2007, a bill to eliminate so-called “drive-through mastectomies.” Now Cross, shedding her TV persona, has stepped up to... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7482-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7482_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:46:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/797759/165076</link><title>currently I'm taking pristiq and my doctor wants to prescribe Effexor xr but I will like to know if I star the Effexor I'm going to star geeting weight,,</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7482-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7482_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:46:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/80106/136870/myr</link><title>Rheumatoid Arthritis Support Comes to Twitter and Facebook</title><description>...   ... You can find us on Facebook and follow us on Twitter , and don't forget to join our twibbon campaign for RA Awareness. ...   ... We look forward to talking to you in both places! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7482-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7482_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:46:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/84404/33970/smaller-messaging</link><title>Twitter: The New Diabetes Social Network</title><description>... What I am talking about is Twitter . Twitter is a micro-blogging platform that saw the light of day in early 2006, starting to pick up steam over the following couple of years and starting to reach a critical mass the first quarter of 2008. ... They define themselves as "a global community of friends and strangers answering one simple question: What are you doing?" As simple as it sounds, it's powerful. No wonder more than one million people are using Twitter these days. ... In Twitter, you can post at most 140 charact... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7482-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7482_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:47:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/26659/66130/twitter</link><title>Utilize Twitter to Keep Up with the Latest Breast Cancer Information</title><description>... ... WTF??? ...   ... I was like, maybe I should be doing Facebook, which I blew off!!? ...   ... Then I was talking to my beloved groovy perfect-score-on-her-SATs genius producer Sarah Park, who laughed and said it was her. ... ... She is the helper/moderator for @BreastCancer on Twitter and is no Grim Reaperessa. ... ... So, don't run. ... ... It's her dream goal to create a place for us Vixen Goddesses on Twitter. ... ... Love ya, ... Marisa ... @CancerVixen ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7482-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7482_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:47:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/26659/63504/cancervixen</link><title>Cancer Research News via Twitter</title><description>...   ... On Twitter, I met the daughter of a newly diagnosed breast cancer patient (Hi, Laura/@GoldyMom)!!! ...   ... Here are my first two tweets (from last night) discussing the Housewives of New York and a special meal cooked at the American Cancer Society's Hope Lodge . ...   ... ...   ... ...   ... Come find ME on Twitter. I'm @CancerVixen !! ...   ... ( Note :Twitter was acting up last night, so lots of people, including yours truly, lost their tweets. Since you can't find them on Twitter, I'm sharing them here with you). ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7482-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7482_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:47:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/161423/migraine-wednesday-8-eastern</link><title>Migraine Twitter Chat - Wednesday at 8 p.m., eastern - Join Us!</title><description>...   ... We'll be on Twitter from 8:00 p.m. until 9:00 p.m., using the hashtag #HealthTipsChat. I've been told that Twitter chats are easier to follow when using www.TweetChat.com , so I'm going to give that a try. ...   ... We'll be chatting about Migraine and headaches of all types, so drop by! ...   ... Live well, ... ... ...   ...   ...   ... Get the latest Migraine and headache news, informational articles, tips for living well, and more in my free Putting Our Heads Together newsletter. To subscribe, CLICK HERE . ... ... ...   ...   ... Follow me on     or  ... ... ...   ...   ... © Teri Robert, 2013. Last updated June 18, 2013. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7482-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7482_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:48:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/906496/147007/twitter-stories</link><title>Twitter Stories</title><description>... Check out how we have been using twitter to answer health questions with your content: http://hcntr.al/0.7 .  We’ve developed @Health_Tips to give people real time, never automated, personalized answers from health experts.  ...   ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>