<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7486">board games teenagers</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:56:39" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7486-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7486_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:56:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/c/89/96197/herd-goats-tag</link><title>A Herd of Goats, A Game of Tag</title><description>...   ... In spite of incredible poverty, ragged school uniforms, little food, and having to take turns using our broken and well-worn pencils in our class, there is still incredible joy as a child begins to learn (even a tiny bit at a time)!  Yesterday, we were outside in the thick red dust of our playground, playing our version of tag, when a herd of goats was suddenly herded through our game.  Of course "my kids" simply spread out and continued playing around the herd, but I found it extremely funny! ...   ... At times, I tend to forget how much different my life is while I'm living in Africa.  I untangled from my mosquito net th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7486-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7486_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:56:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/incontinence/c/3328/49944/bed-youngsters</link><title>How to Encourage Older Children, Adolescents, and Teenagers to Wear Diapers to Bed and Other Issues</title><description>... Ways Parents Can Encourage their Older Child,Teenager,or Adolescent to Wear Diapers to Bed ,How to be Discreet About Bed-wetting and Diaper Use,and Psychological Techniques a Person Can Use to Deal With the Stigma of Using Diapers for Bed-wetting ...   ... ...   If the child,adolescent, or teenager is embarrassed about wearing the diapers and plastic pants to bed there are a number of different ways you can encourage them. First,you can stress how much more comfortable it will be waking up in a dry bed. Second,you can have them go to different online forums(with a younger child it's a good idea to supervise them while they are doing this) and talk to people suffering from similar conditions. There are many online forums dealing with bed-wetting and other incontinence issues. Sometimes it helps to have a sympathetic ear and to realize there are other people in the same boat. ...   ...    Third,you... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7486-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7486_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:57:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/32873/116772/week</link><title>Multiple Sclerosis and Cognitive Function Exercises</title><description>... Do you play games to exercise your cognitive functions and keep your mind sharp? One time my doctor suggested I play games to keep my mind sharp. I have heard other people say the same thing. So I wondered . . . Did your doctor ever suggest that games would help your cognitive functions ? Do you play games? How do you do it? What about a game night? Who plays with you? Family , friends, other game-players? Do you play along with TV games or online games? What about board games? Cards, solitaire, sudoku? The question for this week is: Do you play games to exercise your cognitive functions and keep your mind sharp? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7486-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7486_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:57:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/question/419223/63408</link><title>games</title><description>... Is it ok to mind board games to stimulate the mind, any suggestions? ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7486-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7486_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:57:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/922587/168350/game-life-construction</link><title>game of Life -- under construction</title><description>... What Are We Going to Do With Mother? ... Why Doesn't Anyone Take Me Seriously? ... I'm Doing the Best I Can? ... Significance of Nonsensical Dreams? ... Why Did Someone Set Fire to the Fence at 1:15am? ...   ... The rules don't really change.  People say they change.  People change their minds about whether they want to adhere to the rules.  People claim they are my rules, not theirs.  I wish I could claim Executive Privilege and do whatever the hell I feel like doing without any rules.  But there are rules, e.g., thou shalt not kill; pay your taxes on time or get penalized; you can't hide from Obamacare.  And other rules -- treat others as you want to be treated; don't dive into shallow pools; there is another idiot around every corner; and one of my favorites, "think before you act."  And like the Pharisees were fond of doing, you can make up ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7486-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7486_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:58:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/155373/teaching-healthy</link><title>Teaching Kids to Eat Healthy Using Online Games</title><description>... Gaming Childhood Obesity ...   ... Games targeting healthy behaviors are proliferating. A study published in the Archives of Pediatrics &amp; Adolescent Medicine found that children who played a health game were significantly more likely to select and eat healthier foods than kids who played a game without healthy-stimuli. ...   ... What else does gaming bring that might also be new and important in the fight against childhood obesity? Gaming may make it a little more fun. ...   ... ...   ... Food N’ Me  is an interactive website that aims to promote healthy eating among children. ...   ...   ... The Power of Play: ... Online Games Teach Kids to Eat Healthy ...   ... How can something as seemingly trivial as games improve children’s eating habits and, consequently, their health? Nutrition in and of itself is boring to children. While gaming is fun, exciting, and addicting. So applying gaming theory to nutrition education in the form of online games and mobile apps enables us to ca... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7486-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7486_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:58:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/266176/111901/technology</link><title>Video Games Help Children Manage Diabetes</title><description>...   ... What happens when the two partner up? ...   ... That's what Bayer Labs wants to check out and see with its Didget blood glucose meter and its partner online game. Didget is a blood glucose meter that syncs directly with Nintendo DS (the Gameboy's upgraded version) and into an online adventure game called "Knock 'em Downs World Fair." The tester earns points for testing the prescribed number of times per day and also by staying within targeted BG levels (which are programmable). Didget and the game target kids with diabetes who are between the ages of 4 and 14. An online demo is available, but neither myself nor my son could get it to work. ...   ... Didget and its game are the brainchild of Paul Wessel, whose son Luke has Type 1 Diabetes. Like so many young children who are given with the dau... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7486-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7486_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:58:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/37333/21462/game</link><title>review of automated game system</title><description>... Hi, i am an AS level student, i have just finished manufacturing an automated draughts board machine.     i would really appreciate it if you would email me so that i could send you an email with a Word document attachment that includes all the information about my design so that you could review it for me.   Typical student, i have left my coursework till the last minute, and would really appreciate it if people could get in contact me, and then review my project, for its practicality for a person suffering from arthritis.  my project is meant to limit the movement needed to play a game of draughts, this would be helpful to someone as i am sure it can be very painful movement in the joints sometimes.   i would also be very happy to be given a further understanding of the difficulties of arthritis.     my email is  - myles@smithsbarn.com i would really appreciate it if i could have feedback before the end of this weekend as i must hand my final piece of w... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7486-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7486_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:58:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/education-257650-5.html</link><title>Motivational Games for Teachers for Students with ADHD</title><description>... For teachers, the most difficult part of their job is managing children’s behavior.   While they want to spend their time teaching and passing knowledge along to children, they instead seem to spend their days intervening in arguments, calming out of control children and trying to get others to just stay in their seat for a few minutes.   For a teacher, this is frustrating.   Many teachers who leave the teaching profession do so because of their frustration with their student’s behavior.   While parents, home environment, too much television, violence in the street, violence on television, video games, and much more are often blamed as the source of a child’s disrespect and lack of manners, placing blame is not an answer to behavioral problems.   Often a child, when placed in a well-structured and positive environment will behave as they are expected to.   Children, being children, will also attempt to push the line of acceptance as far as... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7486-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7486_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:59:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/164877/calorie-counts-game-changer</link><title>Are Calorie Counts On Menus A Game Changer?</title><description>... The premise seems sound enough. If consumers see a menu choice followed by a calorie count the length of an area code, they will shy away from the double bacon cheeseburger and make a more healthy choice. ... The idea has become popular enough and appears logical enough that restaurants are being forced to tack on calories counts to their menus . And so we are left with the big dollar question: Does any of this actually work? ... A Case of We Like What We Like ... As mandated by the Affordable Care Act, all restaurants that have 20 or more locations nationally are required to post the number of calories in food and drink items offered on their menus... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>