<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7487">april fools day ideas</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:59:27" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7487-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7487_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:59:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/110/160094/april-metformin-aging-worms</link><title>April Fool’s Day and Metformin and Aging Worms</title><description>...   ... The original research was published 28 March, in the journal Cell , with the typically imposing title of   Metformin Retards Aging in C. elegans by Altering Microbial Folate and Methionine Metabolism .   The studs who wrote the discussion described some extremely interesting findings about how long their worms survived: “In the presence of some E. coli strains, metformin increased lifespan, whereas with other strains or in the absence of microbes it shortened lifespan.” If I understand that sentence correctly, metformin plus some varieties of bacte... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7487-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7487_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:59:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/695780/108197/hate-april</link><title>Why I hate April Fool's Day!</title><description>... Need a laugh?  I work at an elementary school as lunch/recess monitor.  Today I had several kids come up to me with "lies" followed by April Fools!!!  One boy even had his hand wrapped in an ace bandange.  I was horrified to see that blood was seeping thru near the tips of his fingers.  I told him to go right to the nurse.  He whispered that it was fake and the blood stain was food coloring!  So after all these little tricks like being told my shoe was untied, I had a bug in my hair, etc., I made a boo boo.  A boy came up to me and said "I just puked".  I looked at him and said very funny.  He said "I'm serious."  I paused, then said, "If you say April Fools I'm going to be very upset!"  He repeated that he was serious.  I asked "Where?"  He said "On my lunch tray."  I made him take me to his tray and show me.  Sure enough, he had indeed gotten sick.  I told him to go down to the nurse's office.&amp;... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7487-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7487_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 21:59:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/7117/26304/migraine-april-day</link><title>My first migraine ever on April fools day!</title><description>...   ... If anyone has any great advice or info on pineal cyst....let me know. I can use all the help I can get. ...   ... Hopefully something will help soon. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7487-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7487_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:00:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/168451/fools-ruminations-funny-bipolar</link><title>April Fools' Ruminations: A Funny Thing or Two About Bipolar</title><description>...   ... Then it occurred to me: April Fools' would be a great day for a World Bipolar Day. I’m no big fan of special days or weeks or months, but I could really get behind one that fell on the first of April.  ...   ... Bipolar is a joke wrapped in a riddle surrounded by an irony. The joke is on us. Someone up there has to be laughing, right?  ...   ... Imagine the conversations you can have: ...   ... YOU: Hey, did you know that today is World Bipolar Day? ...   ... OTHER PERSON: You’re joking, right? ...   ... This is your cue to deliver any punch line you want. Or maybe you might want to extend the conversation, you know: ...   ... YOU: Did you realize that the person who discovered fire was bipolar? ...   ... OTHER PERSON: Really? ...   ... YOU: Well, this was pre-history, so no one ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7487-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7487_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:00:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/c/78/151700/osteoporosis</link><title>Osteoporosis: Don’t Be an April Fool!</title><description>... April 1 is a day beloved of practical jokesters everywhere. While you may be caught with salt in your coffee (or falling for an email saying pump prices have dropped to 99¢/gallon), there’s no need to be foolish about osteoporosis. Bone up on these five common misperceptions about bone health – and the real story behind each. Osteoporosis is an old lady’s disease. Don’t be fooled: osteoporosis can strike at almost any age. And while it’s most prevalent in women over the age of 65, children and teens can have osteoporosis , too, often in the form of idiopathic juvenile osteoporosis (IJO), but sometimes as a result of poor diet and excessive exercise. And while 80% of osteoporosis sufferers are female, that leaves 20% of diagnosed cases of osteoporosis occurring in males: that’s 1 in 5. So guys, you’re not off the hook. You should be every bit as aware of bone health as women, especially as you get older; and certainly if you smoke, drink to ex... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7487-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7487_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:00:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/110/23769/diabetes-cured</link><title>Diabetes April Fools: Managed Care Finds Diabetes Cure</title><description>... Time for a little humor (or satire). This was originally published at the Diabetes Monitor as the April Fool's page for 1997 (eleven years ago!), but it still resonates with me now.   Managed Care Finds Cure for Diabetes; Endocrinologists Take the Plunge   Declaring diabetes mellitus non-existent, managed care companies nation-wide have managed to wipe out diabetes throughout the United States, it was announced today. It was explained that any patient insisting that they have diabetes will be re-diagnosed as having paranoia, and hence will be ineligible for medical care, as mental health benefits are essentially nonexistent in most managed care plans. The insurance industry also announced that their pre-existing policy of refusing to reimburse for syringes or blood glucose test strips, and discouraging patients' Primary Care Physicians from referring to endocrinologists, has been "totally vindicated."   An estimated three hundred endocrinologists were seen li... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7487-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7487_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:01:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/73654/69735/fooling</link><title>Fooling or foolish?</title><description>...   ... Some days, of course, are bad days. MS takes over body, mind, emotions and intellect and I retreat to the couch. I have to admit that I am weak and cowering on these days, afraid of what is happening and what may still come. On those days, there is unrelenting pain, muscle weakness and an embarrassing lack of mental alertness. ...   ... I never know which day is facing me when I get up in the morning. So when family comes to town, how do I plan entertainment and activities? It's frustrating for me and for them. Recently, with several family members here I experienced both good and bad days. I set out possi... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7487-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7487_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:01:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/460861/73363</link><title>i just got off my period a day or two before this guy and i fooled around...</title><description>... i just got off my period a day or two before this guy and i fooled around. He may have had semen on his finger and then he fingered me, is it possible for me to be pregnant? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7487-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7487_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:01:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/460861/73348</link><title>I just got off my period a day or two before this guy and I fooled around. He may have gotten semen</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7487-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7487_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:02:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/102258/95019</link><title>i was fooling around one day. my friend put his penis into the back of my jeans.</title><description>...  (my pants were buttoned and i had on a belt) and he rubbed his penis in the crack of my anus, he came in my pants onto my panties,(cause my pants were pulled down a little..not even to the halfway mark of my butt) my panties did not touch my vagina and i immediately walked to the bathroom with my pants down,(cause i had touched my vagina lightly to see if cum was on my vagina cause i seen it in my panties but it wasnt) got a hot washcloth with soap and wiped from from to back. then i washed the cloth off again in steaming hot water, then wiped again. i was wondering if i could get pregnant this way. can sperm get into my vagina and fertilize a egg, from the outside of my body. Oh and by the way i changed panties too. i just got off the depo my periods are irregular. this incident happened nov. 4 2009 my last period was oct. 17 2009 but i have been cramping since before this incident. whats going on? ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>