<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7488">DIY shops london open sunday</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:02:15" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7488-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7488_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:02:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/204/68425/life-teleconference</link><title>Managing Life with Migraines Teleconference Registration Still Open for This Sunday April 26th</title><description>... Just like the New Point Comfort Lighthouse did in Maryland, guiding souls to safety on the Chesapeake Bay, Learn how Migraine Management Coach Megan Oltman Guides Migraineurs to a better Life. ...   ... WASHINGTON, D.C.; TUESDAY APRIL 23rd, 2009- After all the excitement of Easter Sunday, after a month of nail biting March Madness Sundays what is a Migraineur to do this Sunday?  MAGNUM has just the thing for you to do to prevent a dreaded post stress let down Migraine this Sunday!  You can join MAGNUM Founder and Executive Director Michael John Coleman when he is the feature guest on the Managing Life with Migraines Teleconference on April 26th; hosted by health advocate and Migraine Management Coach Megan Oltman this Sunday. ...   ... Managing Life with Migraines is a Series of free Sunday afternoon talks hosted by Migraine Management Coach Megan Oltman, featuring Migraine advocates, doctors, experts, coaches, and therapists, on the many aspects of managing our lives with M... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7488-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7488_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:02:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/1443/126514/impulsive-purchases</link><title>Avoiding Impulsive Purchases When Holiday Shopping</title><description>... The number of shopping days until Christmas is quickly dwindling. If you don't yet have your shopping done, or haven't even started, you might be near panic or heading close toward it. And panic mode could very well mean you have a tendency, as I do, to impulse shop. There are times when impulse shopping is good. While strolling through the mall, looking in the different shops, you find the perfect gift for your sister. You see it and know that she will love it. You buy it without thinking. This can be good. You had a open mind, waiting for the right gift to come along. But impulse shopping can cause you to over-extend your budget or choose gifts that looked great in the store but don't look so good once you get home and wonder, "What would make me buy this!" Maybe you bought a gorgeous pink sweater only to get home and remember your sister despises the color pink and never wears anything that is pink. Now, not only do you need to shop again for a gift for your sister, ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7488-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7488_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:02:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/727598/166405/basketball-jan-attention</link><title>"We Back Pat" Basketball Games on Sunday, Jan. 26 Bring Attention to Dementia</title><description>... During this week, NCAA women’s basketball teams are using their games to focus attention on the fight against dementia. And tomorrow (Sunday, January 26), ESPN will highlight the foundation during their broadcast of three women’s basketball games featuring Southeast Conference teams. The first game will involve South Carolina and Vanderbilt while the second game will pit Auburn against Florida. The final game will feature Tennessee, where Coach Summitt still serves as head coach emeritus, against Texas A&amp;M. ... This type of effort isn’t new. In fact, ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7488-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7488_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:03:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/72843/teleconference-cady</link><title>Migraine Teleconference with Dr. Roger Cady Sunday</title><description>...   ... This month's topic is The Connection between Migraines and Emotional Health and How we Can Care for Ourselves in These Areas . The guest expert this month is Migraine and headache specialist Dr. Roger Cady . ...   ... After teleconference host Megan Oltman and Dr. Cady discuss the topic, the call will be open for questions or comments from other participants. ...   ... Roger Cady, M.D. is the Director of the Headache Care Center located in Springfield, Missouri.  ...   ... Dr. Cady is best known in the medical community for his pivotal contributions in the field of headache and migraine management.  He has authored and co-authored numerous books or chapters of books, numerous abstracts, and many articles.  Dr. Cady has presented countless lectures and seminars around the world on headache, migraine and ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7488-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7488_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:03:34">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/1443/164475/adults-adhd-holiday-shopping</link><title>Adults with ADHD: Tips for Holiday Shopping</title><description>... ... ... Love the holidays. You enjoy the lights, the music, the activity - all of it. You start your holiday before Thanksgiving, or maybe even Halloween, attending every party and holiday event. You are out the door before the stores open for Black Friday (or heading out to the mall Thanksgiving night). You check out every sale. You love taking it all in but never seem to get anything accomplished. ... Find shopping overwhelming. You hate standing in line, find the crowds annoying and avoid the mall at all costs. ... You overspend. You head to the mall (or online) with every intention of getting only the gifts on your list but then get taken in by the beautiful displays and hea... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7488-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7488_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:03:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/3900/30120/allergy-shopping</link><title>Allergy-Free Grocery Shopping at Navan</title><description>... ... I had an opportunity to talk with Jennifer Elizondo, owner and founder of Navan in Virginia Beach, Va. about her store, her vision and her process of product selection Health Central: Briefly, why a store for people with food allergies versus an online site? Jennifer Elizondo: I wanted to create a place where people could come and actually see and feel the food products.  It's a much different shopping experience than ordering online.  Specially formulated, allergy-friendly foods tend to cost more, so now people can see what they're buying.  I know I've been disappointed more than once when I've ordered something online and received a tiny little box of food.   Most importantly, I wanted to create a place where kids can find fun products that they can safely eat.  ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7488-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7488_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:04:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/14/1385/food-hoidays</link><title>Food Shopping for a Diabetic Child During the Holidays</title><description>... I went to visit my husband’s family in a small midwestern town for Thanksgiving. Once we arrived we realized that we had only brought two test strips for my daughter’s glucometer. (Not two packages of strips – only two strips.) We got in late the night before Thanksgiving and didn’t realize our mistake until Thanksgiving Day, when most stores in town were closed. So while Grandma was cooking the turkey, we drove to every pharmacy we could find, including a few found inside grocery stores that were actually open. But the pharmacies were not. Test strips are not a controlled substance (like insulin is) so you don’t need a prescription to buy them in a pinch. The only reason the endocrinologist writes prescriptions for them is so that your health insurance plan will cover them. (If you forget them away from home, you’re going to be paying out of pocket unless your insurance company will re-imburse you after the fact.) So you should be able to jus... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7488-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7488_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:04:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/325197/89919/mrf-sweepstakes</link><title>Win Prizes in MRF's Sweepstakes</title><description>...   ... Amazing Prizes! ... ... Amazing Cause! ... ... ... MRF's Door to the Cure Sweepstakes is closing soon! Don't miss your chance to win prizes and support migraine research. The sweepstakes is open through Sunday, October 25. ... ... Go to www.migraineresearchfoundation.org/sweepstakes for your chance to win fabulous prizes like: ... ... • An iPod ... • Luxury hotel packages ... • Shopping sprees ... • Broadway show tickets ...  ....and lots more! ... ... Each prize is a separate drawing, and tickets are just $10 and $25 each. Proceeds will benefit migraine research. Buy lots of tickets to increase your chances of winning! ... ... © Migraine Research Foundation, 2009. Last updated October 8, 2009. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7488-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7488_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:04:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/copd/c/91092/30583/open-natural</link><title>An Open Casket of a Smoker, a Street Fair, and a Natural High</title><description>...   ... An entire street (Vermont Avenue) was blocked off starting ... at Hollywood Blvd. and stretching for a number of blocks up to Franklin Avenue. There were two performance stages – one at ... each end – and bands were scheduled to entertain throughout the event (11 a.m. ... to 8 p.m.). ...   ... A volunteer from the center helped me carry the casket ... containing the body of the unknown smoker , a grotesque display poster, created ... years ago by COLORS Magazine, which has “attracted” countless individuals at ... such events, much like a train wreck would compel notice. ...   ... The ravages of cigarette smoking graphically shown via male ... and female body parts pieced together in the display, startles, motivates, ... repulses, inspires: at day’s end, about 8 p.m., a... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7488-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7488_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:05:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/39653/153122/window-opens</link><title>A Window Closes, A Door Opens</title><description>...   ... I have written in the past about my involvement as a volunteer advocate with the American Pain Foundation (APF).  I was happy when I found an organization with a mission I agreed with and I greatly admired the people I met through APF, both staff and volunteer.  I, and many others, will miss the support and encouragement we received from APF, however we will continue to advocate for positive legislation regarding the treatment of pain and better education on pain and pain management for medical professionals.   In addition, we will continue to reach out to members of the media, people in pain, their families and friends, and the general public to provide a better understanding about pain and pain management and tell the whole story, not just the one-sided articles that are often found associated with stories on pain medications and the too-often misuse and abuse of these medications.  We all agree that far too many people are misusing strong pain medica... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>