<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7489">make skull mask</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:05:22" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7489-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7489_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:05:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/sleep-disorders/c/question/748768/136614</link><title>I have had the nasal mask for a bit over 2 weeks now. I keep it on most of the night. But I have a hard time getting to sleep an hour or more. I can hear the air coming into mask. Or when I move aroun</title><description>... Or when I move around, I hear nosies from the mask so it keeps me awake. I have also experienced in the morning, some anxiety issues. Also some headaches. is this normal? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7489-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7489_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:05:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/imagepages/8795.html</link><title>Skull</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7489-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7489_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:05:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/imagepages/9057.html</link><title>Skull</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7489-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7489_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:06:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/521061/102621/mask</link><title>THE #X@#$# MASK</title><description>... I have been trying to live without "the mask" since the end of December.  Sometimes I can go a few days without the mask, and then it slips back on like a pair of perfect fitting gloves without notice.  When I finally notice I get extremely frustrated.  I am discovering the mask now slips on when stressful things happen in my life and the people around me.  I think I am going to keep the mask on for now so I do not have to deal with life.  I'll keep it on at home and pretend that everything is ok, as right now. If I do not keep on the mask on I am going to have a nervous breakdown. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7489-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7489_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:06:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/36931/35791/mask</link><title>Face Mask while on Remicade</title><description>... Has anyone considered using a face mask while on Remicade?  I start my infusion soon and I'm considering using a mask in a daily basis just to prevent any type of infection.  I know it will look silly, but when it come to my health, who cares about looking silly. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7489-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7489_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:06:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/302869/52384</link><title>can scary mask cause seizures</title><description>... my uncle who is bed bound dementia patient got scared of a horrible mask during last halloween and after that he started having seizures, is it true that his fear and as he scared caused him having seizures (He is bed bound, can't speak but can see and hear and is about 68 years old) ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7489-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7489_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:07:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/incontinence/c/45/2611/masks-hide</link><title>Masks We Hide Behind</title><description>... ... It seems that whenever a potentially embarrassing situation confronts us, it is human habit to hide behind a mask of some kind. When in debt, we go out of our way to seem completely comfortable financially in front of our friends. When we don’t understand the punch line to a joke, we laugh even harder. When we show up for an important event only to realize we’re either over- or under-dressed, we make up a story about everything else being at the drycleaner’s. It seems that in order to “save face” we are willing to put on almost any face – as long as it’s not ours! ... ... If we’re willing to go to these lengths just to seem that we’ve got it “all under control” financially, that we understand every joke the first time around, and that we rarely, if ever, appear i... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7489-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7489_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:07:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/asthma/c/question/905819/47517</link><title>What are the best allergy masks to use?</title><description>... Because my asthma is triggered by pollen, etc. I am lookng at allergy masks.  There are so many that I don't know which type is best - HEPA filter?  I think I want one with a valve to ease breathing.  I live in Arizona so heat buildup is an issue. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7489-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7489_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:07:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/15/99585/wearing-acting-normal</link><title>Wearing the Mask, Acting "Normal"</title><description>... Last week, in a sharepost here , I wrote: We excel at wearing the mask. We fool our friends, our loved ones, our colleagues, our doctors, even. Deep down inside, however, we are the crying clown, our souls in torment, our psyches in a thousand pieces. It appears I struck a chord. Says MerelyMe : I read this and I started to just about cry because you have absolutely nailed it with precision. It is so much about wearing a mask...it takes such an incredible amount of energy to fit in and act "normal" whatever that means. But all the while feeling so different on the inside. Adds Chris , who decided not to put on his mask this particular morning: “[I] just didn’t have the energy or desire to ACT the opposite of how I was feeling.” It’s as if we’re strangers in our own land. Says Alxv : We have to live in two worlds at the same time without losing it and that makes me feel like I'm a tightrope walker on a thin wire with strong winds always crossing my path every ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7489-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7489_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:08:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/question/617463/78583</link><title>has my history of substance abuse masked my schizophrenia</title><description>... Have only recently discovered I am schizophrenic, has my history of substance abuse been masking a condition I was preditermined to have ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>