<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7490">convert wav mp3</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:08:23" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7490-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7490_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:08:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/12658/35143</link><title>i take lexapro 20 mg and i need to convert to effexor, how do i convert?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7490-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7490_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:08:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/question/275843/131418</link><title>please inform me how hepatitis b antibodies titer are measured because british guidelines say level of&gt;100i.u/l is good immunity while usa says &gt;10mlU/l is good.what is the difference.How convert unit</title><description>... how units can be converted from i.u./L to mlU/l ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7490-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7490_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:09:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/50880/62670</link><title>How would you convert oxycodone to buprenorphine</title><description>... would like to know how to convert a aptient from 80mgs of oxycodone to either buprenorphine or methadone ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7490-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7490_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:09:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/question/373526/88219</link><title>ounces but i need to convert to cc,s help me figure this out?</title><description>... help me figure this out? i don't have the memory for how it works .. thanks ... need to convert ounces to cc,s?? please ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7490-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7490_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:09:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/question/327857/151660</link><title>Is breast cancer effect on lungs? and is this effect is converted into lungs cancer?</title><description>... Is breast cancer effect on lungs? and is this effect is converted into lungs cancer?Because for three four months i have problems with my left lungs. I visited my doctor they say that in my xray report there is some dots on top of my left lung. what is this means? and now they take scan report on next day. What is that indicate? Plz reply in detail ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7490-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7490_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:09:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/88625/41059/converting</link><title>Converting oxycontin to the fentanyl patch</title><description>...   ... I'll introduce myself within the next few days. I have an appointment with my doctor shortly however and wanted to get feedback from members on their experience with conversions from oxycontin to the patch. I have seen a variety of conversions in different tables on the internet. While many list ranges, some suggest a 1:1 conversion for oxycontin to the transdermal fentanyl patch. My doctor is going to convert some of my oxycontin to the patch this week and I hoped to find out what others have experienced when converting from one med to the other. ...   ... If you have been on oxycontin and switched to the patch, I would be grateful if you could share what dose of oxycontin you were on and what dose of the patch you wound up on. ...   ... I have gone through two conversions with my doctor so far and he has been so low each time that it has thrown me into withdrawal. The last conversion put me severe withdrawal for two weeks while he continued to increase the dose. If he suggests ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7490-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7490_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:10:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/news/choosing-a-joint-implant-when-converting-a-fused-knee</link><title>Choosing a Joint Implant when Converting a Fused Knee</title><description>... When a knee joint has been fused in place, doctors can sometimes convert the fusion and restore the hinge motion at the knee by implanting a new knee joint. The authors of this study review 36 cases of fused-knee conversion. Most of the patients were young (ranging from 23 to 58) and had a fused knee for many years. The study took place in Korea, where childhood tuberculous arthritis is more common. More than half the patients studied were in this category. The rest had infectious arthritis. Some knees had fused naturally, while others were fused surgically. The joint replacement used in this group of patients was different from the implant normally recommended. A constrained total knee is advised when collateral ligaments along the sides of the knee are absent or weak. However, doctors at the Joint Replacement Center of Korea used a nonconstrained, posterior stabilized total knee replacement. Results were good. Sixty-one percent of all patients were free from pain, and the rest noted ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7490-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7490_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:10:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/question/159517/93203</link><title>if the simple sugar is not burned as energy how long do you have untill it is converted to starch?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7490-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7490_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:10:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/question/441250/61294</link><title>How do you convert foods into numbers of exchanges set up by the american dietetic association?</title><description>... for example looking at a food label how do I know the number of exchanges of starches or proteins that is in that package.  Is there a way to figure that out? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7490-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7490_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:11:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/question/769483/57686</link><title>I have type 2 diabeties. I live in Canada. how can i convert from US reading to Canadian reading</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>