<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7491">convert wav mp3 program</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:11:17" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7491-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7491_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:11:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/42544/elders-digital-tv</link><title>Tips To Help Your Elders Get Ready for Digital TV Switch</title><description>...   ... I'm writing this to give readers information, but I'm most concerned about elders getting scammed. Older people are still more vulnerable to giving out private information over the phone or even in a store, thinking that this nice young woman who is asking must need it in order to help them. ...   ... So, to help your elder, please be aware by reading the tips, below, and then go to the government site, at www.dtv2009.gov , for more information. ...   ... At midnight of February 17, 2009, U.S. television will stop broadcasting in analog and switch to 100% digital broadcasting. People with cable or satellite TV access shouldn't even notice a hiccup. However, those with a TV antenna will no longer get reception, unless they have a converter box. ...   ... You can order coupons at the government site to offset the pr... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7491-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7491_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:11:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/896502/148624/21-program</link><title>21-Day Vegan Kick-Start Program May Make New Year's Resolutions Come True</title><description>... It’s time for New Year’s resolutions, so what about trying to eat better? If you need a little help, the Physicians Committee for Responsible Medicine (PCRM) has developed a free 21-day vegan kick-start program . The next program kicks off January 2, 2012. ... First of all, let me share a little about PCRM. According to its website , “Since 1985, PCRM has been influencing advancements in medicine and science. We advocate for preventive medicine, especially good nutrition, conduct clinical research, and advocate for higher ethical standards in research. More than 125,000 health care professionals and concerned citizens are dedicated to creating a better future for animals and people.” The group has lobbied for reform of the federal nutrition policies and has sponsored clinical research programs to develop breakthroughs in diabetes, cancer and other illnesses. PCRM also recommends a diet focused on “ The New Four Food Groups ,” which is comprised of the follo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7491-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7491_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:12:00">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/58426/38891/competiting</link><title>What About Sarah Palin vs Joe Biden Competiting With Your Running Mate</title><description>...   ... Experience I believe if you want to be successful, copy someone who is already successful and the best of the best athletes use music to get them pumped up for competition and for motivation during their workouts. Remember Michael Phelps? Before every race he used his ipod to get him psyched up and look what happened to the competition. ...   ... Swing State Argument Music is a natural performance aid and can swing your mental state from a mediocre workout to elevating your body to performing at a peak level. ...   ... Appealing to Your Base of Hardworking Fundamentals Nothing can get you in the fitness mood like music. When listening to music during training, you get totally drawn in. Your foc... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7491-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7491_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:12:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/4385/9107/finishing-semester</link><title>finishing the semester</title><description>... I finished my two papers for this semester, after obessing over them for the last three weeks and will hand them in today. Now it's time to study for my final. Ah...some objective data and not synthesis, ...a blessed respite from sitting in front of the blasted computer word program, trying to come up with words, when the last thing my brain wants is a bright screen and its glare and pressure to express what is well established in my head, but what I can't access into coherent words. I can barely focus on the screen anymore, although I so appreciate the convenience my laptop affords me: a website on the "divine hours" for devotional times; calming music on my mp3s; looking for some encouraging e-mail....Thank God for this laptop, maintenance needs and all. But maybe getting off this thing and onto some "hard copy" will be good for me over the next couple of days. Good for my eyes, my head and more importantly, good for my soul. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7491-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7491_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:12:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/3142/109517/june-2009-working</link><title>June 2, 2009-Working it all out</title><description>... ... Well, my low-level, but ever-present migraine is really beginning to get on my nerves.  I have noticed I am not as tolerant of temperature changes, volume levels, hunger, or anything that causes me any discomfort.  I talked to my Neuro and I am going back on Zonegran.  I am still waiting to see if I need B-12 injections. ...   ... Today, I started my new exercise regimine.  I go in a week to a have a personal trainer plan out a program for me, but in the mean time, I walk around the indoor track, use the newstepper, and do a little machine work for my upper arms.  Instead of keeping tracks of laps, or distance, I took a stop watch and used time as my goal.  I did a hard 30 minutes, which is a big step for me.  I know that eventually I will have to work up to an hour, but I think I had a good first step.  I hope I am not too sore tomorrow, so I can go back and do some more work tomorrow.  ...   ... I really enjoy music.  It can li... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7491-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7491_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:12:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/896502/149272/listening</link><title>Listening to Music Can Make Your Workouts Seem Easier</title><description>...   ... But one time when I attended one of these sessions, the power went off in the whole building. Fortunately, the classroom where we were lifting weights was really light since there was a bank of windows on one side so the teacher decided to keep the class going. Her decision felt like a ton of bricks, literally, because those weights that were so easy to lift to a bouncy musical number by Beyonce suddenly felt like dead weight. I never had attended a class that seemed to last longer (and it o... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7491-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7491_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:13:10">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/367993/92964/expenditure</link><title>Your Guide to Calorie Expenditure</title><description>...   ... There are a few different methods of determining your daily calorie burn.  Each of these methods has varying degrees of accuracy and you will find that there are many tools available that can guarantee nearly 100% accuracy. ...   ... The first method is simple guesstimation.  While it is the least accurate and least effective method, it is the most utilized of all.  The way it works is that an individual assumes that if they begin working out it will generate enough increased calorie burn to create a calorie deficit, which would then lead to weight loss.  Clearly this is not a scientific approach and I do not sugg... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7491-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7491_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:13:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/120/28306/tips-traveling</link><title>Tips For Traveling</title><description>... decided to devote a blog entry to tips for healthy traveling, as well as common ... etiquette guides for tipping the people who serve to make your travel ... experience carefree.  Lastly, I'll give ... you some practical matters to consider. ...   ... First, here are "10 Tips for Healthy Traveling," ... taken from the SchizophreniaConnection bookmarks I'll be handing out to ... conference-goers: ...   ... 1.      Start ... the day with whole-grain cereal/oatmeal and a glass of orange juice (OJ helps ... boost your immune system for crowded flights). ...   ... 2.      Minimize ... sodium and alcohol.  If you do drink ... alcohol, make sure you stay hydrated. ...   ... 3.      Bring ... a bottle of water with you when you travel.  ... Dehydration can cause fatigue, headaches and irritability and you're ... already at risk for all three in a hectic day of traveling. ...   ... 4.      Don't... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7491-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7491_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:13:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/2295/diabetes-podcasts</link><title>Another Diabetes Resource: Podcasts</title><description>... ... ... ... ... ... The word podcast is actually a misnomer. You don’t need an iPod to listen to podcasts. All you need is a computer, an Internet connection, and one of many software p... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7491-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7491_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:14:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/tools-252207-5.html</link><title>MAPP Your Migraine!</title><description>... No matter how effective our preventive regimen is, we're going to be struck with a Migraine from time to time. To make those Migraines easier to deal with, let's form a M igraine A ction P lan and P ack, let's MAPP them. Here are the elements of the Plan ... You and your doctor should have a treatment plan in place. For most Migraineurs, your first-line medication when you have a Migraine will be a triptan (Imitrex, Maxalt, Zomig, Amerge, Relpax, Axert, Frova). Some take other medications such as an antinausea medication or NSAID with it. Whatever your doctor has recommended, part of your Plan is being sure you have your medications on hand. In addition to your abortive medications, be sure you have your rescue medications on hand as well. Hopefully you won't need them, but if you do, the last thing you want to discover is that you don't have them. For more information about the different types of medications see Preventive, Abortive, and Rescue Medication... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>