<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7492">oldest jokes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:14:16" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7492-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7492_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:14:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/3974/12778/cruel-jokes</link><title>Cruel jokes played others.</title><description>...     My ex husband thinks it funny to call and hurt me and my children. He has call many times to talk and than he tells his lies to us. I don't understand why he get such a kick out of doing this. He calls and says that he has thew his girlfriend out because she is using drugs and is cheating on him. He says he would love to see his daughters but than, he calls back and says he can't. They have plans with her children. This time when he called he said that caught her at the other guy's house. He laid in on his horn to let her know that he caught her. Than called her on the phone and told her stuffs  and get out of his house. The house he bought for her and her kids. He started talking about every thing he bought for them. Furniture, cars, and trips. This made me so mad. Than he decided to get back at her by going back to another woman he was with when he left me! He didn't care that he made his children homeless and left me to pay $65,000 bills. This incl... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7492-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7492_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:14:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/c/310478/152132/relcast</link><title>relcast what a joke and the jokes on me</title><description>... i reluctently and recently, probably 2 1/2 mths now, had the reclast infusion, my oncololgist suggested it last year , i was against it, once its in you, no turning back.  so then my rheumotologist suggested it and i gave in. now 2mths later, i developed HBP. i never had HBP my whole life, its always been normal low. my heartrate is eratic amoung other new symptoms, like muscular weaknes, short of breath. i mention these because i like to hike and never would be sooo out of breath as i was just recently. these symptoms, signs are all new. i am very disgusted and worried, hoping that in a years time and then some, will the reclast leave the body. too me, its like having a chemo treatment, not as toxic, but toxic enough to raise ones blood pressure to be in hytensive state. I started bp meds 3 wks ago, and bp is still in hypertension, that i'll address with doc. as far as the drug co's. i would love to infuse them and let them have things happen to their body.  the sudden&amp;nbsp... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7492-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7492_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:14:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/question/802401/73162</link><title>does the oldest child have any rights when it comes to a parent with alzhiemers</title><description>... Does the oldest child have any rights when it comes to a parent with alzhiemers? ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7492-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7492_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:15:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/138443/understanding</link><title>“Understanding Well-being in the Oldest Old” highlights culture change in eldercare</title><description>... These aged people have largely been ignored by many as a group that is too old to really live . In many cases, apart from groups active in culture changes such as the Pioneer Network , they have been relegated, for the most part, to just exist until death. ...   ... "Understanding Well-being in the Oldest Old," aims to improve this view. It delivers a comprehensive treatment of how we, as a society, should be looking at the care of the oldest old. The word "well-being," in the title of the book, is what  drew me to this volume. Society needs to continue to look at aged people as human beings entitled to the best quality of life they can live. That, obviously, encompasses more... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7492-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7492_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:15:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/question/552740/118335</link><title>Our oldest son is 49 and has had ADHD since he was a small child. When we lived in Ohio he was treated with medications. When we moved to SC, nobody knew much about ADHD. He has been hoarding cats.</title><description>... He has gotten in trouble with this problem with the County, and his house has suffered also. He was cited about four years ago; we hoped this would not happen again. He sees a Doctor on a regular basis; He has a another court date soon. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7492-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7492_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:15:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/960412/145529</link><title>MY DAD WAS VERY ABUSIVE TO MY MOM, AND HIT HER FROM TIME TO TIME. US KIDS AS WELL. SISTER OLDEST AND TWO BROTHERS. PARENTS NOW DIVORCE.MY SISTER IS ALWAYS GIVING MY MOTHER A HARD TIME. HURTING HER</title><description>... FEELINGS ALL THE TIME. NEVER HAS ANYTHING NICE TO SAY TO HER. I THINK SHE BLAMES HER FOR STAYING WITH OUR DAD. AND THAT'S WHY WERE SO MESSED UP ALL THREE OF US KIDS. DOES SHE HAVE PTSD?? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7492-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7492_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:16:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/114/7695/oldest-living</link><title>The Oldest Living Diabetic</title><description>... I was getting my eyebrowswaxed before heading off to class and the hairdresser explained to me what ahorrible day she was having because her grandfather had just passed away. Hewas 73 years old. He had diabetes—she couldn’t tell me which kind, but I thinkit was probably Type 2—among an impressive assortment of other healthconditions. Both his legs had been amputated, and he also had eye problems,kidney problems, liver problems, etc. I declined to tell her I had diabetes aswell, because I’m sure I would’ve gotten a reaction like, “Oh…geez…I’m sorry,”and the assumption that someday I would be legless, too. As she continued to painfully rip out the hair above myeyes, I thought about her legless grandfather and reminded myself: I want to bethe longest living diabetic there ever was; 73 is not long enough. When I’m 73years old I plan to be teaching yoga classes, sipping freshly squeezedgrapefruit juice on my lake-house porch with my husband and our dogs, andwriting articles about Living Wit... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7492-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7492_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:16:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/c/question/198534/139216</link><title>I am a mother of 5 my oldest is 5 and my youngest is 7 months I am 23 years old..I had my tubes tied 4 months after my youngest was born</title><description>... ..and before that I wouldnt stop bleeding i went past 6 weeks and still bled..and then after I got my tubes I was still bleed..and I bleed when my son was turned        almost 6 months old..and now I havent seen a period going on 4 months now..what is going on..now my back is killing and i feel crampy ...help!!! please does anyone know why?? I can't me pregnant can I ?? I was cut and burned ..and i can't be going through early menopause can I ??? and having a fibroid couldnt be doing this too could it???                                                                     Needs Help In Riverview Fl,   &amp;... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7492-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7492_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:16:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/371052/107938</link><title>What is the oldest drug used effectively to treat anxiety/depression?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7492-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7492_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:16:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/sleep-disorders/c/question/704166/156054</link><title>Why is there no objective devise (machine) to measure pain? Pain is the oldest of all medical problems</title><description>... Pain or sleep it is all the same.  The FDA or government is not trying to solve the problem in any method that makes sense.  Our (American) prisons are full and we have more people in prison that any other country even more than Hitler's Germany or Stalin's Russia.  Yet the government answer to all questions is remove stuff from circulation and put people in prison.  I am surprised that the greedy rich allowed the end of the death penality as that saves the cost of locking up people?  Solving a problem costs money and the greedy rich who run this country will not allow money to be spend for most things.  ...   There are fewer and fewer doctors due to regulations and the cost of medical malpratice.  One solution to malpratice is to limit what lawyers can get and require arbatration of disagreements.  Then maybe more Americans would get into medicine. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>