<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7493">islam discussions social media</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:17:15" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7493-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7493_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:17:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/111587/perspective</link><title>Social Media and It's Effect on Depression and Mental Disorders</title><description>...   ... I thought I would initiate a discussion today about how we patients use social media.  It is a fascinating topic as the world today has drastically changed due to various venues on the Internet to connect with other people. ...   ... Belonging to an older demographic, I remember the days before home computers or the Internet.  Hey...I am so old I remember Pong.  And card catologs.  And records...and...but I digress.  ...   ... But all of a sudden...wham!  We have all these social sites...support groups, blogs, Podcasts, iPhone apps, virtual realitity games, facebook and twitter and the list keeps growing.  ...   ... As a patient...all of this social media can be both a blessing and a curse.  You have sooooo much information streaming onto your computer screen in seconds.  You can plug in your symptoms in a google search and come up with hundreds...maybe thousands of web pages which will tell you about those symptoms and what the... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7493-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7493_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:17:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/123/164087/migraine-patient-30-gratitude</link><title>Social Media - A Migraine Patient's 30 Days of Gratitude</title><description>...   ... We encourage everyone with Migraines or headaches to maintain a Migraine and Headache diary . I do find my Migraine diary helpful, but there's another form of diary that I find just as helpful - my gratitude journal. Some days, I write quite a bit in that journal; other days, just a few words. No matter how much or how little I write, making those entries reminds me that there are many good things in my life. ...   ... It may seem strange, but for day #7 of our 30 Days of Gratitude, I offer my gratitude for social media outlets such as Facebook, Twitter, StumbleUpon, and others. ...   ... Social media outlets have changed the lives of many, many patients. Social media can help us... ... ... find info... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7493-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7493_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:17:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/c/80106/146992/ra</link><title>RA and Social Media: Finding #Rheum Mates</title><description>...   ... Enter the Internet. It has had a revolutionary impact on our ability to connect, person to person and community to community, creating a larger tapestry of people living with RA and other autoimmune diseases. ...   ... The Personal Touch ... People connect in groups on Facebook, LinkedIn and Google+. On Twitter, searching for the hashtag s #rheum,  #spoonie and #autoimmune will show you all sorts of conversations about RA, chronic illness and autoimmune diseases. The possibilities are almost endless, but ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7493-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7493_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:18:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/42538/155658/weight-gain</link><title>Can You Blame Social Media for Your Weight Gain?</title><description>...   ... As the third most popular social media platform, Pinterest now has more than 20 million users with a majority being women. ...   ... When users “pin” their favorite recipes the recipes tend to lean towards the unhealthy high calorie choices. ...   ... Red Velvet Cake ... Chicken Taco Chili ... Oreo Layer Dessert ... Strawberries and Cream Dessert Squares ... Gnocchi, Sweet Corn, &amp; Arugula in Cream Sauce ... Pumpkin Spice Donuts ... Tin Roof Ice Cream Cake ...   ... And the list goes on. . . ...   ... All sounds delicious, right? On the negative side, the recipes tend to be high in added sugars , saturated fat, and calories. ...   ... Why am I writing about Pinterest? ...   ... If you are someone that loves trying new recipes, Pinterest may be a great resource. You not only get the recipe you also get a picture of the finished product. T... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7493-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7493_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:18:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/6509/117338/dementia-social</link><title>Living with Dementia: Using Social Media to Cope with Dementia</title><description>...   ... Facebook allows me to keep up with my friends and family, as well as former students. And, it has the added benefit of being able to “chat” live (in the moment) with anyone listed as my friend on Facebook who is signed in at the same time that I am. ...   ... I have written conversations with my sister-in-law, whom I don’t see very often. It’s the next best thing to actually “being there”. Since my brother’s death, she has moved and is getting on with her life. It is important to me that she remain a part of my family... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7493-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7493_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:18:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/172721/110258/healthcare</link><title>Please participate: Health Social Media Survey on behalf of the California HealthCare Foundation</title><description>... ... ... On behalf of the California HealthCare Foundation, we are compiling a unique study about trends in health social media (HSM). The study will be made available to the general public later this year at no charge. ...   ... As part of this study, we are trying to get an indication of why consumers engage in HSM (health-related blogs, online communities, Twitter and Facebook groups, etc.) and how people rate their experience. Therefore, we are asking you to answer five simple questions, below, which will only take a few minutes of your time. All statements will be published anonymously. ...   ... To take the survey now, please click here: http://www.surveymonkey.com/s/BPD75XK ...   ... Your participation is very important in order to get good insight into how people like you are shaping the emerging world of HSM. ...   ... Thank you very much! ...   ... Burghardt Tenderich ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7493-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7493_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:19:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/743300/154435/increase-anxiety</link><title>Social Media Sites Increase Anxiety, Poll says</title><description>... ... Over half the group said they felt “worried or uncomfortable” when they were unable to access their email or social media accounts. The Telegraph  reports that more than 60 percent of those polled said they have to turn their electronic devices off to relax, and one in three said they turn their gadgets off several times a day. ... The Anxiety Chief Executive Nicky Lidbetter said “If you are predisposed to anxiety it seems that the pressures from technology act as a tipping point, making people feel more insecure and more overwhelmed.” ... ... Of those polled more than half said sites like Facebook and Twitter affected their behavior, and half said it affected their confidence, especially after reading about the achievements of their peers. Nearly two-thirds of ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7493-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7493_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:19:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/9993/113715/relevance-doctors</link><title>The Relevance of Doctors in Social Media</title><description>...   ... Riva had some great points about what social media has been doing for patients. Since the online launch of social health-related sites, patients have been able to find support through online groups, like HealthCentral.com , where patients respond to one another's queries, adding deeper knowledge of their condition and tools for better management.  ...   ... What brought me to HealthCentral was my own experience with a crisis and the failure of the medical community to fix a simple problem. I never wanted to see another person go through this experience again and so I became a patient advocate for people to take a more active role in their care to avoid such mistakes.  I understood very little about what I was getting into, but the journey into this vast diabetes community has become a positive and life cha... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7493-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7493_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:19:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/17/115314/social-media-summit</link><title>Diabetes and a Social Media Summit</title><description>... ... Getting together with 35 other people who have diabetes and write about it online is one of the best things about my work. I just returned home from a full day at the second annual Social Media Summit sponsored by  Roche Diabetes Care . I still find myself invigorated by having spent hours in the company of so many passionate people. ...   ... Four of the 36 bloggers at the summit came from one organization -- HealthCentral. Gretchen Becker posts  here , Ginger  Vieira  posts  here , Kerri  Sparling  posts  here , and I post  here . ...   ...   ... ... Gretchen, Ginger, Kerri, and David ...   ... The combined passion for better diabetes care surfaced most intensely when our eight hosts from Roche brought in representatives from the  American Diabetes Association  and the  American Association of Diabetes Educators  to tell us what they were doing. If they had any idea of the number, range, and intensity of the comments that were going hit th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7493-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7493_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:20:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/142888/media-browsers</link><title>Social Media, Browsers, and More: The Question of the Week!</title><description>...   ... Let's get technical shall we? ...   ... I am very curious about our readership on MyDepressionConnection and the answers you provide to my little questionairre can help us to make this a better site. ...   ... 1.  Which browser do you use to view Health Central content? Do you ever have difficulties viewing our content based upon which browser you are using? ...   ... 2.  How did you find this site?  ...   ... 3.  What would you say are the major technical obstacles to using this site?  For example, do you have difficulty finding information, commenting, posting, etc.? Which things are most problematic for you? ...   ... 4.  What suggestions do you have for improving the site?  ...   ... 5.  What are some of the things you like about this site? Examples can range from the color scheme to the slide shows to the support from other members. ...   ... 6. Do you use twitter or facebook?  Do you want to see Health Central content promoted on twitt... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>