<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7494">cartoons festival</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:20:18" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7494-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7494_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:20:19">http://www.healthcentral.com/copd/c/91092/26991/addictions</link><title>First ever "Festival of Recovery" addresses addiction and mental health issues</title><description>... We opened our doors at 9 A.M., Saturday, April 26, on a warm sunny Southern California morning.  I had arrived a 7:30 A.M. to tie up last minute loose ends and greet numerous presenters, representatives and event volunteers who came in earlier to set up display tables, unbox organizational literature, unstack countless chairs, unpack and open buckets of food, prepare barrels of iced soft drinks. ... We literally took over an entire building: the Center for Inquiry’s famed Steve Allen Theater was host to professional presenters throughout the day and we utilized the center’s lobby, patio, downstairs conference room, my upstairs office ( SOS International ), three other second floor offices and the large second floor seminar area. ... James Underdown, Director and CEO, Cente... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7494-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7494_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:20:33">http://www.healthcentral.com/copd/c/91092/25830/christopher</link><title>Jim Christopher to host Annual "Festival of Recovery" and "Funeral for the Unknown Smoker"</title><description>... We’re getting geared up for a big free event: The First Annual “Festival of Recovery.” The event will take place all day this Saturday, April 26, at the Center for Inquiry, Hollywood, CA. It's an ambitious project, sponsored by SOS (Save Our Selves), SHARE! (Self Help and Recovery Exchange) and Project Return Peer Support Network. I’ll present the 9th annual “Funeral for the Unknown Smoker” as a special component and co-host the festival, along with Ruth Hollman, founder of SHARE!. Wendy, Susan, Armen, Ari – all former smokers – will serve as pallbearers as we carry the casket (marked “open at your own risk”) for the unknown smoker down the aisle of the Center for Inquiry’s Steve Allen Theater up onto the stage.  The casket will be set upright and, as the pallbearers step to the side, I’ll approach and remove the lid of the casket revealing the “body” of the unknown smoker, a horrifically impactful ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7494-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7494_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:20:49">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/62126/43410/festival</link><title>Breast Fest Film Festival 2008</title><description>...   ... Their website states, "BREAST FEST is the world's first film festival dedicated to breast cancer awareness. This annual festival includes short films, documentaries, animation, dramatic features and experimental works which span the emotional spectrum. Through the use of film and new media, BREAST FEST is dedicated to showcasing the many issues surrounding breast cancer in significant and interesting ways, and ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7494-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7494_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:21:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/holiday-guide-196428-5.html</link><title>How to Survive Festive Feasting</title><description>... The holiday season undoubtedly brings a host of delicious food and drink, which can really play havoc with our waist line and cholesterol levels ! Some people throw their hands up and give into temptation as if it’s inevitable while others rationalize that it’s merely a time in the year when they’re destined to put on a few pounds. Whilst there’s no reason to feel guilty about enjoying what you eat, it's worth remembering that, on average, Americans gain around 1-5 pounds over the Christmas period. Un fortunately, this excess weight is rarely lost again.  Rather than giving yourself liberty to eat as you please, then trying to lose it again at the beginning of the year, why not prevent the weight gain in the first place? Here are a few tips to help you merrily munch your way through the festive season:   The Holiday Party If you’re heading to a party don’t starve yourself all day so that you can eat what you like that evening... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7494-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7494_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:21:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/673613/95630/festivities</link><title>rejected from holiday festivities</title><description>... my cousin said it is my fault i dont have my money yet, it is my fault that he is not out of the house yet, it is my fault that my attorney isnt a "bulldog" she said i dont deserve holidays, i deserve to be alone becasue i am poor and i should have been rough and tough, ... I was that being soft hearted is a weakness, and she had to trow in  my being bi-racial , ... I thought i had a family, i was told i dont have the rough tough attitude of the family it matter? ... i was told i am just too white, act too white, and not a strong black woman. ... does, that matter, and that i will never be well from depression, I thought I had family, i was wrong, no one wants me i am so alone, maybe i am just stupid to think that anyone ... would truly care. I am going to bed now, I am too sad to write anymore, i am just a person, not a colour, i was told to buck up and get over depression, her tone was like i used to hear ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7494-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7494_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:21:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/49350/39755/cartoons-mental</link><title>cartoons for Mental Health Humor.</title><description>... \--------------------- ...   ... Terms Of Use: The art work / Cartoons series Mental Health Humor cartoons are not to be edited or modified and when used a tagline “used with permission of Chato B. Stewart” or “reprinted with permission by Chato B. Stewart” and link to http://www.mentalhealthhumor.com should appear with each cartoon when used online or in any type of non-profit print. ... ... http://www.mentalhealthhumor.com ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ...   ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7494-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7494_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:22:08">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/81973/49625/mental-cartoons</link><title>You Weekly Laugh - Mental Health Humor cartoons drawn by little ol' ME :) (part3)</title><description>...   ... ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7494-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7494_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:22:27">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/c/77040/39754/cartoons-mental</link><title>cartoons for Mental Health Humor.</title><description>... Hello all, here are some of my new cartoons for Mental Health Humor. ...   ... ---------------- ...   ... Terms Of Use: The art work / Cartoons series Mental Health Humor cartoons are not to be edited or modified and when used a tagline “used with permission of Chato B. Stewart” or “reprinted with permission by Chato B. Stewart” and link to http://www.mentalhealthhumor.com should appear with each cartoon when used online or in any type of non-profit print. ... ... http://www.mentalhealthhumor.com ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ...   ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7494-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7494_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:22:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/81973/73473/cartoonthon</link><title>Success! Success!! The Cartoon-A-Thon for May 2009 Mental Health Month was a success!</title><description>... Success! Success!! The Cartoon-A-Thon for May 2009 Mental Health Month was a success! ... The purpose of the Cartoon-A-Thon is to use humor and laughter as positive tools in dealing with emotional disturbances which effect many people and families.  ... Mental disorders due to mental Illness or mood disorders and nothing to laugh at, but that does not mean we need to lose our sense of humor. As a “consumer of mental health services” and an amateur cartoonist I was drawing one cartoon a day to help thousands find a smile, even it was for a second.   Soon I will write a post with all the awesome comments I got about the cartoon-a-thon.  Below is a video I with all the toons but you will have to go to mentalhealthcartoons.com to see all the cartoons better. ...   ... Make sure you comment below or e-mail me about the how you like the cartoons.  I’m am making an e-cartoon book of the of the Cartoon-a-thon and will include your comments.   ...   ... I&amp;... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7494-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7494_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:23:04">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/49350/73469/cartoonthon-mental</link><title>Success! Success!! The Cartoon-A-Thon for May 2009 Mental Health Month was a success!</title><description>... Success! Success!! The Cartoon-A-Thon for May 2009 Mental Health Month was a success! ... The purpose of the Cartoon-A-Thon is to use humor and laughter as positive tools in dealing with emotional disturbances which effect many people and families.  ... Mental disorders due to mental Illness or mood disorders and nothing to laugh at, but that does not mean we need to lose our sense of humor. As a “consumer of mental health services” and an amateur cartoonist I was drawing one cartoon a day to help thousands find a smile, even it was for a second.   Soon I will write a post with all the awesome comments I got about the cartoon-a-thon.  Below is a video I with all the toons but you will have to go to mentalhealthcartoons.com to see all the cartoons better. ...   ... Make sure you comment below or e-mail me about the how you like the cartoons.  I’m am making an e-cartoon book of the of the Cartoon-a-thon and will include your comments.   ...   ... I&amp;... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>