<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7496">why IEEE member</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:26:29" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7496-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7496_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:26:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/question/755193/166213</link><title>is there a facility where a family member and a caregiver can go together and receive concentrated therapy for the family member&gt;</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7496-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7496_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:26:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/875999/166412</link><title>if u were with a family member threw a death of another family member.can u being around the person after the death trigger more depresion.</title><description>... i have aunt that lost her brother to cancer.i was with her during the whole time she was his care giver now when we talk it allways goes back to how i was thear in a sad way ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7496-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7496_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:27:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/incontinence/c/45/17365/nosey-family</link><title>Incontinence and Nosey Family Members</title><description>... Do you have one of those know-it-alls in your family? Spending Thanksgiving with my family members got me thinking about this (not that any of them are know-it-alls: wink-wink). Let's face it: we all have that certain family member who knows more than us on every single topic of discussion: and if you don't have that person in your family, then you may want to take a look in the mirror!   I'm going to take a step back for the moment from one of my usual mantras of "don't be so afraid to tell your family about your incontinence - chances are that they'll understand". I very much still stand by this belief, but in many cases the problem goes from thinking they won't understand at all, to realizing that they think they understand far too much. You know what I'm talking about here: that person to whom you finally reveal your leakage, only to hear them go on and on (and on) about their second aunt's best friend's daughter-in-law, Judy.... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7496-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7496_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:27:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/19065/151455/matter</link><title>Mind Over Matter: When Family Members Do Not Believe You Are Sick</title><description>... “I... don’t... feel... so... good...” I say as the room turns black and I start to fall on the kitchen floor.  My mom quickly believed that maybe I really was sick and didn’t just want to avoid going to school that day.  All plans were immediately cancelled.  Mind over matter was not going to cut it. ... Years later when I was diagnosed with multiple sclerosis , my mother didn’t hesitate to believe that something was wrong.  She was there for me and supported me through the process.  There was no instruction to use “mind over matter.”  I’m very fortunate in that those around me do not doubt when I say that I don’t feel wel... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7496-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7496_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:27:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/120/158043/forum-helping</link><title>Family Members Forum: Helping a Loved One</title><description>...   ... Not only was I diagnosed with schizophrenia when I was 22, I'm also the family member of a loved one with a mental health condition.  I can see things from each side of the story. ...   ... The person I love more than life itself is in pain.  You wouldn't be so quick to kiss Bob Whitaker's feet if your loved one didn't take his medication and was depressed, near suicide. ...   ... You might ask, "Where did (my sister, my son-fill in the blank) go and will I ever get her/him back?"  We struggle with the hurt of seeing our loved ones walking around like a shell of their former selves. ...   ... Remember: there's a person inside that shell that is hurting.  He isn't doing this on purpose. ...   ... How can we support them yet get our needs met an... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7496-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7496_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:27:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/bipolar/support-group-1330-143.html</link><title>Bipolar Support Groups: What Are They All About?</title><description>... significance and effectiveness of support groups in bipolar ... disorder treatment plans, meaning the field lacks a prescriptive ... assessment of the role of support groups in treating the ... condition. ... The importance of support groups in my own recovery has been ... clear: Ive been attending support groups for nearly six years ... and regard them as a vital part of my recovery. Ive been ... DBSA Princeton, N.J., ... group that attracts about 20 people one night per week. Our group ... is fairly typical of the 1,000 or so DBSA groups that operate ... throughout the United States, and other groups such as NAMI and the ... Mental Health Association run their patient support groups in a ... broadly similar manner. ... I facilitate our group rather than run it, and there is a clear ... distinction. My job is to watch the clock and make sure everyone ... gets a chance to talk. We do not show up at the group as experts. ... We are patients helping patients. ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7496-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7496_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:28:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/c/question/76444/95440</link><title>~~~~~~~~~~~Member Announcement~~~~~~~~~~~</title><description>... ... ... ... For anyone interested in Forteo for osteoporosis, please see our Member Interview with Taape for further information on this medication.  Here's the link to it. ...   ... Thank you all for your support and participation!!! ...   ... ... ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7496-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7496_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:28:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoporosis/c/question/76444/95455</link><title>»»»»»»»»»»»Second Member Announcement»»»»»»»»»»</title><description>...   ...   ... ... For all members who would like to read about a NATURAL supplement for osteoporosis, please see our members' interview on Strontium Citrate, by Phyllis. ...   ... Many of you ask about natural supplements, since you've had trouble with the conventional medications for osteoporosis. See Phyllis' Interview here on Strontium Citrate and feel free to ask her questions about her experiences with it and how well she is doing!! ...   ... Thanks again to all of you; YOU are what makes us GREAT!! ...   ... »»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»»&amp;... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7496-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7496_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:28:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/menopause/c/727598/112078/men-menopause</link><title>DVD Designed to Educate Men, Family Members, Friends About Menopause</title><description>... ... How does (or did) the man in your life deal with your menopausal symptoms? ... And have you tried to "educate" him about what's going on? ... ... Actually, what surprised me was that I received virtually no response from a group of friends who normally will share a lot of details about what they’re facing. Only Brenda provided a response. She wrote, “Yes I have ‘tried’ to educate my hubby, by talking to him about changes that were going on with my body, mood swings (such as when I lashed out although I couldn't even explain why), etc. I simply asked that he be patient with me and ask that he try to tune in when I become more sensitive at times than others.” ...   ... “On a more serious note it is very important to educate your spouse; that's the least you can do, and hope they will know when you are going through th... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7496-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7496_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:29:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/117332/medication</link><title>Member Medication Review: Geodon</title><description>...   ... It is already Thursday!  How did that happen? ...   ... I received a member request to discuss the medication called Geodon or Generic Name: ZIPRASIDONE - ORAL ...   ... Let me give you a couple of links for finding information about this particular medication. ...   ... We have information on Health Central about Geodon where they say: ...   ... "This medication is used to treat certain mental/mood disorders (schizophrenia or manic/mixed episodes associated with bipolar disorder). It may be used after other medications have not been effective. Ziprasidone is a psychiatric medication (anti-psychotic type) that works by helping to restore the balance of certain natural substances (neurotransmitters) in the brain." ...   ... Here too is the official Geodon web site where you read more about this medication. ...   ... And now it is your turn to talk about your experience with taking Geodon. ...   ...   ... 1. How long did you have to take Geodon before it "kicked in" and you could f... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>