<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7497">shostakovich life</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:29:21" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7497-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7497_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:29:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/1894/9371/good-life-life</link><title>The night life Ain't No good life but it's my life</title><description>... The night life is all I seem to have lately.  I have been sitting here trying to figure out how to download this MSN Messenger.  Man I feel dumb.  It's looks easy but Then when I go to download it ask a question. Do you want to save or Run This program.  Well I kind of want to do both so which one do I select?  I am not very Computer savey as you can tell.  I made a real good friend on this site and we want to be able to talk in real time.  I guess I will wait until I get some advice from him on how to download this thing.  Well My surgery is coming up in 12 hours and 50 minutes. I am not nervous anymore.  I know I am in the Lord's hands.  I just want to get it over with.  This will be my last entry until after surgery and a little recovery time.  Until the next sign on .  Bluesman ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7497-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7497_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:29:46">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/27148/149569/life-surgery</link><title>Life After Back Surgery: Broken and Loose Screws Can Screw Up a Person's Life</title><description>...                       ... Dear Sad, ...   ... Surgeons use hardware such as screws and rods to fix a spine. Unfortunately, this fix can sometimes ruin a life, especially when the screws go askew. These screws are called pedicle screws because they are lodged into the ped... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7497-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7497_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:30:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/142536/bariatric-weight</link><title>My Life after Weight-Loss Surgery is Wonderful - My Bariatric Life</title><description>...   ... My life before weight-loss surgery was a sad life. It was out of control. Much of my spare time was spent eating or shopping. I was a "consume-aholic." I could never have enough food or enough clothes. I was depressed and nothing filled the emptiness inside me. I ran up credit card debt when I should have been saving money for my child's education. ...   ... I bounced around from one psychiatrist to the next, one therapist to the next, one prescription (or more) to the next. I cried a lot. I slept a lot. I lost a lot of jobs. No one would hire me so I had to do temp work. My relationship with... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7497-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7497_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:30:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/144271/living-surgery</link><title>My Bariatric Life Living Life After Weight-Loss Surgery: MBSR is a Tool to Make You Feel More Alive</title><description>...   ... Let's take a moment to reflect... are we joyful in our lives? Were we on "auto-pilot" during the Summer always going, thinking, doing? Do we find ourselves ruminating past resentments or regrets? Are we stuck in a rut of repetitive behaviors saying, "How did I let this happen again?" Looking forward into the holiday season, are we tensed by financial, stability, and other concerns? If so, now's the perfect time to press the reset button! ...   ... As you are living life after weight-loss surgery , you may want to learn a way of being fully in your new life, recognizing the richness and possibility within daily routines, times of difficulty and pain, and times of joy and ease. Using the time-tested practice of mindfulness, root... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7497-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7497_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:30:37">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/670373/149279</link><title>My Sex Life is Ruining my Life, Help!</title><description>...   ... I am hoping that I can get answers and help.  I feel like my sex life is ruining my life.  I rarely want to engage in sexual activity because it causes me so many problems afterward. ...   ... I have not been able to find a birth control that works for me. ... Tried the IUD and it caused so much discharge and foul odor that I had to have it removed after a year or so. ... Tried birth control pills at differing estrogen levels and had severe mood swings and weight gain. ... Tried spermicides which seem to give me yeast afterward. ...   ... I have visited my doctor on several occasions to come up with these different options but I always seem to have issues after sexual intercourse. ...   ... When my fiance ejaculates inside of me, it will cause an odor for maybe one day or two but if I use the spermicide, it turns to yeast. ...   ... If I reach an orgasm, I will also get a foul odor afterwards, for one or two days. ...   ... The answer has been that I have bacterial vaginosis and a course... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7497-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7497_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:31:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/135262/bariatric-living</link><title>My Bariatric Life living life after weight-loss surgery: How Will You Fill-in Your Dash?</title><description>... I came to the realization recently that my life is the dash between the date I was born and the date I die. Do you know what I mean by the dash? It's that short line that will appear on my tombstone and sums up my life(span): 1970 - 20XX. And along that dash are the many moments in time that make up my life. So, I got to thinking, now that I am not spending all those precious moments eating, how will I fill-in my dash? What will I do to make this life, my life, a life that is worth living? Today, I am grateful to God, my healthcare providers, my coaches and mentors, myself, and those who join me on this journey of lifetime weight loss and obesity management. I am able to live my life fully, filling my dash with moments -- each one precious in its own right -- and making a difference in my relationships, my community, my organization, and society. How do I do this? Well, with my relationships I have learned to put the past in the past, to stop holding resentments in the present time fro... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7497-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7497_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:31:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/106296/quantity-quality</link><title>On Death and Dying: Quantity of Life or Quality of Life – Sometimes We Have to Choose</title><description>...   ... I didn't think so. Few of us do. We want to qualify our statements. That is what makes end-of-life decisions so tricky. Few issues are black and white. ...   ... What if we needed to decide with - or for - a loved one whether to, at say age 85, have radical surgery to remove a cancerous breast , followed by chemotherapy and/or radiation which could prolong a life for a few months at best, or let the cancer go and live life a day at a time, until the end? Tough stuff right? But options like these are presented to people on a routine basis. ...   ... All of us should plan ahead so our loved ones know our values and our choices should something dreadful happen to us at a time when we can't make choices for ourselves. Thus, last week's post On Death and Dying: How Do we Talk Parents Out of Denial and Into Getting the Legal Work Do... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7497-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7497_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:31:38">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/151291/life-bariatric</link><title>Sex Life After Bariatric Surgery - My Bariatric Life</title><description>... You have undoubtedly noticed by now that there have been changes since you have had gastric bypass surgery. For one thing, your diet has changed. Your menu has become a high protein, low carbohydrate affair that is rich in fish, lean meat, fruit, and vegetables. Perhaps you have a nutritionist who you consult with. You are working a program of exercise, and you may have a physical trainer who is coaching you. Or perhaps you are more of a "a long walk with your dog" type of person. Regardless of your preference, the benefits of your plan of exercise may have presented by now. You have a healthy look and attitude. You are taking your vitamin supplements and the old lethargy and erratic moods have subsided. You are now more energetic and cheerful. Your physical appearance has changed also. You are more attractive to yourself and to others. People take notice and respond differently to you now. You may or may not be comfortable with the new degree of attention given to you by strangers, but ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7497-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7497_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:31:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/copd/c/91092/46414/smoking-enjoy</link><title>Life’s a Banquet: Quit Smoking and Enjoy!</title><description>... This mental-health-advocacy recovery organization is a marvelous example of the success of and need for alternatives/options in recovery, whether from substance-abuse addictive disorders or mental-health issues. ... This annual award, the "James Christopher Award," which I'm honored and pleased to present each year, was named after me by the SHARE! Organization, for deserving recipient(s) who've championed and exemplified alternatives in their respective recovery fields. SHARE! created this award and they determine who is to receive it each year. ... Although I'm proud to have an award named after me, I'm life-and-death proud of my own recovery from booze addiction (1978) and from cigarette addiction (1993). ... Sadly, at the break, just outside the hotel, I anticipate smokers, some who are prominent ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7497-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7497_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:32:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/sara-nash-comics-baltimore-467612-5.html</link><title>Life in the New Normal</title><description>... Read the full text of Life in the New Normal and leave a comment! See All of Sara's Baltimore Comics Visit the Single Gal's Guide to Rheumatoid Arthritis ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>