<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7498">syria chemical weapons</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:32:28" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7498-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7498_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:32:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/21949/158896/huperzine</link><title>Huperzine A: An All-Natural Secret Weapon Against Brain Aging</title><description>... According to Chinese researchers, huperzine A helps people with Alzheimer’s and other degenerative brain disorders by promoting nerve cell growth, enabling brain cells to better communicate.(1)  ... Another important benefit of huperzine A is protecting acetylcholine, one of your most important neurotransmitters from chemical breakdown in the brain.  Because acetylcholine is a key player in memory function and learning,  dwindling levels are a major contributor to Alzheimer’s and other dementias. ... There are numerous pharmaceutical drugs on the market that inhibit the breakdown of acetylcholine.  Huperzine A has been shown to work as well or better than many of these expensive drugs without the common side effects.  ... Here’s an example.  Studies have shown that compared to ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7498-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7498_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:32:47">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/276918/155178/satiety-weight</link><title>The Satiety Index: A New Weight-Loss Weapon</title><description>...   ... The satiety index, developed by Susanna Holt, PhD, compares popular foods that are portioned at 240 calories and then ranks them with how they compare to a slice of white bread which ranks at 100. Comparatively, oatmeal ranks at 209, a donut at 68, and French fries at 116. The strategy then becomes to help people consume fewer calories and lose weight while eating appropriate meals and not going hungry. The Flavor Point Diet It is speculated that a number of different flavors in one meal over stimulates the appetite center of the brain and therefore people tend to overeat before feeling full. Sensory specific satiety promotes a feeling of fullness and halts eating when the flavors on our ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7498-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7498_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:33:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/question/405637/145737</link><title>I have been breaking out with hives at work now for 3 weeks. I believe it is a chemical vapor. How do you test for chemical exposure</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7498-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7498_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:33:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/293600/131656</link><title>If "depression is caused by a chemical imbalance in the brain" then why aren't the levels of the chemicals, in the brain, measured and, targeted, medications used to restore proper balance?</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7498-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7498_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:33:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-cancer/c/question/861215/143169</link><title>I'm wondering about the chemical effect of sunscreens on our bodies? Sunscreens help block UVA, but they introduce chemicals into our bodies.</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7498-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7498_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:33:59">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/119538/loved-possession</link><title>Guns and Alzheimers Don't Mix: Removing Weapons from Loved Ones' Possession</title><description>...     Hunting season is right around the corner – which brings me to one of the topics I had never considered in relation to caregiving for a loved one with Alzheimer’s.  Last year, a HealthCentral.com Alzheimer’s community member asked about how to deal with her father’s gun collection. Her father, who has Alzheimer’s, would get very angry when the family would address the possibility of removing the weapons or putting them in the gun safe. Instead, the father would hide the guns around the house. And needless to say, the weapons made the family feel unsafe.     It turns out that this issue is not unique.  A recent New York Times story by Dale Russakoff described how a 90-year-old widow who had mild Alzheimer’s refused her son’s request to give up a loaded .38-caliber handgun that she had in kept in her dresser at her retirement community. Russakoff noted that a 2004 National Firearms Survey found that mo... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7498-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7498_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:34:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/896502/103129/diabetes</link><title>Diet, Exercise Are Key Weapons in Fight Against Diabetes</title><description>... My father struggles with his weight and has had a tendency toward Type 2 diabetes . He was on medication to control diabetes in the 1970s, but managed to lose weight and get control of his health. Yet during the past few years the number on the blood glucose test inched higher (as well as the numbers on the scale) to the point where Dad was considered pre-diabetic. In the past year, Dad’s started watching his food choices and has trimmed his weight by 20 pounds. ... It turns out that, unfortunately, Dad isn’t alone in battling diabetes. Approximately 80 million Americans either have diabetes or are in the process of developing the disease. Because of its prevalence, $174 billion is spent in the United States for treatment.  And it’s believed that 95 percent of diabetes cases are Type 2 diabetes, which is a result of obesity in many cases. This prevalence, especially since the disease has struck so close to home, caused me to watch me Oprah Winfrey’s show about ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7498-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7498_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:34:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/159545/nutrition-weapon-alzheimer</link><title>Nutrition One Weapon to Reduce Risk of Alzheimer’s</title><description>...   ... While drug studies are apt to get the lion’s share of publicity, not all research has focused on drug development. Some researchers have studied what nutrition from food and supplements can do to ward off Alzheimer’s disease. Naturally, as is in the case with most research, there is disagreement among investigators. Some scientists argue against the theory that lifestyle changes may affect our Alzheimer’s risk, while others champion their own study results showing that lifestyle changes may prevent or reverse the disease. ...   ... Even though researchers may disagree about proof - or lack there... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7498-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7498_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:34:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/genital-herpes/c/65036/53150/acyclovir</link><title>Herpes Weapons: Safe Sex, Acyclovir and a Extra Dose of Honesty</title><description>... ... The reality is that the only tools currently available for protecting oneself are (a) using a condom every time (b) not having any kind of sexual acitvity in the face of a frank outbreak (c) having your partner take acyclovir if he (she) has herpes (d) knowing as much of your partner's sexual history as you can.  The odds for single heterosexual and homosexual individuals is that you will encounter romantic partners with the disea... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7498-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7498_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:34:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/5868/15561/secret-weapon</link><title>My Secret Weapon for Battling Insulin Resistance</title><description>... Pregnancy Tracker: 29 weeks, 3 days Size of the Baby: Head to toe length is about 16 inches Biggest Obstacle: Getting my daily exercise.   Over the past couple weeks I've seen my insulin needs creep up.   I've been eating a consistent number of carbohydrates for my meals and snacks. My breakfast has been the same each day for at least two months: one slice high fiber wheat bread with egg salad for 15 carbs. This eating schedule allows me to track my insulin needs quite precisely. For several weeks my breakfast required 1.5 units of insulin. Then, just a couple weeks ago, that stopped working.   This is my adversary: insulin resistance.   During these days of increasing insulin needs, I have battled a few high numbers. Since I'm testing just about every hour, I haven't run into many numbers over 200 mg/dl. However, I've had a few instances where I've hovered around 170-180 mg/dl for several hours. Sometimes it s... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>