<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7499">gold price</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:35:13" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7499-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7499_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:35:14">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/110/90314/yellow-stuff</link><title>8 Types of Splenda or Sucralose for Diabetics and Prices of these Yellow Sugars</title><description>... ... On a recent shopping expedition, my wife Steph mentioned that she saw several brands of sucralose available on the shelves of the local supermarket. Several questions immediately come to mind: ... ... * Do the other brands of sucralose contain the same stuff as Splenda? * Do they taste the same as Splenda? * Are they cheaper than Spenda? ... ... Well, first a websearch. I found the following: ... ... Splenda is sold by McNeil Nutritionals, LLC in the USA and Canada. ... ... Tate &amp; Lyle , based in the UK, also sells Splenda brand of sucralose , but from their websites, it's difficult to identify in which ountries they have the rights to the Splenda name. ... ... Fusion Nutraceuticals, based in Ireland, has a brand called SucraPLUS "available on the shelves of major supermarkets by sum... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7499-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7499_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:35:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/headache-specialists/louisiana-39918-5.html</link><title>Richard H. Gold, M.D. - Louisiana Migraine and Headache Specialists</title><description>... Doctor: Richard H. Gold, M.D. Clinic/Facility: Louisiana Headache Center   Address: 7777 Hennessy Blvd Ste 709 Baton Rouge, LA 70808 Telephone: 225-769-7200 Recommendation: Patient Feedback ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7499-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7499_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:36:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/1443/36969/olympic-gold-medallist</link><title>The Many Faces of ADHD: Michael Phelps, Olympic Gold Medalist</title><description>...   ... Michael Phelps has ADHD. He was diagnosed at the age of 9 years old. Michael's mother, in an interview for WJZ in Baltimore MD., discussed his diagnosis and some of the difficulties he has overcome in his life. Michael was hyperactive as a child, according to his mother he "never sat still, never closed his mouth, was always asking questions, always jumping from one thing to another." ...   ... Although he started medication and behavior modification, he stopped medication by age 11 and instead ADHD symptoms we... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7499-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7499_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:36:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/news/new-gold-standard-in-hip-replacement</link><title>New Gold Standard in Hip Replacement</title><description>... Study, time, and experience has brought a new gold standard in total hip replacements (THRs). Cemented femoral implants are being replaced with uncemented components. The femoral component consists of the round head of the femur (thighbone) with a long, tapered stem that sets down into the femur. Why the switch? Because results of long-term studies show increased rates of loosening over time in cemented stems. Thirty years of study at the Indian Research Foundation have resulted in data collected on 6,533 THRs. Uncemented stem implants outperformed cemented stems. There were no cases of loosening for the uncemented group. This 100 per cent survivorship means there was excellent biologic fixation of the implant in the bone. The authors conclude uncemented stems are the first choice for most patients. This includes young or older patients with good or bad bone. The shape (straight or crooked) or the condition of the femur doesn't seem to matter. Patients with hip fracture or replacements... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7499-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7499_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:36:31">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/215658/155889/standard</link><title>Tough Mudder: The Gold-Standard of Mud Runs</title><description>...   ... This past weekend I tackled the Tough Mudder: Mid-Atlantic in Frederick, Maryland.  Days later, I am sore in places I never knew I could be sore.  (My rib cage?  The palms of my hands?) ...   ... Last summer, I took on the Spartan Sprint, a 5k run with 18 obstacles.  It kicked my butt .  But since then I changed my training – it takes a lot more than just running to master one of these courses, I've learned – and I had a better idea of what to expect.  With that in mind, I signed up for the Tough Mudder, the 10+ mile gold-standard of mud runs. ...   ... On the bright side, I learned that supposedly 24,000 people would be embarking on the challenge with me, so I wouldn’t be suffering alone. Looking around the staging area, I was certainly not the caliber of athlete of some of the participants; on the other hand, I was definitely in better shape than quite a few as well.  ... &amp;... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7499-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7499_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:36:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/9009/11927/cells-gold</link><title>Finding breast cancer cells: Precious as gold</title><description>... Researchers at Purdue University have found tiny particles of gold to be capable of identifying marker proteins on breast cancer cells, a tool that may soon play a critical role in the early detection and monitoring of breast cancer .   The gold nanoparticles created by the research team would provide technology about three times cheaper than the most common current method of identifying such proteins, and would provide substantially increased quality and quantity of data.   More on this from EurekAlert!: http://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2007-07/pu-gnm073107.php   Best of health, Maria    Maria Gifford Community Moderator MyBreastCancerNetwork.com ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7499-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7499_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:37:05">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/96/37349/world-picky-eater</link><title>Going for the Gold: World Class Picky Eater</title><description>...   ... Rebecca: World Class Picky Eater ...   ... You may have heard that my daughter Rebecca used to be a World Famous Picky Eater . She never competed in any events but I am sure she would have been in the top 3 and could have achieved Gold Medal status with little effort. ...   ... Here is the breakfast of my Gold Medal level picky eater at age four: ...   ... Breakfast: ... ¼ cup dry cereal ... 4 ounces watered down apple juice ...   ... Lunch: ... ½ ham and mayo sandwich on wheat bread ... 4 ounces of watered down apple juice ...   ... Dinner: ... 2 Tbsp. chicken ... 3 Tbsp. rice ... water ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7499-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7499_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:37:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/ibd/c/17824/36322/disease-carrie-johnson</link><title>Going for Gold with Crohn's Disease: Meet Carrie Johnson</title><description>...   ... Carrie's Crohn's symptoms began while she was training for the Athens Olympic Games in 2004. While she was training for the Games, Carrie began suffering from extreme fatigue, severe weight loss and anemia . At the time, Carrie was unable to hold down food, and lost 20 pounds in 30 days. Maintaining the energy level needed for training as a world class athlete was almost impossible. Carrie was soon diagnosed with Crohn's disease, and fortunately her doctors were able to get her condition under control in time for her to compete in the 2004 Olympics. She finished in tenth place, the highest ever for a U.S. kayaker. ...   ... Carrie is a proud advocate for people living with Crohn's disease. She is actively involved in the CrohnsAndMe website... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7499-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7499_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:37:40">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/1522/46906/inspection</link><title>Canadian Food Inspection Agency Recalls Sherwood Brands Gold Milk Chocolate Coins</title><description>...   ... The recall is limited to Canada. The contaminated candy did not make it into US or other foreign markets. ...   ... You can read more about the recall at the CFIA website: http://www.inspection.gc.ca/english/corpaffr/recarapp/2008/20081008e.shtml ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7499-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7499_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:37:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/31703/28205/gold-stars</link><title>gold stars</title><description>... so im awake (at 1am) and checking yahoo mail (which is not often used) and i see the responses and posts and its like a wave of relief cause the weekend was filled with its fair amount of crying (again).. for little things (again).. because the crying was so bad when i was just diagnosed and my family really took strian i try not to cry around them but this weekend i just couldnt hide it... my two year old (gorgeous) nephew wouldnt stop chatting to me and eventually announced to the world that nita was in tears (again).. and  surprisingly the guilt wa snot foremost but gratitude that my mom and brother sat with me for a while.. theres gold stars everywhere ..and im 30.. on my diary.. on my pc.. on pics.. on post its.. but its strangely comforting.. as if im winning something.. or worth something ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>