<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7501">criquet miler</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:41:21" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7501-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7501_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:41:22">http://www.healthcentral.com/multiple-sclerosis/c/6191/41334/counting</link><title>Ten days and counting</title><description>...   ... Even though it hurts (shin splints and sore feet), I try to stay positive, for a number of reasons: ...   ... One, I am an ambassador (self appointed) of the MS Society. I train with my Challenge Walk t-shirts. So I try to be extra friendly so people (if they even notice my t-shirt) will think the MS Society is a nice society. I actually try to wear the t-shirts as advertisement of the event for all of the events I do. I wear my Walk-MS shirt in the winter right up until April when we have our Walk. Then I switch to my Bike-MS t-shirts until the... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7501-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7501_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:41:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/chronic-pain/c/36562/16785/nerve-damage</link><title>Nerve damage from arthroscopic surgery?</title><description>... I recently had surgery Sept. 20th to repair a tear in my meniscus. After the surgery I developed a cyst on the inside, back of my knee which was pressing against the ligaments making it difficult to straighten my leg. My doctor went in on Nov. 1, 2007 a second time arthroscopically to allow it to drain which he did successfully. After the surgery I noticed I had no feeling above my inside ankle bone that goes down to the arch of my foot. I also get a feeling of an electrically charged wire brush electrical shock from my ankle area up towards the area the cyst was. Also, if I touch the area around my knee where the cyst was, I can feel it down arounf my ankle.  I'm told that it is going to take time for the nerves to settle down and get back to normal. Does anyone have any experience with this as a doctor or patient? If so, please give me some words of encouragement. I'm a former 4 minute miler that just would like to have the hope to run again. Thanks for your help i... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7501-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7501_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:41:58">http://www.healthcentral.com/ency/408/001344prv.html</link><title>Congenital syphilis prevention</title><description>... Alternative Names ... ... ... Congenital lues; Fetal syphilis ... ... ... Prevention ... ... Safer sexual practices may help prevent syphilis. If you suspect you have a sexually transmitted disease such as syphilis, seek medical attention immediately to avoid complications like infecting your baby during pregnancy or birth. ... Prenatal care is very important. A routine blood test for syphilis is done during pregnancy. This identifies infected mothers and allows them to be treated to reduce the risks to the infant and themselves. Infants born to infected mothers who received proper penicillin treatment during pregnancy are at minimal risk for congenital syphilis. ... ... References ... ... Wolff T, Shelton E, Sessions C, Miler T. Screening for syphilis infection in pregnant women: Evidence for the U.S. Preventive Services Task Force Reaffirmation Recommendation Statement. Ann Intern Med . 2009;150:710-716. ... Workowski KA, Berman SM. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. Congenital syphilis. Se... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7501-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7501_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:42:16">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabeteens/c/753408/86598/reflections</link><title>Reflections from a Type 1 Athlete</title><description>...   ... There is no owner's manual for the body.  An endocrinologist cannot prescribe an exact amount of insulin that will, over twenty-four hours, ensure perfect blood sugar levels, just as a coach cannot guarantee that his program is the best for my goals.  Both having diabetes and training are unique to the individual; no two people can count on the sam... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7501-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7501_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:42:29">http://www.healthcentral.com/diet-exercise/c/3801/53935/working-cold</link><title>Working Out in the Cold</title><description>...   ... Firstly, you have to be a little smart about this. There is cold, and then there is COLD. One time I ran a five mile race in February aptly titled the "Frostbite 5 Miler". On race day, it was damp, a little snowy, and 19° F. Surprisingly, a lot of people showed up to that one. Luckily there was minimal wind. That's the first point. Wind is a killer. They don't call it the wind chill factor for nothing. If given a choice about whether I'd want it to be 20°F with no wind, or whether I'd want it to be 30° F but with a wind chill of 20°F, I'd choose the former. Sometimes it's so cold, it's downright dangerous. You folks who live in the upper Mid-West or Northern Plains know what I'm talking about. As I write this... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7501-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7501_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:42:50">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/9993/10427/teach-thing</link><title>Exercise for Diabetics</title><description>... My husband is my inspiration and mentor for fitness. We’ve been together 16 years, and he knows me (sometimes better than I care to admit! ).  Mike is like a metronome, getting up everyday and working out first thing, either running or hitting the gym. When he worked at Nike, he ran every day first thing in the morning, and then would run with his office mates at lunch and sometimes at the end of the day he would run another 10-miler.   It’s no surprise that he has a 2:18 marathon PR!  ( Related Story : Study finds exercise alone makes greater improvement than diet and medicine) For me, running needs to be multifaceted enjoyment. I emotionally feel good, my body feels good and my physical stamina gets stronger, thus my immune system can handle more stresses. And running has always been good at getting rid of the cobwebs in my mind! I’ve written some great shareposts on my run -- I simply wish I could remember them when I get home! But, at age 42, I’m beginnin... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7501-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7501_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:43:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/9993/18552/gluten-free</link><title>Going Gluten Free</title><description>...   A surprising thing happened this past year: I lost my seemingly endless supply of energy!   In May, I started to feel tired all the time. My endocrinologist checked my thyroid level and it came back at 3. That’s not out of range, but she said it was slightly low and we would keep checking.   Throughout the summer, my mind felt foggy, and running, my usual form of exercise, became increasingly harder to do. By 4 in the afternoon my energy would bottom out, and I found myself drinking coffee almost every afternoon to find something to cling to for energy!   To top it off, I woke up faithfully every night, just enough to disturb my sleep, and then I would roll over and try to find my dreams again. By October I was incapable of focusing at all and my body seemed so out of sync.   What was happening? Depression? Too much stress?     My acupuncturist suggested a saliva test. While I agree with MDs that saliva is very inconsistent, I figured... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7501-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7501_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:43:21">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/9993/127818/shareposts-2010</link><title>Best Health Central posts from 2010.</title><description>... The start of a new year can be filled with hope, but sometimes the strength of our convictions comes from what we know.   In order to change patterns and to think differently, we should look to the past!   ...   ... This year has been one that opened many new opportunities for me.   It has been a year of learning more about diabetes then I ever imagined I would care to know!   The best part has been opening my arms wide and letting friends into the interesting world of diabetes and educating them.   But it also has been a two way street!   ...   ... This year fostered my reaching out to fellow type 2 experts, who are so knowledgeable on the relationship with diabetes, food, exercise that their knowledge surpasses most of my phd sports physiology friends!   ...   ... The diversity of information from this group of Amylia, Bill, David, Fran, Gretchen, John, Joan (Verdungal), Kelsey, Beth and Kerri has educated and entertained me all year!   So I have decided, o... ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>