<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7502">baby todler snowsuit</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:43:38" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7502-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7502_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:43:39">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/96/127241/awake-night-baby</link><title>Awake Last Night With Your Baby?</title><description>...   ... Were you awake last night with your baby? Feel exhausted from multiple trips to the crib? Are you awake night after night? Then you already know that the nights are very long this time of year. The Winter Solstice just passed on the night of a total lunar eclipse, giving us the darkest day in 372 years according to NBC Nightly News with Brian Williams. The last time this occurred was in 1638. Now that is a long night and a lot of darkness to deal with! ...   ... I was on the night shift for a long, long time with my baby. Her Gastroesophageal reflux symptoms were worse at night, causing frequent night waking, sometimes every hour, night after night. She was fussy and exhausted from the pain and discomfort. I was exhausted from the moment I woke up until the moment I fell asleep. My brain didn’t work very well and I was forgetful and in a fog most of the time. It was a like a case of “new mother’s brain fog” but it lasted much longer. When she woke up at ni... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7502-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7502_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:43:54">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/881403/82581</link><title>i lost my baby due to severe asphyxia is this will happen to my next baby</title><description>... i delivered a boy baby thorugh vagina on october 2, 2008. he doesnt cry unfortunately i lost my baby after 48 hours due to severe asphexia and infection in the lungs of the baby. now i am 12weeks pregnant  there is any chance for this baby to get affected by the same problem. what are all the things i have to do to get a healthy baby.  ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7502-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7502_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:44:09">http://www.healthcentral.com/sleep-disorders/c/5954/39353/rockabye</link><title>Rockabye Baby - Baby Makes Three</title><description>... Babies do tend to be the center of attention, at least for the first ... few months. But my! Doesn't the little one sleep a lot? ...   ... For the first three to four months, babies tend to sleep sixteen to ... eighteen hours a day, but that sleep seems to come in spurts - sleep ... two or three hours - wake up for a feeding, or a diaper change or just ... because. And sometimes it's not easy to get the little one back to ... sleep. ...   ... Babies have more periods of light sleep than do adults. Often while ... passing from deep sleep to light sleep, baby will awaken, and won't ... know how to get back to sleep. This is when the fussing starts, the ... need to be held and cuddled and rocked. ...   ... Just like adults, sleep needs vary from baby to baby, and so do ... sleep patterns. Every child is different, and you will have to adjust ... your sleep patterns to match baby's. ...   ... By the time baby is six months old, daytime sleep should have ... decreased to three or... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7502-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7502_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:44:28">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/938507/146559/pediatrician</link><title>A Day in the Life of a Refluxing Baby: Helping your pediatrician understand how your baby feels.</title><description>... When my daughter was little, she was a miserable baby most of the time. She had pretty significant reflux and could literally soak me to my underwear when she spit up. Despite all this she was gaining weight, growing taller and had no respiratory issues. ...   ... She cried most of the time, only slept when upright and needed to be held almost constantly. ... But, when I would go to the pediatrician’s office she tended to be on her best behavior. Being a new Mom, I had a hard time “complaining” about her behavior. Her doctor would do her measurements and assure me that the spit up was okay as long as she was growing and not having problems breathing. So we went on and on. Eventually she wound up on meds and felt much better. ...   ... Three years later, her middle brother was born. He was my best refluxing baby but he was also good at showing his misery at the doctors. In fact, at a month of age, she told me “even if I didn’t know the family history, I would recom... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7502-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7502_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:44:45">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/92183/50082/baby-product</link><title>Since Baby is a Sexual Product – Here’s Baby Info</title><description>... ... (1) According to a study this year (American journal of Public Health/CDC study) girls who engaged in 70-300 minutes of physical activity (through Phys.Ed classes) scored consistently higher than kids who had less than 35 minutes of PE/week. This is especially important since many girls in high school typically do less and less physical activity because they don't like to sweat, mess their makeup AND they no longer find it "cool." ... (2) It may not be a good idea to play feeding games with your infants and young childrens - you know those games where the "airplane (spoon) is coming in for a landing (in your mouth)." If you force a child to eat, they actually can become fussy eaters and ultimately weigh less than they should, as they begin to associate forced feedings with unpleasant experiences. That can make mom more anxious and determ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7502-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7502_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:45:01">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/701941/85745/protected</link><title>Acid Reflux in Baby: Keeping Your Baby Protected</title><description>...   ... Acid reflux, which is also termed as gastroesophageal reflux, is one of the most frequent problems among infants. Babies with acid reflux often suffer from a range of conditions, from a mild degree to a severe one, such as recurrent spitting up, abdominal pain, and night waking. ...   ... This discussion would be more comprehensive with the understanding of the physiological or the mechanical aspect of the condition. The body has a band of muscle in a circular structure that is called the lower esophageal sphincter. This muscle detaches the esophagus from the stomach. When food comes into the stomach, it closes so as to prevent the stomach acids and contents from backing up into the esophagus or regurgitating. But in the case of some babies, the lower esophageal sphincter has grown immature. As such, the partially digested food and digestive acids are allowed to be refluxed. This condition causes irritation in the esophagus lining w... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7502-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7502_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:45:23">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/70966/158501/planning-baby</link><title>Family Planning When Your First Baby was a Reflux Baby</title><description>... In my mid-20s we had our first daughter Melina.  She was a blessing and a JOY.  She was also a horrible refluxer.  We immediately began acid reflux boot camp as we started our journey on the reflux roller coaster.  It was hard, it was scary and it often gives parents pause when considering having more children. While it is not possible to predict which children will or will not have reflux as infants there are things you can do to limit the chance of it occurring.  Most of these changes involve making sure you are healthy before you get pregnant and that you have a healthy pregnancy.  This is because infants who are born prematurely or who have certain birth defects also have a higher percentage of acid reflux. Even the perfect pregnancy and healthiest mama can still have an infant with reflux.  There does seem to be a genetic component as well.  This is why many second time parents are nervous if their first baby was a refluxer. All I can tell y... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7502-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7502_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:45:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/question/401995/159530</link><title>Need advice on baby that will only eat in sleep and refuses baby food...</title><description>...   ... He has been taking Axid since he was a newborn.... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7502-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7502_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:46:02">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/77471/131214</link><title>Is It Ok To Swallow Sperm While Pregnant, and what happens when im pregnant and the babys father ejaculates inside of me? is it ok for the baby?</title><description>... Is It Ok To Swallow Sperm While Pregnant, and what happens when im pregnant and the babys father ejaculates inside of me? is it ok for the baby? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7502-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7502_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:46:20">http://www.healthcentral.com/genital-herpes/c/question/766298/89653</link><title>if i have hsv 1 and i am going to have a baby what is the chance the baby will have it.</title><description>... My son has herpies stage 1 and he told me that he and his girlfriend is having a babe ... will the baby be born with it too. ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>