<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7504">leiden schools</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:47:42" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7504-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7504_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:47:43">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/651280/40037/personnel</link><title>Diabetes Management at School- Working with School Officials</title><description>...   ... Ideally, a school nurse will be available full time on campus. In many circumstances, this is not alwa... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7504-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7504_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:48:06">http://www.healthcentral.com/allergy/c/3387/14999/back-school-child</link><title>Back to School: Working with Your School Nurse/Staff to Keep Your Child Healthy</title><description>... ... First, open the lines of communication. It's a good idea to talk with your child's teacher and the school nurse at the beginning of every school year to make sure they know about your child's allergies. A written plan would be helpful in making sure everyone is on the same page. ... ... You can read about Asthma Action Plans . There's no reason why you couldn't develop an Allergy Action Plan for your child that would be along the same lines, spelling out your child's allergy triggers, usual symptoms of an impending allergy attack and how to respond to keep things from getting worse. ... ... Second, know your child's rights in regard to "right to carry" laws for your region. Most states have laws that specify a child's right to carry life-saving allergy and asthma ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7504-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7504_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:48:24">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/18/45535/avoidance-refusal</link><title>School Avoidance/School Refusal Part One</title><description>... Last week my son wanted to play hooky from kindergarten. As I was getting him ready for school, he said, "Mommy, my stomach hurts," trying to look as pathetic as possible. I had a feeling that the problem wasn't his stomach, but might have been connected with the fact that my husband was in the hospital recovering from shoulder replacement surgery. Whenever one of us is ill, Lawrence doesn't like being separated from us. Or perhaps the wish to continue playing "Lego Star Wars" on the Wii.  ... Unfortunately, the timing was not great. Although I believe in the occasional day of hooky for kids (and for adults), I thought that it was a little too soon in the school year to have one. Also, I couldn't miss work. When you work in the classroom scheduling department of a large university, the first three weeks are insane. My husband works from home, so normally Lawrence being sick or wanting a day off wouldn't be an issue, but as he was in the hospital, well, it would be up to my parents.&amp;n... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7504-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7504_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:48:42">http://www.healthcentral.com/migraine/c/question/67363/43703</link><title>My friend is a freshman in high school. He only gets migranes at school. Could it be mental?</title><description>... Also sometimes happens before school on school days while still at home. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7504-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7504_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:48:56">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/children-41105-5.html</link><title>Summertime Reading</title><description>... Many parents may cringe at the idea of forcing their child to complete work over the summer (who can blame them, children with ADHD often require so much monitoring from parents during the school year, parents need a summer break as much as children.)   But a summer reading program doesn’t have to be about completing work or be formal.  Parents can develop a program that fits into their lifestyle, their summer plans, their child’s interests and their daily schedule. By making the reading program personalized to the needs of your child, you will help to create successes and increase their self-esteem as well.  Most children will benefit from as little as 15 to 30 minutes of reading per day.  If your child has problems with reading comprehension you can add in writing a sentence or paragraph about what they have read, or having them give you an oral summary.  Younger children can draw pictures or cut pictures from magazines to create a collage o... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7504-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7504_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:49:13">http://www.healthcentral.com/osteoarthritis/eorthopod/faq/swimmer-school-college-1544</link><title>I was always a swimmer through grade school, high school, and college.</title><description>... I was always a swimmer through grade school, high school, and college. I probably should have kept it up because now I need a hip replacement. The exercise would have been good for me. Oh well. What do the experts say about swimming after a hip replacement? How soon can I start? With the recent effort to reduce the length of hospital stays, physical therapists are exploring the most effective ways to treat orthopedic patients. The standard rehab program after hip or knee joint replacement includes a mix of exercises to improve circulation and to prevent blood clots and other complications. Other goals include improving motion, strength, and function (especially walking). Aquatic therapy after hip replacement may fill the bill nicely. Aquatic (pool) therapy is defined as physical therapy that is performed in the water. There are good reasons to consider using aquatic therapy after joint replacement. Aquatic therapy uses the resistance of water instead of weights. With the reduced load pr... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7504-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7504_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:49:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/c/849319/82061/school-phobia-afraid</link><title>School Phobia: What to do when your child is afraid to go to school</title><description>...   ... Unfortunately this is not an issue which gets much understanding from the public or from school personnel.  I viewed one forum which discussed school phobia where a principal's advice was for the parent and child dealing with school phobia to "just suck it up."  For the child who has this, i... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7504-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7504_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:49:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/skin-care/c/1443/155348/school-psoriasis</link><title>Back to School: Helping Your Child Cope with Psoriasis at School</title><description>... The following are some tips for parents to help their child during the upcoming school year: ... ... If your child has psoriasis , you probably are familiar with the physical symptoms as well as how the skin condition impacts your child emotionally. But teachers and other school personnel may not be. Print out some basic information on psoriasis to share with your child’s teacher. You may also want to set up a meeting within the first week or so of school to talk privately with the teacher and explain what... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7504-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7504_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:50:07">http://www.healthcentral.com/adhd/back-to-school-260678.html</link><title>Quiz: Back to School with ADHD</title><description>... 260 ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7504-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7504_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:50:25">http://www.healthcentral.com/anxiety/c/question/934237/88483</link><title>Hello, I hope you can help. My daughter has just started senior school but is scared of school.</title><description>...   ... Miss Taylor ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>