<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7505">ethnic myanmar</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:50:46" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7505-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7505_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:50:48">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/57548/56301/experience</link><title>Ethnicity and the Experience of Alzheimer's Disease</title><description>...   ... We know that to have the best social, welfare and healthcare provision you have to have a broad knowledge of the people you are targeting. For example, you have to understand their social identity, economic disadvantage, their household and neighborhood structures, education and their understanding of health. You have to appreciate how people with health issues seek help and understand the barriers that people of color face when they look for help and support. Only then can you plan and put into place the most effective health care provision. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7505-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7505_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:51:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/62/15373/elder-care-ethnic</link><title>How Elder Care is Recognizing Ethnic Backgrounds</title><description>... An article in The San Antonio Express-News, titled "Adult day care booming in South Texas: Culture, demographics driving industry," brings to light a whole new attitude toward our aging and elders. This article speaks to the Latino culture and talks about the fierce competition among adult day care centers that cater to them.   I have my computer set to send me alerts on many elder care subjects. Lately, I've been getting articles directed toward the aging population of Japan, China, India and even Ireland. Obviously, it's not just the United States and Canada that are mulling over their aging populations and how best to care for our elders.   I don't know that we are all so different. The San Antonio Express-News article mentions the close ties that Latinos have with their elders; it speaks of the guilt the families feel about putting their elders "in a home." Is that really so different that the "white bread" culture of the high plain... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7505-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7505_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:51:17">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/57548/116214/minorities</link><title>Elder Abuse in Ethnic Minorities</title><description>... Elder abuse is a hidden crime. Elder abuse in ethnic minorities presents certain difficulties for social services and other agencies. In this sharepost I want to introduce the subject and how different cultural and ethnic differences impact on people being abused. Professional caregivers, social service agencies have to be aware to be able to meet the needs of this group of elders. ...   ... Elder abuse crosses racial, ethnic, gender, class, economic and minority group divides. In a recent sharepost written by Carol Bradley Bursack, she reported on a study from the University of California that found nearly half of Alzheimer's patients were abused. It is a shocking and surprising statistic that does not identify race, ethnicity, or culture, yet it exists in all societies as far as we know. Fraud, sexual assault, emotional abuse, neglect, violations of personal rights, physical abuse probably all happen in your own community. ...   ... I recognise the huge diversity within and across dif... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7505-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7505_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:51:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/introduction-1965-108.html</link><title>Breast Cancer Risk Factors: Ethnicity, Race, Genes, and Family History</title><description>... Definition Breast cancer is a cancer that starts in the tissues of the breast. There are two main types of breast cancer: Ductal carcinoma starts in the tubes (ducts) that move milk from the breast to the nipple. Most breast cancers are of this type. Lobular carcinoma starts in the parts of the breast, called lobules, that produce milk. In rare cases, breast cancer can start in other areas of the breast. Breast cancer may be invasive or noninvasive. Invasive means it has spread from the milk duct or lobule to other tissues in the breast. Noninvasive means it has not yet invaded other breast tissue. Noninvasive breast cancer is called "in situ." Ductal carcinoma in situ (DCIS), or intraductal carcinoma, is breast cancer in the lining of the milk ducts that has not yet invaded nearby tissues. It may progress to invasive cancer if untreated. Lobular carcinoma in situ (LCIS) is a marker for an increased risk of invasive cancer in the same or both breasts. Many breast cancers are sensitive to the ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7505-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7505_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:51:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/r/breast-cancer/article/race-ethnicity-3991</link><title>Race/Ethnicity</title><description>... White women are slightly more likely to develop breast cancer than African American, Hispanic, and Asian women. But African American women are more likely to develop more aggressive, more advanced-stage breast cancer that is diagnosed at a young age. African American women are also more likely to die from breast cancer. Some of these differences in outcomes may be due to less access to mammography and lower quality medical care, as well as various lifestyle patterns (eating habits and weight issues for example) that are more common in some ethnic groups than in others. These factors can be changed and improved. ... Still, triple-negative breast cancer, which is more aggressive than other types, is more common in African American women. Triple-negative breast cancer is estrogen-receptor-negative, progesterone-receptor-negative, and HER2-negative. New treatments for triple-negative breast cancer are being studied in clinical trials. But African American women are under-represented in clinic... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7505-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7505_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:52:03">http://www.healthcentral.com/diabetes/c/110/61408/diabetes-children</link><title>Diabetes in U.S. Children by 5 Major Ethnicities: Some Highest Rates in World</title><description>...   ... The authors describe the study's objective as "to describe childhood diabetes [in children and teenagers less than age 20] as it occurs among the five major race and ethnic groups in the U.S." They evaluated over 9000 kids with type 1 diabetes and almost 1600 with type 2 during the period 2001-2005. ... ... In non-Hispanic white youth, they found that the incidence of type 1 diabetes is "one of the highest in the world" and added "while type 2 diabetes is still relatively rare, rates are several-fold higher than those reported by European countries." ... ... In Hispanic American youth, they noted that type 1 diabetes was more common than type 2 diabetes. The incidence of type 2 diabetes for girls aged 10-14... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7505-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7505_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:52:18">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/c/question/671110/81479</link><title>Ethnic specific Body Mass Index Guidelines</title><description>...   ...  The question I have, and have been completely unable to get a simple answer on, is as... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7505-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7505_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:52:36">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/chemo-000006_2-145.html</link><title>Breast Cancer Risk Factors: Ethnicity, Race, Genes, and Family History</title><description>... Risk Factors About 12% of women will develop invasive breast cancer in their lifetime. Each year in the United States, about 207,000 women are diagnosed with invasive breast cancer and about 54,000 women are diagnosed with pre-invasive breast cancer. (Although breast cancer in men is rare, about 2,000 American men are diagnosed each year with invasive breast cancer.) About 40,000 American women die from breast cancer each year. Breast cancer death rates have declined significantly since the 1990s, especially for women younger than age 50. The earlier that breast cancer is diagnosed, the earlier the opportunity for treatment. In the United States, there are currently more than 2.5 million breast cancer survivors. Risk factors for breast cancer include: Age Most cases of breast cancer occur in women older than age 60. According to the American Cancer Society, about 1 in 8 cases of invasive breast cancer are found in women younger than age 45, while 2 in 3 cases of invasive breast cancer occu... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7505-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7505_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:52:55">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/question/564297/105837</link><title>ethnic groups in Alzheimers?</title><description>... Does certain ethnc groups tend to have Alzheimers more so than another? ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7505-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7505_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:53:11">http://www.healthcentral.com/obesity/quizzes-256498.html</link><title>Smart Ethnic Food Choices Quiz</title><description>... 219 ...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>