<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7506">I touch myself singer dead</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:53:29" name="HealthCentral" id="FW14-e066"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e066-7506-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7506_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:53:30">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/84292/150244/singer-houston</link><title>Singer Whitney Houston Dead at 48: A Life of Super Stardom Mixed with Mental Illness and Abuse</title><description>...   ... This is a celebrity who has certainly had her share of life struggles despite or perhaps due to her incredible fame.  I think everyone knows about her troubled marriage to Bobby Brown, who, in addition to drug addiction had also been diagnosed with bipolar disorder .  In an interview with Oprah I remember everyone's shock when Houston spoke of the abuse she endured in her relationship. We all felt disgust when she revealed that he would even spit on her.  It was hard to believe that this international super star diva was being treated with such disrespect.  But it also made her all the more human that despite her fame and fortune, Whitney Houston was also a woman who was a victim of emotional abuse .  It showed the world that domestic abuse knows no boundaries.  You can be young, old, rich, poor, or even famous and still be vulnerable to abuse ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7506-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7506_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:53:44">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/67813/36930/singer-hayes</link><title>Soul Singer Isaac Hayes Dies at 65</title><description>... after collapsing at his Tennessee ... home . The New York ... Times reported Hayes had a history of ... heart problems. ...   ... While the cause of death has not been announced, Hayes ... suffered a stroke in 2006, but had since recovered to perform in the Stax’s Reunion ... tour last year. ...   ... Hayes fought on after his stroke and kept performing and ... acting.  As our stroke survivor and expert, Cleo Hutton, has taught us, life ... after a stroke can be a difficult time to heal, both physically and ... mentally. ...   ... Hayes a singer-songwriter, musician, actor and film score ... producer was well-known for writing the theme song to 1971’s Shaft , ... which earned him an Academy Award and two Grammys. ...   ... He was also the voice of “ Chef ” on the Comedy Central ... cartoon series South Park . ...   ... Hayes considered himself a “health fanatic,” who had ... suffered numerous medical conditions in the last few years, his family said. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7506-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7506_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:53:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/heart-disease/c/67813/76157/jackson-dead</link><title>Pop Legend Michael Jackson Dead at 50</title><description>...   ... UPDATE: CNN is reporting allegations of Jackson's possible overuse of painkillers. ...   ... According to MSNBC , Jackson had been due to start a series of comeback concerts in London on July 13th running until March 2010. The singer, whose hits included "Thriller" and "Billie Jean," had been rehearsing in the Los Angeles area for the past two months. ...   ... Jackson has been in the headlines in recent years regarding his declining health, but sources say he had recently passed several health exams. ...   ... Rest in peace, Michael. Take some time and post your favorite Michael Jackson moments below. ...   ... To learn more about possible causes of cardiac arrest, click here . ...   ...   ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7506-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7506_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:54:15">http://www.healthcentral.com/sexual-health/c/question/786718/53561</link><title>Necrosis or dead skin on edges of Labia Minora, dangerous or affecting sensitivity?</title><description>...   ... My labia minora appears to have dead skin encrusted along their outer edges. It is soft with cracking revealing alive skin underneath. its not like a scab, i have had it for as long as i can remember, except it has progressively become worse over the years of my life. It starts at my clit and grows thicker and more ugly before thinning off as it nears the vaginal opening. It doesn't hurt when i pinch it but if i pull at a bit of the looser stuff it does.  ...   ... I am 17 years of age and have been in my first and only sexual relationship for nearly 2 years now (but have been dating for nearly 3). On other sites, girls with this problem noted how long they have been masturbating, which for me is before i turned 12 (i cant quite remember). My boyfriend is curious about the dead skin but not disturbed. ...   ... Now, recently me and my boyfriend agreed to experiment w... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7506-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7506_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:54:32">http://www.healthcentral.com/depression/c/question/835936/131571</link><title>I'm absolutely brain dead and need help now.</title><description>... So this hard to get out the way its happened but I need help so here goes..Back in August of 2010 I had a massive life changing event. My wife left me with my son, I quit my job, quit smoking marijuana, my brother disowned me, quit drinking 15 red bulls a day, my whole world came crashing down, everything I thought about me, you and life in general has been thrown up in the air. I went to a website called bipolarorwakingup and found alot of things that I conected because i had no idea what was going on. I became obsessed with getting smarter, knowledge and thought itself. I read the book Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance, and the means in which Robert Pirsig decribed things, Ive pondered being schizophrenic. It was a "manic" episode that I came up with, a touch of depersonalization, mixed with being narsassitic traits... About 90% of what he talked about happened to me. I've been in and out of AA for 6 years, finding it not very useful because I dont c... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7506-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7506_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:54:51">http://www.healthcentral.com/schizophrenia/c/93829/30187/loss-reality</link><title>If I die- voices, loss of touch witih reality</title><description>... If I Die ...   ...   ... If I am to die today, ... listen and please try to understand ... I am not to be ... blamed, as ... These woods are ... adamantly magical, although the sky, ... Overcast and gray as ... it is, ... I could envision the ... rain falling, though ... No droplets seem to ... be touching the ground, ... Paved with asphalt it ... is, ... Black as a nightmare ... it is, and ... If I were to have ... been attacked or strangled by ... This strange person ... whose voice I have heard commanding me to die, ... Some horrific ... humanoid creature that wants me damned, dead and gone, ... If I am to die to ... day, it is to be my fate; ... I just cannot ... persevere, ... Not one more moment, ... neither a second longer, as ... My pain has cut me so ... deeply, ... I believe my time has ... come. ... Please do not pick ... roses for me, neither ... Wild flowers whether ... be wild violets, dandelions or ... Let the morning ... glories open and laugh all they care to, as ... I cannot laugh, but ... neither can I weep, ... Though pain cuts ... deeply into my soul and the very core of me. ... No rain has ever ... fallen from my heart, or laughter ... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7506-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7506_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:55:12">http://www.healthcentral.com/breast-cancer/c/78/2330/warmth-touch</link><title>The Power of Touch Helps Those with Cancer</title><description>...   ... Before cancer, I remember visiting the hospital and walking blithely past hallway signs pointing to hematology/oncology, the breast program, the infusion suite... ...   ... Amazingly, I had no idea what any of these words signified. I had some vague notion that oncology had to do with cancer. And the infusion suite sounded high-class and high-tech; for some reason, I had visions of a well-equipped health spa. ...   ... But the rest? No business of mine. Thank God. Till suddenly it was. And I found out that the infusion suite wasn’t exactly a spa. It’s been 5 years since I sat in those padded reclining chairs, spending 3 hours every 3 weeks getting the deadly poison that would cure or kill poured into my veins. The visceral memory of the experience fades, just as the physical pain of childbirth disappears. ...   ... But I do recall vividly how the nurs... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7506-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7506_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:55:26">http://www.healthcentral.com/acid-reflux/c/question/595462/48028</link><title>I'm a singer. How can I get over this as quickly as possible?</title><description>... I'm also a singer and I'm a voice major at a University. I just can't afford to take a hiatus from my instrument and have to sing every single day. I'm pretty sure I have silent acid reflux, as I wake up in the morning with that raw-ish, sore feeling in my throat and can't sing for a few hours. I also get sick fairly often with sinus infections. ... Are these typical symptoms of acid reflux? ... I'm seeing my doctor as soon as I get home for Thanksgiving break this year, and he will hopefully refer me to the ENT here in Chicago. ...   ... Thanks! ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7506-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7506_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:55:41">http://www.healthcentral.com/alzheimers/c/42/140351/country-announces</link><title>Country Singer Glen Campbell Announces He Has Alzheimer's Disease</title><description>... I grew up listening to Glen Campbell. I have this vague memory of my dad buying me an eight-track tape (remember those?) of Campbell’s best hits. He always had an emotive way of singing, whether it was “Galveston” or “By the Time I Get to Phoenix.” According to E! Online , Campbell sold 45 million albums, won four Grammys and hosted his own variety show, The Glen Campbell Goodtime Hour on CBS. Now it’s been announced in an article in People that Glen Campbell has reached another milestone, but one that is much sadder – he’s been diagnosed with Alzheimer’s disease at the age of 75. ... This announcement helps put into perspective a recent Campbell performance with Jimmy Webb, who was the songwriter for Campbell’s hits “By the Time I Get to Phoenix,” “Wichita Lineman” and “Galveston.”  Under the headline of “Glen Campbell gives mystifyingly bad show,” David Lindquist of IndyStar.c... ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e066-7506-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e066/7506_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 22:55:57">http://www.healthcentral.com/common/images/image.html</link><title>singer, singing, music, microphone</title></snippet></snippets></search_results>