<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7230">council bluffs</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:52:17" name="Healthlinks.net" id="FW14-e068"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e068-7230-01"><link>http://www.healthlinks.net/cgi-bin/directory/hyperseek.cgi?ID=1323451033</link><title>Public Health Nursing Division - Council Bluffs Department of Public Health</title><description>Public Health Nursing Division - Council Bluffs Department of Public Health 
The Council Bluffs Public Health Department provides information about animal control, public health nurses, recycling and solid waste management for the city. Also, view the members that serve on the board of health here.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7230-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7230_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:53:40">http://www.fivestarseniorliving.com/</link><title>Council Bluffs \- Northcrest Care and Rehabilitation</title><description>Council Bluffs \- Northcrest Care and Rehabilitation 
Northcrest Care and Rehabilitation in Council Bluffs, Iowa, is nestled in the beautiful Loess Hills, where the deer frequently stroll through our front yard to drink from the birdbath.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7230-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7230_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:54:38">http://www.alegentcreighton.com/mercy-hospital</link><title>Council Bluffs \- Mercy Hospital</title><description>Council Bluffs \- Mercy Hospital 
Alegent Health Mercy Hospital in Council Bluffs is setting a new standard for what community medical centers can and should offer.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7230-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7230_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:55:40">http://www.midlandslivingcenter.com/</link><title>Council Bluffs \- Midlands Living Center</title><description>Council Bluffs \- Midlands Living Center 
Midlands Living Center is a locally owned and operated 100-bed skilled nursing and rehabilitation facility located on the north edge of Council Bluffs.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7230-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7230_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:56:20">http://www.totalcarecbia.com/</link><title>Council Bluffs \- Total Care Chiropractic</title><description>Council Bluffs \- Total Care Chiropractic 
We've been delivering quality chiropractic care to the Council Bluffs community since 2004. In our practice Dr. Woods explains treatment options to patients and serves them where they need to be served. We are a family oriented practice and offer both relief and wellness care.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7230-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7230_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:57:22">http://www.foxrunassisted.com/</link><title>Council Bluffs \- Fox Run</title><description>Council Bluffs \- Fox Run 
Welcome to Fox Run, Council Bluffs, Iowa’s premier assisted living community. We are conveniently located just 5 minutes from downtown Omaha, Nebraska, and Council Bluffs Iowa.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7230-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7230_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:57:57">http://bethanylutheranhome.org/page11.asp</link><title>Council Bluffs \- Bethany Heights</title><description>Council Bluffs \- Bethany Heights 
Sponsored by Bethany Lutheran Home, Bethany Heights offers apartment homes and additional services to meet your individual needs. You can expect the same high level of quality, value and care at Bethany Heights that other area seniors have been enjoying at Bethany Lutheran Home for many years.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7230-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7230_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:58:56">http://www.christianhomes.org/facilities/Risen-Son-Christian-Village/Pages/default.aspx</link><title>Council Bluffs \- Risen Son Christian Village</title><description>Council Bluffs \- Risen Son Christian Village 
We’ve been open since 1990 and we have developed a close working relationship between our staff, volunteers and residents. Our full-service retirement community includes 50 Garden Homes, 46 Independent Living Senior Apartments, 36 Residential Care Apartments, 23 Assisted Living Dementia Apartments with three double-room suites and 102 bed Health Care Center.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7230-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7230_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:59:44">http://bethanylutheranhome.org/</link><title>Council Bluffs \- Bethany Lutheran Home</title><description>Council Bluffs \- Bethany Lutheran Home 
Bethany Lutheran Home was founded and sponsored in 1975 by 15 area Lutheran Churches. All of Bethany staff, including our full-time Chaplain, provide loving, compassionate care in a faith based environment. People of all faiths are welcome. Our caring, professional staff is dedicated to meeting the needs of our residents physically, mentally, emotionally, socially, and spiritually through our programs and services.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7230-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7230_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 01:00:15">http://www.ctsnet.org/home/rsellers</link><title>Council Bluffs \- Robert D. Sellers, MD</title><description>Council Bluffs \- Robert D. Sellers, MD 
Home page of Robert D. Sellers, MD</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>