<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7405">light therapy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:30:30" name="Healthlinks.net" id="FW14-e068"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e068-7405-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7405_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:31:22">http://www.fuzeelogik.com/</link><title>Self-Help Assistance Program Presents: Sound &amp; Light Therapy With Crystal Bowls</title><description>Self-Help Assistance Program Presents: Sound &amp; Light Therapy With Crystal Bowls 
Self-Help Assistance Program presents: Sound &amp; Light Therapy With Crystal Bowls.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7405-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7405_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:31:48">http://www.columbia.edu/~mt12/blt.htm</link><title>Q&amp;A on Bright Light Therapy</title><description>Q&amp;A on Bright Light Therapy 
Light therapy involves exposure to intense levels of light under controlled conditions. The recommended light therapy system consists of a set of fluorescent bulbs installed in a box with a diffusing screen, and set up on a table or desk top at which one can sit comfortably for the treatment session</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7405-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7405_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:32:23">http://www.lightsoundtechnology.com/</link><title>Light Therapy, Sound Therapy &amp; Color Therapy from Light Sound Therapeutic Techno</title><description>Light Therapy, Sound Therapy &amp; Color Therapy from Light Sound Therapeutic Techno 
Light therapy, sound therapy and color therapy through Light Sound Therapeutic Technology provide benefits such as stress reduction and pain relief.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7405-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7405_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:33:02">http://www.lighttherapyonline.com/light-therapy-benefits.html</link><title>Full Spectrum Light Box Seasonal Disorder Therapy, Light Therapy Depression</title><description>Full Spectrum Light Box Seasonal Disorder Therapy, Light Therapy Depression 
We offer the listing of benefits of full spectrum light box for seasonal disorder therapy. It's the natural light therapy for seasonal depression.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7405-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7405_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:33:39">http://www.bioptron.eu/</link><title>Bioptron Light Therapy Systems</title><description>Bioptron Light Therapy Systems 
BIOPTRON AG was founded in spring 1988 and dedicates its work to research, development and production of medical products, the BIOPTRON Light Therapy Systems.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7405-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7405_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:34:15">http://www.psycheducation.org/depression/LightTherapy.htm</link><title>Light Therapy for depression</title><description>Light Therapy for depression 
If you already have figured out you have some degree of bipolarity (Bipolar II, soft bipolar disorder), then before you read on you should probably read about Bipolar Disorder: Light and Darkness. Then come back here to learn more about light therapy, starting right here -- because light therapy may need to be different in people with bipolar disorders.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7405-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7405_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:34:41">http://www.britebox.co.uk/</link><title>BriteBox SAD light therapy</title><description>BriteBox SAD light therapy 
The BriteBox is a SAD light therapy unit for the treatment of Seasonal Affective Disorder (SAD). Within just a few days your Seasonal Affective Disorder can be gone with only thirty minutes use per day. Includes free next day delivery and a 60 day money back guarantee for complete satisfaction. The BriteBox site includes a wide variety of information on light therapy and seasonal affective disorder.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7405-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7405_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:35:15">http://www.veinsolutions.com/en/Default.aspx</link><title>Carmel - Vein Solutions</title><description>Carmel - Vein Solutions 
Aesthetics. Medicine. VeinSolutions artfully combines the two in the comprehensive care of cosmetic and therapeutic venous problems. Our physicians are board-certified general and vascular surgeons trained to identify not only the surface condition, but the underlying cause of the problem. With this knowledge our physicians select from a variety of treatment options including sclerotherapy, PhotoDerm (r) VL light therapy or minimally invasive surgery to tailor an individualized program for your specific needs. Meet our staff and learn about our innovative procedures at our offices in Indianapolis, Columbus, Cincinnati and Toledo.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7405-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7405_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:35:47">http://laserlightforhairgrowth.com/</link><title>Laser Hair Growth Therapy</title><description>Laser Hair Growth Therapy 
Laser Light For Hair Growth is one of the largest low level laser light therapy distributors in the country providing hair loss solution devices such as Capillus, Lasercap, iGrow, and our powerful in-office laser, the Revage670 Laser.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7405-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7405_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 08:36:32">http://www.lumie.com/collections/light-therapy-sad</link><title>Guide To Seasonal Affective Disorder (SAD) And Winter Blues - Light Therapy \- Lu</title><description>Guide To Seasonal Affective Disorder (SAD) And Winter Blues - Light Therapy \- Lu 
Animals react to the changing seasons with changes in mood, metabolism and behaviour and human beings are just the same. Many people find they eat and sleep slightly more in winter and dislike the dark mornings and short days and this is commonly referred to as 'winter blues'. For some, however, symptoms are severe enough to disrupt their lives and to cause considerable distress. These people are suffering from SAD</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>