<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7447">running shoes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:31:13" name="Healthlinks.net" id="FW14-e068"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e068-7447-01"><link>http://www.healthlinks.net/cgi-bin/directory/hyperseek.cgi?ID=921017088</link><title>Tel-a-Runner</title><description>Tel-a-Runner 
running shoes, jogging shoes, running apparel, running accessories and running winter apparel sold by mail order</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7447-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7447_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:32:51">http://www.runnersworld.ltd.uk/</link><title>Runnersworld - running equipment, marathon training, running shoes from RunnersW</title><description>Runnersworld - running equipment, marathon training, running shoes from RunnersW 
Runnersworld is the UK resource for runners. Purchase running equipment online, read marathon training tips and use our shoes finder.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7447-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7447_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:33:22">http://www.vpma.org/</link><title>Virginia Podiatric Medical Association</title><description>Virginia Podiatric Medical Association 
The Virginia Podiatric Medical Association is the professional medical association representing podiatric physicians in Virginia. Doctors of Podiatric Medicine specialize in the medical and surgical treatment of foot related medical conditions.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7447-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7447_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:34:08">https://massdpms.site-ym.com/</link><title>Massachusetts Podiatric Medical Society</title><description>Massachusetts Podiatric Medical Society 
The Massachusetts Podiatric Medical Society, an affiliate of the American Podiatric Medical Association is the professional medical association representing podiatric physicians in Massachusetts. Doctors of Podiatric Medicine specialize in the medical and surgical treatment of foot related medical conditions. This site is designed for use by both the general public and our member Doctors of Podiatric Medicine.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7447-05"><link>http://www.healthlinks.net/cgi-bin/directory/hyperseek.cgi?ID=1019776645</link><title>Global Podiatry Quarterly</title><description>Global Podiatry Quarterly 
Global Podiatry Quarterly,GPQ The magazine about feet and legs</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7447-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7447_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:35:28">http://www.nationalrunningcenter.com/</link><title>National Running Center</title><description>National Running Center 
National Running Center offers the best prices on running shoes, jogging shoes, running clothes and running products for cross country and track runners, marathons, triathlons and new runners. We have the perfect fit whether you are training for an Ultra-distance competition or jogging for weight loss.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7447-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7447_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:36:03">http://www.exerlopers.com/</link><title>Exerlopers Fitness Systems</title><description>Exerlopers Fitness Systems 
Unique patented products for a total workout - Exerloper no-impact running shoes, Insta-Pulse heart rate monitors, Antense anti-tension device, Insta-Runner home exerciser.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7447-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7447_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:36:31">http://www.insolesandbeyond.com/</link><title>Insoles and Beyond - Arch Support Inserts</title><description>Insoles and Beyond - Arch Support Inserts 
We are an online insoles retailer providing a variety of insoles in a variety of brands and sizes. We have insoles for arch support, plantar fasciitis, and other foot pain issues. You'll find insoles for your running shoes, dress shoes, work boots, hiking boots, sneakers, and more on our website. We offer great discounts and our shipping is fast and always free. Come check us out.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7447-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e068/7447_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:37:24">http://skotips.blogspot.nl/</link><title>Skobutikker</title><description>Skobutikker 
Norwegian website that provide free information on shoes intended for different fitness activities, such as hiking, running, skiing, soccer, cycling and aeorobics.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e068-7447-10"><link>http://www.healthlinks.net/cgi-bin/directory/hyperseek.cgi?ID=1157826355</link><title>Sugoi Cycling, Triathlon &amp; Fitness Clothing - Sports Basement</title><description>Sugoi Cycling, Triathlon &amp; Fitness Clothing - Sports Basement 
Sugoi cycling, triathon &amp; fitness clothing for men &amp; women on sale at discount prices. Cheap tri, bike &amp; run apparel. Save up to 30 to 60% off retail prices on jerseys, shorts, tri tops, running and fitness clothing.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>