<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7003">Male circumcision</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:57:50" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7003-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7003_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 21:57:51">http://www.forbes.com/sites/danielfisher/2011/05/24/im-not-making-this-up-dept-san-francisco-mulls-ban-on-circumcisions/</link><title>I'm Not Making This Up Dept.: San Francisco Mulls Ban On Circumcisions</title><description>Constitutional questions swirl around San Francisco's proposed ban on male circumcision, read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7003-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7003_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:00:41">http://www.forbes.com/sites/abigailesman/2011/09/19/circumcision-makes-you-crazy-so-holland-moves-to-stop-it/</link><title>Circumcision Makes You Crazy. So Holland Moves To Stop It.</title><description>Calling the practice “a violation of human rights “ and a precursor to mental illness, Holland’s Royal Society of Medicine is encouraging  the country’s parliament to place a ban on male circumcision. Of course, such proposals come up regularly – there’s one out now in San Francisco, for instance – but [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7003-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7003_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:03:05">http://www.forbes.com/sites/richardhyfler/2011/05/26/circumcision-you-cant-have-it-both-ways/</link><title>Circumcision: You Can't Have It Both Ways</title><description>Der Yiddische Tiresias ("The Jewish Tiresias") is a play by Peretz Pntschik that was first presented at the Brownsville (Brooklyn) Roumanian Art Theatre in 1926 and most recently revived, as a musical, at SUNY Purchase in 2006, with funding from the Pntschik Foundation. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7003-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7003_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:07:42">http://www.forbes.com/sites/rahimkanani/2013/12/18/making-an-aids-free-generation-a-reality/</link><title>Making An AIDS-Free Generation A Reality</title><description>Editor's Note: In a recent interview with Craig McClure, Chief of the HIV/AIDS section at UNICEF New York’s headquarters, we discussed their latest report examining the progress being made in the response to HIV and AIDS for children. The report highlights key strategies to prevent HIV and to accelerate access to the treatment, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7003-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7003_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:10:09">http://www.forbes.com/sites/skollworldforum/2013/03/08/philanthropy-that-delivers-for-women/</link><title>Philanthropy that Delivers for Women</title><description>Editor’s Note: Kate Roberts is Vice President of Corporate Marketing, Communications and Advocacy for Population Services International (PSI), a global health organization. This article was published as part of a debate on International Women’s Day at the Skoll World Forum on how best to advance women and girls worldwide. There are some global [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7003-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7003_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:12:04">http://www.forbes.com/sites/knowledgewharton/2013/10/03/182013/</link><title>Was Jesus An Effective Leader? Insights From Reza Aslan's 'Zealot'</title><description>The following post was published on the Knowledge@Wharton website on October 1, 2013. In his bestselling new book, Zealot: The Life and Times of Jesus of Nazareth, author Reza Aslan’s goal was to write a biography of one of history’s most influential people, drawing on historical sources instead of the traditional Gospels to help people understand [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7003-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7003_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:15:22">http://www.forbes.com/sites/michaelwaldholz/2012/07/31/aids-at-defining-moment-will-new-science-end-the-plague/</link><title>AIDS at Defining Moment: Will New Science End the Plague?</title><description>AIDS at Historic Crossroads: Will the opportunity be seized or squandered? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7003-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7003_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:16:04">http://www.forbes.com/sites/mitch2maya/2011/07/15/gilead-makes-a-splash-dives-deep-into-the-patent-pool-and-comes-up-with-a-pill/</link><title>Gilead Makes a Splash: Dives Deep Into the Patent Pool and Comes Up With a Pill</title><description>12 July 2011. The pharmaceutical giant, Gilead, has announced that it’s putting into the Medicines Patent Pool several of its antiretroviral drugs, including tenofovir, an essential drug for one of today’s safest and most effective treatment regimens for AIDS. What’s the Medicines Patent Pool (http://www.medicinespatentpool.org)? It aims to [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7003-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7003_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:18:07">http://www.forbes.com/sites/rahimkanani/2012/09/21/deborah-derrick-on-how-to-fight-aids-tuberculosis-and-malaria/</link><title>Deborah Derrick on How to Fight AIDS, Tuberculosis, and Malaria</title><description>Deb Derrick, President of Friends of the Global Fight, with Sister Nelly Chisense, a Hospital Administrator at St. Theresa Hospital in Ndola, Zambia. In a recent in-depth interview with Deborah Derrick, President, Friends of the Global Fight Against AIDS, Tuberculosis and Malaria, we discussed her motivations for pursuing a career in [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7003-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7003_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:18:36">http://www.forbes.com/2009/09/02/mazar-i-sharif-khaled-amiri-opinions-21-century-cities-09-ann-marlowe.html</link><title>A Humane Afghan City?</title><description>Mazar-i-Sharif looks beyond the typical urban dystopia. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>