<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7010">manchester united FC football</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:11:49" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7010-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7010_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:11:50">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonbelzer/2014/04/10/manchester-united-vs-real-madrid-tilt-at-university-of-michigan-stadium-sells-out-in-24-hours/</link><title>Manchester United Vs. Real Madrid Tilt At University Of Michigan Stadium Sells Out In 24 Hours</title><description>Did someone say that the United States didn't have soccer fans? In what is projected to become the most attended soccer game in US history, the upcoming clash between Manchester United's and Real Madrid FC at the University of Michigan's Big House has also managed to shatter sales records, with over 100,000 tickets [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7010-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7010_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:13:08">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kurtbadenhausen/2014/04/08/arsenal-fc-makes-u-s-push-with-exhibition-and-summer-camps/</link><title>Arsenal FC Makes U.S. Push With Exhibition And Summer Camps</title><description>The Arsenal Way is coming to the U.S. in a series of camps, as well as the EPL club's first appearance on U.S. soil in 25 years for an friendly with the Red Bulls. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7010-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7010_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:15:38">http://www.forbes.com/sites/bobbymcmahon/2014/03/16/while-a-door-opens-for-liverpool-is-the-same-one-closing-on-manchester-united/</link><title>While A Door Opens For Liverpool Is The Same One Closing On Manchester United?</title><description>Moyes talks about looking to United’s tradition of attacking football but it is as convincing as Vladimir Putin espousing the need for greater democracy. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7010-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7010_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:18:50">http://www.forbes.com/sites/mikeozanian/2013/05/24/manchester-uniteds-debt-refinancing-will-boost-teams-profits/</link><title>Manchester United's Debt Refinancing Will Boost Team's Profits</title><description>Manchester United is going to be the next team to score as a result of central banks pushing down interest rates. Manchester United's striker Wayne Rooney (L) vies with Real Madrid's defender Alvaro Arbeloa (R) during the UEFA Champions League round of 16 first leg football match Real Madrid CF vs [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7010-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7010_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:20:15">http://www.forbes.com/sites/quickerbettertech/2013/04/08/how-manchester-united-f-c-may-have-lost-this-small-business-thousands/</link><title>How Manchester United F.C. May Have Lost This Small Business Thousands</title><description>What was this madness? Why was an employee at this small business acting so stubbornly over such a small amount with such a good customer? Did this have something to do with his team’s disappointing performance the day before? Was Manchester United FC the cause of this crazy behavior? Or maybe it was something else. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7010-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7010_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:23:19">http://www.forbes.com/sites/benzingainsights/2012/08/10/manchester-united-scores-233-million-in-ipo/</link><title>Manchester United Scores $233 Million in IPO</title><description>By Mathew Kanterman Manchester United (NYSE: MANU) raised $233 million in its much anticipated IPO as the club sold shares on the New York Stock Exchange. This made Manchester United the first English football club to list on an American exchange. After fees, commissions, and other expenses, Manchester United accrued $110.3 million in [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7010-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7010_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:24:36">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jeffbercovici/2013/05/21/with-new-york-city-fc-does-mls-still-have-room-for-the-cosmos/</link><title>With New York City FC, Does MLS Have Room For The Cosmos?</title><description>The news that Manchester City and the New York Yankees are partnering to bring a new Major League Soccer franchise to Queens is great news for New Yorkers who want to watch the beautiful game without crossing the Hudson. But it's somewhat concerning to those soccer history buffs who were holding out hope that New York's next MLS team might be the [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7010-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7010_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:26:28">http://www.forbes.com/sites/bobbymcmahon/2012/12/23/april-2012-revisited-the-game-that-cost-manchester-united-the-title-dortmund-repeat-dempsey-keeps-scoring/</link><title>April 2012 Revisited - The Game That Cost Manchester United The Title; Dortmund Repeat; Dempsey Keeps Scoring</title><description>Manchester City comes very close to losing at the Etihad Stadium for the first time in 15 months but fight back from 3-1 down with only minutes left to draw 3-3 with Sunderland. Los Angeles Galaxy’s horrible start to the new North American season continues as they lose their third home [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7010-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7010_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:27:39">http://www.forbes.com/sites/mikeozanian/2012/06/16/banks-and-glazer-family-battle-over-value-of-manchester-united/</link><title>Banks And Glazer Family Battle Over Value Of Manchester United</title><description>Given all the economic turmoil across the globe the Glazer family may be seeking too rich a valuation for Manchester United even though the soccer club is perhaps the most well-known sports team in the world. Dimitar Berbatov of Manchester United FC walks off after being substituted during the Barclays Premier League [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7010-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7010_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:31:10">http://www.forbes.com/sites/mikeozanian/2012/04/18/manchester-united-again-the-worlds-most-valuable-soccer-team/</link><title>Manchester United Again The World's Most Valuable Soccer Team</title><description>Manchester United once again captured the top spot among the world's most valuable soccer teams, but Spanish powerhouses Real Madrid and Barcelona are closing ground.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>