<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7024">reinforcement learning</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:06:01" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7024-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7024_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:06:02">http://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2013/10/16/redefining-workplace-learning-for-the-21st-century/</link><title>SAP​Voice: Redefining Workplace Learning For The 21st Century</title><description>By Jenny Dearborn, Vice President, Chief Learning Officer, SuccessFactors – an SAP company Photo credit: Shutterstock Disruptive technologies and shifting demographics are redefining the workforce. In response, smart companies are reinventing workplace learning in an effort to make their programs more relevant and effective, and to create a [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7024-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7024_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:10:40">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jordanshapiro/2013/09/17/rosetta-stone-launches-a-digital-learning-app-for-preschoolers/</link><title>Rosetta Stone Launches A Digital Learning App For Preschoolers</title><description>Rosetta Stone’s first foray into the consumer kids learning app market includes “activities that promote English phonetic awareness, pronunciation of letter sounds, and a grasp of everyday Spanish phrases.” The free iOS app called “Lingo Letter Sounds” uses cute animated “GoGo Lingos” and engaging touch screen mechanics to immerse kids [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7024-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7024_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:12:15">http://www.forbes.com/sites/joshbersin/2013/03/20/how-corporate-learning-drives-competitive-advantage/</link><title>How Corporate Learning Drives Competitive Advantage</title><description>Many business people think of training as something distracting or often a waste of time. And despite the fact that US business spends more than $60 billion a year in employee development (2013 Corporate Learning Factbook), many executives question its return on investment. Well our research shows that one of the [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7024-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7024_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:13:45">http://www.forbes.com/sites/michaelhorn/2012/02/29/bright-spots-shine-in-online-blended-learning/</link><title>Bright Spots Shine in Online Blended Learning</title><description>VideoA month has passed since the first-ever national Digital Learning Day. Given the excitement generated from teachers and others tuning in to the National Town Hall meeting and given today's National Leadership Summit on Online Learning up on Capitol Hill in Washington, D.C. that iNACOL sponsored, I thought it was [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7024-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7024_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:17:20">http://www.forbes.com/sites/emilywillingham/2013/12/10/is-everyday-math-the-worst-math-program-ever/</link><title>Is Everyday Math The Worst Math Program Ever?</title><description>Ask me what my second or fifth grader is learning in math right now. I can’t answer you because it’s Tuesday, and their school uses Everyday Math. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7024-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7024_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:17:50">http://www.forbes.com/sites/meghanbiro/2013/11/17/7-characteristics-of-a-social-leader/</link><title>7 Characteristics Of A Social Leader</title><description>Okay, it’s time to come clean: Besides HR and Talent Management - I’m obsessed with social media, community, leadership and continuous learning. And I have been for years. In fact, this week marks the third year anniversary of my weekly TalentCulture #TChat Radio and Twitter Chat. I feel like the world [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7024-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7024_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:20:52">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jordanshapiro/2013/09/16/education-reform-theres-not-an-app-for-that/</link><title>Education Reform: There's NOT An App For That</title><description>I’m an edTech guy. I celebrate game-based learning. As a result, probably twice a day, people ask me, “which apps should I download for my kid?” Parents are excited about the possibilities of digital learning technology. They see that a game-based approach makes learning fun. It promises a personalized experience, complete [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7024-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7024_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:22:18">http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikaandersen/2013/09/09/6-things-60-year-olds-dont-get/</link><title>6 Things 60-Year-Olds Don't Get</title><description>Getting older doesn't necessarily mean getting better. Some ways to keep yourself from calcifying... read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7024-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7024_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:23:14">http://www.forbes.com/sites/nicolefisher/2014/03/04/two-gamers-aim-to-transform-hospital-performance-evaluation/</link><title>Two Gamers Aim To Transform Hospital Performance Evaluation</title><description>Key evidence suggests that as hospital systems in the US reach a crisis point – involving the transition to value-based purchasing and tying Medicare and Medicaid dollars to performance – quality of care must improve. In many ways hospital employees have become the most important piece of the puzzle to [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7024-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7024_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:26:40">http://www.forbes.com/sites/danschawbel/2014/03/05/douglas-stone-the-importance-of-feedback-in-business-communications/</link><title>Douglas Stone: The Importance Of Feedback In Business Communications</title><description>I recently sat down with Douglas Stone, who is a Managing Partner at Triad Consulting Group and a Lecturer on Law at Harvard Law School, where he teaches negotiation. Through Triad, he consults to a wide range of organizations, including Fidelity, Honda and Shell. Aside from his time spent at Harvard and [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>