<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7025">M/G/1 queue</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:27:03" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7025-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7025_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:27:04">http://www.forbes.com/sites/antonyleather/2014/04/14/why-oculus-rift-and-virtual-reality-could-be-huge-and-not-just-for-gamers/</link><title>Why Oculus Rift And Virtual Reality Could Be Huge And Not Just For Gamers</title><description>VideoOver two decades ago, I was in a theme park near London and in a small room tucked out of the way and with a far smaller queue than any of the vomit-inducing rides outside, sat two large seats with computers built into them. Something like 'Virtual Reality Gaming' was [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7025-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7025_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:30:14">http://www.forbes.com/sites/larissafaw/2012/05/25/professional-line-talkers-and-flash-mobs-coming-soon-to-a-queue-near-you/</link><title>Professional Line Talkers And Flash Mobs Coming Soon To A Queue Near You</title><description>Lines — or queues — are an inevitable part of life. People will spend what amounts to two years of their lives just waiting in line, according to time management firm Q-Matic. And we are impatient. Four minutes is the maximum amount of time that shoppers are willing to wait [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7025-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7025_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:34:41">http://www.forbes.com/sites/heatherstruck/2011/10/11/queue-tips-netflix-recovering-from-momentary-lapse-of-sanity/</link><title>Queue-Tips: Netflix Recovering From Momentary Lapse Of Sanity</title><description>Monday’s email from Netflix to its subscribers might have been one of the more awkward ones that CEO Reed Hastings has signed his name to. It is clear that for many of our members two websites would make things more difficult, so we are going to keep Netflix as one place read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7025-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7025_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:35:46">http://www.forbes.com/sites/chuckjones/2013/12/11/apples-iphone-5s-1-worldwide-smartphone-and-quadruples-chinese-share/</link><title>Apple's iPhone 5s #1 Worldwide Smartphone And Quadruples Chinese Share</title><description>Apple's iPhone 5s is the best selling smartphone worldwide and is helped to increase iPhones share in China by 4x. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7025-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7025_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:38:11">http://www.forbes.com/sites/lydiadishman/2013/11/14/brand-busting-online-and-in-stores-hms-isabel-marant-line-sells-out-disappoints-customers/</link><title>Brand Busting? Online and In Stores H&amp;amp;M's Isabel Marant Line Sells Out, Disappoints Customers</title><description>The hype had been building for months. Announced this summer, H&amp;M's collaboration with Isabel Marant generated enough buzz in the blogosphere to intrigue even those unfamiliar with the French designer who's a favorite of fashion's cognoscenti. Last month, there was a party in Paris filled with models who mingled with guests [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7025-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7025_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:40:16">http://www.forbes.com/sites/careers-at-forbes/2014/02/06/forbes-career-opportunity-video-production-assistant/</link><title>Forbes Career Opportunity: Video Production Assistant</title><description>Forbes Media’s Video team seeks an organized and reliable Production Assistant to support their team. Responsibilities: Maintain, coordinate and update the Production Schedule' o   Field email requests for scheduling o   Monitor the video queue, keeping abreast of deadlines  Media management o   Back up drives daily o   Organize archives o   [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7025-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7025_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:42:04">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jimgorzelany/2013/03/06/a-six-wheeled-mercedes-g-class-could-be-the-ultimate-road-warrior/</link><title>A Six-Wheeled Mercedes G-Class Could Be The Ultimate Road Warrior</title><description>At first glance this looks like an early April Fool’s Day spoof, but we’re assured that it is, in fact, no joke. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7025-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7025_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:44:18">http://www.forbes.com/sites/quora/2014/04/03/do-high-frequency-traders-front-run-the-market-by-using-their-speed-advantage/</link><title>Do High Frequency Traders Front-Run The Market By Using Their Speed Advantage?</title><description>Do high frequency traders front-run the market by using their speed advantage? This question was originally answered on Quora by Alan Chan. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7025-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7025_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:45:33">http://www.forbes.com/sites/fathom/2014/04/19/tuck-into-taiwan-an-ultimate-food-tour/</link><title>Tuck Into Taiwan: An Ultimate Food Tour</title><description>TAIPEI, Taiwan – You start the day in Taipei with turnip cakes and water-fried buns and end it with shaved ice and oyster omelets. Lifetime Taiwan visitor Cyrena Lee takes us on the ultimate food tour. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7025-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7025_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:49:12">http://www.forbes.com/sites/brucebooth/2014/01/02/perspectives-on-vc-backed-biotech-looking-backward-forward/</link><title>Perspectives On VC-Backed Biotech: Looking Backward &amp;amp; Forward</title><description>Tis the season for reflecting and predicting, so I figured I'd follow the custom and share some of my thoughts about the state of biotech in 2013 and the year to come. Reflections on 2013. The Biotech IPO Returns.  This is clearly a (the) major biotech market story of the year, and [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>