<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7029">best buy store closings</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:45:37" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7029-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7029_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:45:38">http://www.forbes.com/sites/danbigman/2012/03/30/here-are-the-best-buy-stores-closing-first-and-why-i-care/</link><title>Here Are The Best Buy Stores Closing First, And Why I Care</title><description>The Best Buy I go to looks remarkably similar to this, minus the palm trees. (Photo credit: Wikipedia) A day after electronics retailer Best Buy announced they'd be shuttering 50 big box stores as part of a new strategy to cut costs and revamp the way they sell, I gave them [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7029-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7029_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:49:00">http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2014/02/26/sony-closing-20-retail-stores-cutting-1000-jobs-in-us/</link><title>Sony Closing 20 Retail Stores, Cutting 1,000 Jobs In US</title><description>Sony is closing 20 retail stores in the US and cutting 1,000 jobs as part of a broader strategy to reduce costs. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7029-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7029_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:52:00">http://www.forbes.com/sites/lauraheller/2012/03/30/why-sears-could-be-the-next-best-buy/</link><title>Why Sears Could Be The Next Best Buy</title><description>Best Buy is closing stores, Sears is shopping Lands End. What do these two retailers have in common and can Sears become the next big box electronics store?</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7029-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7029_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:52:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/maggiemcgrath/2013/11/19/holiday-promotions-a-gift-to-consumers-but-coal-for-best-buy-margins/</link><title>Best Buy Warns Holiday Promotions Will Hurt Fourth-Quarter Margins</title><description>Best Buy reports better-than-expected profit but says fourth-quarter promotions will hurt margins, sending stock into the red read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7029-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7029_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:55:38">http://www.forbes.com/sites/schifrin/2014/01/06/guru-round-up-the-43-best-investment-ideas-for-2014/</link><title>Guru Round Up: The 43 Best Investment Ideas For 2014</title><description>What to buy in 2014? Here are what the experts like. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7029-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7029_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:57:21">http://www.forbes.com/sites/barbarathau/2013/11/07/prediction-four-surprising-retail-hits-and-misses-this-holiday-season/</link><title>Prediction: Best Buy Will Be A Winner This Holiday Season (And So Will JC Penney)</title><description>Will Best Buy be a hit with shoppers this holiday selling season? (Image credit: Getty Images via @daylife) Warning: The following list predicting retail’s hits and misses this holiday season might raise eyebrows, prompt some eye rolling. That’s because it challenges conventional wisdom about one retail darling as well as two of the sector’s [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7029-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7029_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:00:25">http://www.forbes.com/sites/walterloeb/2013/09/04/why-best-buy-fights-with-bare-hands-to-succeed/</link><title>Why Best Buy Fights With Bare Hands To Succeed</title><description>Recent earnings reports from Best Buy and Barnes &amp; Noble point to challenging times ahead. They demonstrate how companies win or lose in competition with Amazon, Costco and others Internet companies. I think Best Buy’s new initiatives will solidify their presence. However, Barnes &amp; Noble has been closing stores and [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7029-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7029_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:03:04">http://www.forbes.com/sites/clareoconnor/2013/11/27/amazons-naughty-walmarts-nice-learn-which-stores-have-your-back-ahead-of-black-friday/</link><title>Amazon's Naughty, Walmart's Nice? Learn Which Stores Have Your Back Ahead Of Black Friday</title><description>As Black Friday approaches, review bible Consumer Reports releases its annual round-up of twenty retailers, airlines, and telecom firms, highlighting punitive practices like hidden store-card fees as well as helpful extras like free shipping on every purchase.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7029-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7029_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:03:55">http://www.forbes.com/sites/danbigman/2012/03/30/a-closer-look-at-best-buys-big-problems/</link><title>A Closer Look At Best Buy Closings</title><description>(Photo credit: Wikipedia) Best Buy's announcement on Thursday that it would close 50 of its biggest "big box" stores as part of a shift in strategy roiled retail watchers and set off a firestorm of discussion online, fueled, in part by Forbes contributors Larry Downes and Laura Heller. Here's [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7029-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7029_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:06:44">http://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2013/05/20/how-much-will-best-buys-turnaround-efforts-lift-earnings/</link><title>Can Best Buy's Turnaround Efforts Lift Earnings?</title><description>Best Buy was in news this quarter for three main reasons: the commencement of its price matching policy, setting up its Samsung-branded boutiques in its stores and the decision to exit Europe by selling off its stake in its joint venture with Carphone Warehouse. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>