<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7031">Thomas test</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:10:10" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7031-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7031_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:10:11">http://www.forbes.com/sites/danielfisher/2014/02/20/global-warming-case-tests-the-limits-of-an-aging-clean-air-act/</link><title>Global-Warming Case Tests The Limits Of An Aging Clean Air Act</title><description>A lawsuit over regulating greenhouse gases is really about Congress's failure to update the law. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7031-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7031_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:14:33">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kurtbadenhausen/2014/01/08/early-ballots-have-maddux-glavine-thomas-and-biggio-in-hall-of-fame-piazza-morris-out/</link><title>Early Ballots Have Maddux, Glavine, Thomas And Biggio In Hall Of Fame; Piazza, Morris Out</title><description>This year's ballot features a bevy of superstars who are eligible for the first time. An early look at the voting indicates at least three, and as many as five, former players will get the call for enshrinement. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7031-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7031_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:17:46">http://www.forbes.com/sites/thomasdelbeccaro/2014/03/12/can-one-judge-stop-california-from-being-railroaded/</link><title>Can One Judge Stop California From Being Railroaded?</title><description>California High Speed Rail runs into the Rule of Law read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7031-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7031_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:20:10">http://www.forbes.com/sites/scottmendelson/2013/06/27/review-the-heat-passes-bechdel-test-fails-laugh-test/</link><title>Review: 'The Heat' Passes Bechdel Test, Fails Laugh Test</title><description>Box Office Take: Well, if Identity Thief can open to $35 million with basically just McCarthy's face on the poster alongside Jason Bateman (great actor, but not box office), then one would presume that McCarthy and Sandra Bullock should equal at least that much, if not something closer to $50 million. [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7031-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7031_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:22:08">http://www.forbes.com/sites/connieguglielmo/2013/09/04/at-cornin-the-glass-is-always-half-full-corning/</link><title>Working With Innovators From Thomas Edison To Steve Jobs, Corning Finds A Glass Fix</title><description>Corning has lasted a century and a half through boom and bust yet always comes up with the glass inventors like Thomas Edison or Steve Jobs need to conquer new markets. CEO Wendell Weeks says the company's best days lie ahead. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7031-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7031_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:24:33">http://www.forbes.com/sites/larrybell/2013/09/03/professor-or-not-obama-repeatedly-flunks-constitution-law-tests/</link><title>Professor Or Not, Obama Repeatedly Flunks Constitution Law Tests</title><description>The President cannot legislate through executive fiat or pick which parts of the law to comply with or decline. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7031-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7031_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:26:55">http://www.forbes.com/sites/oracle/2013/05/08/oracle-software-chief-thomas-kurian-10-strategic-cloud-computing-insights/</link><title>Oracle​Voice: Oracle Software Chief Thomas Kurian: 10 Strategic Cloud Computing Insights</title><description>(Revolweb) As cloud computing surges into the mainstream of business-technology strategies and deployments, plenty of questions are still swirling around regarding security, time to value, public versus private, lock-in, cost, and more. For businesses, these questions are reasonable as cloud adoptions grow rapidly around the world and increasingly [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7031-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7031_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:28:35">http://www.forbes.com/sites/gaygaddis/2014/04/16/entrepreneurs-of-austin-alamo-drafthouse/</link><title>Entrepreneurs Of Austin: Alamo Drafthouse</title><description>Sometimes things don’t turn out how we expect them to. Just ask Alamo Drafthouse owner, Tim League. The now film-famous Austin resident started his career with Shell Oil after graduating from Rice University with a degree in mechanical engineering. After quickly realizing oil was not the right path for him, he started to seek exit strategies for [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7031-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7031_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:29:15">http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikaandersen/2014/04/07/how-google-picks-new-employees-hint-its-not-about-your-degree/</link><title>How Google Picks New Employees (Hint: It's Not About Your Degree)</title><description>What makes a great job candidate these days? You may be surprised to hear what the folks at Google think.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7031-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7031_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:30:13">http://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2012/09/08/could-lance-thomas-100000-worth-of-bling-cause-duke-to-vacate-its-2010-ring/</link><title>Could Lance Thomas' $100,000 Worth Of "Bling" Cause Duke To Vacate Its 2010 Ring?</title><description>HOUSTON - MARCH 28: Lance Thomas #42 of the Duke Dlue Devils celebrates a win over the Baylor Bears during the south regional final of the 2010 NCAA men's basketball tournament at Reliant Stadium. (Image credit: Getty Images North America via @daylife) Former Duke Basketball player, Lance Thomas, is being sued [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>