<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7037">how to write journalistic review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:31:39" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7037-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7037_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:31:40">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jonentine/2013/12/19/got-healthier-milk-how-activist-scientists-and-journalists-bungled-a-report-on-organic-foods/</link><title>Got (Healthier) Milk? How Activist Scientists And Journalists Bungled Report On Organic Foods</title><description>As the Genetic Literacy Project reports, a study touting the alleged benefits of drinking organic milk became a made-for-headlines event and a financial bonanza for the health and natural products industry. Let's separate the hype from the facts. The web erupted last week after Washington State University issued a news release [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7037-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7037_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:33:52">http://www.forbes.com/sites/cherylsnappconner/2013/02/24/5-rules-how-to-survive-and-thrive-in-the-chaos-of-current-media/</link><title>5 Rules: How To Survive (And Thrive) In The Chaos Of Current Media</title><description>Today’s journalism industry is in “seismic turmoil,” says Forbes editor Tom Post. Forbes’ Lewis Dvorkin is commiserating what we’ve been noting as well. Very few of the star journalists (the ones who made the lives of PR people havoc during the last two decades) have made the transition to digital [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7037-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7037_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:35:15">http://www.forbes.com/sites/booked/2011/10/17/booked-review-rin-tin-tin-the-life-and-the-legend/</link><title>Booked Review: "Rin Tin Tin: The Life and the Legend"</title><description>Susan Orlean's new book Rin Tin Tin: The Life and the Legend is, like much of her previous work, a story that shines a light on obsession. Orlean delights in elegantly recasting fringe characters on their own terms, following them along narrative arcs from an exterior perspective, where they might seem [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7037-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7037_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:38:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2012/10/26/all-the-pretty-doritos-how-video-game-journalism-went-off-the-rails/</link><title>All The Pretty Doritos: How Video Game Journalism Went Off The Rails</title><description>The problems facing gaming journalism and the gaming industry have been going on for years. A look at the state of the gaming press in 2012.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7037-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7037_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:39:46">http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidkroll/2014/03/22/will-north-carolina-central-universitys-1st-ncaa-tournament-appearance-promote-their-academic-programs/</link><title>Will North Carolina Central University's 1st NCAA Tournament Bid Boost Academics?</title><description>Despite the shadow of Duke University just four miles away, the NCCU Eagles earned a NCAA tournament berth in only their third season playing Division I men's basketball. As a former pharmaceutical sciences professor at the well-regarded HBCU, I wonder how the national exposure might help the university and its programs? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7037-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7037_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:42:01">http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidewalt/2011/11/17/how-to-do-things-with-videogames-ian-bogost/</link><title>How To Do Things with Videogames: An Interview With Ian Bogost</title><description>A game scholar explores the ways computer games are used today, and argues for their proper place in art and culture. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7037-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7037_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:43:09">http://www.forbes.com/sites/lewisdvorkin/2012/01/17/inside-forbes-how-our-94-year-old-brand-engages-and-finds-success-in-a-social-world/</link><title>Inside Forbes: How Our 94-Year-Old Brand Engages and Finds Success in a Social World</title><description>My first email exchange of the day typically occurs around 6:15 am with Coates Bateman, who oversees a large part of our contributor network. We're both obsessed with Forbes.com traffic and he's always full of insights about the prior day's posts -- why some resonated with users, why others didn't [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7037-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7037_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:47:16">http://www.forbes.com/sites/yec/2012/07/10/5-things-to-know-before-using-bloggers-to-grow-your-brand/</link><title>5 Things to Know Before Using Bloggers to Grow Your Brand</title><description>Before using bloggers -- your own, or someone else's -- to grow your brand, get acquainted with a few rules of play. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7037-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7037_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:50:28">http://www.forbes.com/sites/tomwatson/2012/02/27/murdoch-assange-and-the-need-to-know/</link><title>Murdoch, Assange and the Need to Know</title><description>The gods of symmetry must surely have moved into the firmament over London this week. How else to explain the two most renowned Australians in the world, both on the Shakespearean stage at the same time in the shadow of the London Eye - and both for hacking private information in pursuit [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7037-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7037_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:54:41">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jenniferleggio/2012/06/25/cyber-crime-to-crime-novel-dennis-fisher-discusses-motherless-children/</link><title>Cyber Crime to Crime Novel: Dennis Fisher Discusses 'Motherless Children'</title><description>A professional journalist for more than 15 years, Dennis Fisher has spent most of his time writing about computer security. But after considering writing a novel for more than a decade, he took a leap from writing about non-fictional cyber criminals to writing a fictional crime novel titled "Motherless Children", a murder mystery for the [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>