<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7044">song of ice and fire</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:43:22" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7044-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7044_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:43:23">http://www.forbes.com/sites/allenstjohn/2014/04/04/five-reasons-why-you-should-watch-hbos-game-of-thrones-even-if-youre-not-into-castles-and-dragons/</link><title>Five Reasons Why You Should Watch HBO's 'Game of Thrones' (Even If You're Not Into Castles and Dragons)</title><description>VideoOver the past few days, I’ve been binge watching Game of  Thrones to catch up before the Season 4 Premiere on Sunday on HBO.  I had always thought the series, based on A Song of Ice and Fire, George R.R. Martin's series of  fantasy novels by Martin, would be a [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7044-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7044_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:45:03">http://www.forbes.com/sites/carolpinchefsky/2013/04/15/game-of-thrones-3-03-the-hand-of-the-king-the-hand-of-the-kingslayer/</link><title>Game of Thrones 3.03: The Hand of the King, the Hand of the Kingslayer</title><description>Game of Thrones may be a great HBO television show, but first it was a great series of books, A Song of Ice and Fire, by George R.R. Martin. The events of the season 3 in the television show are following book 3, A Storm of Swords, part 1. But which is better? Let’s take a look at “Walk of Punishment” and see. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7044-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7044_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:46:37">http://www.forbes.com/sites/carolpinchefsky/2013/04/08/game-of-thrones-3-02-catelyn-stews-in-guilt-theon-stews-in-blood/</link><title>Game of Thrones 3.02: Catelyn Stews in Guilt, Theon Stews in Blood</title><description>A Storm of Swords, book three in the saga A Song of Ice and Fire, was such a large, sprawling epic that George R.R. Martin had to break it into two parts. Part 1: Steel and Snow is the base on which season 3 of Game of Thrones rests. But there are quite a few differences between what we’ve read and what we saw last night. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7044-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7044_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:50:04">http://www.forbes.com/sites/merrillbarr/2014/03/31/game-of-thrones-plants-the-seeds-of-self-empowered-anarchy-in-season-four/</link><title>'Game of Thrones' Plants The Seeds of Self-Empowered Anarchy In Season Four</title><description>Except for a rare bump or two in the road, Game of Thrones has remained one of the most consistently great series on television, and rest assured that as far as the premiere’s concerned, the season run is off to a fantastic start that could lead to the most game changing set of episodes to date. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7044-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7044_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:51:58">http://www.forbes.com/sites/carolpinchefsky/2012/12/27/7-game-of-thrones-apps-to-get-you-through-the-long-winter/</link><title>7 'Game of Thrones' Apps to Get You Through the Long Winter</title><description>When I’m not reading A Song of Ice and Fire series, rewatching HBO’s Game of Thrones, or praying to the seven gods to make author George R.R. Martin write faster, I’m looking for something else to keep the Winterfell fires burning until Martin releases the latest installment, The Winds of [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7044-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7044_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:55:08">http://www.forbes.com/sites/carolpinchefsky/2013/02/11/in-dramatic-game-of-thrones-season-3-trailer-petyr-baelish-describes-the-nature-of-chaos/</link><title>In Dramatic 'Game of Thrones' Season 3 Trailer, Petyr Baelish Describes the Nature of Chaos</title><description>“Chaos isn’t a pit,” says Petyr Baelish, “Chaos is a ladder.” He would know. In Game of Thrones (and in the books, A Song of Ice and Fire), Petyr is a minor noble from a poor family who had climbed his way to the title of Westeros’ master of coin. Although we don’t know exactly how he received his job, we have an idea that it involves the ladder [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7044-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7044_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:55:42">http://www.forbes.com/sites/carolpinchefsky/2013/01/09/george-r-r-martin-releases-a-new-chapter-in-the-game-of-thrones-series/</link><title>George R.R. Martin Releases a New Chapter in the 'Game of Thrones' Series</title><description>Good, no, great news, fans of George R.R. Martin’s series “A Song of Ice and Fire” (which I refer to in the title as “Game of Thrones” for the purpose of aggregation only): For those of us who have been dying in anticipation since the release of A Dance with Dragons, Martin is reviving us with another advanced chapter of The Winds of Winter. But [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7044-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7044_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:57:47">http://www.forbes.com/sites/carolpinchefsky/2012/12/12/4-things-i-learned-about-game-of-thrones-actress-emilia-clarke-via-jimmy-kimmel/</link><title>4 Things I Learned About 'Game of Thrones' Actress Emilia Clarke, via Jimmy Kimmel</title><description>Emilia Clarke, the charismatic Game of Thrones actress who plays Daenerys Targaryen, the khaleesi who would be queen, recently made a guest appearance on The Jimmy Kimmel Show. Clarke didn’t spoil any happenings about the show—to be fair, you have only to read the Song of Ice and Fire series to see what happens next—but she did reveal a few [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7044-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7044_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:01:53">http://www.forbes.com/sites/carolpinchefsky/2012/09/16/why-game-of-thrones-won-those-6-creative-arts-emmy-awards-some-speculations/</link><title>Why 'Game of Thrones' Won Those 6 Creative Arts Emmy Awards (Some Speculations)</title><description>Game of Thrones the fantastic HBO series based on George R.R. Martin's continuing saga, A Song of Ice and Fire, has recently won six Creative Arts Emmy Awards, the Emmy awards designed to honor the people who work behind the camera--such as casting directors and sound editors--rather than in front of it. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7044-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7044_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:02:43">http://www.forbes.com/sites/carolpinchefsky/2012/07/16/game-of-thrones-the-math-edition/</link><title>'Game of Thrones': The Math Edition</title><description>Game of Thrones is a sprawling HBO television show based on an even more sprawling book series, A Song of Ice and Fire, by George R.R. Martin. With as many characters as there are stars in the sky, it’s incredibly complex. Don’t you want someone to just math it out for you? read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>