<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7056">ROADM</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:31:01" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7056-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7056_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:31:02">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ericsavitz/2012/12/06/jdsu-raymond-james-cuts-rating-trims-ests-after-rally/</link><title>JDSU: Raymond James Cuts Rating, Trims Ests After Rally</title><description>Shares of optical networking component and test equipment provider JDSU are trading lower Thursday after Raymond James analyst Simon Leopold cut his rating on the stock to Market Perform from Outperform. He notes that the stock had rallied 19% since reporting earnings on October 30. But this isn't just a valuation [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7056-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7056_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:33:50">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ericsavitz/2011/03/14/jdsu-citi-turns-bullish/</link><title>JDSU: Citi Turns Bullish</title><description>JDSU shares are getting a modest lift this morning from Citigroup analyst Kevin Dennean, who upped his rating on the stock to Buy from Hold after a recent sell-off in the shares triggered by a flurry of bad news from other companies in the optical networking sector. The Citi analyst notes [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7056-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7056_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:35:19">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ericsavitz/2011/03/04/jdsu-the-stock-market-has-optical-networking-fever/</link><title>JDSU: The Stock Market Has Optical Networking Fever</title><description>Investors have the fever. And the only prescription is...more JDSU shares. In an otherwise ugly equity market today, investors are piling in to optical networking component stocks. I'm not sure on the precise catalyst for the move this afternoon, but it certainly is eye-opening. Leading the way is JDSU (JDSU), a [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7056-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7056_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:37:26">http://www.forbes.com/forbes/2011/0314/technology-eric-savitz-tech-trade-light-returns.html</link><title>The Light Returns</title><description>An impressive revival for one of the biggest bubble stocks ever. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>