<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7057">web of science</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:39:44" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7057-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7057_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:39:45">http://www.forbes.com/sites/realspin/2014/03/31/the-ipccs-latest-report-deliberately-excludes-and-misrepresents-important-climate-science/</link><title>The IPCC's Latest Report Deliberately Excludes And Misrepresents Important Climate Science</title><description>This week, the United Nations’ Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC) is releasing its latest report, the “Working Group II Contribution to the Fifth Assessment Report.” Like its past reports, this one predicts apocalyptic consequences if mankind fails to give the UN the power to tax and regulate fossil fuels and subsidize and mandate [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7057-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7057_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:42:43">http://www.forbes.com/sites/netapp/2014/03/27/aws-cloud-better-and-cheaper/</link><title>NetApp​Voice: As Cloud Market Heats Up, Amazon Web Services Now Better And Cheaper</title><description>Amazon announces interesting new features for Amazon Web Services (AWS) and certification by the Department Of Defense (DoD). It also slashes prices. On the one hand, the AWS cloud services are even more competitive than they were last week. On The Other Hand, the entire cloud-services market is getting more competitive, so [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7057-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7057_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:45:34">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ciocentral/2014/04/18/8-ways-to-build-and-use-the-new-breed-of-data-driven-applications/</link><title>8 Ways To Build And Use The New Breed Of Data-Driven Applications</title><description>By Brian Ascher, partner at Venrock Software-as-a-Service and cloud computing has been transformational for the software industry, but compared to what is coming next, you ain’t seen nothing yet. First, to appreciate where we are heading a quick review of where we’ve been is in order. Back in the olden days of business [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7057-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7057_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:46:50">http://www.forbes.com/sites/abrambrown/2014/04/16/how-wayfair-sells-nearly-1-billion-worth-of-sofas-patio-chairs-and-cat-playgrounds/</link><title>How Wayfair Sells Nearly $1 Billion Worth Of Sofas, Patio Chairs And Cat Playgrounds</title><description>Wayfair is the Web's Sears, Roebuck. But its business is as much data mining as retailing. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7057-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7057_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:49:07">http://www.forbes.com/sites/bridaineparnell/2013/12/10/tweeting-scientists-find-penile-fracture-and-sperm-bags-of-squid-just-as-funny-as-everyone-else-does/</link><title>Tweeting Scientists Find Penile Fracture And 'Sperm Bags Of Squid' Just As Funny As Everyone Else Does</title><description>Funny or startling science news generally tops the Twitter charts, even when academics are doing the tweeting, according to a new study. Of the most tweeted peer-reviewed articles published between 2010 and 2012, based on over a million documents from the PubMed and Web of Science databases, many had something of a humorous slant to them. The top [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7057-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7057_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:50:19">http://www.forbes.com/sites/gretchenfox/2014/04/09/the-re-emergence-of-the-private-social-network/</link><title>The Re-Emergence of the Private Social Network</title><description>Private mobile social network offers solution to protecting data for organizations and users read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7057-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7057_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:52:11">http://www.forbes.com/sites/emilywillingham/2013/12/19/7-science-based-parenting-practices/</link><title>7 Science-Based Parenting Practices</title><description>I'm pleased to announce that my science-writing work has been selected for inclusion in Open Lab 2013, an anthology of the best science writing on the Web. The piece that landed me among a field that includes Aatish Bhatia, Deborah Blum, Matthew Francis, Maggie Koerth-Baker, Seth Mnookin, Jennifer Ouellette, and other wonderful [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7057-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7057_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:52:53">http://www.forbes.com/sites/narrativescience/2014/03/14/profit-expected-to-dip-for-adobe-systems/</link><title>Profit Expected to Dip for Adobe Systems</title><description>Despite an expected dip in profit, analysts are generally optimistic about Adobe Systems as it prepares to reports its first-quarter earnings on Tuesday, March 18, 2014. The consensus earnings per share estimate is 12 cents per share.Analysts are projecting earnings of 55 cents per share for the fiscal year. After [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7057-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7057_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:53:50">http://www.forbes.com/sites/netapp/2014/04/03/europe-net-neutrality-otoh/</link><title>NetApp​Voice: Here Comes European Net-Neutrality, Despite Criticism Of 'Connected Continent' Rules</title><description>The European Parliament has kick-started the high-speed train to network-neutrality. And once they've got next month's elections over with, they're expected to get on with the messy business of lawmaking. On the one hand, fans of the so-called "open Internet" are rejoicing. On The Other Hand, beware of unintended consequences... [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7057-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7057_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:56:40">http://www.forbes.com/sites/netapp/2014/03/25/warby-parker-focus-on-easy/</link><title>NetApp​Voice: 9 Ways Of Warby Parker: Focus On These "Easy" Growth Tips</title><description>Warby Parker sells prescription eyeglasses online. And they're widely considered a successful startup. But why, exactly? What's the secret to Warby Parker's positive public image and rapid growth? [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>