<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7059">doctor Amsterdam</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:00:51" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7059-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7059_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:00:51">http://www.forbes.com/sites/singularity/2013/05/09/your-next-doctor-could-save-your-life-from-hundreds-of-miles-away/</link><title>Your Next Doctor Could Save Your Life From Hundreds Of Miles Away</title><description>credit: Philips Healthcare Collaborating with colleagues through a telepresence robot, taking notes while the teacher lectures to your avatar while you remain comfortably at home, and receiving a prescription from a doctor you’ve only met on a video screen are all realities today. But certainly caring for the critically ill and their need for [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7059-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7059_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:03:43">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ptc/2014/03/28/becoming-cyborgs-ear-based-wearable-tech-disrupts-healthcare/</link><title>PTC​Voice: Becoming Cyborgs: Wearable Tech Disrupts Healthcare</title><description>By Lydia Leavitt Health and healthcare have typically been a personal relationship between doctors and patients – kept private and behind closed doors. More recently, however, healthcare is being opened up by technology.  Medical questions are crowdsourced, records are electronic and doctors are connected directly with their patients –  before, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7059-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7059_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:06:05">http://www.forbes.com/sites/digitaldownload/2006/06/06/see-you-in-28-days/</link><title>See You In 28 Days</title><description>Can a level 60 Paladin serve as grounds for involuntary commitment? I hope not, because doctors in Amsterdam have opened up a rehab clinic dedicated solely to the treatment of video game addicts. Gamespot has details. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7059-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7059_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:09:51">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ceciliarodriguez/2012/04/04/holland-targets-its-drugs-and-death-tourism/</link><title>Holland Targets Its Drugs-and-Death Tourism</title><description>It's no coincidence that under a right-leaning Prime Minister, two old debates are back to prominence in the Netherlands, both related to hard-to-define tourisms:  “Bad tourism,” “dark tourism", “medical tourism” or the less contentious “new tourism.” Labels aside, they're highly controversial and tied to ideology: drug tourism and [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7059-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7059_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:11:26">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johnmauldin/2014/03/29/129/</link><title>When Inequality Isn't</title><description>“An imbalance between rich and poor is the oldest and most fatal ailment of all republics.” –Plutarch, Greek historian, first century AD “In the economic sphere an act, a habit, an institution, a law produces not only one effect, but a series of effects. Of these effects, the first alone is immediate; [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7059-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7059_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:13:45">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johnmauldin/2014/03/16/mauldin-inequality-and-opportunity/</link><title>Inequality And Opportunity</title><description>“Nothing is more dangerous than a dogmatic worldview – nothing more constraining, more blinding to innovation, more destructive of openness to novelty.” – Stephen Jay Gould  My letters the last few weeks on income inequality (here and here) brought more response from readers than any topic I’ve written on in the history [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7059-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7059_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:14:47">http://www.forbes.com/sites/tedgreenwald/2011/12/23/mobile-gaming-comes-alive-creator-of-tiki-bar-tv-launches-live-action-iphone-adventure/</link><title>Mobile Gaming Comes Alive: Creator of Tiki Bar TV Launches Live-Action iPhone Adventure</title><description>Jeff Macpherson, a.k.a. Doctor Tiki, produced one of the standout video series of the vodcast era. His Tiki Bar TV — a charming take on the not-so-charming premise that the solution to all mankind’s problems can be found in a bottle — was featured by Steve Jobs himself at the [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7059-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7059_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:17:38">http://www.forbes.com/sites/stevecooper/2013/05/30/the-most-important-book-of-the-year-is-out-and-you-likely-wont-read-it/</link><title>The Most Important Book Of The Year Is Out -- And You Likely Won't Read It</title><description>The DSM-5 helps clinicians classify, describe and diagnose mental disorders. (Photo: American Psychiatric Association) You won't find this book on The New York Times Best Sellers list or find it making an appearance in Oprah's Book Club, but this one book will have a direct impact on your insurance, employees, pharmaceutical [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7059-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7059_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:18:48">http://www.forbes.com/sites/anthonynitti/2013/08/22/will-bradley-mannings-gender-reassignment-be-tax-deductible/</link><title>Will Bradley Manning's Gender Reassignment Be Tax Deductible?</title><description>On Wednesday, Army Pvt. Bradley Manning was sentenced to 35 years at Fort Leavenworth for sending classified material regarding the U.S. war in Iraq to the Web site WikiLeaks. Thursday morning, he let the world know he will begin living as a woman named Chelsea. And I thought my week was stressful. To [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7059-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7059_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:19:15">http://www.forbes.com/sites/gilpress/2013/02/26/big-data-news-roundup-from-porn-to-data-ism/</link><title>Big Data News Roundup: From Porn to Data-ism</title><description>Grade 9th Math problem (Photo credit: arjin j) “We need data about big data,” says The Economist, citing Lord Kelvin "to measure is to know." The Economist asks the question in the context of the decades-old (remember “Intellectual Capital”?) and elusive search for the value of the data companies hold. But [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>