<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7061">startup advisors chicago</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:24:19" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7061-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7061_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:24:20">http://www.forbes.com/sites/alanhall/2012/10/04/investors-weigh-in-on-crowdfund-investing-at-chicago-event/</link><title>Investors Weigh In On Crowdfund Investing At Chicago Event</title><description>Much has been said about Crowdfund Investing (CFI) from the entrepreneurs’ point of view—but where do investors currently stand?  How can CFI which is scheduled to “go live” when the SEC posts its regulations in early 2013 maximize the potential for positive impact from the JOBS Act for local communities? [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7061-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7061_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:27:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/quora/2012/10/30/to-what-extent-can-a-startup-work-without-an-office/</link><title>To What Extent Can A Startup Work Without An Office?</title><description>To what extent can a startup work without an office? This question was originally answered on Quora by Paul DeJoe. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7061-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7061_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:29:16">http://www.forbes.com/sites/zipfitme/2012/07/06/re-starting-your-startup-or-how-to-overcome-rejection/</link><title>Re-Starting Your Startup - Or, How To Overcome Rejection</title><description>iStockPhoto/Paci77 I hate being rejected. No matter how many times I face it, it still pains me when my call isn’t returned, a phone is hung up, or I get the cold shoulder. After a while though, you do start to feel a little numb and you improve quite a bit. [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7061-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7061_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:31:22">http://www.forbes.com/sites/women2/2012/08/06/this-is-what-a-healthcare-startup-investor-looks-like-meet-joanne-chang/</link><title>This Is What A Healthcare Startup Investor Looks Like: Meet Joanne Chang</title><description>Women 2.0 profiles women angel investors in our "This Is What An Angel Investor Looks Like" series. By Angie Chang (Co-Founder &amp; Editor-in-Chief, Women 2.0) Chicago-based Joanne Chang is a healthcare angel investor and advisor with companies in stealth and early-stage mode. She holds a joint MBA-MS degree in healthcare, clinical sciences [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7061-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7061_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:34:07">http://www.forbes.com/2010/12/22/chicago-climate-club-carbon-barack-obama-opinions-contributors-larry-bell.html</link><title>The Chicago Climate Club Gets Capped</title><description>The amount of influential Democrats in this group is perhaps too coincidental. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7061-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7061_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:34:35">http://www.forbes.com/sites/zipfitme/2012/07/23/8-ways-business-school-can-be-an-incubator-for-your-startup/</link><title>8 Ways Business School Can Be An Incubator For Your Startup</title><description>University Of Chicago Business School (Photo credit: Wikipedia) Are you ready to drop $100,000? I started business school in the fall of 2010. When I applied, I had no intention of starting a company. I was attending to help grow my family’s business. However, your path can change. Mine did. In March of [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7061-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7061_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:37:59">http://www.forbes.com/sites/maryjosephs/2014/03/12/selling-your-business-the-seven-year-itch/</link><title>Selling Your Business: The Seven-Year Itch</title><description>For a lot of reasons, successful companies between four and eight years post-startup end up selling. Call it the seven-year itch: by that point, in a study of 342 privately held acquisitions, half the companies had sold. You know the reasons: 1. Buyers come calling – both strategic and financial – [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7061-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7061_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:39:17">http://www.forbes.com/sites/alexkonrad/2014/01/28/indiegogo-raises-big-time-funding/</link><title>Crowdfunder Indiegogo Raises Its Own Big-Time Funding</title><description>Slava Rubin is more than just the founder and CEO of Indiegogo, the would-be global leader in crowdfunding. As he promotes campaigns raised over his platform, Rubin also acts as part missionary, part mascot. Three months ago, he appeared onstage at Chicago Ideas Week to raise money for an embattled Chicago [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7061-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7061_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:41:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kellyreid/2013/04/08/will-bitcoin-be-a-facebook-or-a-myspace-either-way-its-a-revolution/</link><title>Will Bitcoin Be A Facebook Or A Myspace? Either Way, It's A Revolution.</title><description>Disclaimer and Disclosure: I own a very small amount of BitCoins. My company is now accepting BitCoin as a valid method of payment, alongside PayPal. I am not a professional investment advisor nor a professional economist but I am an entrepreneur, investor and most importantly (and shamefully), a former online [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7061-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7061_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:45:11">http://www.forbes.com/sites/alexkonrad/2014/03/27/the-top-life-sciences-investors-of-2014/</link><title>The Top Life Sciences Investors Of 2014</title><description>By Alex Konrad and TrueBridge Capital Partners The 2014 Midas List features the top 100 tech investors in venture capital, and this year’s List is a formidable group. But as in years past, life science investors aren’t as represented in the main group as that booming sector deserves. Part of the [...]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>