<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7062">marquette university news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:45:57" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7062-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7062_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:45:58">http://www.forbes.com/sites/tomvanriper/2014/03/14/the-new-big-east-with-the-first-year-in-the-books-commissioner-val-ackerman-looks-ahead/</link><title>The New Big East: With The First Year In The Books, Commissioner Val Ackerman Looks Ahead</title><description>The new commissioner doesn't think she needs football to build a powerhouse conference. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7062-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7062_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:49:16">http://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2014/03/10/jay-z-has-99-problems-but-is-being-a-sports-agent-one/</link><title>Jay Z Has 99 Problems, But Is Being A Sports Agent One?</title><description>An excerpt from a Marquette Sports Law Review article titled, Jay Z Has 99 Problems, And Being A Sports Agent May Be One. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7062-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7062_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:50:43">http://www.forbes.com/sites/prishe/2013/03/01/butler-university-hoops-bulldogging-their-way-into-big-time-basketball-bucks-and-branding/</link><title>Butler University Hoops: Bulldogging their Way into Big Time Basketball Bucks and Branding</title><description>Butler University Athletics is Pulling a 'Jeffersons'...They Are Movin' on Up to the Big Time' with Impending Move to the Big East The currency earned from two consecutive trips to the NCAA Men's Basketball finals in 2010 and 2011 has positioned Butler University to parlay those achievements into long-term financial success. [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7062-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7062_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:51:54">http://www.forbes.com/sites/tomvanriper/2013/09/23/college-football-players-unite/</link><title>College Football Players Unite</title><description>A handful of college football players showed union-like solidarity on the field this past weekend. Can the movement gain momentum? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7062-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7062_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:52:58">http://www.forbes.com/sites/tomvanriper/2013/03/19/georgetown-carries-the-weight-of-new-big-east-into-tournament/</link><title>Georgetown Carries The Weight Of New Big East Into Tournament</title><description>With its first televsion deal on the line, the new Big East needs to make some noise in the tournament. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7062-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7062_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 10:56:02">http://www.forbes.com/sites/prishe/2013/03/08/whats-in-a-name-try-history-brand-affinity-as-new-big-east-stands-shoulders-above-america-12/</link><title>What's In A Name? Try History, Brand Affinity as New Big East Stands Shoulders Above "America 12"</title><description>Head coach John Thompson III of the Georgetown Hoyas...Representing the Legacy of Big East Basketball Thanks to the impending launch of Fox Sports One in August 2013, the time table of the Catholic 7 defecting from the tatters of a decaying conference was expedited. Wisely, and perhaps rightly so, the Catholic 7 [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7062-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7062_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:00:25">http://www.forbes.com/sites/tomvanriper/2013/01/02/pennsylvania-sues-the-ncaa-over-penn-state-and-it-could-win/</link><title>Pennsylvania Sues The NCAA Over Penn State - And It Could Win</title><description>The state can argue that the NCAA overstepped in the Sandusky case, failing to cite any specific rules violations.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7062-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7062_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:01:56">http://www.forbes.com/sites/richardstiennon/2014/03/23/stem-stinks-for-cybersecurity/</link><title>STEM Stinks For Cybersecurity</title><description>I am getting fed up with the clamor on the part of policy makers for more degrees in Science, Technology, Engineering, and Math (STEM) as the path to success in the United States, especially in cybersecurity. The numbers don’t add up, and the problem of not having enough cybersecurity workers [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7062-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7062_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:04:14">http://www.forbes.com/sites/maggiemcgrath/2014/04/04/money-isnt-everything-when-its-worth-taking-on-50000-or-more-in-student-debt/</link><title>Money Isn't Everything: When It's Worth Taking On $50,000 Or More In Student Debt</title><description>The student-debt drumbeat might have you thinking that everyone who has taken out big student loans is miserable and filled with regret. Not so. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7062-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7062_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:05:22">http://www.forbes.com/sites/mikeozanian/2013/04/04/big-east-to-be-renamed-american-athletic-conference/</link><title>Big East To Be Renamed American Athletic Conference</title><description>Mike Aresco became the commissioner of the Big East last summer as the conference was in the midst of tumult. Syracuse was on its way out of the conference and a few months later DePaul, Marquette, Georgetown, Providence, St. John's, Seton Hall and Villanova announced they were bolting the Big East [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>