<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7063">Spanish unemployment</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:07:19" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7063-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7063_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:07:20">http://www.forbes.com/sites/danalexander/2013/02/08/with-youth-unemployment-at-55-percent-spanish-students-take-to-the-streets/</link><title>With Youth Unemployment At 55 Percent, Spanish Students Take To The Streets</title><description>Spain's Popular Party, led by Prime Minister Mariano Rajoy, passed a $4 billion cut to public education in May and has proposed an overhaul of the education system. MADRID — On most weekday afternoons, 21-year-old Spanish student John Suarez is sitting in class at his school on the outskirts of [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7063-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7063_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:11:55">http://www.forbes.com/sites/stephenpope/2012/11/30/spanish-usufruct/</link><title>Spanish Usufruct</title><description>Countries using the Euro de jure Countries and territories using the Euro de facto Countries in the EU not using the Euro (Photo credit: Wikipedia) One never ceases to be amazed at the number of popinjay’s that strut about the Eurozone. Jose Manuel Gonzalez-Paramo is a former ECB Executive Board member and [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7063-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7063_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:15:40">http://www.forbes.com/sites/deanpopplewell/2013/01/17/spanish-bulls-chase-eur-higher/</link><title>Spanish Bulls Chase Euro Higher</title><description>Forex markets are eyeing their brethren, the bond market, for direction. Spain and France both come to the bond market today and whether they are successful or not will ultimately decide the direction that the EUR will take in the medium term. Obviously, the ‘single’ currency’s recovery over the past two quarters has been strongly correlated to [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7063-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7063_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:17:53">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ceciliarodriguez/2013/02/24/bad-timing-for-a-royal-spanish-scandal/</link><title>Bad Timing for a Royal Spanish Scandal</title><description>If this scandal had happened in better economic times it probably would have been shut down without a stretch, as are most embarrassments relating to Europe's various royal families. A few phone calls in the name of the king, the queen or other royal representatives to some privileged connections or [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7063-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7063_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:18:20">http://www.forbes.com/sites/benzingainsights/2012/08/01/spanish-italian-economies-show-signs-of-life/</link><title>Spanish, Italian Economies Show Signs of Life</title><description>Eurozone growth slowed in July, as the debt, financial, and unemployment crises continue to cripple the continents economy. Data released overnight showed that the European economy slowed in July from June ever so slightly. However, peripheral nations including Spain and Italy actually showed some signs of life. The Eurozone Purchasing Managers [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7063-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7063_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:20:44">http://www.forbes.com/sites/michaelpento/2012/08/07/why-more-money-printing-will-increase-unemployment/</link><title>Why More Money Printing Will Increase Unemployment</title><description>(Image credit: AFP/Getty Images via @daylife) The developed world’s central banks are now foolishly preparing for a full assault on their respective currencies in an attempt to lower unemployment rates. Spurring these central bankers into action is persistently anemic markets and employment data, which they believe can be rectified by [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7063-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7063_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:24:34">http://www.forbes.com/sites/billharris/2012/10/05/unemployment-rate-falls-stocks-rise-on-mixed-economic-news/</link><title>Unemployment Rate Falls, Stocks Rise on Mixed Economic News</title><description>Mario Draghi, ECB President (Photo credit: World Economic Forum) This is a guest post by Craig Birk, director of portfolio management at Personal Capital. In typical bull market fashion, stocks rose on mixed economic news. Friday’s monthly jobs report, the last before the Presidential election, was better than expected, pushing the unemployment [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7063-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7063_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:25:54">http://www.forbes.com/sites/afontevecchia/2012/11/09/spanish-woman-commits-suicide-as-foreclosure-agents-walk-into-her-apartment/</link><title>Spanish Woman Commits Suicide As Foreclosure Agents Walk Into Her Apartment</title><description>A woman jumped to her death in Spain as foreclosure agents forced open her door on Friday. This isn't an isolated case, last month, a man hung himself hours before being foreclosed on, while another attempted, and failed, to commit suicide before foreclosure. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7063-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7063_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:26:54">http://www.forbes.com/sites/afontevecchia/2012/06/27/spanish-banks-capital-shortfall-substantially-bigger-than-stress-tests-show/</link><title>Spanish Bank Stress Tests Dramatically Underestimate Capital Shortfall</title><description>The Spanish banking sector audits charged with figuring out how much capital was needed to shore those banks up in a stress scenario failed to represent a truly pessimistic situation, thus underestimating how much capital they actually need. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7063-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7063_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:29:26">http://www.forbes.com/2010/12/01/spain-ireland-banking-opinions-columnists-nouriel-roubini.html</link><title>A Spanish Inquisition</title><description>With Ireland's financial woes exposed, Spain's similarities warrant inspection. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>