<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7064">Korea weather</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:30:55" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7064-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7064_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:30:56">http://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesasia/2013/11/20/things-are-brewing-in-north-koreas-rason-zone/</link><title>Things Are Brewing In North Korea's Rason Zone</title><description>The favorable omens and long odds of North Korea's Rason zone. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7064-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7064_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:33:30">http://www.forbes.com/sites/patrickhanlon/2013/02/06/why-korea-needs-to-become-a-brand-2/</link><title>Why Korea Needs To Become A Brand</title><description>Korea’s Samsung Electronics Co. announced Tuesday that it capped its best year ever with another record quarterly profit. Korean car manufacturer Hyundai announced another year of record auto sales—double digits over the previous year’s record-breaking sales. Korean Air continues to delight flyers, and  South Korean rapper Psy's video 'Gangnam [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7064-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7064_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:36:38">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jesscollen/2013/04/05/cyberattacks-is-north-korea-already-at-war-with-us/</link><title>Cyberattacks -- Is North Korea Already At War With Us?</title><description>Citigroup Center (Photo credit: chrisswann26) Cyberattacks keep affecting a record number of companies internationally. Yet the 27 largest American companies that have reported cyberattacks also report that they have suffered no severe financial damages. The government disagrees. The U.S. Government reports the losses to be in the billions. [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7064-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7064_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:40:47">http://www.forbes.com/sites/patrickhanlon/2013/01/11/why-korea-needs-to-become-a-brand/</link><title>Why Korea Needs To Become A Brand</title><description>Camiseta de PSY 'Gangnam Style' (Photo credit: nvivo.es, 5gig) Korea’s Samsung Electronics Co. announced Tuesday that it capped its best year ever with another record quarterly profit. Korean car manufacturer Hyundai announced another year of record auto sales—double digits over the previous year’s record-breaking sales. South Korean [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7064-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7064_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:44:09">http://www.forbes.com/sites/andrewsalmon/2014/04/16/seaborne-tragedy-gathers-pace-off-south-korea/</link><title>Hundreds Missing After Passenger Ferry Sinks Off South Korean Coast</title><description>Tragedy unfolded across South Korea Wednesday as a passenger vessel with 459 persons aboard sank in the Yellow Sea off the southwest coast of the peninsula. Reports were confused, but latest information indicates four people confirmed dead, with 291 unaccounted for. The cause of the disaster is unknown. The Sewol (“Time and [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7064-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7064_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:47:28">http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidewalt/2012/12/12/north-korean-rocket-reaches-orbit/</link><title>North Korea Rockets To Orbit, Renews Concerns Of Global Threat</title><description>Observers are concerned that the militaristic country will soon be capable of firing missiles that reach the United States. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7064-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7064_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:49:13">http://www.forbes.com/sites/dougbandow/2012/11/26/the-new-north-korea-prisons-with-designer-hand-cuffs/</link><title>The "New" North Korea: Prisons With Designer Hand-Cuffs</title><description>Washington should limit its ambitions in dealing with Pyongyang. There is little upside. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7064-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7064_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:52:03">http://www.forbes.com/sites/dougbandow/2012/04/16/north-korea-a-paper-tiger-threatens-the-peace/</link><title>North Korea: A Paper Tiger Threatens the Peace</title><description>By Doug Bandow Dealing with North Korea always leaves a sense of déjà vu.  Whether Pyongyang is making threats, proposing negotiations, pocketing concessions, or violating agreements, the U.S. and its allies have heard it all before.  The Democratic People’s Republic of Korea is perfectly predictable in an unpredictable sort of way. Dealing [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7064-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7064_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:53:13">http://www.forbes.com/sites/billflax/2011/12/27/north-koreas-plight-proves-the-power-of-markets/</link><title>North Korea's Plight Proves the Power of Markets</title><description>Much can be learned from Korea’s competing economic visions. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7064-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7064_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:55:25">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jonspringer/2014/03/21/mongolia-growth-groups-new-ceo-seeks-step-change/</link><title>Mongolia Growth Group's New CEO Seeks Step Change</title><description>Paul J. Byrne has moved from a global financial center with first world comforts and warm weather temperatures during winter months to an infrastructure needy country with winter temperatures that go down to minus 40. As a longtime shareholder of Mongolia Growth Group – a Mongolia real estate investment and [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>