<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7067">used kindle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:58:20" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7067-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7067_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 11:58:20">http://www.forbes.com/sites/anthonykosner/2014/04/15/large-screen-apple-iphones-and-amazon-kindle-phones-and-the-rise-of-mobile-video/</link><title>Large Screen Apple iPhones and Amazon Kindle Phones And The Rise Of Mobile Video</title><description>Steve Jobs dismissed large screen smartphones and 7" tablets as "tweeners." Maybe he should have talked to actual tweens who prefer the convenience of mobile video. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7067-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7067_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:00:06">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2013/12/21/amazon-kindle-fire-hdx-8-9-review-an-unmatched-hardware-experience/</link><title>Amazon Kindle Fire HDX 8.9 Review: An Unmatched Hardware Experience</title><description>Amazon has spent the last few years building up their hardware line, starting with the e-ink Kindles, and moving on to tablets powered by their own variant of Android. The latest tablet is the Kindle Fire HDX 8.9, and I've spent the last week finding out what this tablet can do. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7067-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7067_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:01:03">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2013/12/22/kindle-paperwhite-review-if-only-every-e-book-reader-was-this-good/</link><title>Kindle Paperwhite Review: If Only Every E-Book Reader Was This Good</title><description>Amazon is at the top of the tree in terms of e-ink based readers. With the Kindle devices now in their sixth generation, how does the 2013 version of the Kindle Paperwhite measure up to the task of on-the-go reading of digital texts? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7067-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7067_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:01:46">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jeremygreenfield/2013/10/30/kindle-most-popular-device-for-ebooks-beating-out-ipad-tablets-on-the-rise/</link><title>Kindle Most Popular Device For Ebooks, Beating Out iPad; Tablets On The Rise</title><description>More people who read ebooks own an Amazon Kindle dedicated e-reader than own an Apple iPad -- or any other device for that matter. As more people buy tablets and fewer buy e-readers, however, that fact is set to flip. According to a new study from the Book Industry Study Group, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7067-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7067_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:03:42">http://www.forbes.com/sites/matthickey/2013/09/06/will-amazon-combine-free-wireless-broadband-with-those-free-kindle-phones/</link><title>Will Amazon Combine Free Wireless Broadband With Those Free 'Kindle Phones'?</title><description>Kindle phone mock up el oh el Last weekend a friend of mine visited Seattle for the Penny Arcade Expo, or PAX. He’s an avid gamer but not much of a “tech guy” and I noticed he was in need of a new phone; his Palm Pre had a cracked screen, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7067-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7067_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:07:53">http://www.forbes.com/sites/forrester/2013/05/23/amazons-kindle-fire-hd-a-stealth-byod-tablet-competitor/</link><title>Amazon's Kindle Fire HD: A Stealth BYOD Tablet Competitor</title><description>By J.P. Gownder J.P. Gownder Amazon announced today that its Kindle Fire HD tablet offerings will rocket from availability in just seven markets (U.S., U.K., Germany, France, Spain, Italy and Japan) to 170+ countries in mid-June. The 7” and 8.9” Amazon Kindle Fire HD models have enjoyed great success in the consumer market, as Forrester predicted [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7067-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7067_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:09:55">http://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2013/02/14/is-amazon-ready-to-sell-used-digital-products/</link><title>Is Amazon Ready To Sell Used Digital Products?</title><description>While the patent doesn’t imply that such a marketplace will be launched anytime soon, it does show Amazon's interest in entering the online secondary market business that was pioneered by eBay. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7067-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7067_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:11:43">http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2013/05/30/why-digital-distribution-is-the-future-and-gamestop-is-not-taking-the-long-view-on-used-games/</link><title>Why Digital Distribution Is The Future And GameStop Is Not: Taking The Long View On Used Games</title><description>In the long run, the end of used games and brick-and-mortal retailers will be good for gamers and the video game industry. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7067-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7067_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:12:45">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jeremygreenfield/2013/03/11/what-happens-to-publishers-and-authors-if-a-used-ebook-market-becomes-legal/</link><title>What Happens to Publishers and Authors If a Used Ebook Market Becomes Legal?</title><description>Amazon has a patent to develop a market for used digital content. Apple has filed for a similar patent and ReDigi, a self-styled marketplace for used digital content, is currently embroiled in a legal battle with Capitol Records over the resale of digital music files. Basically, it looks like a used [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7067-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7067_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:16:54">http://www.forbes.com/sites/chuckjones/2013/02/04/kindle-fire-dominates-us-android-market-but-seemingly-non-existent-outside-the-us/</link><title>Kindle Fire Dominates US Android Market but Seemingly Non-existent Outside the US</title><description>Localytics, which has its software installed on over 500 million devices, analyzed the Android tablet market that used apps with Localytics analytics integrated and determined the following. The US accounted for 59% of Android tablets The US and Great Britain (5%) account for almost two-thirds of Android tablets In particular Amazon’s Kindle Fire [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>