<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7077">django django</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:30:08" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7077-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7077_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:30:09">http://www.forbes.com/sites/simonmontlake/2013/04/11/tarantinos-django-unchained-is-unplugged-by-chinese-regulators/</link><title>Tarantino's 'Django Unchained' Is Unplugged By Chinese Regulators</title><description>Chained in China (Image credit: AFP/Getty Images via @daylife) A toned-down cut of Quentin Tarantino's Oscar-winning slavery movie 'Django Unchained' opened Thursday in China. But not for long. In an embarrassing setback for Sony Pictures, Chinese regulators abruptly pulled the film from rotation, in some cases just minutes into the day's first [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7077-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7077_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:31:20">http://www.forbes.com/sites/igorgreenwald/2013/01/04/six-bullets-from-the-django-mba/</link><title>6 Bullets From the Django MBA</title><description>Django star Jamie Foxx and director Quentin Tarantino execute a business strategy I saw Django Unchained on New Year’s Eve, and after nearly three hours of honest, hard-working entertainment emerged with a Quentin Tarantino MBA. I hold these truths to be self-evident and liberated from dusty B-school case studies at long last. 1. [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7077-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7077_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:33:50">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markhughes/2012/12/21/django-unchained-a-masterpiece-from-the-king-of-genr/</link><title>'Django Unchained' - A Masterpiece From The King Of Genre</title><description>VideoJohn Houzer Smith's 'Django Unchained' Design The "D" may be silent, but the "A+" scores aren't. Quentin Tarantino's new spaghetti western Django Unchained delivers one of the best times you'll have at the movies all year, in the director's best film in almost two decades (which is saying a lot). First and [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7077-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7077_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:36:49">http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2012/06/15/quentin-tarantino-goes-western-with-django-unchained/</link><title>Quentin Tarantino Goes Western With 'Django Unchained'</title><description>Video I'm glad Tarantino's been tackling other genres outside of crime and martial arts. Inglorious Bastards was one of the best things the Pulp Fiction director has done in years, and Django Unchained looks great, in no small part thanks to the welcome reappearance of Cristoph Waltz. Waltz's Hans Landa basically stole the show [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7077-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7077_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:37:27">http://www.forbes.com/sites/anthonykosner/2012/06/08/tarantinos-django-unchained-trailer-blaxsploitation-meets-blazing-saddles/</link><title>Tarantino's "Django Unchained" Trailer: Blaxsploitation Meets Blazing Saddles</title><description>Video The first official trailer for Quentin Tarantino's next film, "Django Unchained," was just released and it's an all-out hoot. This "Southern," starring Christopher Waltz, Jamie Foxx and Leonardo DiCaprio, is a tribute to Spaghetti Westerns with enhanced Tarantino splatter. The trailer opens with Johnny Cash singing Ain't No Grave (Can Hold My [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7077-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7077_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:39:28">http://www.forbes.com/2009/09/11/teamwork-duos-buffett-leadership-managing-directorship.html</link><title>The Buffett And Munger Way</title><description>Eight famous pairings present a spectrum of the unique qualities and dynamic teamwork necessary for the effective management of innovative organizations. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7077-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7077_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:42:42">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markhughes/2013/12/20/review-the-wolf-of-wall-street-is-scorseses-finest-film-since-goodfellas/</link><title>Review - 'The Wolf Of Wall Street' Is Scorsese's Finest Film Since 'Goodfellas'</title><description>During the 23 years since the release of his iconic gangster film Goodfellas, director Martin Scorsese has given us many exceptional films -- Hugo, Shutter Island, The Departed, The Aviator, Gangs of New York, Casino, and Cape Fear. But with his new release The Wolf of Wall Street, Scorsese has delivered [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7077-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7077_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:44:56">http://www.forbes.com/sites/benkepes/2014/03/19/bitnami-the-boy-scout-of-cloud-applications/</link><title>Bitnami - The Boy Scout For Cloud Applications</title><description>Bitnami is kind of like the Boy Scout who helps the little old lady cross the street. Essentially the premise of Bitnami is simple - let users deploy the applications they want to use regardless of where they want to put them. Bitnami achieves this by having around 100 different [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7077-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7077_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:46:39">http://www.forbes.com/sites/dorothypomerantz/2013/04/24/hollywoods-china-solution-two-versions-of-some-movies/</link><title>Hollywood's China Solution: Two Versions Of Some Movies</title><description>Studios are finding dealing with China's many regulations increasingly frustrating. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7077-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7077_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:48:52">http://www.forbes.com/sites/dorothypomerantz/2013/01/11/millions-more-to-get-outraged-about-kathryn-bigelows-oscar-snub-as-zero-dark-thirty-opens-wide/</link><title>Millions More To Get Outraged About Kathryn Bigelow's Oscar Snub As 'Zero Dark Thirty' Opens Wide</title><description>The film is expected to top the box office this weekend with $26 million.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>