<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7078">count in korean</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:50:31" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7078-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7078_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:50:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/donaldkirk/2014/02/26/kim-yu-nasilver-at-sochi-wins-gold-in-korean-hearts/</link><title>Kim Yu-Na, Silver At Sochi, Wins Gold In Hearts Of Korean People</title><description>If there were a gold medal for good sportsmanship, Korean figure skater Kim Yu-na would surely have been the winner at the Sochi Winter Olympics. While the protests flowed fast and furiously over her loss to the Russian Adelina Sotnikova, Yu-na showed she was as flawless off ice as on. From [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7078-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7078_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:53:08">http://www.forbes.com/sites/paulroderickgregory/2014/03/26/mr-putin-tear-down-that-potemkin-village/</link><title>Mr. Putin: Tear Down That Potemkin Village In Crimea</title><description>Why did Mr. Putin insist on a ludicrous North-Korean-Soviet-era election result instead of a 60 percent vote that could have been more credibly manipulated and explained? Throughout his Ukrainian campaign, Putin’s propaganda machine has used hyperbole and extreme exaggeration. The Euro Maidan demonstrators were all neo Nazis or extremists, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7078-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7078_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:56:56">http://www.forbes.com/sites/donaldkirk/2014/02/23/foreign-factories-in-north-koreas-kaesong-complex-great-idea-or-pie-in-the-sky/</link><title>Foreign Factories In North Korea's Kaesong Complex -- Great Idea Or Pie In The Sky?</title><description>In the realm of believe-it-not, the Kaesong Industrial Complex just above the line between North and South Korea is beginning to appear as perhaps the best hope for the western world to gain a significant toehold into the closed society of North Korea. So desperate is North Korea for cash that [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7078-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7078_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:00:35">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ryanmac/2014/02/19/whatsapp-founders-become-billionaires-in-19-billion-deal-with-facebook/</link><title>WhatsApp Founders Become Billionaires In $19 Billion Facebook Deal</title><description>WhatsApp cofounders Jan Koum and Brian Acton are Silicon Valley's newest billionaires thanks to a $19 billion deal with Facebook. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7078-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7078_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:01:42">http://www.forbes.com/sites/luisakroll/2013/01/31/convicted-south-korean-billionaire-may-be-headed-to-jail-again/</link><title>Convicted South Korean Billionaire May Be Headed To Jail, Again</title><description>South Korean Billionaire Chey Tae-Won was sentenced to four years in prison on Thursday for embezzling millions of dollars of company money for personal investments.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7078-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7078_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:03:12">http://www.forbes.com/sites/haydnshaughnessy/2014/02/05/will-the-samsung-galaxy-s5-surpass-the-apple-5s/</link><title>Will There Be Enough In The Galaxy S5 To Compete With The iPhone 5S?</title><description>It seems almost certain now that the Samsung Galaxy S5 will launch ahead of schedule, with an unpacking on February 24th and a launch in time to contribute to Samsung's Q1 earnings. Samsung was beaten up badly by Apple following the launch of the latter's iPhone 5S at the end of [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7078-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7078_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:05:05">http://www.forbes.com/sites/donaldkirk/2014/01/05/for-kim-jong-uns-birthday-dennis-rodmans-nba-stars-in-north-korea/</link><title>For Kim Jong-un's Birthday: Rodman's NBA Stars In N. Korea</title><description>North Korea’s “supreme leader” Kim Jong-un seems sure of a terrific birthday bash on Wednesday thanks to basketball buddy Dennis Rodman bringing over a team of former NBA players to join in the festivities. While Kim’s exact age remains a mystery, the show featuring Rodman’s “dream team” against the North Korean [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7078-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7078_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:08:06">http://www.forbes.com/2010/02/13/census-population-count-polls-opinions-columnists-karlyn-bowman.html</link><title>Census Counts</title><description>A look into the U.S. decennial survey. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7078-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7078_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:10:29">http://www.forbes.com/sites/connieguglielmo/2013/11/21/apple-gets-290-5-million-in-damages-from-samsung-in-patent-penalty-review-but-its-not-over-yet/</link><title>Apple Gets $290.5 Million In Damages From Samsung In Patent Penalty Review -- But It's Not Over Yet</title><description>Updates to include breakout of jury award. Apple was awarded $290.5 million in additional damages by a jury today as part of its 2012 patent victory over mobile device rival Samsung. The award is less than the $380 million Apple was seeking, and it brings the company's total award in the patent [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7078-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7078_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:11:25">http://www.forbes.com/sites/billsinger/2012/01/09/the-desperate-stockbroker-and-her-fathers-korean-war-medals/</link><title>The Desperate Stockbroker and Her Father's Korean War Medals</title><description>In response to an angry customer, one broker offers her father's war medals and jewelry but to no avail read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>