<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7082">The raven</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:04:49" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7082-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7082_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:04:51">http://www.forbes.com/sites/dividendchannel/2014/03/14/raven-industries-becomes-oversold-ravn/</link><title>Raven Industries Becomes Oversold (RAVN)</title><description>Legendary investor Warren Buffett advises to be fearful when others are greedy, and be greedy when others are fearful. One way we can try to measure the level of fear in a given stock is through a technical analysis indicator called the Relative Strength Index, or RSI, which measures momentum [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7082-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7082_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:05:19">http://www.forbes.com/sites/chrissmith/2013/02/01/can-the-baltimore-ravens-afford-to-keep-joe-flacco/</link><title>Can The Baltimore Ravens Afford To Keep Joe Flacco?</title><description>All signs point to Baltimore re-signing quarterback Joe Flacco, but doing so may cost the team its competitive future.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7082-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7082_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:08:58">http://www.forbes.com/sites/richardbusch/2013/01/09/the-ravens-beat-the-colts-last-weekend-but-will-their-old-logo-be-a-loss-for-madden-nfl/</link><title>The Ravens Beat the Colts Last Weekend, But Will Their Old Logo Be a Loss for Madden NFL?</title><description>EAST RUTHERFORD, NJ - SEPTEMBER 13: Ray Lewis #52 of the Baltimore Ravens reacts after defeating the New York Jets during their home opener at the New Meadowlands Stadium on September 13, 2010 in East Rutherford, New Jersey. (Image credit: Getty Images North America via @daylife) Legendary Baltimore Ravens linebacker Ray [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7082-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7082_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:13:03">http://www.forbes.com/sites/monteburke/2013/02/03/the-baltimore-ravens-beat-the-san-francisco-49ers-in-a-wild-super-bowl/</link><title>The Baltimore Ravens Beat The San Francisco 49ers In A Wild Super Bowl</title><description>Joe Flacco (Image credit: Getty Images via @daylife) The Baltimore Ravens defeated the San Francisco 34-31 in the 47th edition of what’s become America’s great secular holiday, the Super Bowl. The game looked like a loser in the first half. Ravens quarterback, Joe Flacco, threw for three touchdowns, looking very much like [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7082-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7082_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:18:13">http://www.forbes.com/sites/monteburke/2013/01/20/the-san-francisco-49ers-and-the-baltimore-ravens-will-meet-in-the-super-bowl-the-storylines/</link><title>The San Francisco 49ers And The Baltimore Ravens Will Meet In The Super Bowl: The Storylines</title><description>Ray Lewis (Photo credit: Keith Allison) The San Francisco 49ers came back to beat the Atlanta Falcons, 28-24, in a true thriller. The Baltimore Ravens came back to beat the New England Patriots, 28-13, in a game that may have lacked the drama of the first, but still had its moments. [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7082-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7082_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:21:28">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johnhall/2013/02/04/5-lessons-you-can-learn-from-the-baltimore-ravens-championship-season/</link><title>5 Lessons You Can Learn from the Baltimore Ravens' Championship Season</title><description>Success is so much sweeter when you can look back at the barriers you toppled in order to win. I’m about as far away from being a Ravens fan as you can be, but I completely respect the challenges they overcame to hoist the Vince Lombardi Trophy last night. (Chris Graythen/Getty [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7082-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7082_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:25:22">http://www.forbes.com/sites/anthonynitti/2013/02/04/congratulations-to-the-baltimore-ravens-now-pay-your-louisiana-tax-bill/</link><title>Congratulations To The Baltimore Ravens! Now Pay Your Louisiana Tax Bill</title><description>While last night’s Super Bowl was certainly thrilling the game did leave a few lingering questions.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7082-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7082_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:29:02">http://www.forbes.com/sites/paulhodgson/2012/06/06/chesapeake-energy-the-governance-ravens-come-home-to-roost/</link><title>Chesapeake Energy: the Governance Ravens Come Home to Roost</title><description>The following is an excerpt from our forthcoming report, Ratings Foresights, which summarizes a few of the companies where GMI Ratings made predictions that governance, accounting, environmental and/or social failures would lead to significant value destruction. Indeed, in November 2007, this is what we wrote: We are downgrading our rating on read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7082-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7082_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:29:48">http://www.forbes.com/sites/dividendchannel/2012/07/05/cash-dividend-on-the-way-from-raven-industries-inc-ravn/</link><title>Cash Dividend On The Way From Raven Industries, Inc. (RAVN)</title><description>Looking at the universe of stocks we cover at Dividend Channel, on 7/6/12, Raven Industries, Inc. (NASD: RAVN) will trade ex-dividend, for its quarterly dividend of $0.21, payable on 7/25/12. As a percentage of RAVN's recent stock price of $72.10, this dividend works out to approximately 0.29%. Click here to find [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7082-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7082_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:33:16">http://www.forbes.com/sites/prishe/2013/01/03/ray-lewis-100-125-million-impact-on-the-growth-of-baltimore-ravens-franchise-value/</link><title>Ray Lewis' $100-125 Million Impact on the Growth of Baltimore Ravens Franchise Value</title><description>Last Home Stand for Ray Lewis of the Baltimore Ravens this Sunday Versus Indianapolis Emotions will run high at M&amp;T Bank Stadium on Sunday as Ray Lewis will in all likelihood be playing his last home game with a team whose tenure in Baltimore mirrors his own. From 1996 to the present, [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>