<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7083">I'm on the road again</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:36:28" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7083-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7083_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:36:29">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jamesgruber/2014/03/23/investors-fall-for-indonesia/</link><title>Investors Are Falling For Indonesia Again</title><description>Indonesia has gone from being part of the "fragile five" to a quasi market darling. The optimism appears overdone. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7083-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7083_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:37:52">http://www.forbes.com/sites/groupthink/2013/11/22/recipe-for-fundraising-starbucks-humble-pie-and-p-o-d/</link><title>Tough Knocks Along The Road To Fundraising</title><description>Fundraising on a larger scale was an experience I sought out and dove into it. It was even harder than I thought it would be, and here’s what I learned along the way. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7083-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7083_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:40:31">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonfogelson/2014/03/05/yamaha-champions-riding-school-teaches-motorcycling-on-the-track/</link><title>Yamaha Champions Riding School Teaches Motorcycling On The Track</title><description>The Yamaha Champions Riding School trains motorcyclists to be safer on the street -- by putting them on the racetrack. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7083-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7083_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:43:00">http://www.forbes.com/sites/wallaceforbes/2014/04/01/make-as-much-money-as-you-can-without-taking-on-lots-of-risk/</link><title>(Try To) Make As Much Money As You Can, Without Taking On Lots Of Risk</title><description>Larry Pitkowsky and Keith Trauner, Co-Founders, Managing Partners, and Co-Portfolio Managers, GoodHaven Capital Management &amp; the GoodHaven Fund Larry Pitkowsky: Keith and I started our firm and the GoodHaven Fund to capitalize on our prior success and take advantage of our decades of experience in value investing. We approach investing in [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7083-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7083_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:45:00">http://www.forbes.com/sites/emc/2013/11/05/help-im-stuck-in-the-muck-of-my-job-part-i/</link><title>EMC​Voice: Help! I'm Stuck in the Muck of My Job, Part I</title><description>I have no idea how sage writers churn out endless gems in books that help us better navigate our careers but they do. I’m not a voracious reader but I have stumbled on a few books that seem to parallel my thought process. My short list includes: Good to Great: Why Some [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7083-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7083_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:49:50">http://www.forbes.com/sites/andygreenberg/2013/12/20/at-least-two-moderators-of-the-silk-road-2-0-drug-site-forums-arrested/</link><title>At Least Two Moderators Of 'Silk Road 2.0' Drug Site Forums Arrested</title><description>The resurrection of the popular Silk Road drug website known as "Silk Road 2.0" has been online for less than two months. But law enforcement already seems to be closing its net. On Friday morning an FBI source told me that agents have now made multiple arrests related to the website, [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7083-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7083_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:53:24">http://www.forbes.com/sites/fathom/2014/03/29/take-a-family-boat-trip-around-the-british-virgin-islands/</link><title>Take A Family Boat Trip Around The British Virgin Islands</title><description>Live on a boat instead of a hotel? With a family? Fathom contributor Malia Frame was skeptical — and then she tried it. And liked it so much she went back. Here's her guide to the best aquatic road trip around the British Virgin Islands. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7083-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7083_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:56:10">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jamesgruber/2013/07/27/the-royal-road-to-riches/</link><title>The Royal Road To Riches</title><description>With euphoria returning to equity markets, it's worth remembering that stocks are unlikely to make you really rich. We have some ideas what might though. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7083-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7083_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 15:57:33">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markhughes/2014/02/07/the-counselor-blu-ray-offers-new-vision-on-screen-and-behind-the-scenes/</link><title>'The Counselor' Blu-Ray Offers New Vision On Screen And Behind The Scenes - UPDATED</title><description>VideoDirector Ridley Scott's morality tale The Counselor comes to DVD and Blu-ray next week on February 11 (it is already available on Digital-HD), offering an extended cut with deleted footage, plus some of the best behind-the-scenes extras I've seen in a long time. My original full review of the theatrical [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7083-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7083_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:00:12">http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2014/03/24/the-walking-dead-season-4-episode-15-review-family-reunion/</link><title>'The Walking Dead' Season 4, Episode 15 Review: Family Reunion</title><description>'The Walking Dead' Season 4 finally starts reuniting characters after their mid-season diaspora. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>