<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7084">Burn after reading review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:02:54" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7084-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7084_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:02:55">http://www.forbes.com/sites/scottmendelson/2014/02/05/review-george-clooneys-monuments-men-is-important-but-mediocre/</link><title>Review: George Clooney's 'Monuments Men' Is Important But Mediocre</title><description>The Box Office: Here's a fun little fact: Barring some kind of added value, George Clooney star-vehicles tend to open to around $13 million. I'm not talking about the all-star Ocean's trilogy or blockbusters like Batman &amp; Robin, The Perfect Storm, or Gravity. I'm talking about the old-school star vehicles that Clooney has consistently used his [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7084-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7084_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:05:51">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markhughes/2013/10/26/review-the-counselor-gets-a-mixed-verdict/</link><title>Review: 'The Counselor' Gets A Mixed Verdict</title><description>VideoThe Counselor, the newest film from director Ridley Scott and the first feature film written by acclaimed novelist Cormac McCarthy, has an early scene in which protagonist Michael Fassbender speaks with a jeweler about diamonds. Diamonds, the jeweler explains, are defined by their flaws. It's a theme that applies very [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7084-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7084_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:09:50">http://www.forbes.com/sites/scottmendelson/2013/10/10/blu-ray-review-batman-the-dark-knight-returns-deluxe-edition-is-a-needless-double-dip/</link><title>Blu Ray Review: 'Batman: The Dark Knight Returns' Deluxe Edition Is Needless Double-Dip</title><description>It's bad enough that the DCAU is dominated by Batman and Superman titles.  It's bad enough that they saw fit to do an adaptation of The Dark Knight Returns, surely a graphic novel that needs no wider fan base, while splitting it up into two releases.  But now, as somewhat [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7084-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7084_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:10:29">http://www.forbes.com/sites/scottmendelson/2014/02/09/weekend-box-office-lego-movie-opens-to-69-million/</link><title>Weekend Box Office: 'LEGO Movie' Opens To $69 Million</title><description>Everything is indeed awesome for anyone connected to The LEGO Movie. The much anticipated LEGO Movie debuted this weekend with a with a dynamite $69.1 million. That figure includes $17.14m on Friday and a whopping $30.9m on Saturday, an 80% increase. Throw in a $21m Sunday (yes, 22% more than Friday), and you [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7084-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7084_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:14:41">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonevangelho/2012/11/27/review-60-days-with-a-digital-storm-ode-v2-gaming-pc/</link><title>Review: Digital Storm ODE V2 Gaming PC</title><description>Crafting the perfect PC gaming rig is a lot like preparing the perfect meal: it’s all about the components complimenting each other, merging together in harmony and transforming into something greater than the sum of their parts. After 60 days with Digital Storm’s ODE V2 gaming system, I’m convinced the Fremont, CA-based company has captured that [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7084-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7084_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:16:42">http://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2010/06/10/reading-chinas-mixed-signals/</link><title>Reading China's Mixed Signals</title><description>Whether China is in a boom or a bubble, the nation is rich and getting richer. Get your share. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7084-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7084_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:17:43">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ryanholiday/2012/05/14/read-to-lead-the-secret-code-for-cracking-tough-books-and-reading-above-your-level/</link><title>Read to Lead: The Secret Code for Cracking 'Tough' Books and Reading Above Your Level</title><description>(Image credit: Getty Images via @daylife) The best advice I've ever got about reading came from a secretive movie producer and talent manager who'd sold more than 100 million albums and done more than $1B in box office returns. He said to me one day, "Ryan, it's not enough that you [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7084-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7084_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:21:27">http://www.forbes.com/sites/francinemckenna/2012/09/04/jeff-connaughtons-the-payoff-why-wall-street-always-wins-a-book-review/</link><title>Jeff Connaughton's "The Payoff: Why Wall Street Always Wins" A Book Review</title><description>Jeff Connaughton has a new job: truth teller. The Payoff: Why Wall Street Always Wins is a memoir and more, covering Connaughton’s twenty-plus years working, one way or another, for Senator, and now Vice President, Joe Biden. He’s a “Professional Democrat” turned Washington lobbyist who sought answers, and pushed for reforms, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7084-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7084_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:25:05">http://www.forbes.com/sites/andygreenberg/2010/09/10/will-youtube-censor-burn-a-koran-day-and-should-it/</link><title>Will YouTube Censor "Burn A Koran Day"? And Should It?</title><description>Even if networks don't broadcast burning Korans Saturday, the world's largest video site likely will. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7084-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7084_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:27:25">http://www.forbes.com/sites/peterjreilly/2013/11/19/live-from-gettysburg-address-sesquicentennial/</link><title>Live From Gettysburg Address Sesquicentennial</title><description>It was quiet in Gettysburg yesterday afternoon. My covivant and I stopped at the National Cemetery around 4:00 and only a couple of people were there.  Plastic chairs were already set up facing the podium.  A large screen was setup in the field near Meade's Headquarters where the ceremonies will be [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>