<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7088">Ezz-thetic</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:59:30" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7088-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7088_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 16:59:30">http://www.forbes.com/sites/christophercoats/2013/11/08/egypt-moves-to-meet-surging-energy-needs/</link><title>Egypt Moves To Meet Surging Energy Needs</title><description>Faced with surging local demand and billions in energy sector debt, Egypt has laid out a series of new oil and gas efforts meant to boost domestic production and finally offer some relief for a government in desperate need of it. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7088-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7088_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:00:05">http://www.forbes.com/sites/robertlenzner/2013/12/05/the-inequality-boom-has-become-president-obamas-number-one-priority/</link><title>The Inequality Boom Has Put 100 Million Americans Below the Poverty Line</title><description>The "Inequality Boom" is what social scientist Sheldon Danziger, President of the Russell Sage Foundation here in New York, uses to describe the current condition of 100 million Americans -- if the cost of housing, transportation and healthcare were subtracted from the median income of full-time workers. It's a boom [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7088-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7088_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:04:41">http://www.forbes.com/sites/abrambrown/2012/05/29/firebombs-and-elections-aside-egyptian-stocks-look-undervalued/</link><title>Firebombs And Elections Aside, Egyptian Stocks Look Undervalued</title><description>In Egypt, undervalued companies are as plentiful as ancient tombs. That's the thesis from Citi's Hasnain Malik. (Image credit: AFP/Getty Images via @daylife) All your attention focused on Europe? Maybe you should look further south. To Egypt, that is. The Land of the Pharaohs is as rich with depleted tombs as undervalued [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7088-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7088_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:07:52">http://www.forbes.com/sites/zinamoukheiber/2011/03/30/president-assad-and-the-syrian-business-elite/</link><title>President Assad And The Syrian Business Elite</title><description>Syrian President Bashar al-Assad addressed the Parliament today in the wake of deadly protests, but offered little in the way of reform. He acknowledged that although reforming the country’s institutions was important, it took a backseat to stability.  Back in January Assad gave a rare interview to the Wall Street Journal.  [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>