<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7091">don't listen to a word i say</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:17:03" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7091-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7091_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:17:04">http://www.forbes.com/sites/investor/2014/03/26/why-i-still-wouldnt-buy-apple/</link><title>Why I Still Wouldn't Buy Apple</title><description>Five reasons why Apple isn't a buy.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7091-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7091_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:20:38">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jennifereum/2014/02/04/warren-buffetts-idea-of-heaven-i-dont-have-to-work-with-people-i-dont-like/</link><title>Warren Buffett's Idea Of Heaven: "I Don't Have To Work With People I Don't Like"</title><description>EDITOR'S NOTE: Forbes launched an e-book on Warren Buffett today. In it you'll find Forbes and ForbesLife magazine profiles from 1969 to 2013 written by staffers and Buffett himself. The feature below can be found in the e-book along with 14 others that shed light on the philanthropist Buffett has become [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7091-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7091_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:21:06">http://www.forbes.com/sites/theyec/2014/04/18/10-steps-for-giving-a-convincing-sales-pitch/</link><title>10 Steps For Giving A Convincing Sales Pitch</title><description>Selling is the #1 activity entrepreneurs need to master but for most, it's also their weakest link. Here are 10 steps to get comfortable selling -- to anyone. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7091-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7091_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:23:07">http://www.forbes.com/sites/brucekasanoff/2014/04/06/2-little-tips-for-a-big-life/</link><title>20 Little Tips For A Big Career And Life</title><description>I structure my career and life around a simple sentence: Be generous and expert, trustworthy and clear, open-minded and adaptable, persistent and present. To keep this sentence in the front of my mind, I look for specific tips that support these qualities. Here are some of my favorites: 1. [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7091-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7091_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:26:34">http://www.forbes.com/sites/bobegan/2014/04/11/a-billion-smartphones-users-may-be-affected-by-the-heartbleed-security-flaw/</link><title>A Billion Smartphone Users May Be Affected by the Heartbleed Security Flaw</title><description>Heartbleed may be a billion times worse than you thought. The Internet security world and the media have sounded alarms about potential vulnerabilities for consumers using “desktop” browsers to visit websites that may be running bogus server code. Yet little attention has been paid to the global problem of 40-60 billion [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7091-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7091_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:30:12">http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikaandersen/2014/03/03/how-to-be-a-successful-salesperson-especially-if-you-think-you-cant/</link><title>How To Be A Successful Salesperson - Especially If You Think You Can't</title><description>Today, everyone has to sell. Here's how to break through almost everyone's biggest barrier to selling. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7091-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7091_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:31:17">http://www.forbes.com/sites/nextavenue/2014/03/28/7-secrets-to-get-good-customer-service-by-phone/</link><title>7 Secrets To Get Good Customer Service By Phone</title><description>Agents are now better trained, if you can get past phone purgatory. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7091-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7091_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:32:42">http://www.forbes.com/sites/danschawbel/2014/03/15/john-jantsch-why-sales-teams-must-have-a-marketing-mindset/</link><title>John Jantsch: Why Sales Teams Must Have A Marketing Mindset</title><description>Both the marketing and sales world has changed over the past decade with the introduction of new tools and technologies. In order to learn more about this change and what people can do, I spoke to John Jantsch. He is a marketing consultant and author of Duct Tape Marketing, The [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7091-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7091_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:36:37">http://www.forbes.com/sites/robasghar/2014/03/25/a-spring-cleaning-for-your-career-toss-out-these-5-excuses-today/</link><title>A Spring Cleaning For Your Career: Toss Out These 5 Excuses Today</title><description>The spring cleaning is a tradition that dates back centuries. The concept can also be a valuable one for our careers, especially since we’ve managed by now to forget our New Year’s resolutions. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7091-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7091_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 17:39:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/tonybradley/2013/10/14/in-their-own-words-iosafe-founder-and-ceo-robb-moore/</link><title>In Their Own Words: ioSafe Founder And CEO Robb Moore</title><description>VideoAre you familiar with ioSafe? This small company has made a name for itself by creating external and portable data storage devices capable of surviving just about any possible disaster. ioSafe is known for making dramatic presentations at the annual CES event in Las Vegas. Robb Moore invites analysts and media [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>