<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7095">iron in water supply</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:31:24" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7095-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7095_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:31:25">http://www.forbes.com/sites/meghabahree/2014/03/12/doing-big-business-in-modis-gujarat/</link><title>Doing Big Business In Modi's Gujarat</title><description>India's most alluring GDP growth story looks different if you're Gautam Adani or a villager living off the land. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7095-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7095_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:32:38">http://www.forbes.com/sites/christopherhelman/2013/09/09/billionaire-battles-native-americans-over-iron-ore-mine/</link><title>Billionaire Battles Native Americans Over Iron Ore Mine</title><description>Chris Cline made a fortune in coal mines; now he's vying against the Chippewa to dig a giant iron ore mine in Wisconsin.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7095-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7095_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:34:59">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jamesconca/2013/02/04/fracking-with-bad-water/</link><title>Fracking With Bad Water</title><description>The Pennsylvania Department of Environmental Protection published a white paper in January detailing how the agency intends to review proposals from Oil &amp; Gas drillers on the use of Mine Influenced Water (MIW) or acid mine drainage for drilling operations such as fracking. The practice could save billions of gallons of fresh water each year. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7095-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7095_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:36:07">http://www.forbes.com/sites/quora/2013/05/03/how-close-are-we-to-a-real-iron-man-suit/</link><title>How Close Are We To A Real Iron Man Suit?</title><description>How close are we to a real Iron Man suit? This question was originally answered on Quora by Ariel Williams. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7095-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7095_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:38:34">http://www.forbes.com/sites/oppenheimerfunds/2013/09/03/investing-in-the-u-s-energy-revolution/</link><title>OppenheimerFunds​Voice: Investing In The U.S. Energy Revolution</title><description>(Photo Credit: iStockPhoto) Until quite recently, the U.S.—the world’s largest energy consumer—faced what many believed to be an immutable and uncomfortable reality. With inadequate domestic supplies of accessible oil and natural gas, the U.S. would depend, indefinitely, on external sources for the lifeblood of its economy. This paradigm had deep [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7095-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7095_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:42:26">http://www.forbes.com/sites/randalllane/2013/11/17/how-americas-richest-people-are-bringing-hope-to-the-eighth-poorest-nation-in-the-world/</link><title>How America's Richest People Are Bringing Hope To The Eighth-Poorest Nation In The World</title><description>Can entrepreneurial market-based philanthropy fix one of the poorest spots on Earth? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7095-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7095_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:45:13">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ericagies/2011/08/23/game-changing-vacuum-creates-market-opportunity-to-clean-fracking-water/</link><title>Shale Gas Boom Creates Market Opportunity To Clean Fracking Water</title><description>As U.S. shale gas resources and hydraulic fracturing, or fracking, have entered the national consciousness, protests from nearby residents, then regulation, have followed. Yet rather than being bad for business, this regulation is actually spurring a new market in water technologies, according to a comprehensive report by the Artemis Project, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7095-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7095_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:49:49">http://www.forbes.com/sites/timtreadgold/2014/03/04/citi-man-drops-a-bucket-on-miners-parade/</link><title>Citi Man Drops A Bucket On Miners' Parade</title><description>If it's going to rain on your parade it would be nice to have the parade before the rain sets in, which is probably not what's going to happen at the world's top iron ore  conference next week. The problem is that the man scheduled to make the opening remarks at [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7095-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7095_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:53:18">http://www.forbes.com/sites/nadiaarumugam/2011/09/19/plastic-bottle-filters-can-help-millions-poisoned-by-arsenic-contaminated-water/</link><title>"Plastic Bottle" Filters Can Help Millions Poisoned by Arsenic-Contaminated Water</title><description>Scientists have just unveiled an easy-to-use, inexpensive method for removing arsenic from contaminated drinking water using chopped up bits of discarded plastic bottles. The plastic chips are first coated in cysteine - an amino acid nutrient that is commonly found in foods and nutritional supplements, before they can be used [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7095-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7095_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:54:29">http://www.forbes.com/sites/lydiadishman/2013/08/01/fashionably-late-hm-finally-launches-e-commerce-in-the-u-s/</link><title>Fashionably Late: H&amp;M Finally Launches E-Commerce In The U.S.</title><description>It’s taken 13 years from the time Swedish fashion retailer H&amp;M landed on American shores for it to finally launch an e-commerce site here.  Cue the sound of hundreds of thousands of fashionistas flexing their click fingers and whipping out their credit cards. H&amp;M’s been hedging on the promise made three [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>