<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7103">cystic fibrosis treatment</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:35:16" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7103-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7103_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:35:17">http://www.forbes.com/sites/investor/2014/04/10/low-priced-stock-buys-new-treatments-for-eye-disease-respiratory-difficulties/</link><title>Low-Priced Stock Buys: New Treatments For Eye Disease, Respiratory Difficulties</title><description>The health care sector is a good place to look for low-priced stocks with big potential. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7103-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7103_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:38:55">http://www.forbes.com/sites/edsilverman/2013/04/19/vertex-scores-a-big-win-with-its-cystic-fibrosis-experiment/</link><title>Vertex Scores A Big Win With Its Cystic Fibrosis Experiment</title><description>Vertex Pharmaceuticals released study results of a combination treatment for cystic fibrosis - its exsisting Kalydeco treatment and an experimental compound - that greatly increases its chances of thoroughly dominating this hard-to-treat market. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7103-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7103_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:39:23">http://www.forbes.com/sites/marketnewsvideo/2014/01/08/forest-labs-acquires-aptalis-for-2-9b/</link><title>Forest Labs Acquires Aptalis for $2.9B</title><description>This morning, Forest Labs (FRX) announced it had agreed to acquire Aptalis for $2.9 billion in cash. Aptalis is a privately held company that specializes in treatments for both cystic fibrosis and gastrointestinal issues. In the announcement, Forest Labs said it expects the acquisition to add 78 cents per share [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7103-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7103_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:41:58">http://www.forbes.com/sites/marketnewsvideo/2013/04/19/analyst-moves-vrtx-nflx-aph/</link><title>Analyst Moves: VRTX, NFLX, APH</title><description>This morning, Deutsche Bank increased its price target on shares of Vertex Pharmaceutical (VRTX) to $100 following news that the company's cystic fibrosis treatment is performing better than expected. Shares of VRTX were sharply higher this morning, gaining more than 55% on the news. Lazard increased its EPS estimates on shares [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7103-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7103_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:43:16">http://www.forbes.com/sites/matthewherper/2013/04/18/personalized-cystic-fibrosis-drugs-get-a-booster-shot/</link><title>Personalized Cystic Fibrosis Drugs Get A Booster Shot</title><description>Shares of Vertex Pharmaceuticals are up 51% in after-hours trading because of new test results of one of the company's drugs for cystic fibrosis, the genetic lung disease. The results may represent a new and promising chapter in one of the most important stories in medicine. Vertex already sells a drug [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7103-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7103_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:46:38">http://www.forbes.com/sites/matthewherper/2012/12/07/guest-post-pfizer-research-boss-on-why-hes-working-with-the-cystic-fibrosis-foundation/</link><title>Guest Post: Pfizer Research Boss On Why He's Working With The Cystic Fibrosis Foundation</title><description>This guest post was written by Mikael Dolsten, President, Worldwide R&amp;D, Pfizer, who just put on a bravura performance as one of the guest at our first annual Forbes Healthcare Summit. The week before, Dolsten attended another meeting, FasterCures' Partnering For Cures summit, and was inspired to send us this [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7103-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7103_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:50:03">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johnlamattina/2012/11/28/should-the-cystic-fibrosis-foundation-invest-58-million-in-pfizer-research/</link><title>Should the Cystic Fibrosis Foundation Invest $58 Million in Pfizer Research?</title><description>As National Institutes of Health (NIH)  funding has stagnated over the past few years, an increasingly important source of research funding for academic laboratories and start-up biotech companies has been non-profit organizations like the Michael J. Fox Foundation and the American Cancer Society. Researchers with exciting, cutting edge, but [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7103-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7103_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:52:02">http://www.forbes.com/2008/06/06/inspire-pharmaceuticals-biotech-markets-equity-cx_ra_0606markets41.html</link><title>Inspire Pharma Inspires Investors</title><description>The drug developer's shares skyrocketed on results from a study of its cystic fibrosis treatment. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7103-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7103_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:56:06">http://www.forbes.com/sites/matthewherper/2012/05/07/a-one-two-punch-against-cystic-fibrosis-and-maybe-someday-other-diseases-too/</link><title>A One-Two Punch Against Cystic Fibrosis, And Maybe Someday Other Diseases Too</title><description>New data on experimental drug combination being developed by Vertex Pharmaceuticals of Cambridge, Mass., should give hope to tens of thousands of people suffering from cystic fibrosis, the deadly lung disease that afflicts 70,000 people worldwide and kills most of them in their 20s. If the drug combo proves successful, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7103-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7103_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:59:01">http://www.forbes.com/sites/matthewherper/2011/02/23/vertex-may-make-history-with-cystic-fibrosis-drug/</link><title>Vertex May Make History With Cystic Fibrosis Drug</title><description>A new treatment far exceeded investors expectations in a late-stage clinical trial. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>