<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7104">How to go from New York to Montreal</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:59:46" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7104-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7104_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:59:47">http://www.forbes.com/sites/andrewbender/2013/12/31/top-10-travel-news-stories-of-2013/</link><title>Top 10 Travel News Stories Of 2013</title><description>A massive airline merger, ride-sharing and government shutdown all helped shape America's travel scene in 2013. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7104-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7104_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:00:57">http://www.forbes.com/sites/learnvest/2013/10/18/8-inexpensive-vacation-alternatives-to-big-ticket-getaways/</link><title>8 Inexpensive Vacation Alternatives To Big-Ticket Getaways</title><description>Dreaming of Paris? Wishing for Greece? Try these beautiful, affordable destinations instead. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7104-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7104_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:03:22">http://www.forbes.com/sites/joeharpaz/2013/11/15/tax-in-sports-brooklyn-style/</link><title>How The Brooklyn Nets' $80 Million Tax Penalty Is Making Basketball Competitive Again</title><description>How the luxury tax has revived the Brooklyn Nets and made basketball more competitive. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7104-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7104_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:08:17">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kitconews/2013/07/22/focus-gold-prices-rise-through-key-technical-chart-levels-as-dollar-weakens/</link><title>FOCUS: Gold Prices Rise Through Key Technical Chart Levels As Dollar Weakens</title><description>(Kitco News) - Gold prices broke through the key $1,300-an-ounce level on Monday as a weaker U.S. dollar and buying back of previously sold positions and new purchases took the metal to a four-week high. As of 10:11 a.m. EDT, most-active August gold futures on the Comex division of the New York [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7104-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7104_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:12:11">http://www.forbes.com/sites/danschawbel/2012/09/20/how-to-build-a-successful-nonprofit-that-supports-your-community/</link><title>How to Build a Successful Nonprofit That Supports Your Community</title><description>Charles Bronfman and Jeffrey Solomon I recently spoke to both Charles Bronfman and Jeffrey Solomon about their new book called The Art of Doing Good: Where Passion Meets Action. Charles, of the Seagram's corporate family, was the founding owner of the Montreal Expos and is the chairman of the Andrea and Charles Bronfman Philanthropies. Among his [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7104-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7104_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:14:36">http://www.forbes.com/sites/brucerogers/2014/03/20/will-greg-isenbergs-5by-help-stumbleupon-maintain-its-momentum/</link><title>Will Greg Isenberg's 5by Help StumbleUpon Maintain Its Momentum?</title><description>A  Series of Forbes Insights Profiles of Thought Leaders Changing the Business Landscape: Greg Isenberg, Serial Entrepreneur and Founder of 5by.... All of 25 years of age, uber networker and serial entrepreneur Greg Isenberg has already founded and sold three businesses.  His latest start-up is video curation app, 5by, which he [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7104-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7104_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:18:00">http://www.forbes.com/sites/deborahljacobs/2012/09/06/how-to-find-shoes-for-baby-boomer-feet/</link><title>How To Find Comfortable Shoes That Don't Compromise Style</title><description>Manufacturers of pretty designer shoes have largely forgotten or ignored the fact that baby boomers have disposable cash and are ready to spend.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7104-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7104_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:20:27">http://www.forbes.com/sites/georgequraishi/2012/04/27/red-bulls-competing-for-new-york-fans-first-soccer-fans-second/</link><title>Red Bulls Competing For New York Fans First, Soccer Fans Second</title><description>On Tuesday I wrote about a Wall Street Journal story examining the team's attempts to be perceived as one of the area's major sports franchises. I focused on a quote from MLS commissioner Don Garber, but the most interesting quote in the piece actually came from the Red Bulls' president [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7104-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7104_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:21:09">http://www.forbes.com/sites/brucerogers/2014/02/12/dax-dasilvas-lightspeed-creates-apple-store-experience-for-retailers/</link><title>Dax Dasilva's LightSpeed Creates 'Apple Store' Experience for Retailers</title><description>A Series of Forbes Insights Profiles of Thought Leaders Changing the Business Landscape:  Dax Dasilva, Founder and CEO, LightSpeed... It all started when Dax Dasilva received a Mac for his 12th birthday, growing up in Vancouver, Canada.  He soon began programming, and landed a job as an apprentice at an Apple [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7104-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7104_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:22:16">http://www.forbes.com/sites/tomvanriper/2013/03/27/the-toronto-blue-jays-push-to-re-ignite-baseball-in-canada/</link><title>The Toronto Blue Jays Push to Reignite Baseball In Canada</title><description>A once-great market has grown dormant. Will Toronto's spending splurge bring the fans back?</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>