<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7105">dark knight rises dvd</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:25:55" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7105-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7105_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:25:56">http://www.forbes.com/sites/scottmendelson/2014/01/30/pitch-perfect-2-can-pull-a-dark-knight-style-box-office-coup/</link><title>'Pitch Perfect 2' Can Pull A 'Dark Knight'-Style Box Office Coup</title><description>As was announced on Tuesday, Gold Circle and Universal (a division of Comcast) will be releasing a theatrical sequel to the 2012 sleeper smash hit Pitch Perfect. Produced for just $17 million, the Anna Kendrick-led comedy about a female singing group slowly grossed $113m worldwide, along with strong DVD/VOD business [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7105-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7105_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:27:58">http://www.forbes.com/sites/scottmendelson/2013/10/10/blu-ray-review-batman-the-dark-knight-returns-deluxe-edition-is-a-needless-double-dip/</link><title>Blu Ray Review: 'Batman: The Dark Knight Returns' Deluxe Edition Is Needless Double-Dip</title><description>It's bad enough that the DCAU is dominated by Batman and Superman titles.  It's bad enough that they saw fit to do an adaptation of The Dark Knight Returns, surely a graphic novel that needs no wider fan base, while splitting it up into two releases.  But now, as somewhat [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7105-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7105_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:29:53">http://www.forbes.com/sites/scottmendelson/2013/09/25/the-dark-knight-trilogy-ultimate-collectors-edition-is-all-sizzle-no-steak/</link><title>The 'Dark Knight' Trilogy Ultimate Collector's Edition Is All Sizzle, No Steak</title><description>When Warner Bros. released the Ultimate Matrix Collection on DVD in 2004, it came with all three films, two new commentaries per film, the previously released Animatrix, every bit of previously released content from prior DVD releases of the three films, plus around 6 million hours of new documentary material [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7105-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7105_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:31:37">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johngaudiosi/2012/12/04/christopher-nolan-delivers-super-hero-perfection-with-the-dark-knight-rises/</link><title>Christopher Nolan Delivers Super Hero Perfection With The Dark Knight Rises</title><description>I’m old enough to have lived through a litany of horrible super hero movies. In some ways, it’s what we’re currently experiencing with horrible video game movies. Hollywood made a lot of crappy super hero movies like Judge Dredd (the Stallone one), Superman III, Catwoman, Fantastic Four and Batman and [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7105-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7105_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:33:00">http://www.forbes.com/sites/carolpinchefsky/2012/07/05/6-batman-related-activities-to-keep-you-occupied-before-the-dark-knight-rises/</link><title>6 Batman-Related Activities to Keep You Occupied Before 'The Dark Knight Rises'</title><description>The Dark Knight Rises won’t be hitting theaters until July 2o, 2012, which gives us over two weeks of Batman-obsessed anticipation to work through. We can twiddle our thumbs or we can pass the time (336 hours, but hey, who’s counting) celebrating our Batmania. I know what I’ll be doing: read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7105-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7105_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:33:50">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markhughes/2014/01/03/2013-sets-all-time-box-office-record/</link><title>2013 Sets All-Time Box Office Record</title><description>It's popular in some circles to insist that they don't make films as good as they used to, and that modern box office has suffered a steady decline as less people attend and the studios make less money. Well, that's all myth, as 2013 helped demonstrate by becoming the second [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7105-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7105_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:36:16">http://www.forbes.com/sites/scottmendelson/2013/10/03/cloudy-2-batman-begins-and-5-more-hits-that-survived-disappointing-debuts/</link><title>'Cloudy 2', 'Batman Begins', And 5 More Hits That Survived "Disappointing" Debuts</title><description>How big is big enough?  Cloudy With A Chance of Meatballs 2 opened with a solid $34 million to top the weekend box office, above the $30m debut of Cloudy With A Chance Of Meatballs back in 2009. But there were pre-release rumblings that it would open with around $40m, and hopes [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7105-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7105_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:38:44">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markhughes/2014/02/01/how-warner-is-rebranding-batman-vs-superman/</link><title>How Warner Is Rebranding 'Batman Vs. Superman'</title><description>With Friday's announcement by Warner Bros. that Jesse Eisenberg will play Lex Luthor in the upcoming sequel to 2013's Superman reboot blockbuster Man of Steel, with Jeremy Irons announced as Batman's faithful butler Alfred, the Internet was abuzz with fan and media reaction. However, mostly overlooked in the studio's official [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7105-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7105_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:42:22">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markhughes/2014/01/30/will-ben-affleck-direct-justice-league-movie/</link><title>Will Ben Affleck Direct 'Justice League' Movie?</title><description>The flood of rumors and so-called "exclusives" continues across comic book fan sites week after week regarding the upcoming Warner Bros. sequel to the Man of Steel, from false casting claims to wild rumors about Ben Affleck departing the project (his wife Jennifer Garner is talking publicly about how cool [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7105-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7105_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:44:17">http://www.forbes.com/sites/scottmendelson/2013/11/15/jurassic-world-the-best-man-holiday-and-other-class-reunion-sequels/</link><title>'Jurassic World', 'The Best Man Holiday', And More "Class Reunion" Sequels</title><description>When the fourth Jurassic Park film, which will allegedly star Chris Pratt, Bryce Dallas Howard, and presumably one or two members of the original cast in small roles, arrives in theaters on June 12th, 2015, there will be teenagers aplenty who will not have even been born when the last entry [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>