<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7106">active learning survey</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:45:35" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7106-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7106_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:45:36">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jenniferrooney/2014/04/16/annual-effies-survey-content-is-king/</link><title>Annual Effies Survey: Content Is King</title><description>Marketers are officially hooked on content. That it has emerged as one of the primary areas of focus is clear in this year’s survey of North American Effie Awards Final Round judges, conducted in partnership with the Forbes CMO Network. The survey, now in its fourth year, gauges advertising executives’ [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7106-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7106_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:47:33">http://www.forbes.com/sites/berlinschoolofcreativeleadership/2014/01/07/digital-learning-for-free-or-a-cost-extends-the-usas-creative-and-competitive-advantage/</link><title>Digital Learning - For Free Or At A Cost - Extends The USA's Creative And Competitive Advantage</title><description>By Marilee Turscak “I spent three days a week for 10 years educating myself in the public library, and it's better than college. People should educate themselves—you can get a complete education for no money.” – Ray Bradbury In a viral YouTube debate discussing the future of higher education in America, Berkeley physicist [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7106-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7106_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:49:12">http://www.forbes.com/sites/oracle/2013/07/24/smart-grid-is-on-the-big-data-learning-curve/</link><title>Oracle​Voice: Smart Grid Must Ascend The Big Data Learning Curve</title><description>(Credit: iStockphoto) The utility industry’s “smart grid” still has a lot to learn, which I experienced firsthand as I sat in the dark after Hurricane Sandy. A new study from Oracle reveals what electric service providers must do to convert the vast amounts of data generated by the smart grid into [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7106-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7106_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:50:29">http://www.forbes.com/sites/theyec/2013/09/06/starting-up-use-a-survey-to-assess-your-strengths-and-weaknesses/</link><title>Starting Up? Use A Survey To Assess Your Strengths And Weaknesses</title><description>For first-time entrepreneurs who want to know how and what to delegate, it's important to understand your weaknesses first. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7106-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7106_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:52:26">http://www.forbes.com/sites/michaelhorn/2014/03/17/kaist-doesnt-wait-for-change-in-korea-pioneers-education-3-0/</link><title>KAIST Doesn't Wait For Change In Korea, Pioneers 'Education 3.0'</title><description>As South Korea struggles to escape the downsides of centuries of a Confucian emphasis on rote learning while retaining the positives from that Confucian legacy, at least a couple institutions in the country aren’t waiting for permission to move forward. KAIST, the Korean Advanced Institute of Science and Technology, a top [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7106-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7106_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:54:19">http://www.forbes.com/sites/oreillymedia/2014/02/04/business-analysts-want-access-to-advanced-analytics/</link><title>Business Analysts Want Access To Advanced Analytics</title><description>By Ben Lorica I talk with many new companies who build tools for business analysts and other non-technical users. These new tools streamline and simplify important data tasks including interactive analysis (e.g., pivot tables and cohort analysis), interactive visual analysis (as popularized by Tableau and Qlikview), and more recently data [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7106-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7106_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:57:59">http://www.forbes.com/sites/benkepes/2014/04/18/lubricating-the-wheels-of-technology-in-education/</link><title>Lubricating The Wheels Of Technology In Education</title><description>VideoMy eldest son starting high school this year has given me a fascinating inside view on technology as it applies to education. I'm of the perfect age to have started my high school education sans computers, but to have ended it with at least the start of technology becoming more [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7106-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7106_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:59:29">http://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2014/03/06/workforce-planning-and-the-busted-generation/</link><title>SAP​Voice: Workforce Planning and the 'Busted Generation'</title><description>By Karie Willyerd, Vice President of Learning &amp; Social Adoption, SuccessFactors, an SAP Company They say three’s a crowd, so what will they say when five generations work together? Millennials are on their way in, but Boomers are in no hurry to make their way out. In fact, American workers are [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7106-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7106_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:00:59">http://www.forbes.com/sites/citi/2014/02/26/one-company-uses-data-to-help-solve-some-of-the-worlds-biggest-problems/</link><title>Citi's​Voice: One Company Uses Data To Help Solve Some Of The World's Biggest Problems</title><description>From file cabinets full of reports to global cell phone surveys to open government databases, philanthropic organizations often have access to mountains of information. But few have the resources required to sift through all of that data and identify meaningful insights. DataKind is working to solve that problem. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7106-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7106_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:03:30">http://www.forbes.com/sites/work-in-progress/2014/04/10/how-to-drive-innovation-in-five-steps/</link><title>How To Drive Innovation In Five Steps</title><description>Companies say they want innovation, but their actions often support playing it safe. Here are five ways to encourage smart risk taking that drives innovation. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>