<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7107">grimm episodes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:04:18" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7107-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7107_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:04:19">http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2011/10/30/happy-halloween/</link><title>Happy Halloween</title><description>VideoHave a lovely Halloween. I thought The Office Halloween episode (Spooked) this past week was actually pretty good. In fact, the first season without Michael Scott has been surprisingly entertaining. And I watched the Grimm pilot, which was fun. But it's hard to beat the Muppets. Follow me on Twitter or Facebook. [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7107-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7107_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:05:28">http://www.forbes.com/sites/merrillbarr/2013/12/02/why-is-nbc-afraid-of-original-material/</link><title>Why is NBC Afraid of Original Material?</title><description>NBC has original hits, why are they still playing it safe? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7107-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7107_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:06:13">http://www.forbes.com/sites/carolpinchefsky/2012/03/19/new-snow-white-and-the-huntsman-trailer-is-as-dark-as-a-real-fairy-tale/</link><title>New 'Snow White and the Huntsman' Trailer Is as Dark as a Real Fairy-Tale</title><description>As some of you may know, there are not one but two Snow White movies coming out this year: Snow White and the Huntsman and Mirror, Mirror. From the trailer of Mirror, Mirror, I can already tell you I won’t be seeing it: it looks silly rather than funny, plus it uses the title of one of my favorite Star Trek episodes without giving me Spock’s [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7107-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7107_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:07:03">http://www.forbes.com/sites/danielnyegriffiths/2013/10/22/bruised-women-and-big-bad-wolves-the-noir-of-the-wolf-among-us/</link><title>Bruised Women And Big, Bad Wolves: The Noir Of 'The Wolf Among Us'</title><description>Snow Whites, Red Roses and Blue Dahlias - when we talk about Telltale Games' The Wolf Among Us as noir, what do we mean? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7107-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7107_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:07:45">http://www.forbes.com/sites/quora/2012/11/15/what-are-the-pros-and-cons-of-disneys-4-05b-purchase-of-lucasfilm/</link><title>What Are The Pros And Cons Of Disney's $4.05B Purchase Of Lucasfilm?</title><description>What are the pros and cons of Disney's $4.05B purchase of Lucasfilm? This question was originally answered on Quora by Sanjay Sabnani. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7107-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7107_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:10:44">http://www.forbes.com/2008/04/11/videogames-serials-fun-tech-personal-cx_mji_0411serials_slide.html</link><title>In Pictures: Seven Hot Videogames You Can Play Tonight</title><description>Why spend half a life playing a videogame? Polish off one of these serialized games in a few hours.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7107-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7107_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 21:12:26">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markhughes/2013/03/15/what-made-oz-so-great-and-powerful-starlight-runners-jeff-gomez-tells-us/</link><title>What Made 'Oz' So Great And Powerful? Starlight Runner's Jeff Gomez Tells Us</title><description>VideoAlready topping $100 million at the domestic box office and more than $70 million overseas as it heads into it's second weekend of release (during which it will likely add another $80+ million worldwide to its total), Disney's it Oz the Great and Powerful is 2013's first true blockbuster. But why [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>