<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7112">facebook icons</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:26:19" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7112-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7112_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:26:19">http://www.forbes.com/sites/martinsosnoff/2013/11/25/icahn-aint-no-icon/</link><title>Icahn Ain't No Icon</title><description>I've seen Carl Icahn's name in print nearly daily so I'm highly confident I can spell his surname with ease. The “highly confident” phraseology was Drexel Burnham speak, denoting its capacity to raise billions in capital for assorted greenmailers, LBO practitioners and takeover honchos who operated in the mid-seventies and [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7112-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7112_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:29:41">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ralphbenko/2014/02/24/what-facebooks-58-genders-mean-for-politics/</link><title>What Facebook's 58 Genders Mean For Politics</title><description>Could widespread gender deconstruction lead to a social Hiroshima? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7112-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7112_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:32:18">http://www.forbes.com/sites/russellflannery/2013/06/23/china-tech-icons-deepen-ties-at-internet-security-company/</link><title>China Tech Icons Deepen Ties At Internet Security Company</title><description>Two of China’s most prominent tech billionaires are deepening their ties at an Internet security company. TCH, a subsidiary of Chinese Internet giant Tecnent  Holdings, will pay $52 million for new shares in Kingsoft Internet Security Holdings, a subsidiary of Hong Kong-listed Kingsoft Corp., Kingsoft Corp. said in an announcement on [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7112-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7112_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:33:35">http://www.forbes.com/sites/larrymagid/2013/10/16/facebook-allows-teens-to-post-publicly/</link><title>Facebook Allows Teens To Post Publicly</title><description>An example post that a teen might want the public to see Facebook announced today that it will lift the restriction on teens posts that set the maximum audience to friends of friends. Starting today, teens can post publicly. The company also said that the first time a teen new to Facebook [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7112-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7112_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:34:57">http://www.forbes.com/sites/amitchowdhry/2013/11/19/facebook-privacy-tips/</link><title>20 Tips On Increasing Your Facebook Privacy And Security</title><description>Let's face it, we all have an embarrassing photo that we don't want people to see on Facebook.  Maintaining privacy on Facebook is important because recruiters, teachers, bosses and college admission committees are highly likely to look at your profile and make judgments about your professionalism based on what they can see. [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7112-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7112_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:38:16">http://www.forbes.com/sites/michaelhumphrey/2013/10/25/how-i-made-facebook-better-in-five-steps/</link><title>How I Made Facebook Better, In Five Steps</title><description>see photosAPClick for full photo gallery: The Evolution Of Facebook It wasn't Bitstrips fault really. Had it come at any other time, I would have tolerated it -- and perhaps even appreciated some of its uses by my Facebook friends. It's just that the new No. 1 free app, according to [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7112-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7112_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:39:39">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johnfarrell/2012/11/28/death-of-a-science-fiction-icon-the-other-strugatsky-brother/</link><title>Death of a Science Fiction Icon: The Other Strugatsky Brother</title><description>1978 Pocket Book edition of the celebrated Soviet Science Fiction classic. (Photo credit: John Farrell) This week saw the passing of Boris Strugatsky, co-author along with his brother Arkady of one of science fiction's classic novels, Roadside Picnic. According to the obituary in the New York Times:  Employed as an astronomer read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7112-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7112_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:42:21">http://www.forbes.com/sites/larrymagid/2013/06/12/facebook-adds-twitter-like-hashtags/</link><title>Facebook Adds Twitter-Like Hashtags</title><description>Sample Facebook hashtag (photo: Facebook) Facebook announced today that it is allowing users to create and click on hashtags, "similar to other services like Instagram, Twitter, Tumblr, or Pinterest." A hashtag, which is simply a word preceded by a pound or hash symbol (#) is a way to participate in a [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7112-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7112_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:43:13">http://www.forbes.com/sites/tomiogeron/2013/05/22/why-facebook-should-buy-waze/</link><title>Why Facebook Should Buy Waze</title><description>The social media giant needs more mobile traction. Navigation startup Waze might be the $1 billion answer. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7112-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7112_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 22:44:01">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markrogowsky/2013/10/12/a-guide-to-fixing-the-latest-privacy-attacks-from-facebook-and-google/</link><title>A Guide To Fixing The Latest Privacy Attacks From Facebook And Google</title><description>Surely, the fact that Google and Facebook both chose this week to again erode your privacy had to be coincidental. But Thursday, Facebook was out with a small change that affects millions of users who tried to make themselves a bit harder to find and Friday, Google followed with a plan [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>