<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7115">pittsburgh steelers news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:38:46" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7115-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7115_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:38:47">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johntamny/2013/12/22/why-the-cleveland-browns-and-green-bay-packers-have-more-out-of-town-fans-than-the-washington-redskins/</link><title>Why The Pittsburgh Steelers And Green Bay Packers Have More Out-Of-Town Fans Than The Washington Redskins</title><description>It's a bad economic signal for the NFL teams and cities that can claim a national fan base. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7115-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7115_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:40:49">http://www.forbes.com/sites/steveschaefer/2014/02/01/stocks-and-super-bowls-buy-companies-that-look-like-the-steelers-not-the-jets/</link><title>Stocks And Super Bowls: Buy Companies That Look Like The Steelers, Not The Jets</title><description>Culture matters in the financial world just like it does on the gridiron, says fund manager Zac Wydra. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7115-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7115_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:41:23">http://www.forbes.com/sites/leighsteinberg/2013/08/01/washington-dcchicago-pittsburgh-examples-of-nfl-frenzy/</link><title>Washington DC, Chicago, Pittsburgh--Examples Of NFL Frenzy</title><description>I spent last week in Washington DC and the area is ablaze with Redskin mania. Every cab driver, shopkeeper and person I encountered is in a state of excitement about the prospects of the team. RG III could be elected Mayor in a landslide. It is stunning to witness coming [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7115-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7115_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:45:01">http://www.forbes.com/sites/bleacherreport/2012/04/17/pittsburgh-steelers-80th-anniversary-throwback-jerseys-you-be-the-judge/</link><title>Pittsburgh Steelers 80th Anniversary Throwback Jerseys: You Be the Judge</title><description>Photo courtesy of @Steelers, the official Steelers Twitter feed By Andrea Hangst, Bleacher Report Oh my. The Pittsburgh Steelers have released their 80th anniversary throwback jerseys on Tuesday, and they are, in a word, unique. You may recall the most recent round of Steelers throwback jerseys, first debuted during their 75th anniversary season [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7115-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7115_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:45:48">http://www.forbes.com/sites/aliciajessop/2012/09/30/shaq-the-pittsburgh-steelers-and-sports-leagues-adapt-to-shifts-in-social-media-to-build-brand-power/</link><title>Shaq, the Pittsburgh Steelers and Sports Leagues Adapt To Shifts in Social Media To Build Brand Power</title><description>The face of social media is changing.  While once largely text-driven, social media sites are becoming more image-based, allowing users to upload pictures and share videos with the click of a button.  This image-based shift in social media is largely due to the birth of image-sharing websites like Instagram and [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7115-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7115_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:48:25">http://www.forbes.com/sites/prishe/2012/09/14/nfls-week-2-secondary-ticket-market-trends-steelers-hot-jaguars-not/</link><title>NFL's Week 2 Secondary Ticket Price Trends: Steelers Hot, Jaguars Not</title><description>Based on some feedback from my friends at StubHub, here is a snapshot of secondary ticket price trends for Week 2 of the NFL season.  Secondary prices reported below reflect the price of tickets actually sold to date through StubHub. HIGHEST-PRICED GAME...JETS @ STEELERS The highest average secondary price is in Pittsburgh [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7115-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7115_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:49:32">http://www.forbes.com/2009/09/02/pittsburgh-g-20-economy-innovation-opinions-columnists-21-century-cities-09-pittsburgh.html</link><title>Pittsburgh? Yes, Pittsburgh</title><description>Why the city on the Ohio River is the perfect G-20 host. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7115-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7115_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:52:28">http://www.forbes.com/2011/02/04/steelers-packers-wells-fargo-markets-roethlisberger-rodgers.html</link><title>Investment Lessons From The Steelers And Packers</title><description>There's a lot in common when it comes to football and investing strategies. Pittsburgh and Green Bay show that. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7115-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7115_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:54:44">http://www.forbes.com/sites/leeigel/2014/03/10/retiring-from-the-nfl-at-26-rashard-mendenhall-is-heading-into-halftime/</link><title>Retiring From The NFL At 26, Rashard Mendenhall Is Heading Into "Halftime"</title><description>Rashard Mendenhall, an NFL running back, has announced his retirement at age 26. It comes, he says, at a point in time when he is drawn to focusing on personal interests that have always “spread a lot further than the acceptable athletic stereotypes and conformity.” Is he part of a growing trend? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7115-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7115_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:55:43">http://www.forbes.com/sites/sportsmoney/2011/01/24/fox-will-score-ratings-touchdown-with-steelers-packers-super-bowl/</link><title>Fox Will Score Ratings Touchdown With Steelers-Packers Super Bowl</title><description>The network hardly could have chosen a sexier match-up than Pittsburgh versus Green Bay. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>