<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7116">pumpkin pie recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:56:19" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7116-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7116_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:56:19">http://www.forbes.com/sites/nadiaarumugam/2013/11/19/why-you-want-canned-pumpkin-for-a-better-pie-not-fresh/</link><title>Why You Want Canned Pumpkin For A Better Pie, Not Fresh</title><description>With farm-to-fork perhaps the most prevalent conceit in culinary matters today, there's a general presumption that made-from-scratch is always better, and that fresh consistently trumps processed. But here's the caveat, not so with pumpkin pie. If you've ever gone to the great lengths of lugging home an actual pumpkin, cooking it, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7116-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7116_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 23:58:52">http://www.forbes.com/sites/michelinemaynard/2013/09/22/how-starbucks-turned-pumpkin-spice-into-a-marketing-bonanza/</link><title>How Starbucks Turned Pumpkin Spice Into A Marketing Bonanza</title><description>Image via Papermag.com It used to be when you thought of fall, you thought of cider, falling leaves, and hot soup. Now, as autumn begins, the American landscape is dominated by a single force: pumpkin spice. Look about you and you'll see it, in coffee and doughnuts, bagels and pancakes. At Starbucks, [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7116-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7116_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:00:57">http://www.forbes.com/sites/nadiaarumugam/2013/11/06/why-you-should-buy-pecans-for-your-thanksgiving-pie-now/</link><title>Why You Should Buy Pecans For Your Thanksgiving Pie Now</title><description>(Photo credit: Wikipedia) A typical Thanksgiving pecan pie calls for half a pound of pecan halves. If you purchase your stock of nuts now from your local supermarket, it’ll set you back around about $4.50 (or $9 for a one-pound bag). Wait until the holiday is upon us, however, and [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7116-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7116_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:01:22">http://www.forbes.com/sites/victoriavonbiel/2011/11/22/skip-the-pie-5-awesome-pumpkin-desserts/</link><title>Skip the Pie: 5 Awesome Pumpkin Desserts</title><description>Image by stu_spivack via Flickr Who says pumpkin belongs only in a pie crust? The classic flavors of molasses, sweet spices, and that wonderful, undefinable taste of fall, work just as well in lots of other desserts. Here are a few that I think are worth adding to your Thanksgiving table. Upside [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7116-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7116_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:03:21">http://www.forbes.com/2009/11/12/thanksgiving-holiday-pie-forbes-woman-time-family-matters.html</link><title>The Last Pie</title><description>We found a buried treasure in our basement freezer: my late mother-in-law's last pumpkin pie. If only we knew what to do with it. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7116-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7116_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:04:42">http://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesstylefile/2013/11/21/the-perfect-dress-for-thanksgiving-day/</link><title>The Perfect Dress For Thanksgiving Day</title><description>Whether you're traveling to see family for Thanksgiving or throwing a "Friendsgiving" for your closest pals, you should make an effort to dress up for the occasion.  But what does one wear on a holiday dedicated entirely to eating, drinking and merriment, when over indulgence is on the menu? A wrap [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7116-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7116_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:06:29">http://www.forbes.com/sites/marketshare/2012/05/16/ge-general-mills-and-sears-explain-their-success-in-content-marketing-part-1/</link><title>GE, General Mills And Sears Explain Their Success In Content Marketing (Part 1)</title><description>Two months ago we asked Kraft Foods to dish out their recipe for successful content marketing. Since then more and more marketers have been requesting additional perspective from fellow leading advertisers. Therefore, we decided to interview three more Fortune 500 companies that appear to be effectively running part of their [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7116-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7116_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:07:30">http://www.forbes.com/sites/agoodman/2013/08/09/jim-beam-glows-after-hooking-up-with-bethenny-frankel/</link><title>Jim Beam Glows After Hooking Up With Bethenny Frankel</title><description>It’s wedding season and as many couples look forward to their warm weather nuptials, the leap of faith Jim Beam and Skinnygirl took together over two years ago looks just as promising as contemporary “I do’s” at the altar. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7116-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7116_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:09:53">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jennifercohen/2012/12/04/comfort-foods-that-will-save-you-thousands-of-calories/</link><title>Comfort Foods That Will Save You Thousands Of Calories</title><description>The holidays are absolutely filled with hot-zones. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7116-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7116_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:11:40">http://www.forbes.com/sites/nadiaarumugam/2011/12/15/cookbook-gifts-for-the-foodies-in-your-life/</link><title>Cookbook Holiday Gifts For The Foodies In Your Life</title><description>No doubt it hasn't escaped you that Christmas is, gulp...10 days away. It possibly also hasn't escaped you that a sizable amount of your Christmas shopping remains....well, still in the stores. I ask you then, to consider the interests of the loved - or liked - ones in your life. [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>