<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7118">part time jobs texas city</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:33:49" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7118-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7118_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:33:50">http://www.forbes.com/sites/joelkotkin/2014/04/03/americas-new-brainpower-cities/</link><title>America's New Brainpower Cities</title><description>Brainpower is dispersing, largely to the South, the Southeast and the Intermountain West, with ramifications that will be felt in the economy in the decades ahead.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7118-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7118_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:34:55">http://www.forbes.com/sites/joelkotkin/2013/11/20/the-surprising-cities-creating-the-most-tech-jobs/</link><title>The Surprising Cities Creating The Most Tech Jobs</title><description>The Bay Area may get all the buzz, but a host of less-celebrated cities are gaining jobs at a faster pace as the center of gravity in technology disperses from Silicon Valley.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7118-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7118_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:39:04">http://www.forbes.com/sites/joelkotkin/2013/10/24/the-cities-creating-the-most-middle-class-jobs/</link><title>The Cities Creating The Most Middle-Class Jobs</title><description>Three years since employment hit bottom, the U.S. still has 2 million fewer middle-income jobs than at the onset of the financial crisis in 2007. These are the metro areas that are bucking the trend and have created more good jobs for its middle-class residents.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7118-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7118_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:40:54">http://www.forbes.com/sites/joelkotkin/2013/11/05/american-cities-may-have-hit-peak-office/</link><title>American Cities May Have Hit 'Peak Office'</title><description>A persistently weak economy and the growing dispersion of business service employment to smaller markets, and into people’s homes, means the glory days of the American office tower are likely over.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7118-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7118_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:41:25">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markadomanis/2013/08/20/why-arent-there-any-russians-in-texas/</link><title>Why Aren't There Any Russians In Texas?</title><description>Thanks to Matt Yglesias I discovered a truly fascinating data visualization tool created by the Census Bureau. The tool allows you to select one of fifteen languages (Spanish, French, German, Italian, Polish, Russian, etc.), to differentiate between people who speak a language and people who speak that language while also speaking [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7118-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7118_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:41:53">http://www.forbes.com/sites/larrybell/2013/08/27/texas-doesnt-need-to-secede-tis-better-for-the-union-to-join-texas-and-succeed/</link><title>Texas Doesn't Need To Secede; Tis Better For The Union To Join Texas And Succeed</title><description>It’s sure a good thing that Texas has lots of space, because a booming economy is bringing in lots of people</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7118-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7118_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:44:49">http://www.forbes.com/sites/joelkotkin/2013/05/31/the-cities-taking-finance-jobs-from-wall-street/</link><title>The Cities That Are Stealing Finance Jobs From Wall Street</title><description>The industry is shifting jobs away from New York and Chicago to second-tier cities rarely associated with industry heavyweights. These are the surprising winners.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7118-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7118_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:48:11">http://www.forbes.com/sites/robertwood/2013/03/06/texas-is-the-new-california/</link><title>Texas Is the New California</title><description>Taxes aren't the only thing influencing who moves where. Still, taxes can play a key role. We're now told Texas Dominates The Best Cities For Good Jobs. In part, that could be its favorable regulatory climate for business, more moderate housing and other costs. But California still has many [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7118-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7118_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:51:23">http://www.forbes.com/sites/robertwood/2013/09/13/everythings-big-in-texas-but-taxes-online-tool-compares-yours-state-by-state/</link><title>Everything's Big In Texas But Taxes---Online Tool Compares Yours State-By-State</title><description>Texas Governor 's signature. (Photo credit: Wikipedia) Texas Gov. Rick Perry is at it again, encouraging Americans to pick up stakes and move to Texas. There’s no Texas income tax, he coaxes. Businesses and their employees can live large with no state income tax. Gov. Perry is travelling the country touting the advantages [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7118-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7118_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 00:52:13">http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidblackmon/2013/08/21/shale-fracking-are-not-the-main-cause-of-texas-water-shortages/</link><title>Shale, Fracking Are Not The Main Cause Of Texas Water Shortages</title><description>A West Texas Windmill pumping water from the Ogallala Aquifer. (Photo credit: Wikipedia) One of the challenging aspects of shale oil and gas development in the United States comes from the fact that some of the large shale reservoirs are located in areas that are arid or semi-arid.  Some, like the [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>