<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7121">who is the man in the m&amp;m commercial</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:23:11" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7121-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7121_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:23:12">http://www.forbes.com/sites/allenstjohn/2014/03/27/showrunner-scott-m-gimple-on-the-creation-of-the-walking-deads-best-episode-ever/</link><title>Showrunner Scott M. Gimple On the Creation of 'The Walking Dead's' Best Episode Ever</title><description>VideoScott M. Gimple has one of the best jobs in America. And one of the worst.  He’s the showrunner of  The Walking Dead, television’s most popular show in the most important demographic.  (Spoilers for The Walking Dead, to Episode 415, as well as the comic.) Which means that he gets to [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7121-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7121_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:24:04">http://www.forbes.com/sites/susanadams/2014/03/11/where-the-jobs-will-and-wont-be-this-spring/</link><title>Where The Jobs Will (And Won't) Be This Spring</title><description>see photosClick for full photo gallery: Where The Jobs Will (And Won’t) Be This Spring If you hope to land a job in the next three months, where in the country will you find the most vibrant employment scene? According to the just-released Employment Outlook Survey from Milwaukee-based staffing giant ManpowerGroup, [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7121-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7121_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:24:26">http://www.forbes.com/sites/scottmendelson/2013/06/05/why-sony-was-wrong-to-hide-m-night-shyamalan-while-marketing-after-earth/</link><title>Why Sony Was Wrong To Hide M. Night Shyamalan While Marketing 'After Earth'</title><description>We'll truly never know whether Sony would be looking at a bigger opening weekend for the Will Smith/Jaden Smith vehicle After Earth if they hadn't chosen to hide the fact that the film is directed by M. Night Shyamalan.  I've argued for much of the last week that said decision [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7121-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7121_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:25:58">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinharrington/2014/01/31/save-your-money-celebrity-endorsements-not-worth-the-cost/</link><title>Save Your Money: Celebrity Endorsements Not Worth The Cost</title><description>After helping launch more than 500 products, I’ve come to this conclusion: If a product is really strong, you don’t need a celebrity to sell it to consumers. According to a study that appeared in the Social Influence journal, celebrity endorsements are just not worth the cost. Rather than spend too much [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7121-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7121_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:28:44">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ruthblatt/2013/11/04/lou-reed-and-the-problem-with-the-innovation-imperative/</link><title>Lou Reed And The Problem With The Innovation Imperative</title><description>People usually think it’s best to be the first to hit the market with a disruptive innovation. But more often than not, the advantages don’t pan out. The career of the late Lou Reed reveals the dark side of the innovation imperative and the disadvantages that come with being a first mover. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7121-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7121_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:31:27">http://www.forbes.com/sites/allenstjohn/2013/09/16/why-breaking-bad-is-the-best-show-ever-and-why-that-matters/</link><title>Why 'Breaking Bad' Is The Best Show Ever And Why That Matters</title><description>VideoTwenty three minutes into Episode 514, entitled "Ozymandias" after a Shelley poem, Breaking Bad made television history. Except that most fans didn’t notice. They were instead ready to cry, scream, vomit, or hurl a waffle iron at the plasma TV, or some combination of the above. Sometime around that first commercial [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7121-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7121_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:32:07">http://www.forbes.com/sites/allenstjohn/2013/09/29/working-bad-breaking-bad-writer-tom-schnauz-on-killing-mike-stuffing-gus-frings-heart-in-a-suitcase-and-who-almost-shot-hank/</link><title>Working Bad: 'Breaking Bad' Writer Tom Schnauz On Killing Mike, Stuffing Gus Fring's Heart In A Suitcase, And Who Almost Shot Hank</title><description>VideoLike everything worthwhile, Breaking Bad has a creation myth. And writer-producer Tom Schnauz is at the center of this one, and gives his perspective in the first question. A college buddy of Vince Gilligan, Schnauz joined the writer’s room in the second season, in time enough to (Spoiler Alert for [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7121-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7121_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:33:53">http://www.forbes.com/sites/alexkonrad/2013/02/08/who-won-the-super-bowl-in-social-media-budweiser-or-pepsi/</link><title>Who Won The Super Bowl In Social Media, Budweiser or Pepsi?</title><description>Every Super Bowl ad campaign touts its social media use in the days before the game—part of how it justifies record prices for buying a spot. To declare victory with a social campaign requires some justification with engagement numbers and better sales. Brands will spend the next few weeks running their own [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7121-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7121_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:38:05">http://www.forbes.com/sites/prishe/2012/02/06/the-winners-and-losers-of-super-bowl-commercials-in-2012/</link><title>The Winners and Losers of Super Bowl Commercials in 2012</title><description>Image via Wikipedia The New York Giants and Eli Manning were the big winners on Sunday night as Mr. Manning once again led his team to a fourth quarter comeback versus the New England Patriots, once again denying Coach Bill Belichek and quarterback Tom Brady from reaching immortal heights in the [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7121-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7121_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:38:37">http://www.forbes.com/forbes/2012/0213/feature-peter-diamandis-tourism-x-prize-rocket-man.html</link><title>Rocket Man</title><description>Peter Diamandis' $10 million X Prize bounty sparked a boom in commercial tourism. You won't believe what he wants to do next. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>