<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7123">raleigh bike</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:44:31" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7123-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7123_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:44:31">http://www.forbes.com/sites/larryolmsted/2013/05/23/2013-bicycle-buyers-guide-part-2-choosing-a-road-bike/</link><title>2013 Bicycle Buyers Guide Part 2: Choosing A Road Bike</title><description>There has never been better value in the road bike market. Here's how to buy wisely. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7123-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7123_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:48:12">http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidkroll/2014/02/04/7-reasons-its-finally-time-to-live-in-research-triangle-park/</link><title>7 Reasons It's Finally Time To Live In Research Triangle Park</title><description>The establishment of North Carolina's Research Triangle Park in 1959 was aimed at reversing the "brain drain" of graduates from the area's top research universities seeking science and engineering jobs in the Northeast and elsewhere. Beyond providing jobs for North Carolinians, the 1965 expansion of IBM into the Park set the [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7123-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7123_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:50:12">http://www.forbes.com/sites/monteburke/2013/04/24/the-best-new-outdoor-gear-for-spring-and-summer-2013/</link><title>The Best New Outdoor Gear For Spring And Summer 2013</title><description>Outdoor gear that will actually make you want to get outdoors.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7123-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7123_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:52:00">http://www.forbes.com/sites/christinaaragon/2012/07/16/top-10-cities-after-you-say-i-do/</link><title>The 10 Best Cities For Newlyweds 2012</title><description>View the 2013 list of the Best Cities for Newlyweds &gt; Wedding season is in full swing and after the happy couple has recovered from the wedding mania, it will be time to search for the perfect place to start a life together. Rent.com researched cities across the country, looking at cost of [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7123-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7123_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:53:54">http://www.forbes.com/sites/statoil/2013/11/29/las-vegas-gambles-on-a-future-with-car-sharing-for-everyone/</link><title>Statoil Energy Realities​Voice: Las Vegas Gambles On A Future With Car Sharing For Everyone</title><description>By Smithsonian, an Energy Realities Partner Give people free shipping and a yearlong window for returns, as the retailer Zappos did, and suddenly buying shoes online is a lot more appealing. Give them access to manifold transportation options in a place where good jobs, homes and entertainment are within walking distance, and going car-free [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7123-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7123_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:56:15">http://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestravelguide/2013/05/06/luxury-voluntourism/</link><title>Luxury Voluntourism</title><description>When planning your next vacation, consider giving back to those less fortunate while you’re getting away from it all. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7123-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7123_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:59:49">http://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestravelguide/2013/04/22/luxury-hotels-go-eco-chic/</link><title>Luxury Hotels Go Eco-Chic</title><description>In honor of Earth Day, we found a few hotels that are as luxurious as they are eco-friendly, where you can do your part by just checking in. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7123-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7123_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:03:49">http://www.forbes.com/sites/hannahelliott/2013/04/01/real-estate-baron-michael-dezers-impressive-wheel-estate/</link><title>Meet The Real Estate Baron Who Owns James Bond's Soviet Tank - And The Batmobile</title><description>Miami real estate baron Michael Dezer has a thing for vintage cars, Vespas, bicycles--even New Age scooter chairs. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7123-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7123_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:06:29">http://www.forbes.com/sites/tomvanriper/2012/04/04/the-best-cities-for-raising-a-family/</link><title>The Best Cities For Raising A Family</title><description>You won't find much flash in Grand Rapids, Michigan or Boise, Idaho. But you will find good schools, affordable housing and low crime.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7123-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7123_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:09:22">http://www.forbes.com/sites/joelkotkin/2012/12/27/is-americas-future-progressive/</link><title>Is America's Future Progressive?</title><description>America: His to lose. (Photo credit: Wikipedia) Progressives may be a lot less religious  than conservatives, but these days they have reason to think that Providence-- or Gaia -- has taken on a bluish hue. From the solid re-election of President Obama, to a host of demographic and social trends, the progressives [...]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>