<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7131">golf games</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:17:31" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7131-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7131_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:17:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestravelguide/2014/04/09/master-your-golf-game-at-this-hidden-gem-hotel/</link><title>Master Your Golf Game At This Hidden Gem Hotel</title><description>With six courses, a world-class club-fitting facility and Forbes Travel Guide Four-Star The Ritz-Carlton Lodge, Reynolds Plantation this golf haven makes everyone feel like a PGA pro. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7131-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7131_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:20:08">http://www.forbes.com/sites/larryolmsted/2014/04/15/10890/</link><title>Can A Bigger Hole Save Golf? Top PGA Tour Pros Follow The Masters With Bold Experiment</title><description>Much has been written in recent years about the slow, steady decline of golf as a participant sport in this country. The usual rationale for the lack of new participants in the game follows a two-tiered thought process. First, it is argued that golf takes too much time in an [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7131-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7131_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:22:30">http://www.forbes.com/sites/larryolmsted/2014/04/14/new-scottish-luxury-lodgings-and-world-class-courses-woo-golf-travelers/</link><title>New Scottish Luxury Lodgings And World-Class Courses Woo Golf Travelers</title><description>With the addition of the two new world class courses nearby, the area suddenly warrants its own week-long golf visit. Fortunately for golfers, there is now an equally impressive place to stay, Links House. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7131-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7131_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:25:00">http://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2014/04/13/jordan-spieths-scintillating-performance-shines-spotlight-on-under-armour-golf-at-the-masters/</link><title>Jordan Spieth's Scintillating Performance Shines Spotlight On Under Armour Golf At The Masters</title><description>Tiger Woods' absence and Rory McIlroy's sub-par performance has left Nike in the dark at The Masters, but rival Under Armour is flourishing with golfer Jordan Spieth's scintillating success through 3 rounds of the Tournament.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7131-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7131_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:26:08">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johnellett/2014/04/10/822/</link><title>How Mizuno Golf Scores With Average Joes In Addition To Masters Contenders</title><description>VideoAs the attention of the golfing world focuses on stories coming from this week’s Masters Tournament, Mizuno Golf is also paying attention to the millions of average golfers and their stories. At the ANA Brand Masters Conference, Ahmet Abaci, VP of Brand Marketing and Management for Mizuno USA, shared how [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7131-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7131_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:29:17">http://www.forbes.com/sites/lauriewerner/2013/07/08/stay-at-this-bermuda-hotel-and-boost-your-golf-game/</link><title>Stay At This Bermuda Hotel And Boost Your Golf Game At The Same Time</title><description>Bermuda is a beautiful island to visit anyway, but it's nirvana if you want to play golf--especially if you stay at Rosewood Tucker's Point. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7131-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7131_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:32:31">http://www.forbes.com/sites/brentbeshore/2012/08/20/golf-the-game-of-life/</link><title>Golf: The Game Of Life</title><description>“Golf is the closest game to the game we call life. You get bad breaks from good shots; you get good breaks from bad shots, but you have to play the ball where it lies.” - Bobby Jones “One of the most fascinating things about golf is how it reflects the [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7131-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7131_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:35:12">http://www.forbes.com/sites/larryolmsted/2013/01/04/take-strokes-off-your-golf-game-today-the-best-way-to-buy-new-clubs/</link><title>Take Strokes Off Your Golf Game Today - The Best Way To Buy New Clubs</title><description>Anyone who plays golf with any regularity should have custom-fitted clubs - no exceptions! I've personally tested many custom club-fitting options - this is one is by far the best. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7131-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7131_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:35:35">http://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestravelguide/2012/01/31/top-10-ways-to-save-your-golf-game-this-winter/</link><title>Top 10 Ways To Save Your Golf Game This Winter</title><description>Don't let your golf game go to waste this offseason. Follow these top 10 tips from Forbes Travel Guide Five-Star resort golf pros. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7131-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7131_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:39:47">http://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2014/02/06/donald-trump-reopens-the-blue-monster-at-doral-and-answers-questions-about-his-role-in-golf/</link><title>Donald Trump Reopens The Blue Monster At Doral And Answers Questions About His Role In Golf</title><description>Donald Trump golf course in Doral has gone through a major renovation in time for the World Golf Championships. What's next for the Donald?</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>