<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7132">massachusetts general hospital jobs</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:42:08" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7132-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7132_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:42:09">http://www.forbes.com/sites/theapothecary/2013/12/04/after-obamacare-can-don-berwick-implement-single-payer-in-massachusetts/</link><title>After Obamacare, Can Don Berwick Implement Single-Payer In Massachusetts?</title><description>Former CMS administrator Don Berwick is running for Governor in Massachusetts. He has an uphill battle in the ever growing primary for the Democratic nominee. Yet his controversial tenure in DC, his pursuit of the Corner Office in the state that birthed RomneyCare (a state that is home to some of the best medical research institutions in the [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7132-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7132_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:43:15">http://www.forbes.com/sites/chrisconover/2014/02/24/obamacare-will-cost-2-9-million-or-more-jobs-a-year/</link><title>Obamacare Will Cost 2.9 Million or More Jobs a Year</title><description>Nearly two years ago, I assured readers Obamacare would result in the equivalent of a loss of 1 million or more jobs. Little did I realize the true figure would turn out to be closer to 2.9 million.  What changed?  The non-partisan Congressional Budget Office recently reported that Obamacare will [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7132-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7132_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:45:05">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johnlamattina/2014/04/07/should-med-school-leaders-serve-on-pharma-boards/</link><title>Should Med School Leaders Serve On Pharma Boards?</title><description>These are exactly the type of people who should be serving on the Boards of biopharmaceutical companies. To restrict AMC leaders from being on company Boards would be a major mistake that would not be in the best interests of the world’s patient population. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7132-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7132_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:48:21">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johnmcquaid/2013/04/17/how-a-decade-of-disasters-helped-boston-hospitals-handle-the-marathon-bombings/</link><title>How A Decade Of Disasters Helped Boston Hospitals Handle The Marathon Bombings</title><description>A man in a Boston Marathon 2013 shirt carries flowers near a memorial site at Boylston and Arlington streets along the course of the Boston Marathon on April 16, 2013, a few blocks from where two explosions struck near the finish line on April 15. (Image credit: AFP/Getty Images via [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7132-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7132_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:51:54">http://www.forbes.com/sites/davechase/2012/11/24/hospital-based-strategic-venture-funds-to-spark-innovation/</link><title>Hospital-based Strategic Venture Funds To Spark Innovation</title><description>Healthcare providers are finding their “play it safe” culture isn’t conducive to breakthrough innovation. Facing the inevitable deflationary pressures being put upon the healthcare system, innovation is critically needed. Having spoken with several innovation groups in health systems, most examples of “innovation” are decidedly uninspiring. [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7132-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7132_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:55:03">http://www.forbes.com/sites/aroy/2012/05/06/massachusetts-institutes-health-care-price-controls-is-america-next/</link><title>Massachusetts Moves Toward Health-Care Price Controls. Is America Next?</title><description>Under Governor Deval Patrick, Massachusetts has tried a couple of methods for limiting the government’s exposure to rising health-care costs. First, Patrick forced insurers to stop raising premiums, which led to a predictable train wreck, as insurers started hemorrhaging cash. When a state appeals board overturned Patrick’s decree, he shifted [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7132-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7132_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:56:33">http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidwhelan/2012/02/26/medicares-hospital-web-site-reeks-of-the-dmv/</link><title>Medicare's Hospital Web Site Reeks Of The DMV</title><description>Have you ever tried to use Medicare data to research a hospital? If so, I bet you've been disappointed. Let's say you live in Las Vegas and you have heart problems. There are three hospitals nearby. You'd like to know the answer to a simple question. "If I ever have a [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7132-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7132_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:59:35">http://www.forbes.com/sites/theapothecary/2012/03/01/how-hospital-mergers-increase-health-costs-and-what-to-do-about-it/</link><title>How Hospital Mergers Increase Health Costs, and What to Do About It</title><description>In November, the Massachusetts Association of Health Plans asked me to speak at their 2011 annual conference, on the topic of hospital consolidation. Given Massachusetts’ central role in the debate over health reform, and the top-notch health policy thinkers in the Boston area, I readily accepted. In this post are the video and slides from my [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7132-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7132_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:02:33">http://www.forbes.com/sites/aroy/2011/08/12/rick-perrys-texas-vs-mitt-romneys-massachusetts-the-health-statistics-almanac/</link><title>Rick Perry's Texas vs. Mitt Romney's Massachusetts: The Health Statistics Almanac</title><description>I've gone through a wealth of statistical data compiled by the U.S. Census, the Kaiser Family Foundation, and the Commonwealth Fund in order to ask: how does health care in Texas compare to that of Massachusetts? Does the data help illuminate the health care records of Perry and Romney as governors of their states, and what they could achieve on [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7132-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7132_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:05:10">http://www.forbes.com/2010/01/25/hospitals-complications-surgery-lifestyle-health-death-rate.html</link><title>America's Least Deadly Hospitals</title><description>Some regional hospitals do a better job preventing fatal complications than famous academic medical centers. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>