<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7133">museum of natural history</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:06:44" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7133-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7133_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:06:44">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jonathonkeats/2014/03/19/no-transgenic-spider-goats-at-the-smithsonian-welcome-to-the-first-post-natural-history-museum/</link><title>No Transgenic Spider-Goats At The Smithsonian? Welcome To The First Post-Natural History Museum</title><description>The typical natural history museum shows stuffed specimens of elephants, alligators and penguins. But you won't find a transgenic spider-goat, an oversight that Pittsburgh's Center for PostNatural History recently rectified by putting one on exhibit. The spider-goat – genetically engineered to produce high-strength spider silk in its milk – joins [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7133-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7133_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:09:15">http://www.forbes.com/sites/carolinehoward/2014/02/12/inside-texas-entrepreneur-randy-bests-private-natural-history-museum/</link><title>Inside Texas Entrepreneur Randy Best's Private Natural History Museum</title><description>Randy Best is a compulsive collector not just of businesses but also of ancient artifacts: "It's a remarkable connection to millions of years ago. Or maybe I never grew up." read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7133-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7133_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:10:42">http://www.forbes.com/sites/marcbabej/2013/08/07/discovery-jumps-the-shark-on-shark-week-and-draws-stellar-ratings/</link><title>Discovery Jumps The Shark On Shark Week... And Draws Stellar Ratings</title><description>Megalodon jaws at the American Museum of Natural History, New York. (Photo credit: Wikipedia) Discovery Channel has come under fire from viewers and critics for its program, “Megalodon: The Monster Shark Lives,” which opened opened the network's “Shark Week”. The ratings were not the problem: Megalodon drew the highest dating for any [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7133-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7133_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:11:58">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johnfarrell/2014/02/27/the-real-evolution-debate-is-it-all-just-natural-selection/</link><title>The Real Evolution Debate: Is It All Just Natural Selection?</title><description>With all the attention given to the debate over evolution and creationism, you'd never know that a much more interesting debate has been going on for decades amongst evolutionary biologists: about the rivals to natural selection. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7133-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7133_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:14:04">http://www.forbes.com/sites/paulrodgers/2014/02/11/ancient-footprints-throw-early-human-history-into-turmoil/</link><title>Ancient Footprints Throw Early Human Pre-History Into Turmoil</title><description>VideoThe discovery of 850,000-year-old muddy footprints on an English beach have thrown our understanding of early human pre-history into turmoil. The 49 prints, found in Happisburgh, Norfolk, are the earliest in Europe by half a million years. They raise questions about how and when humans spread from their ancestral home in [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7133-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7133_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:17:24">http://www.forbes.com/sites/anthonydemarco/2013/02/16/cindy-chaos-butterfly-brooch-added-to-smithsonian-gem-hall/</link><title>Cindy Chao's Butterfly Brooch Added to Smithsonian Gem Hall</title><description>The Smithsonian Institute National Museum of Natural History will add to its celebrated gem collection with Masterpiece Royal Butterfly by jewelry artisan Cindy Chao. The brooch will be the first jewelry piece by a Taiwanese designer to be inducted into the institution’s permanent collection. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7133-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7133_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:20:00">http://www.forbes.com/sites/sethporges/2012/07/20/neil-degrasse-tyson-vegas-got-me-into-twitter/</link><title>Neil deGrasse Tyson: Vegas Got Me Into Twitter</title><description>Photo credit: Wikipedia These days, astrophysicist Neil deGrasse Tyson is quite simply the face of space science. To say that the director of New York's Hayden Planetarium at the American Museum of Natural History has developed a cult-like following is an understatement—geeks simply go gonzo in his presence. It's not just his undeniable [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7133-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7133_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:23:21">http://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestravelguide/2013/03/19/londons-late-night-museums/</link><title>London's Late-Night Museums</title><description>London is filled with museums of all types and one of the coolest ways to see them is after hours. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7133-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7133_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:26:37">http://www.forbes.com/sites/zackomalleygreenburg/2014/03/26/why-wu-tang-will-release-just-one-copy-of-its-secret-album/</link><title>Why Wu-Tang Will Release Just One Copy Of Its Secret Album</title><description>Wu-Tang's aim is to use the album as a springboard for the reconsideration of music as art, hoping that the approach will help restore recorded music to a place alongside visual art--and change the music business in the process.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7133-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7133_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:29:04">http://www.forbes.com/sites/carolpinchefsky/2012/01/25/nycs-planetarium-to-become-a-200-person-video-game/</link><title>NYC's Planetarium to Become a 200-person Video Game</title><description>If you’ve been to the Rose Center for Earth and Space, a.k.a. the Planetarium in New York City’s American Museum of Natural History, you know just how impressive it is. (Really, really impressive.) But thanks to a group of independent game developers, Babycastles, it’s about to become even more awesome than that. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>