<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7134">history of yoga</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:30:29" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7134-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7134_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:30:30">http://www.forbes.com/sites/peggydrexler/2014/03/24/is-the-fear-of-future-regret-a-valid-motivator-for-having-children/</link><title>Is The Fear Of Future Regret A Valid Motivator For Having Children</title><description>As the debate rages about the merits of the childfree life is the fear of future regret a valid motivator for popping out babies. Regret made a cameo in a Time magazine cover story about the rise in childfree couples. Many women and men struggling over the decision—have kids or don’t have kids?—wonder [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7134-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7134_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:31:49">http://www.forbes.com/sites/alicegwalton/2012/05/03/the-great-yoga-debate-is-western-practice-evolving-or-devolving/</link><title>The Great Yoga Debate: Has Yoga Sold Its Soul?</title><description>One group wants to “Take Back Yoga.” Others say that launching such a campaign is un-yogic to begin with. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7134-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7134_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:33:19">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jacquelynsmith/2013/12/06/the-biggest-career-crashes-of-2013/</link><title>The Biggest Career Crashes Of 2013</title><description>Thought you had a tough year at work? Check out our list of the biggest career crashes of 2013.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7134-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7134_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:34:53">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jamespoulos/2013/07/31/the-embarrassing-failure-of-our-politics-of-religion-industry/</link><title>The Embarrassing Failure Of Our Politics-Of-Religion Industry</title><description>Over at BuzzFeed, Andrew Kaczynski has done the world a favor by pointing out that Reza Aslan, a person who's good at staying dignified in an abusively dumb interview, turned right around and did unto others on Twitter what was done to him -- and more -- sometimes toward trolls, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7134-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7134_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:37:06">http://www.forbes.com/sites/robertglatter/2013/10/10/the-perils-of-hip-injuries-in-mens-tennis-how-mike-bryan-of-the-bryan-brothers-beat-the-odds/</link><title>The Perils Of Hip Injuries In Men's Tennis: How Mike Bryan-Of The Bryan Brothers-Beat The Odds</title><description>NEW YORK, NY - SEPTEMBER 07: Bob Bryan and Mike Bryan of the United States pose with the trophy after their men's doubles final match against Leander Paes of India and Radek Stepanek of the Czech Republic on Day Twelve of the 2012 US Open at USTA Billie Jean King [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7134-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7134_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:38:36">http://www.forbes.com/sites/andrewbender/2014/01/21/layover-guide-chicago-ohare/</link><title>Layover Guide: Chicago O'Hare</title><description>If you've got to be stuck somewhere, Chicago ain't a half-bad place. O'Hare Airport has easy access to shopping, a nice gym and one of America's great downtowns. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7134-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7134_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:39:56">http://www.forbes.com/sites/annabel/2013/08/08/a-hawaiian-classic-better-than-ever-turtle-bay-resort-on-the-north-shore-of-oahu/</link><title>A Hawaiian Classic, Better Than Ever: Turtle Bay Resort On The North Shore Of Oahu</title><description>Instead, the owners of Oahu's Turtle Bay are investing millions of dollars in making it more comfortable, more modern, and more memorable.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7134-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7134_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:41:48">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jimpowell/2013/08/01/how-did-rich-connecticut-morph-into-one-of-americas-worst-performing-economies/</link><title>How Did Rich Connecticut Morph Into One Of America's Worst Performing Economies?</title><description>Why the human capital exodus from one of our most prosperous states? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7134-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7134_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:44:56">http://www.forbes.com/sites/daviatemin/2013/07/19/getting-out-of-the-heat-10-ways-for-leaders-to-deal-with-an-angry-public/</link><title>Getting Out Of The Heat: 10 Ways For Leaders To Deal With An Angry Public</title><description>Yes, we’re having a heat wave. But beyond 97 degree temperatures, there is another kind of heat that some leaders around the world are facing – an increasingly angry public. The true wisdom of corporations, organizations or individuals is to know when to be quiet and bear or ignore it, when to fight back, and when to change. Here are 10 new tips [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7134-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7134_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 04:46:30">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johngaudiosi/2013/04/02/wwe-hall-of-fame-diva-trish-stratus-talks-wrestlemania-video-games-and-aj-lee/</link><title>WWE Hall Of Fame Diva Trish Stratus Talks WrestleMania, Video Games And AJ Lee</title><description>Patricia Anne Stratigias is better known to millions of professional wrestling fans as WWE Diva Trish Stratus. On April 6 at Madison Square Garden, Stephanie McMahon will induct Stratus into the WWE Hall of Fame. The seven-time Women’s Champion was a pioneer for female wrestling and one of the icons [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>