<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7141">Cambridge must do</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:36:16" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7141-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7141_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:36:16">http://www.forbes.com/sites/timworstall/2014/03/01/ha-joon-chang-should-know-this-the-sp-500-and-ftse-100-do-not-reflect-the-us-and-uk-domestic-economies/</link><title>Ha-Joon Chang Should Know This, The S&amp;amp;P 500 And FTSE 100 Do Not Reflect The US And UK Domestic Economies</title><description>I have to admit that I found myself staring rather gape mouthed at this argument put forward by Ha-Joon Chang in The Guardian. I'm perfectly willing to listen to, possibly even agree with, arguments that the S&amp;P 500 or the FTSE 100 might be overvalued. I can think of a [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7141-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7141_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:39:55">http://www.forbes.com/sites/avidlarizadeh/2013/11/18/we-must-inspire-women-to-design-their-own-paths/</link><title>We Must Inspire Women To Design Their Own Paths</title><description>I have been very fortunate throughout my formative years and still today to be surrounded by inspiring men and women. At the age of 34, I feel I have only scraped the surface of everything I am yet to experience and achieve both professionally and personally. My resume so far [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7141-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7141_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:44:02">http://www.forbes.com/sites/riabiz/2011/03/07/compliance-fears-are-causing-some-rias-to-do-a-reverse-breakaway/</link><title>Cambridge, Commonwealth See Reverse Breakaways</title><description>More financial advisors are rolling up their own RIAs to join those of Cambridge Investment Research and Commonwealth Financial Network to avoid red tape spewing out of government regulators in the wake of the financial crisis, according to executives of those two companies. The tougher regulatory environment is helping those RIA-friendly IBDs [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7141-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7141_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:45:58">http://www.forbes.com/sites/tanyamohn/2011/07/13/royal-couple-inspire-travel-to-historic-cambridge-2/</link><title>Royal Couple Inspire Travel to Historic Cambridge</title><description>Prince William and Kate Middleton  have created a fair amount of buzz the last few months, from the  celebrated royal wedding and honeymoon in the secluded Seychelles to their first official foreign visits to Canada and the United States in recent weeks. But beyond all the glitz and glamour, it seems [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7141-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7141_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:48:48">http://www.forbes.com/sites/riabiz/2011/05/06/cambridge-commonwealth-vault-advisors-into-social-media/</link><title>Cambridge, Commonwealth Vault Advisors Into Social Media</title><description>Will partnerships with, respectively, Socialware and Erado, translate into elusive growth-via-networking? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7141-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7141_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:50:52">http://www.forbes.com/sites/stevedenning/2013/01/17/the-boeing-debacle-seven-lessons-every-ceo-must-learn/</link><title>The Boeing Debacle: Seven Lessons Every CEO Must Learn</title><description>Seven Lessons That All CEOs Must Learn From The Boeing Debacle: The Follies of Offshoring read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7141-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7141_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:54:52">http://www.forbes.com/2009/09/30/cambridge-massachusetts-opeb-pensions-ratings-opinions-contributors-peter-schweich.html</link><title>Cambridge Runs Amok</title><description>A template for massive municipal profligacy. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7141-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7141_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:55:45">http://www.forbes.com/sites/berlinschoolofcreativeleadership/2014/03/21/a-g-lafleys-recent-book-is-a-leaders-guide-to-building-an-everyday-strategic-practice/</link><title>A.G. Lafley's Recent Book Is A Leader's Guide To Building An Everyday Strategic Practice</title><description>A review of A.G. Lafley and Roger L. Martin, Playing to Win: How Strategy Really Works, Cambridge: Harvard Business Review Press, 2013. By David Slocum A.G. Lafley, CEO of Procter &amp; Gamble from 2000-2009, is one of the most-respected and successful corporate leaders of the young 21st century. (He’s also much beloved by Berlin School [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7141-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7141_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 06:57:56">http://www.forbes.com/sites/mgiresearch/2014/03/04/the-future-of-venture-capital-tech-valuations-and-the-fate-of-tech-incumbents-conversation-with-bill-janeway/</link><title>The Future of Venture Capital, Tech Valuations and the Fate of Tech Incumbents - Conversation with Bill Janeway</title><description>I recently had a chance to catch up with Bill Janeway of Warburg-Pincus to get his take on a whole spectrum of technology investment and innovation issues. Bill, - who is currently a Senior Adviser at Warburg-Pincus, devotes a great deal of his time to teaching at Cambridge and Princeton, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7141-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7141_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 07:02:07">http://www.forbes.com/sites/stevenberglas/2012/01/27/the-top-10-steps-you-must-take-to-use-anger-effectively/</link><title>The Top 10 Steps You Must Take To Use Anger Effectively</title><description>Image via Wikipedia There was rare, near-universal agreement among folks who care about such things, that Newt Gingrich won the South Carolina Republican primary because of how he tore-into moderator John King of CNN. Although Mr. Gingrich’s approval ratings have since dipped from the high point they reached after he gutted [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>