<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7147">breast cancer review</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:06:55" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7147-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7147_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:06:56">http://www.forbes.com/sites/robertglatter/2014/03/25/guideline-updated-regarding-role-of-sentinel-lymph-node-biopsy-in-early-stage-breast-cancer/</link><title>Guideline Updated Regarding Role Of Sentinel Lymph Node Biopsy In Early Stage Breast Cancer</title><description>New recommendations regarding the use of sentinel lymph node biopsy in patients with early stage breast cancer were issued by The American Society of Clinical Oncology (ASCO) and published in the Journal of Clinical Oncology on March 24. ASCO organized a group of experts in medical oncology, pathology, surgical oncology, and radiation [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7147-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7147_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:08:27">http://www.forbes.com/sites/trevorbutterworth/2013/07/30/bpa-and-breast-cancer-when-academics-spin-statistics/</link><title>BPA And Breast Cancer: When Academics Spin Statistics</title><description>A new study, funded by the National Institute of Environmental Health Sciences (NIEHS), and published in a journal the institute subsidizes – Environmental Health Perspectives (EHP) – raises an alarm. This is not, in itself, unusual; EHP is a repository of alarming claims about the environment; but what makes this [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7147-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7147_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:10:25">http://www.forbes.com/sites/peterubel/2013/05/08/who-wants-to-take-a-pill-to-prevent-breast-cancer/</link><title>Who Wants to Take a Pill to Prevent Breast Cancer?</title><description>(Photo credit: Wikipedia) On April 14, The United States Preventive Services Taskforce concluded that women with an elevated risk of breast cancer – who have never been diagnosed with breast cancer but whose family history and other medical factors increase their odds of developing the disease--should consider taking one of two pills [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7147-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7147_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:11:34">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jjcolao/2012/10/17/how-a-breast-cancer-pioneer-finally-turned-a-profit/</link><title>How A Breast Cancer Pioneer Finally Turned A Profit</title><description>Myriad Genetics was a pioneer in detecting the breast cancer gene. Nearly two decades--and hundreds of millions of dollars later--it's finally turning a profit. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7147-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7147_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:12:23">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johnlamattina/2012/12/20/rd-lessons-from-pfizers-new-breast-cancer-drug-pd-332991/</link><title>R&amp;amp;D Lessons from Pfizer's New Breast Cancer Drug, PD-332,991</title><description>Earlier this month, Pfizer reported extremely exciting phase 2 results regarding its experimental breast cancer medication, PD-332,991. As related by Bloomberg’s Michelle Fay Cortez, when PD-332,991 was combined with Novartis’ drug, Femara, post-menopausal patients with estrogen receptor positive breast tumors showed no tumor progression [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7147-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7147_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:14:54">http://www.forbes.com/sites/womensenews/2012/06/01/breast-cancer-marketing-laid-bare-in-junes-feminist-film-releases/</link><title>Breast Cancer Marketing Laid Bare in June's Feminist Film Releases</title><description>By Jennifer Merin WeNews film critic (WOMENSENEWS)--Opening on June 1, Lea Pool’s investigative "Pink Ribbons, Inc.” focuses on the nonprofit industry that has developed around, and more or less taken over, fundraising for breast cancer research. Patients with various stages of breast cancer, public health advocates and researchers raise three [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7147-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7147_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:15:23">http://www.forbes.com/sites/trevorbutterworth/2014/04/09/bpa-the-scientists-the-scare-the-100-million-dollar-surge/</link><title>BPA: The Scientists, The Scare, The 100-Million Dollar Surge</title><description>Conspiracy, incompetence, a federal agency out of control. A recent Mother Jones story by Mariah Blake indicts the Food and Drug Administration (FDA) as a threat to science and public health over the way it’s conducting research into bisphenol A (BPA), the never-ending chemical scare story of the 21st century. [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7147-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7147_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:16:19">http://www.forbes.com/sites/trevorbutterworth/2011/09/21/the-breast-cancer-funds-despicable-class-warfare/</link><title>Breast Cancer Fund Study: Science Or Class Warfare?</title><description>As I’ve noted here on Forbes, the mainstream media has a pretty amazing knack for ignoring key research when there’s a controversy. So, this summer, we’ve seen a whole series of important studies on the chemical bisphenol A (BPA) come and go with next to no coverage, even though the [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7147-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7147_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:16:53">http://www.forbes.com/sites/matthewherper/2013/06/23/the-fdas-cancer-czar-says-he-cant-approve-new-drugs-fast-enough/</link><title>The FDA's Cancer Czar Says He Can't Approve New Drugs Fast Enough</title><description>Dr. Richard Pazdur Maybe more than any other person alive, Richard Pazdur, the director of the Food and Drug Administration's Office of Oncology and Hematology Products, personifies the tension between the need to get new drugs to patients fast and the competing desire to make sure they are safe and effective [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7147-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7147_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 08:18:55">http://www.forbes.com/sites/scottgottlieb/2013/06/10/why-we-should-spend-more-on-pricey-cancer-drugs/</link><title>Why We Should Be Spending More On Some Pricey Cancer Drugs</title><description>By Scott Gottlieb, M.D. Here’s a heretical statement: We don’t spend enough money on high-priced cancer drugs. In recent months, there have been provocative editorials by leading academic cancer doctors arguing that the price of many new cancer drugs is too high. But what if the high price of new drugs is a [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>