<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7153">pig latin help</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:47:09" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7153-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7153_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:47:10">http://www.forbes.com/sites/bethhoffman/2014/03/26/how-increased-meat-consumption-in-china-changes-landscapes-across-the-globe/</link><title>How Increased Meat Consumption In China Changes Landscapes Across The Globe</title><description>Dramatic meat consumption in China is responsible for reshaping landscapes in west hemisphere. Meat eating is also affecting the health and well being of communities across the globe in ways we have not thought of before. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7153-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7153_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:48:06">http://www.forbes.com/sites/robertlaura/2012/09/27/make-the-most-out-of-your-401k-contributions-right-now/</link><title>Make The Most Out Of Your 401(k) Contributions Right Now</title><description>Savvy investors can use a strategy normally reserved for more knowledgeable and experienced market players to help them get the most out of their 401(k). Here's how. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7153-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7153_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:48:42">http://www.forbes.com/sites/zackomalleygreenburg/2013/12/10/grammy-nominations-2014-the-full-list/</link><title>Grammy Nominations 2014: The Full List</title><description>The nominations have been announced for the 56th Annual Grammy Awards, with Jay Z's nine nods leading the pack. Four acts garnered seven nominations apiece: Kendrick Lamar, Pharrell Williams, Justin Timberlake and Macklemore &amp; Ryan Lewis. But there are plenty more superstars--and lesser-known but stupendously talented musicians--among the [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7153-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7153_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:50:55">http://www.forbes.com/sites/richardbehar/2013/08/28/why-so-many-palestinian-high-tech-entrepreneurs-hate-my-forbes-cover-story/</link><title>Why So Many Palestinian High-Tech Entrepreneurs Hate My FORBES Cover Story</title><description>\--- "The negative reactions to an article that tries to suggest an optimistic perspective on Israeli-Palestinian relationships are disappointing. They are a reflection of the strengthening culture of avoidance and extremism promoted heavily by some Palestinian leaders who have given up hope for peace. All this said, readers of read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7153-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7153_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:53:15">http://www.forbes.com/sites/skollworldforum/2013/05/02/the-rise-of-social-entrepreneurship-suggests-a-possible-future-for-global-capitalism/</link><title>The Rise Of Social Entrepreneurship Suggests A Possible Future For Global Capitalism</title><description>Editor's Note: Richard McGill Murphy is the managing editor of Voices on Society, a print and online publication from McKinsey &amp; Company. Denielle Sachs is director of social impact for McKinsey &amp; Company.  As the first Internet stock bubble neared its popping point in 1999, IBM chief executive Lou Gerstner famously dismissed the [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7153-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7153_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:54:08">http://www.forbes.com/forbes/2008/1013/101b.html</link><title>Cleaning Up Cheaply</title><description>A Guatemalan engineering firm sells clean infrastructure that people can afford. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7153-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7153_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:56:57">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jamesmarshallcrotty/2012/01/26/the-end-of-the-diploma-as-we-know-it/</link><title>Why Get a Pricey Diploma When a Bleepin' Badge Will Do?</title><description>Against the backdrop of a student loan bubble, the high cost of four-year college, and an extremely difficult job market, alternate forms of skill certification are gaining steam. Chief among these is the digital badge. Is this the beginning of the end for the long-coveted, much-touted college diploma? Perhaps, at long last, the credential [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7153-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7153_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:57:28">http://www.forbes.com/2007/11/21/investments-stocks-real-estate-pf_cx_pm_07invguide_land.html</link><title>2008 Investment Guide</title><description>Our latest semiannual investment guide offers tips galore for investing and financial planning in volatile times. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7153-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7153_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 09:59:06">http://www.forbes.com/2010/05/08/gsk-fda-rotavirus-vaccines-business-healthcare-glaxosmithkline.html</link><title>GlaxoSmithKline On FDA's Rotavirus Vaccine Concerns</title><description>A statement in response to the FDA's Advisory Committee Meeting on rotavirus vaccines. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7153-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7153_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:00:53">http://www.forbes.com/2009/09/17/schmidheiny-caaguazu-paraguay-personal-finance-jorge.html</link><title>From Paraguay, With 18 Siblings And Ambition</title><description>One graduate of a Schmidheiny funded school tells his story. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>