<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7155">ted talk mooc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:24:50" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7155-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7155_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:24:50">http://www.forbes.com/sites/groupthink/2013/12/05/youll-never-guess-whos-disrupting-online-learning/</link><title>You'll Never Guess Who's Disrupting Online Learning</title><description>We have been hearing for the past 18 months that higher education is on the precipice of a massive and disruptive transformation because of the MOOC. Not so fast!</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7155-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7155_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:27:59">http://www.forbes.com/sites/naveenjain/2013/05/18/effective_addictive_education/</link><title>Creating Adaptive, Personalized, Effective and Addictive Education System for the Next Century</title><description>I suggested in my first article that our education system is not broken but has simply become obsolete. It’s doing exactly what it was designed to do but unfortunately, our needs have changed. We can’t just make incremental improvement to the current education system to somehow make it work for [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7155-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7155_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:30:40">http://www.forbes.com/sites/matthewherper/2013/02/11/in-reddit-ama-bill-gates-discusses-vaccines-climate-change-and-steve-jobs/</link><title>In Reddit AMA, Bill Gates Discusses Vaccines, Climate Change, And Steve Jobs</title><description>VideoThe image Bill Gates sent Reddit as verification. You can learn a lot about the world's most generous man when he does an AMA ("ask me anything") on the popular Web site Reddit. Bill Gates likes to listen to Weezer, U2, and Spinal Tap, and his favorite book of the last decade [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7155-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7155_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:31:38">http://www.forbes.com/sites/skollworldforum/2013/04/07/education-finally-ripe-for-radical-innovation-by-social-entrepreneurs/</link><title>Education Finally Ripe For Radical Innovation By Social Entrepreneurs</title><description>Editor's Note: Debra Dunn is on the faculty at Stanford University’s Hasso Plattner Institute of Design (d.school), where she spearheads classroom and project work in Design for Sustainable Abundance and the application of user-centred design to service learning. This article was published in advance of the 2013 Skoll World Forum. Watch the live [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>