<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7168">fabric glue</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:30:31" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7168-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7168_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:30:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/benkepes/2013/11/18/exclusive-salesforce-picks-bluejeans-for-first-appexchange-video-integration/</link><title>Salesforce Picks BlueJeans For First Video Integration. But It's Complicated</title><description>This week is DreamForce, the Salesforce.com extravaganza that will see a reported 120000 people descend on San Francisco for the week. The announcements are coming thick and fast and tomorrow sees CEO Marc Benioff take the stage for one of his legendary (and epic) keynotes. It's always nice to be able to break [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7168-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7168_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:33:08">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jonathansalembaskin/2013/10/24/brooks-brothers-should-get-grilled-for-its-steakhouse-plan/</link><title>Brooks Brothers Should Get Grilled For Its Steakhouse Plan</title><description>Brooks Brothers invented apparel retailing for America's ruling class, back before being rich was synonymous with looking and acting like Paris Hilton, and then watched Tommy Hilfiger and A&amp;F turn its brand position into a reality show in which any of us could participate. It has since experimented with an [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7168-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7168_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:34:22">http://www.forbes.com/sites/dougbandow/2013/11/19/americans-are-living-better-then-they-have-at-any-point-in-human-history/</link><title>Americans Are Living Better Then They Have At Any Point In Human History</title><description>Thank you to the innovative 1 percenters for removing unease from our lives. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7168-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7168_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:35:35">http://www.forbes.com/sites/thomasbasile/2013/07/19/jimmy-carter-may-actually-be-right-this-time/</link><title>Jimmy Carter May Actually Be Right This Time</title><description>It's up to all of us to make the government work. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7168-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7168_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:37:03">http://www.forbes.com/forbes-life-magazine/2012/0521/porfolio-dan-scheinman-baseball-collector-detective-work.html</link><title>Collector's Detective Work</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7168-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7168_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:39:18">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ericsavitz/2012/05/07/sidebar-the-true-story-behind-bobby-thomsons-1951-jersey/</link><title>The True Story Behind Bobby Thomson's 1951 Jersey</title><description>This story appears in the May issue of ForbesLife magazine, dated May 21. It is a sidebar to a story on investor Dan Scheinman's collection of historic baseball uniforms. Bobby Thomson's 1951 New York Giants uniform. Dan Scheinman, a former Cisco Systems senior executive, bought his most famous piece from Bobby Thomson himself in [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7168-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7168_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:41:01">http://www.forbes.com/sites/meghancasserly/2012/05/04/workplace-fashion-sos-quick-and-unexpected-fixes-for-apparel-disasters/</link><title>Workplace Fashion SOS: Quick And Unexpected Fixes For Apparel Disasters</title><description>A few short years ago, as an employed, rent-paying 25-year-old, I bought myself my first truly expensive pair of shoes. They were Kate Spade, knee-high, four-inch black boots and set me back about $350. I was in love. So in love that I justified the expenditure and its serious dent [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7168-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7168_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:44:14">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jerrymclaughlin/2012/04/26/hey-have-you-ever-noticed-this/</link><title>Hey, Have You Ever Noticed This?</title><description>I was recently attending a baseball game at AT&amp;T Park when I got a pleasant surprise: a friend of many years was making his way to a seat right in front of mine. He looked in my direction; I smiled at him. Then he sat down without acknowledging me. My [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7168-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7168_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:46:20">http://www.forbes.com/sites/innovatorsdna/2012/04/12/how-procter-gamble-keeps-its-innovation-edge/</link><title>How Procter &amp; Gamble Keeps Its Innovation Edge</title><description>At P&amp;G, the best connectors and analogy-makers are the best innovators. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7168-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7168_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 13:47:23">http://www.forbes.com/sites/benzingainsights/2011/10/07/exit-stage-left-possible-societal-costs-if-the-economy-fails-to-recover/</link><title>Exit Stage Left: Possible Societal Costs if the Economy Fails to Recover</title><description>By Marco Rabinowitz While the US economy continues to hobble its way back towards recovery, I think it is important that we keep in mind the sociological context of the current financial crisis and to where it could evolve if the economy fails to recover. In particular, I am speaking of [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>