<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7174">seal team 6</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:05:41" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7174-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7174_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:05:41">http://www.forbes.com/sites/quora/2012/03/02/why-was-seal-team-6-devgru-chosen-over-delta-force-1st-sfod-d-for-the-abbottabad-operation/</link><title>Why Was SEAL Team 6 (DEVGRU) Chosen Over Delta Force (1st SFOD-D) For The Abbottabad Operation?</title><description>Why Was SEAL Team 6 Chosen Over Delta Force For The Abbottabad Operation? This question was originally answered on Quora by Sergio Rodriguera Jr. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7174-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7174_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:06:12">http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidsturt/2014/03/19/nails-in-the-coffin-6-examples-of-recognition-gone-wrong/</link><title>Nails In The Coffin: 6 Examples Of Recognition Gone Wrong</title><description>Stacks of research have proven that purposeful employee recognition can ignite engagement, accelerate performance, and build strong cultures. But, can recognition go wrong? Well, what does bad recognition look like anyway? Through the years, we’ve heard stories of managers who mispronounced employee names while presenting awards for achievement. [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7174-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7174_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:09:09">http://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2013/05/23/will-sprints-final-clearwire-offer-seal-the-deal/</link><title>Will Sprint's Final Clearwire Offer Seal The Deal?</title><description>Sprint said that the sweetened offer was its ‘best and final’ one, implying that it isn’t willing to enter into a protracted bidding war to acquire the remaining nearly 50% of Clearwire that it doesn’t already own. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7174-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7174_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:11:07">http://www.forbes.com/sites/joshlinkner/2013/04/23/6-lessons-from-an-american-renegade/</link><title>6 Lessons From An American Renegade</title><description>English: City seal of Detroit, Michigan. (Photo credit: Wikipedia) Over the course of a few years, Dan Gilbert has purchased approximately 3 million square feet of commercial space in downtown Detroit, spent almost a billion dollars to acquire and renovate buildings,  and moved the entire Michigan-based Quicken Loans staff into these [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7174-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7174_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:13:38">http://www.forbes.com/sites/katiedrummond/2012/08/25/navy-seal-book/</link><title>Navy SEAL Memoirist Also Consulted On Video Game</title><description>Since leaving the Navy last year, it seems that former SEAL Matt Bissonnette has been keeping himself busy. Earlier this week, Bissonnette was revealed as the author of a forthcoming memoir about the raid that killed Osama bin Laden. Now, an unnamed source has told the Los Angeles Times that Bissonnette, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7174-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7174_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:15:56">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markhughes/2013/08/24/6-reasons-the-internet-is-wrong-about-ben-affleck-as-batman/</link><title>6 Reasons The Internet Is Wrong About Ben Affleck As Batman</title><description>The announcement this week that Ben Affleck has been cast to play Batman in Batman vs. Superman (see my full report on the story here), the upcoming Warner Bros. sequel to Man of Steel, prompted surprise from those who didn't see it coming, and a significant amount of outrageous reactions [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7174-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7174_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:16:20">http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2012/11/09/navy-seals-face-disciplinary-action-after-consulting-on-medal-of-honor-warfighter/</link><title>Navy Seals Face Disciplinary Action After Consulting On 'Medal Of Honor: Warfighter'</title><description>The US government has produced its own video game in the past, but Navy SEALS caught moonlighting for EA are facing disciplinary action. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7174-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7174_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:17:27">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ericbasu/2012/04/04/how-to-run-a-startup-like-a-seal-platoon/</link><title>How to run a startup like a SEAL Platoon</title><description>Start off every day at 4 am by forcing everyone to jump in 50 degree water, roll around in the sand, and run 10 miles with a 6 foot tall, 250 lb tough-as-nails instructor yelling at you the entire time...or not. Cover of Art of War There are lots of books on [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7174-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7174_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:19:53">http://www.forbes.com/sites/katiedrummond/2012/08/29/no-easy-day-seal-book/</link><title>'No Easy Day': SEAL Memoir Contradicts Official Account of Bin Laden's Death</title><description>The White House version of the raid that killed Osama bin Laden contains key differences from the account presented in a new memoir. (Image credit: Getty Images via @daylife) "No Easy Day," a memoir penned by an ex-Navy SEAL, won't hit bookstores for another week. But already, the book is making [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7174-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7174_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:21:01">http://www.forbes.com/sites/brentgleeson/2012/10/31/6-ways-brands-build-trust-through-social-media/</link><title>6 Ways Brands Build Trust Through Social Media</title><description>Using social media for business marketing has been a hot topic for years now, but brands are still trying to harness the power of the digital socialsphere to discover the best ways to directly impact their bottom lines. As social media use advances, so does the frequency in which brands [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>