<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7176"> weather in nyc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:41:19" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7176-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7176_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:41:20">http://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesstylefile/2014/01/23/six-spring-trend-essentials/</link><title>Six Spring Trend Essentials</title><description>After the polar vortex and now freezing temperatures in NYC, warm weather could not come soon enough! I combed through all of the spring looks (for vicarious warmth) and picked out the ones that I thought were the best, most wearable and would ultimately last in your closet for longer [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7176-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7176_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:43:50">http://www.forbes.com/sites/prishe/2014/01/29/super-bowl-xlviii-how-weather-proximity-impact-secondary-pricing/</link><title>Super Bowl XLVIII: How Weather, Proximity Impact Secondary Pricing</title><description>Weather forecasts and lack of proximity of the participating teams to the host site are playing major roles in how the secondary prices for Super Bowl XLVIII have fluctuated since the Denver Broncos and Seattle Seahawks earned their tickets to the big game. And the reality is that proximity (or lack [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7176-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7176_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:45:55">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kurtbadenhausen/2014/02/07/washington-chicago-are-best-bets-for-next-cold-weather-super-bowl/</link><title>Washington, Chicago Are Best Bets For Next Cold Weather Super Bowl</title><description>Super Bowl XLVIII went off without a hitch and now every northern city wants its shot. We break down the best candidates. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7176-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7176_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:46:34">http://www.forbes.com/sites/prishe/2014/01/22/the-business-of-super-bowl-xlviii-why-hotel-spikes-might-be-lower-for-nyc-super-bowl/</link><title>The Business Of Super Bowl XLVIII: Why "Hotel Spikes" Might Be Lower For NYC Super Bowl</title><description>When a city hosts a Super Bowl, there are usually considerable spikes in various hotel industry metrics such as occupancy rates, average daily rates, and revenue per available room. But due to a variety of factors, these "hotel spikes" may not be as large for Super Bowl XLVIII at MetLife Stadium [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7176-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7176_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:49:39">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ricardogeromel/2013/03/29/ultimate-nyc-easter-weekend-guide/</link><title>Ultimate NYC Easter Weekend Guide</title><description>Pedro Andrade (Photo by Caitlin Mitchell) Who better to serve as a guide to Manhattan’s best offerings this Easter weekend than Pedro Andrade? The Brazilian journalist-model-actor based in New York, who received an award for “Best Up and Coming TV Host” from the NY Press, told FORBES the ultimate NYC [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7176-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7176_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:51:08">http://www.forbes.com/sites/tomkonrad/2012/06/25/a-private-company-running-nyc-parking-environmentalists-should-rejoice/</link><title>A Private Company Running NYC Parking? Environmentalists Should Rejoice.</title><description>Q: When is paying more for parking a good idea? Image credit: Getty Images via @daylife) A: When it means you can find a spot. Check out Felix Salmon's discussion of dynamic pricing for New York's parking meters.  New York is only looking into the idea of variable pricing for parking, but that idea [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7176-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7176_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:54:40">http://www.forbes.com/sites/gregorymcneal/2012/10/30/rat-invasion-will-subway-rodents-move-into-flooded-nyc-neighborhoods/</link><title>UPDATED: Rat Invasion? Will Subway Rodents Move Into Flooded NYC Neighborhoods?</title><description>VideoUPDATE:  Various media outlets, including Fox News, have now picked up on the story line I initially outlined here on October 30th. CBS news, in their piece "Sandy May Drive Subway Rats Onto NYC Streets" wrote: "Most of the rats that are living there will actually drown," said Herwig read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7176-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7176_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:57:04">http://www.forbes.com/sites/larryolmsted/2012/04/17/deltas-new-laguardia-hub-revolutionary-for-nyc-fliers/</link><title>Delta's New LaGuardia Hub Revolutionary For NYC Fliers</title><description>But travelers don’t have to wait on construction to begin reaping the many benefits of Delta’s newest hub. The upgrades have had an immediate impact, starting with non-stop service to 12 new cities that launched on March 25. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7176-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7176_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:57:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jeneneronick/2011/05/24/sunset-sips-nycs-summer-rooftops/</link><title>Sunset Sips: NYC's Summer Rooftops</title><description>By Kyle Udelson, Lifestyle Manager Labor Day is nearing and with it, the promise of sunshine-filled weekends wandering Soho and the West Village, lemonade strolls on the Highline and rooftop barbeques. When the sun sets, head to the rooftoops below for some cool sips and scenes. Mulberry Project 149 Mulberry Street, near Grand [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7176-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7176_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 15:58:23">http://www.forbes.com/sites/quora/2012/02/28/is-there-any-reason-to-take-uber-versus-nyc-cabs/</link><title>Is There Any Reason To Take Uber Versus NYC Cabs?</title><description>Is There Any Reason To Take Uber Versus NYC Cabs? This question was originally answered by Bradley Voytek on Quora. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>