<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7185">constitution of italy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:39:48" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7185-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7185_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:39:48">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ralphbenko/2014/03/20/3510/</link><title>Crimea, Venice, Colorado Are Saying That The Era Of Big Government Is Over</title><description>"Regionalization is people's way to send a message to the Big Heads." read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7185-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7185_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:40:15">http://www.forbes.com/sites/christinemoorman/2014/02/18/the-riddle-of-marketing-in-russia/</link><title>The Riddle Of Marketing In Russia</title><description>This post was co-authored with Evgenia Barkanova, Irina Kudryashova, and Irina Melnik, all MBA students at the Fuqua School of Business, Duke University. Winston Churchill said, “Russia is a riddle wrapped in a mystery inside an enigma.” This becomes clear when thinking about U.S. companies marketing in Russia (more properly called [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7185-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7185_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:41:49">http://www.forbes.com/sites/juliewilcox/2012/07/01/health-benefits-of-broccoli/</link><title>Health Benefits Of Broccoli</title><description>Thanks to yesterday’s passage of Obamacare, broccoli is at the forefront of global consciousness as never before. Chief Justice John G. Roberts Jr. ruled that the commerce clause of the United States Constitution “doesn’t give Congress the power to make people buy health insurance— or, for that matter, healthy green Health Benefits of [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7185-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7185_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:43:12">http://www.forbes.com/sites/maryclairekendall/2012/10/11/remembering-ernest-borgnine-on-50th-anniversary-of-mchales-navy-premiere/</link><title>Remembering Ernest Borgnine On 50th Anniversary Of McHale's Navy Premiere</title><description>Consider this: If not for Mussolini, Ernest Borgnine (1917-2012) would have likely died an Italian count. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7185-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7185_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:44:24">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johntamny/2013/02/12/obamas-state-of-the-union-a-blast-to-a-slow-growth-past/</link><title>Obama's State Of the Union: A Blast To a Slow-Growth Past</title><description>Obama's policies remain the barrier to the economic recovery that Americans are clamoring for. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7185-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7185_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:45:11">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jimpowell/2012/02/22/the-economic-leadership-secrets-of-benito-mussolini/</link><title>The Economic Leadership Secrets of Benito Mussolini</title><description>Where might America go if a president embraces Mussolini’s leadership secrets? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7185-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7185_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:47:27">http://www.forbes.com/sites/billflax/2011/10/20/europes-debt-crisis-is-no-failing-of-federalism/</link><title>Europe's Debt Crisis Is No Failing Of Federalism</title><description>"The powers not delegated to the United States by the Constitution, nor prohibited by it to the States, are reserved to the States respectively, or to the people." - Tenth Amendment Assorted pundits chronicling Europe's debt crisis bemoan that insufficient federal authority undermines systemic solutions to the fiscal pressures [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7185-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7185_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:48:50">http://www.forbes.com/sites/alejandrochafuen/2014/01/30/top-free-market-think-tanks-combat-the-hegemony-of-the-bureaucrats-2/</link><title>Thinking about Think Tanks: Which ones are the best? 2013 edition</title><description>Last week, the most comprehensive rankings on think tanks was released. So, what are the top think tanks in the U.S. and around the globe? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7185-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7185_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:50:05">http://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2012/05/07/french-elections-tip-balance-of-european-power-may-stick-germany-with-bailout-tab/</link><title>French Elections Tip Balance Of European Power, May Stick Germany With Bailout Tab</title><description>Paradoxically, the election of a socialist president in France may help find a new balance between austerity and growth measures. For better or for worse, the result of the French and the Greek elections increased the likelihood that Germany will be forced to bail out its southern neighbors. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7185-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7185_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 17:52:21">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jimpowell/2012/04/29/obamas-plan-to-seize-control-of-our-economy-and-our-lives/</link><title>Obama's Plan To Seize Control Of Our Economy And Our Lives</title><description>President Obama has made clear that he’s determined to continue pushing his “progressive” agenda, regardless of constitutional limitations on his power. He aims to have his way by issuing more and more executive orders. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>