<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7189">judiciary act 1789</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:15:55" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7189-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7189_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:15:56">http://www.forbes.com/sites/daviddavenport/2013/04/25/the-supreme-court-blocks-the-politicization-of-international-law/</link><title>The Supreme Court Blocks The Politicization Of International Law</title><description>The U.S. is not the world's courtroom. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7189-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7189_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:18:08">http://www.forbes.com/sites/realspin/2013/04/21/the-supreme-court-unanimously-rejects-universal-jurisdiction/</link><title>The Supreme Court Unanimously Rejects Universal Jurisdiction</title><description>A wise example of judicial restraint. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7189-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7189_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:18:58">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jimpowell/2014/01/30/how-president-obama-could-be-swept-away-with-his-executive-orders-that-defy-congress-and-the-courts/</link><title>How President Obama Could Be Swept Away With His Executive Orders That Defy Congress And The Courts</title><description>Apparently President Obama has become convinced that he can make magic with that pen he keeps talking about, the one he plans to use for signing executive orders to revive his beleaguered presidency.  Executive orders are irresistible, because a president doesn’t have to propose anything, debate the issues, endure hearings [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7189-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7189_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:21:16">http://www.forbes.com/sites/michaelbobelian/2013/10/16/supreme-court-rebuffs-human-rights-claimants-from-abroad/</link><title>Supreme Court Rebuffs Human Rights Claimants From Abroad</title><description>American courts have long been a favored destination for plaintiffs. Compared to many other judicial systems, U.S. courts are - with rare exceptions - free of corruption and have well-established precedents and procedures that make them fair and predictable forums to bring cases. Though they are not swift, cases in [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7189-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7189_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:21:45">http://www.forbes.com/sites/peterferrara/2012/04/05/why-the-supreme-court-will-strike-down-all-of-obamacare/</link><title>Why the Supreme Court Will Strike Down All of Obamacare</title><description>The Court kept asking the government for a principle that would limit its interpretation of the Commerce Clause, and its failure to come up with one is fatal to the government’s case. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7189-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7189_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:23:57">http://www.forbes.com/sites/michaelbobelian/2012/03/23/supreme-court-eyes-scope-of-controversial-alien-tort-statute/</link><title>Supreme Court Eyes Scope Of Controversial Alien Tort Statute</title><description>Within days after hearing oral arguments on whether corporations can be sued for human rights violations under the Alien Tort Statute (ATS) last month, the Supreme Court instructed the lawyers in the case to file a new round of briefs analyzing whether federal courts could serve as a forum in [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7189-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7189_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:24:59">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jimpowell/2012/04/29/obamas-plan-to-seize-control-of-our-economy-and-our-lives/</link><title>Obama's Plan To Seize Control Of Our Economy And Our Lives</title><description>President Obama has made clear that he’s determined to continue pushing his “progressive” agenda, regardless of constitutional limitations on his power. He aims to have his way by issuing more and more executive orders. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7189-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7189_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 18:26:24">http://www.forbes.com/2007/09/11/attorney-general-doj-cx_0912oxfordanalytica.html</link><title>Effective U.S. Attorney General Defined</title><description>The chief law officer and adviser to the president must successfully balance law and politics. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>