<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7215">squamous cell carcinoma</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:19:39" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7215-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7215_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:19:39">http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidkroll/2013/08/14/possible-efficacy-of-necitumumab-imc-11f8-in-squamous-nsclc-lung-cancer-subset/</link><title>Possible Efficacy Of Lilly's Necitumumab (IMC-11F8) In Lung Cancer Subset</title><description>Epidermal growth factor receptor (EGFR) signaling pathway. (Photo credit: Wikipedia) Eli Lilly announced yesterday their very preliminary and non-quantitative conclusions on the SQUIRE study, a 1093-patient Phase III trial of their anti-epidermal growth factor receptor (EGFR) antibody, necitumumab (IMC-11F8), against Stage IV squamous, non-small [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7215-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7215_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:20:46">http://www.forbes.com/sites/larryhusten/2014/04/08/study-suggests-link-between-viagra-and-melanoma/</link><title>Study Suggests Link Between Viagra And Melanoma</title><description>In recent years researchers have uncovered a potentially important pathway whereby PDE5A inhibitors (which include sildenafil-- Viagra-- and other drugs used to treat erectile dysfunction and pulmonary hypertension) could potentially increase the risk of developing melanoma. Now a new study provides early evidence showing an association between [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7215-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7215_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:22:54">http://www.forbes.com/sites/melaniehaiken/2012/10/03/indoor-tanning-skin-cancer-new-research-suggests/</link><title>Indoor Tanning = Skin Cancer For Those Under 25, New Research Suggests</title><description>Take that, reality TV: Scientists offer definitive proof that indoor tanning causes skin cancer. And those at worst risk? People under 25. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7215-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7215_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:24:22">http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidkroll/2013/05/06/if-tanning-beds-were-a-drug-theyd-be-illegal/</link><title>If Tanning Beds Were A Drug, They'd Be Illegal</title><description>Inside a tanning bed. (Photo credit: leyla.a) There's potentially cancer-causing radiation in your neighborhood. But some of you -- and your kids -- aren't running away from it. In fact, you may be knowingly willing to pay money to be exposed to this type of radiation -- in the name of darkening your [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7215-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7215_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:24:57">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johnnosta/2013/03/14/simply-amazing-instantly-diagnosis-melanoma-with-the-flash-of-a-light/</link><title>Simply Amazing! Instantly Diagnose Melanoma with the Flash of a Light.</title><description>VideoEarly detection is your best defense. It is widely accepted that early cancer detection not only offers the best possible chances for successful treatment, but also saves health care costs and a large overburden to the health care system. Innovations in the methods for early detection and treatment have helped to decrease [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7215-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7215_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:27:06">http://www.forbes.com/sites/robertglatter/2012/07/09/can-three-cups-of-coffee-a-day-reduce-your-risk-of-skin-cancer/</link><title>Can Three Cups of Coffee a Day Reduce your Risk of Skin Cancer?</title><description>English: A photo of a cup of coffee. Esperanto: Taso de kafo. Français : Photo d'une tasse de caffé Español: Taza de café (Photo credit: Wikipedia) The answer is yes - According to data from a recent study, the caffeine contained in your coffee may have the ability to reduce your [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7215-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7215_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:28:25">http://www.forbes.com/sites/stuartanderson/2013/03/17/at-the-fred-hutchinson-cancer-research-center-immigrants-and-native-born-work-together-to-save-lives/</link><title>At the Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center Immigrants and Native-Born Work Together to Save Lives</title><description>One of the world’s leading cancer centers, the Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center in Seattle, Washington, describes its mission as focusing on “important breakthroughs in the prevention, early detection and treatment of cancer.” An analysis of staff biographies in a new study by the National Foundation for American Policy finds [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7215-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7215_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:29:40">http://www.forbes.com/sites/melaniehaiken/2012/05/30/aspirin-the-new-anti-cancer-wonder-drug/</link><title>Aspirin: The New Anti-Cancer Wonder Drug?</title><description>Could skin cancer protection be as close as your medicine cabinet? New research shows taking aspirin or ibuprofen daily can cut your risk of the two most common kinds of skin cancer. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7215-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7215_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:31:53">http://www.forbes.com/2008/02/19/onyx-nexavar-cancer-biz-healthcare-cx_mh_0219onyx.html</link><title>Questions For Onyx Pharmaceuticals</title><description>Bayer and biotech Onyx Pharmaceuticals announce a devastatingly disappointing result for their cancer pill Nexavar. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7215-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7215_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:34:31">http://www.forbes.com/2008/08/21/skin-cancer-detection-forbeslife-cx_avd_0820health.html</link><title>Six New Ways To Diagnose Skin Cancer</title><description>Invasive biopsies may soon be a thing of the past if these detection methods prove effective. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>