<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7219">honda insight</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:31:31" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7219-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7219_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:31:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/neilwinton/2014/04/17/europes-car-sales-boom-but-honda-trips-over-lame-product-lineup/</link><title>Europe's Car Sales Boom, But Honda Trips Over Lame Product Lineup</title><description>Car sales in Western Europe continued to rally from a six year slump, but Honda of Japan’s sales dived as its range of CR-V SUVs and Civic small cars proved unloved and too expensive. And don’t expect an improvement from Honda any time soon. Car sales rose 7.2 per cent in the [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7219-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7219_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:32:03">http://www.forbes.com/2005/02/02/cx_dl_0202show_ls.html</link><title>Honda Insight Vs. Toyota Prius</title><description>A showdown between two of the only "full" gas/electric-hybrid cars. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7219-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7219_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:35:13">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kitconews/2012/09/12/hondas-reduced-use-of-rhodium-part-of-effort-to-shift-away-from-more-expensive-metals/</link><title>Honda's Reduced Use Of Rhodium Part Of Effort To Shift Away From More-Expensive Metals</title><description>A move by Honda Motor Co. to reduce the amount of rhodium used in auto catalysts is part of an ongoing effort to curtail the consumption of this or any other higher-cost metal that worries manufacturers, analysts said. A loss of demand has negative price implications for any commodity. Still, while one [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7219-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7219_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:35:48">http://www.forbes.com/2009/10/20/japan-manufacturing-fit-yen-dollar-business-autos-honda.html</link><title>Honda Mulls Factory Move</title><description>A stronger yen makes it more profitable to make cars in the U.S. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7219-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7219_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:37:37">http://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2011/04/08/buy-honda-now-for-a-45-stock-later/</link><title>Buy Honda Now For A $45 Stock Later</title><description>We envision a scenario where Japan vehicle sales could drop by as much as 10% this year before starting to recover next year. Given the size of the auto market in Japan, the government may look to offer incentives as consumers look to replace lost cars, which could help limit these losses in the near term. We have a price estimate of $45.04, which [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7219-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7219_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:38:56">http://www.forbes.com/sites/forbespr/2012/03/01/press-release-forbes-insights-study-predicts-strong-luxury-auto-sales-will-continue-through-first-half-of-2012/</link><title>Forbes Insights Study Predicts Strong Luxury Auto Sales Will Continue Through First Half of 2012</title><description>Luxury Car Buzz Index ranks performance of 10 leading luxury car brands in U.S. NEW YORK (March 1, 2012)—Good times should continue to roll for the U.S. auto market, especially in the luxury segment, into the foreseeable future, according to "2012 Special Report: Luxury Automotive Outlook," a new study released by [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7219-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7219_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:40:23">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johnellett/2014/02/28/highlights-from-ana-brand-masters-conference/</link><title>Highlights From ANA Brand Masters Conference</title><description>VideoMarketing leaders from several brands presented case studies of successful programs at this year’s ANA Brand Masters Conference in Hollywood, Florida. There were a few recurring themes among the presenters: Customers have changed so it is important to engage them with 360 degree experiences across paid, owned and earned media. The [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7219-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7219_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:40:52">http://www.forbes.com/sites/danschawbel/2014/03/05/douglas-stone-the-importance-of-feedback-in-business-communications/</link><title>Douglas Stone: The Importance Of Feedback In Business Communications</title><description>I recently sat down with Douglas Stone, who is a Managing Partner at Triad Consulting Group and a Lecturer on Law at Harvard Law School, where he teaches negotiation. Through Triad, he consults to a wide range of organizations, including Fidelity, Honda and Shell. Aside from his time spent at Harvard and [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7219-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7219_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:43:06">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jimgorzelany/2014/01/28/the-eco-meanest-cars-for-2014/</link><title>The Environmentally 'Meanest' Cars For 2014</title><description>Full size trucks and exotic luxury/sports cars dominate the list of the 2014 cars that were determined to be most harmful to the environment.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7219-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7219_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 01:44:54">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jimgorzelany/2014/01/28/the-greenest-and-eco-meanest-cars-for-2014/</link><title>The 'Greenest' Cars For 2014</title><description>Hybrids and electrics top the list again this year, but shoppers can find cleaner choices among all model classes thanks to the latest “Green Scores.”</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>