<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7241">flight simulators</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:24:18" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7241-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7241_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:24:19">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jjcolao/2013/04/22/a-hand-controlled-flight-simulator-brought-to-you-by-leap-motion-and-google-earth/</link><title>A Hand-Controlled Flight Simulator, Brought To You By Leap Motion And Google Earth</title><description>Video Leap Motion—makers of futuristic, motion-controlled computer interface technology—is moving quickly. Just last week the company announced a partnership with HP, the world’s largest PC maker, to bundle the Leap Motion Controller with HP desktops and laptops. According to FORBES contributor Anthony Wing Kosner, HP plans to embed Leap Motion [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7241-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7241_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:27:06">http://www.forbes.com/sites/tjmccue/2013/10/14/billion-dollar-view-castar-plans-to-assist-you-with-reality/</link><title>Billion Dollar View: castAR Plans To Assist You With Reality</title><description>Name your reality view and castAR can probably help you with it. From gaming to flight simulator training, this new pair of glasses from startup Technical Illusions will help you see and interact in three dimensions. According to a recent market research report of "Augmented Reality &amp; Virtual Reality Market” (title [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7241-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7241_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:27:46">http://www.forbes.com/2005/04/28/cx_de_0428toyboxmarcella.html</link><title>Las Vegas CIO's Flight Simulator</title><description>Fly radio-controlled aircraft from the comfort of your living room. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7241-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7241_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:28:19">http://www.forbes.com/sites/matthewstibbe/2011/07/26/flying-nasas-space-shuttle-simulator/</link><title>Flying NASA's Space Shuttle Simulator</title><description>What happens when you put a private pilot into the ultimate simulator? Find out how I got on flying NASA's Space Shuttle simulator. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7241-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7241_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:29:53">http://www.forbes.com/sites/tomtaulli/2012/01/06/should-you-give-away-your-product/</link><title>Should You Give Away Your Product?</title><description>This week, Microsoft (Nasdaq:MSFT) said it would give away its Flight Simulator product. To make money on it, the company plans to sell premium items like different planes or locales. This approach is known as the "freemium" model -- and it is gaining traction in the tech world. In fact, one [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7241-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7241_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:31:50">http://www.forbes.com/sites/alexknapp/2011/12/21/santa-does-his-pre-christmas-flight-training-with-a-giant-robot-arm/</link><title>Santa Does His Pre-Christmas Flight Training With A Giant Robot Arm</title><description>This year, Santa's doing his flight training on the University of Deakin's Universal Motion Simulator. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7241-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7241_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:32:18">http://www.forbes.com/forbes-life-magazine/1998/1116/055.html</link><title>Pull Up, You Fool! Pull Up!</title><description>Greasing bogeys in the new computer flight simulators. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7241-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7241_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:32:52">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jordanshapiro/2014/03/13/yoshis-new-island-nurtures-kids-problem-solving-skills/</link><title>Yoshi's New Island Nurtures Kids' Problem Solving Skills</title><description>I was really excited when Nintendo told me Yoshi’s New Island was ready for review. I immediately downloaded it to the 2DS. My kids (boy six and eight) each started personal files. And I started one for myself. I’ve always loved Yoshi. He’s one of my favorite Nintendo characters. I also [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7241-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7241_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:34:34">http://www.forbes.com/sites/businessaviation/2013/11/19/facebooks-gulfstream-girl-takes-off-with-an-uplifting-message/</link><title>BusinessAviation​Voice: Facebook's Gulfstream Girl Takes Off With An Uplifting Message</title><description>While an attractive woman in the left seat of a business jet cockpit is likely to draw attention, Nadia Marcinko is attracting followers for far more important reasons. Her message to young people about the joy of flight and career opportunities in aviation is inspiring. Jeff Miller interviewed Nadia recently. by [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7241-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7241_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 05:37:22">http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikaandersen/2014/03/24/looking-to-find-your-passion-heres-how-to-recognize-the-real-thing/</link><title>Looking To Find Your Passion? Here's How To Recognize The Real Thing</title><description>It's worthwhile to discover your passion. Jus don't get faked out along the way - read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>