<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7261">elvish language</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:16:34" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7261-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7261_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:16:35">http://www.forbes.com/sites/parmyolson/2013/09/25/duolingo-takes-online-teaching-to-next-level-by-crowd-sourcing-new-languages/</link><title>Duolingo Takes Online Teaching To The Next Level, By Crowd Sourcing New Languages</title><description>After providing the first six languages it expects to get dozens more from volunteers in the coming months, including Chinese, Russian, even Klingon. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7261-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7261_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:18:37">http://www.forbes.com/sites/maurapennington/2012/02/28/american-political-economy-is-no-different-from-english-language/</link><title>American Political Economy Is No Different From English Language</title><description>Language is purely a means of exchange. The market is no different. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7261-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7261_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:20:39">http://www.forbes.com/sites/reuvencohen/2012/11/01/germanys-pirate-party-technocrats-with-a-new-purpose-refugeecamp/</link><title>Germany's Pirate Party: Technocrats With A New Purpose #refugeecamp</title><description>Frankfurt Skyline - Image By @rUv For those who know me, know I travel a lot. According to the Star Alliance something in the order of 50,000 miles in October alone. As I travel, I enjoy meeting with people involved in various local technology scenes. Earlier today I had the chance [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7261-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7261_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:21:09">http://www.forbes.com/sites/danielnyegriffiths/2012/06/12/the-new-lara-croft/</link><title>Gender, Sex and Games: A New Lara Croft Hits An Old, Old Problem</title><description>A 'preboot' of the iconic Tomb Raider franchise features a younger, more vulnerable Lara Croft - but the way that vulnerability is expressed raises thorny issues around sex and the creative process. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7261-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7261_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 09:21:48">http://www.forbes.com/sites/danielnyegriffiths/2012/02/21/bioware-hepler-harassment/</link><title>The Changing Face of Games: Feeling Angry and Ignored, Fans Look for Someone to Blame</title><description>Video Mass of angry gamers, more like Until recently Jennifer Brandes Hepler, a writer at BioWare, Electronic Arts' role-playing game subsidiary, was little-known outside the inner circle of BioWare fandom. Within those small circles, Hepler had for some time been a polarising figure. Or, more precisely, a kind of hypothetical Jennifer Hepler [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>