<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7274">detroit riot</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:49:13" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7274-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7274_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:49:14">http://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2013/11/29/lessons-from-detroit-and-france-if-you-overtax-them-they-will-go/</link><title>Lessons From Detroit And France: If You Overtax Them, They Will Go</title><description>Throughout history, humanity has engaged in countless experiments. Some have proven more useful than others. But all have taught us something. The financial plights of both Detroit and France are no exception. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7274-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7274_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:50:57">http://www.forbes.com/sites/tonybradley/2013/08/07/detroit-youth-are-powered-to-dream/</link><title>Detroit Youth Are 'Powered To Dream'</title><description>Detroit has lived with a negative reputation it just can't seem to shake for decades, but in recent years it seems to have been branded as the 'poster child' for the economic woes of the nation. With an economy driven almost completely by automobile manufacturing, Detroit has been hard hit [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7274-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7274_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:51:31">http://www.forbes.com/sites/michelinemaynard/2013/08/03/the-comments-detroits-emergency-manager-will-wish-he-can-take-back/</link><title>The Comments Detroit's Emergency Manager Will Wish To Take Back</title><description>Detroit Emergency Manager Kevyn Orr (Image credit: Getty Images via @daylife) Kevyn Orr has been loquacious since he was appointed Detroit's emergency manager last spring by Gov. Rick Snyder. His descriptions of the city's dismal state and reams of eye-opening data have been his ammunition in the decision to seek Chapter [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7274-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7274_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:53:34">http://www.forbes.com/sites/theapothecary/2013/07/22/as-detroit-goes-bankrupt-michigans-senate-considers-adding-billions-of-unfunded-liabilities-to-its-medicaid-program/</link><title>As Detroit Goes Bankrupt, Michigan's Senate Considers Adding Billions Of Unfunded Liabilities To Its Medicaid Program</title><description>Last week, the City of Detroit filed for bankruptcy, making it the largest municipal bankruptcy in American history. It’s a remarkable story, especially for natives of the state, like me, who have watched Detroit slowly decline for decades. But it’s even more remarkable when you consider the fact that the Michigan state legislature is on the verge [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7274-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7274_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:56:40">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markbergen/2012/04/30/city-ledes-from-riots-to-rut/</link><title>City Ledes: From Riots to Rut</title><description>A shameless pitch for a one-of-a-kind city newsletter. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7274-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7274_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:57:51">http://www.forbes.com/sites/realspin/2013/01/13/detroit-betrayed-the-radical-wrecking-of-an-iconic-city/</link><title>Detroit Betrayed: The Radical Wrecking Of An Iconic City</title><description>The greatness of Detroit can forever be a fading memory, or there can be a new beginning. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7274-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7274_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 11:58:44">http://www.forbes.com/sites/richardhyfler/2011/08/15/just-another-urban-riot-what-happened-in-the-u-k/</link><title>Just Another Urban Riot? What Happened in the U.K.?</title><description>It would appear that, even with the introduction of new social media, riots haven't changed that much in the last 50 years. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7274-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7274_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:00:11">http://www.forbes.com/sites/joannmuller/2011/08/09/detroit-loses-a-treasure-in-focushope-founder/</link><title>Detroit Loses A Treasure In Focus:HOPE Founder</title><description>Eleanor Josaitis was a pioneer in rebuilding a city ravaged by racial tension and poverty. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7274-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7274_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:01:29">http://www.forbes.com/sites/annedoyle/2011/08/14/eleantor-josaitis-detroits-mother-teresa-refused-to-be-a-spectator/</link><title>Eleanor Josaitis, Detroit's Mother Teresa, Refused To Be A Spectator</title><description>Detroit just buried a great leader, Eleanor Josaitis, who inspired presidents, members of Congress and global business executives from Ford, GM, Chrysler and others to CARE MORE, to GIVE MORE and to DO MORE to overcome racism, poverty and injustice. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7274-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7274_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 12:02:16">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markhendrickson/2014/02/07/the-beatles-on-ed-sullivan-yeah-yeah-yeah/</link><title>The Beatles On Ed Sullivan: Yeah, Yeah, Yeah!</title><description>There was electric excitement in the air that night of February 9, 1964. The night that changed the baby boomers forever. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>