<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7293">basil recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:36:08" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7293-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7293_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:36:10">http://www.forbes.com/sites/juliewilcox/2012/08/22/healthy-pizza-recipes-for-your-fall-celebrations/</link><title>Healthy Pizza Recipes For Your Fall Celebrations</title><description>Labor Day will soon be behind us and we will be back in the swing of fall entertaining. Healthy pizza recipes provide the basis for one of my go-to meals for celebrations. While the usual burgers, fries, guacamole, chips, and wings can be tempting to adhere to, remember that there are other better and delicious options you can eat and serve. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7293-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7293_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:37:31">http://www.forbes.com/sites/carolpinchefsky/2012/09/13/four-guild-wars-2-recipes-you-can-craft-in-your-kitchen/</link><title>Four 'Guild Wars 2' Recipes You Can Craft in Your Kitchen</title><description>I'm enjoying Guild Wars 2 (GW2) for its gorgeous graphics and its non-stop adventure. But playing GW2 has resulted in a strange side effect: It's making me hungry. That's because whenever I use the discovery tab to find new recipes, I think, "Mmm...tasty." read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7293-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7293_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:38:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/larryolmsted/2013/02/17/breaking-bourbon-news-the-public-spoke-makers-mark-listened-returning-to-original-formula/</link><title>Breaking Bourbon News: The Public Spoke, Maker's Mark Listened - Returning To Original Formula</title><description>After a controversial formula change, Maker's Mark bourbon is going back to its original recipe - immediately! read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7293-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7293_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:40:39">http://www.forbes.com/sites/lisamogensen/2013/04/17/food-and-finance-live-in-harmony-at-empire-a-new-napa-valley-dining-experience-opening-in-may/</link><title>Food and Finance Live In Harmony At Empire, A New Napa Valley Dining Experience Opening In May</title><description>Mid-May marks the opening of Empire, an exciting new contemporary small plates restaurant and lounge located in downtown Napa.  Arthur Prieston, chairman of The Prieston Group, a group of companies specializing in financial services, insurance and data analytics is owner along with Nick Rimedio former general manager of restaurant Charlie [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7293-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7293_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:41:22">http://www.forbes.com/sites/katiebell/2013/06/04/special-bourbons-for-celebrating-fathers-day/</link><title>Best Bourbons For Celebrating Father's Day</title><description>Buffalo Trace Distilled Bourbons If your father is a bourbon fan, this is the year to give him something special. To say bourbon is hot is a gross understatement; this brown spirit is enjoying a welcome and powerful renaissance among consumers of all stripes, but most especially among men. The market, once [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7293-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7293_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:41:56">http://www.forbes.com/2010/12/03/giada-de-laurentiis-food-recipe-forbes-woman-well-being-holiday-hors-doeurves_slide.html</link><title>The Perfect Holiday Party Menu By Giada De Laurentiis</title><description>Emmy-winning chef suggests 10 hors d'oeuvres that will be perfect for your holiday party.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7293-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7293_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:43:30">http://www.forbes.com/sites/juliewilcox/2012/06/19/cooling-healthy-salads-for-hot-days-at-work-or-home/</link><title>Cooling Healthy Salads For Hot Days At Work Or Home</title><description>Try these fabulous healthy salads for lunch on a sweaty summer day. They are cool and delicious! The recipes are also very easy to make and travel well in Tupperware to work! read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7293-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7293_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:44:35">http://www.forbes.com/sites/booked/2011/03/23/forgotten-bookmarks-he-who-controls-the-spice/</link><title>Forgotten Bookmarks: He Who Controls The Spice</title><description>Recipe for artichokes and pasta found in Frank Herbert's "Dune: Messiah" read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7293-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7293_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:46:12">http://www.forbes.com/sites/nadiaarumugam/2013/04/30/cocktails-and-canapes-for-your-kentucky-derby-party/</link><title>Cocktails And Canapés For Your Kentucky Derby Party</title><description>Throwing a party to celebrate the 139th Kentucky Derby, but don't want to trot out the same old bourbon-flavored  bites and tipples? Here are some fresh ideas that will keep your guests sated all the way to the finish line. If you don't want to do away with tradition altogether, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7293-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7293_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 15:48:02">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jennagoudreau/2010/12/03/giada-de-laurentiis-favorite-holiday-hors-doeuvres-food-network-party-christmas-target-john-mayer/</link><title>Giada De Laurentiis' Favorite Holiday Hors D'oeuvres</title><description>The Food Network's Giada De Laurentiis offers tips for party hosts and recipes for her favorite holiday hors d'oeuvres. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>