<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7307">causes of the cold war</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:13:23" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7307-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7307_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:13:24">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kenrapoza/2014/04/14/for-many-war-already-happening-in-ukraine/</link><title>For Many, 'War' Already Happening In Ukraine</title><description>Markets will react to Russia-Ukraine fist fight for weeks to come as tensions heat up between former Soviet partners.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7307-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7307_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:15:07">http://www.forbes.com/sites/stratfor/2014/04/10/u-s-defense-policy-in-the-wake-of-the-ukrainian-affair/</link><title>U.S. Defense Policy In The Wake Of The Ukrainian Affair</title><description>By George Friedman Ever since the end of the Cold War, there has been an assumption that conventional warfare between reasonably developed nation-states had been abolished. During the 1990s, it was expected that the primary purpose of the military would be operations other than war, such as peacekeeping, disaster relief and the [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7307-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7307_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:16:34">http://www.forbes.com/sites/dougbandow/2014/03/03/avoid-war-cold-or-hot-with-russia-over-ukraine-finding-a-way-back-from-the-catastrophic-brink/</link><title>Avoid War, Cold Or Hot, With Russia Over Ukraine: Finding A Way Back From The Catastrophic Brink</title><description>The West must try to draw Russia back from the brink in Ukraine. The world cannot a new cold war, let alone a hot conflict involving nuclear powers. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7307-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7307_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:18:10">http://www.forbes.com/sites/susanadams/2014/04/15/the-worst-jobs-for-2014/</link><title>The Worst Jobs For 2014</title><description>see photosClick for full photo gallery: The Worst Jobs For 2014 Lumberjacks work outside in bitter cold and blazing heat, running heavy, dangerous machinery. They deal with massive trees and logs that can slip and cause serious injury. According to the Occupational Safety and Health Administration, logging is the most dangerous [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7307-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7307_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:19:39">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markadomanis/2014/04/20/obamas-new-russia-strategy-is-the-right-one-the-question-is-whether-it-will-work/</link><title>Obama's New Russia Strategy Is The Right One, The Question Is Whether It Will Work</title><description>In today's New York Times Peter Baker has an excellent overview of the changes in Obama's Russia policy that have been brought about by the annexation of Crimea and the ongoing crisis in Ukraine. Without simplifying too greatly, the new strategy can fairly be called "containment 2.0" - it bears [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7307-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7307_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:21:08">http://www.forbes.com/sites/brucedorminey/2014/03/08/regional-nuclear-war-would-still-wreak-global-climate-havoc-says-study/</link><title>Regional Nuclear War Would Still Wreak Global Climate Havoc, Says Study</title><description>With Ukrainian tensions mounting, the notion that such regional conflicts could morph into something nuclear is now dogging Western leaders in a way not seen in a generation. Cold War policy was long built on Mutually Assured Destruction (MAD), the idea that a global thermonuclear war would be so horrific that [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7307-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7307_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:21:42">http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidblackmon/2014/04/13/the-weekly-oil-gas-follies-30/</link><title>The Weekly Oil &amp;amp; Gas Follies</title><description>The Weekly Oil and Gas Follies – Volume 41, April 14, 2014 In which we drill down into the @GDBlackmon Twitter feed to briefly chronicle the week’s silliness, shenanigans, fake news and real news related to the oil and natural gas industry.   This guy writing for The Atlantic wants the United States [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7307-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7307_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:23:18">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johngreathouse/2014/03/03/a-dozen-team-building-tips-inspired-by-a-great-war-film/</link><title>A Dozen Team-Building Tips Inspired By A Great War Film</title><description>Stop complaining about how difficult it is to encourage well-mannered, highly educated, civilized professionals to work together. Instead, consider how difficult it would be to transform twelve convicted felons, with an affinity for violence and no desire to work together, into a cohesive, effective team. That is exactly what Major Reisman [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7307-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7307_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:24:38">http://www.forbes.com/sites/stephenharner/2014/03/03/eminent-japan-scholar-john-w-dower-on-eight-problematic-legacies-of-the-san-francisco-system/</link><title>Eminent Japan Scholar John W. Dower On Eight Problematic Legacies Of 'The San Francisco System'</title><description>Dower underscores two fateful and problematic realities surrounding and informing the San Francisco peace conference. The first, that “Japan was still occupied and under U.S. control when the treaties were signed, and the Cold War was at fever pitch." Second, “equally significant....Neither Communist China nor the Chinese Nationalist regime that [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7307-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7307_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 17:25:45">http://www.forbes.com/sites/gregsatell/2014/03/08/who-needs-ukraine/</link><title>Why The World Has A Stake In Ukraine</title><description>We have crucial interests at stake in Ukraine. If Vladimir Putin goes unopposed, he will continue to destabilize Europe. Failure to act now will only cause us bigger problems later. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>