<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7348">map of the united states</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:05:02" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7348-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7348_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:05:03">http://www.forbes.com/sites/robertlenzner/2013/11/02/obamacare-will-raise-average-health-insurance-premiums-by-32-for-21-million-people/</link><title>ObamaCare Will Raise Average Insurance Claims By 32% For Individual Coverage The Next Four Years</title><description>In my search for the truth about how much ObamaCare will increase the cost of health care insurance, I came upon a frightening map of the United States that projected what the percentage hikes would be state by state for people with individual coverage. The projections, prepared by the Society of Actuaries [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7348-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7348_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:07:20">http://www.forbes.com/sites/stratfor/2014/04/04/the-geopolitics-of-energy/</link><title>The Geopolitics Of Energy</title><description>By Robert D. Kaplan Geopolitics is the battle for space and power played out in a geographical setting. Just as there are military geopolitics, diplomatic geopolitics and economic geopolitics, there is also energy geopolitics. For natural resources and the trade routes that bring those resources to consumers is central to the study [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7348-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7348_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:08:29">http://www.forbes.com/sites/georgeleef/2014/04/21/college-degrees-arent-becoming-more-valuable-their-glut-confines-people-without-them-to-a-shrinking-low-pay-sector-of-the-market/</link><title>College Degrees Aren't Becoming More Valuable -- Their Glut Confines People Without Them To A Shrinking, Low-Pay Sector Of The Market</title><description>How can it be that college education is getting more and more valuable in financial rewards when there is abundant evidence that many students learn little while in college? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7348-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7348_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:10:15">http://www.forbes.com/sites/williampentland/2014/01/26/patent-map-reveals-rise-of-thin-film-solar-technology/</link><title>Patent Map Reveals Rise Of Thin-Film Solar Technology</title><description>I am a sucker for data visualization graphics, especially if the data being visualized is related to energy innovation. Needless to say, I was thrilled to discover a dynamic mapping of the geographic history of thin-film solar cell innovation developed by researchers at the University of Amsterdam. A photovoltaic cell consists of two [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7348-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7348_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:12:09">http://www.forbes.com/sites/united/2014/01/08/app-entrepreneurs-corner-the-niche-travel-market/</link><title>United​Voice: App Entrepreneurs Corner The Niche Travel Market</title><description>In the past, a savvy travel agent or a local connection were the only ways to assemble a travel experience that satisfied niche interests. But the recent proliferation of location-specific mobile apps means the power is in your pocket. Now, anyone with specific local interests has a personal tour guide only a few clicks away. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7348-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7348_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:13:48">http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidparnell/2014/04/21/paul-lippe-of-legal-onramp-on-the-legal-market-david-parnell/</link><title>Paul Lippe Of Legal OnRamp: Every Legal Department Will Seek To "Cisco-ify" Themselves</title><description>Legal OnRamp CEO Paul Lippe discusses the legal market, law schools, and what to expect in the years to come. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7348-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7348_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:15:12">http://www.forbes.com/sites/csylt/2014/04/04/why-formula-one-has-races-in-eight-of-the-ten-countries-with-the-highest-gdp/</link><title>Why Formula One Has Races In Eight Of The Ten Countries With The Highest GDP</title><description>Formula One moves to the Middle East this weekend for the Bahrain Grand Prix and as it does so it races into controversy. The tiny Gulf state has been in the news for the past few years due to clashes between the Shia majority and the ruling Sunnis. However that isn’t [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7348-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7348_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:16:03">http://www.forbes.com/sites/stratfor/2014/03/14/crimea-the-revenge-of-geography/</link><title>Crimea: The Revenge Of Geography?</title><description>By Robert D. Kaplan The Obama administration claims it is motivated by the G-8, interdependence, human rights and international law. Russian President Vladimir Putin is a more traditional historical actor. He is motivated by geopolitics. That is why he temporarily has the upper hand in the crisis over Ukraine and Crimea. Geopolitics, according [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7348-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7348_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:17:39">http://www.forbes.com/sites/claudiarosett/2014/01/20/peace-and-prejudice-at-the-united-nations/</link><title>"Peace" and Prejudice at the United Nations</title><description>Claiming concerns about harming the Middle East “peace process,” the United Nations cultural agency has abruptly postponed an exhibition on Jewish ties to the Holy Land. This display was scheduled to open Jan. 20 at the Paris headquarters of the U.N. Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO). But after 22 Arab [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7348-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7348_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 00:18:10">http://www.forbes.com/sites/stratfor/2014/03/05/the-lure-of-nationalism/</link><title>The Lure Of Nationalism</title><description>By Robert D. Kaplan Nationalism is in the air. The scholars may talk about universal values and the need to combat all forms of determinism and essentialism. The media may see the world through the prism of universal human rights. The global elite may meet at Davos and proclaim the ability to [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>