<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7402">little johnny</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:31:50" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7402-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7402_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:31:51">http://www.forbes.com/sites/scottmendelson/2014/04/21/johnny-depps-transcendence-is-a-no-fault-box-office-bomb/</link><title>Johnny Depp's 'Transcendence' Is A No-Fault Box Office Bomb</title><description>Transcendence opened last weekend and is pretty much the very definition of a bomb. The $100 million production opened with just $11 million. With poor reviews, no buzz, and the summer season just around the corner, it's sure to sink fast and needs an overseas miracle to have any hope of [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7402-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7402_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:33:13">http://www.forbes.com/sites/briangoff/2013/08/13/punishing-johnny-manziel/</link><title>Punishing Johnny (Manziel)</title><description>The accusations against Johnny Manziel may cost him several games or an entire season of suspension. In a bigger view, however, the episode shines more light on the professional world of college sports that masquerades as amateurism. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7402-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7402_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:34:23">http://www.forbes.com/sites/tomvanriper/2013/09/19/browns-deal-aimed-at-bringing-johnny-football-to-cleveland/</link><title>Browns Deal Aimed At Bringing Johnny Football To Cleveland?</title><description>The Browns deal promising running back Trent Richardson to the Colts for a first round pick. And they sure need a quarterback. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7402-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7402_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:34:58">http://www.forbes.com/sites/robertlaura/2013/08/06/rich-little-impersonating-retirement/</link><title>Rich Little: Impersonating Retirement</title><description>Have you ever wondered what advice John Wayne would give you about retirement? Or how Jimmy Stewart would describe his golden years? I asked impressionist extraordinaire Rich Little what he thought, as well as how, when, and if he, himself, is planning to retire. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7402-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7402_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:35:45">http://www.forbes.com/sites/dinagachman/2013/08/13/lady-gaga-and-johnny-depp-when-celebs-slam-critics/</link><title>Lady Gaga And Johnny Depp: When Celebs Slam Critics</title><description>Lady Gaga’s message has always been to be yourself and stop caring what anyone thinks of you, so why does she suddenly care about a few critics? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7402-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7402_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:36:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/prishe/2013/08/05/johnny-be-dumb-as-manziels-mayhem-outpaces-ncaas-hypocrisy/</link><title>Johnny Be Dumb As Manziel's Mayhem Outpaces NCAA's Hypocrisy</title><description>On Sunday, numerous stories (here, here, and here) reported that The NCAA is investigating whether Heisman Trophy winner Johnny Manziel was paid for signing hundreds of autographs on photos and sports memorabilia in January.  The report is that he received something in the 5-figure range for signing various pieces of [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7402-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7402_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:37:35">http://www.forbes.com/sites/rogergroves/2013/07/31/how-much-johnny-manziel-loses-per-frat-party-ouster/</link><title>How Much Johnny Manziel Loses Per Frat Party Ouster</title><description>Johnny Manziel may be the only quartberback looking to enter next year's NFL draft to already lose $5 million a year for frat party mishaps. Very expensive parties. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7402-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7402_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:38:52">http://www.forbes.com/sites/prishe/2013/09/16/johnny-manziel-won-more-than-he-lost-in-defeat-to-top-ranked-alabama/</link><title>Johnny Manziel Won More Than He Lost In Defeat To Top-Ranked Alabama</title><description>Johnny Manziel celebrates after throwing a first quarter touchdown against Alabama on Saturday at Kyle Field in College Station, TX. Sometimes in life, we lose the battle but win the war. The battle Johnny Manziel lost was his much-hyped and thoroughly entertaining rematch with Alabama that ended in a ho-hum 49-42 defeat, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7402-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7402_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:39:21">http://www.forbes.com/sites/prishe/2013/10/19/the-st-louis-cardinals-baseballs-little-engine-that-could-just-did-against-baseballs-highest-payroll/</link><title>The St Louis Cardinals: Baseball's "Little Engine That Could" Just Did Against Baseball's Highest Payroll</title><description>Michael Wacha of the St. Louis Cardinals pitches in the first inning against the Los Angeles Dodgers in Game Six of the National League Championship Series at Busch Stadium on October 18, 2013 in St Louis, Missouri. Wacha beautiful morning in St Louis today. As St Louisans and members of Cardinal Nation [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7402-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7402_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:39:54">http://www.forbes.com/sites/larissafaw/2013/07/12/why-have-thousands-of-customers-chosen-to-get-the-johnny-cupcakes-brand-logo-tattooed-on-themselves/</link><title>Why Have Thousands Of Customers Chosen To Get The Johnny Cupcakes Brand Logo Tattooed On Themselves?</title><description>Johnny Cupcakes founder Johnny Earle points out shoppers waiting to enter his store. Photo by Dave Green. Eager fans pitched their tents, powered up their laptops, and tried to get comfortable for their two-week long wait. But these campers weren’t waiting for the release of the latest Air Jordan, smartphone, or [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>