<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7403">usc trojans</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:40:20" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7403-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7403_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:40:21">http://www.forbes.com/sites/trulia/2014/03/21/vince-vaughn-buys-former-usc-football-coach-lane-kiffins-6-5-million-beach-house/</link><title>Vince Vaughn Buys Former USC Football Coach Lane Kiffin's $6.5 Million Beach House</title><description>‘Guy’s guy’ actor Vince Vaughn just helped out former USC football coach Lane Kiffin by taking his high-priced Manhattan Beach mansion off his hands, paying $6,447,000 for the place. First reported by the Los Angeles Times, the ‘Wedding Crashers’ and ‘Old School’ actor was identified as the buyer for Kiffin’s 7,308 square foot Craftman-style home, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7403-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7403_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:41:50">http://www.forbes.com/sites/chrissmith/2014/02/05/national-signing-day-adoree-jackson-to-usc/</link><title>National Signing Day: Adoree' Jackson To USC, Alabama Gets Top Class</title><description>College football's National Signing Day is one of the sport's biggest events of the year, and the day's many announcements send college football fans across the country into frenzies of joy and disappointment. The biggest names left on the docket have finally announced their destinations. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7403-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7403_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:42:40">http://www.forbes.com/sites/leighsteinberg/2013/09/30/kiffen-self-destructed-at-usc/</link><title>Kiffin Self-Destructed At USC</title><description>Old Trojans don't die, they just move to Newport Beach. Wealthy alums here venerate a winning USC football tradition. Houses hang USC banners and flags, Cardinal and gold colors are everywhere. I am grudgingly tolerated as a Cal-Berkeley alum. A whole lifestyle revolves around SC football in Southern California. The alums [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7403-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7403_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:43:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/prishe/2013/12/22/fresno-state-usc-both-hurt-their-image-during-2013-royal-purple-las-vegas-bowl/</link><title>Fresno State, USC Both Hurt Their Image During 2013 Royal Purple Las Vegas Bowl</title><description>Some football games are just hard to watch, and as I left USC's 45-20 victory over Fresno State in the 2013 Royal Purple Las Vegas Bowl before the fourth quarter began, I drove away wondering if both programs had actually just really hurt themselves. Normally during bowl season, despite the fact [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7403-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7403_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:44:44">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonbelzer/2013/01/15/uscs-fall-from-college-sports-elite-a-cautionary-tale/</link><title>USC's Fall From College Sports Elite A Cautionary Tale</title><description>Déjà vu - a fleeting sensation that one has experienced a unique event in the past. Although the majority of people experience this unpleasant feeling at random, fans of the University of Southern California(USC) Trojans are becoming accustomed to seemingly never ending bouts of Déjà vu. A once mighty beacon of college athletics [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7403-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7403_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:45:10">http://www.forbes.com/sites/prishe/2013/09/29/lane-kiffins-ousting-at-usc-about-economics-branding-and-survival/</link><title>Lane Kiffin's Ousting At USC About Economics, Branding, And Survival</title><description>No 'Sweet Memory Lane' for Coach Kiffin, now the ex-USC head football coach after being ousted by AD and former Trojan quarterback Pat Haden hours after the team's blowout loss at Arizona State. The folks in Knoxville TN and Westwood Village are hootin' and hollerin' this morn over the demise of [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7403-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7403_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:46:07">http://www.forbes.com/sites/rogergroves/2013/09/29/kiffin-fired-at-usc-for-good-reason/</link><title>Kiffin Fired At USC For At Least 10 Good Reasons</title><description>10 reasons why Lane Kiffin firing this early in the season was mandatory for a program that expects excellence. Is Chip Kelly alergic to Eagles in Philly? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7403-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7403_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:47:22">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johntamny/2013/10/22/will-muschamps-poor-2nd-season-is-a-fair-warning-to-texas-and-usc-fans/</link><title>Will Muschamp's Poor 3rd Season Is Fair Warning To Texas And USC Fans</title><description>If great coaches were easy to find, Alabama, Texas and USC would rarely lose. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7403-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7403_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:48:56">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johntamny/2013/09/19/usc-football-has-big-problems-well-beyond-lane-kiffin/</link><title>USC Football Has Big Problems That Go Well Beyond Lane Kiffin</title><description>Weak scheduling is the path to mediocrity. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7403-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7403_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:50:36">http://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2013/01/01/quarterback-matt-barkley-selects-caa-sports-for-representation/</link><title>Quarterback Matt Barkley Selects CAA Sports For Representation</title><description>Quarterback Matt Barkley #7 of the USC Trojans has signed a Standard Representation Agreement with agents at Creative Artists Agency. (Image credit: Getty Images via @daylife) University of Southern California quarterback, Matt Barkley has chosen Creative Artists Agency (CAA) as his sports agency of record.  Gary Klein of the Los Angeles [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>