<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7404">kobe bryant</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:51:45" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7404-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7404_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:51:46">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markheisler/2014/04/21/weather-forecast-for-lakers-kobe-bryant-is-upset/</link><title>Weather Forecast for Lakers: Kobe Bryant Is Upset</title><description>Ain't no sunshine any more in Lakerdom, as rebuilding drags into its second season. Kobe Bryant was in Paris (the one in France) when his teammates were in El Segundo (the one next to Los Angeles) for exit interviews. He had a migraine headache six days before when he was supposed to [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7404-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7404_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:52:24">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kurtbadenhausen/2014/03/24/kobe-bryant-invests-millions-in-sports-drink-bodyarmor/</link><title>Kobe Bryant Invests Millions In Sports Drink BodyArmor</title><description>The Lakers superstar nabs more than 10% of BodyArmor in the first investment for Kobe Inc. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7404-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7404_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:53:34">http://www.forbes.com/sites/emilycanal/2014/03/24/best-of-forbes-kobe-bryant-invests-millions-in-sports-drink-disney-announces-new-president/</link><title>Best Of FORBES: Kobe Bryant Invests Millions In Sports Drink, Disney Announces New President</title><description>Forbes Is Now Updating Net Worths And Rankings Of More Than 1,600 Billionaires Every Trading Day "For more than a quarter of a century, Forbes has been tracking the fortunes of the richest people on the planet, annually publishing the rankings of the 400 Richest Americans and the World’s Billionaires. In [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7404-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7404_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:54:11">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markheisler/2014/03/04/kobe-bryants-mission-impossible-this-season-now-looks-like-next-season/</link><title>Kobe Bryant's 'Mission Impossible' This Season Now Looks Like Next Season</title><description>You know that comeback that only Kobe Bryant and the Lakers thought he could make this season? It looks like it has been moved back to next season... when, of course, only Kobe and the Lakers will think he can do it. There was already a vast gulf between Bryant and the Lakers, who just [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7404-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7404_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:54:45">http://www.forbes.com/sites/tommytomlinson/2013/12/20/what-can-we-expect-from-kobe-bryant-now/</link><title>What Can We Expect From Kobe Bryant Now?</title><description>Kobe Bryant is sideline with another major injury. He'll probably never be the same. But that might make him even more interesting. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7404-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7404_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:55:15">http://www.forbes.com/sites/hannahelliott/2014/01/29/kobe-bryant-on-nikes-new-flyknit-basketball-shoe-his-pedicure-routine-and-who-he-thinks-will-win-the-super-bowl/</link><title>Kobe Bryant On Nike's New Flyknit Basketball Shoe, His Pedicure Routine, And Who He Thinks Will Win The Super Bowl</title><description>Kobe is an expert on shoe design - and on paraffin wax pedicures.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7404-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7404_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:56:03">http://www.forbes.com/sites/tomvanriper/2013/12/20/kobe-bryants-latest-injury-is-far-from-the-lakers-only-problem/</link><title>Kobe Bryant's Latest Injury Is Far From The Lakers' Only Problem</title><description>Even with their aging star, the Lakers weren't looking like a contender. And that's not good for the league. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7404-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7404_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:57:10">http://www.forbes.com/sites/prishe/2013/12/20/regarding-kobe-bryant-lakers-will-pay-for-opting-loyalty-over-common-sense/</link><title>Regarding Kobe Bryant, Lakers Will Pay For Opting Loyalty Over Common Sense</title><description>When the Lakers signed Kobe Bryant to a 2-year extension several weeks ago, I was a bit concerned for the organization and their fans. On Thursday, the worst of those fears began to materialize when it was announced that Mr. Bryant fractured his lateral tibial plateau - the top of his [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7404-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7404_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 09:58:30">http://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2013/12/19/did-the-lakers-make-a-mistake-by-extending-kobe-bryants-contract/</link><title>Did The Lakers Make A Mistake By Extending Kobe Bryant's Contract?</title><description>With Kobe Bryant injured again, did the Lakers make a bad decision signing him to a 2-year, $48.5 million contract? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7404-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7404_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:00:00">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jesselawrence/2013/12/05/lakers-tickets-up-12-for-tuesday-night-game-on-news-of-kobe-bryants-return/</link><title>Lakers Tickets Up 12% For Tuesday Night Game On News Of Kobe Bryant's Return</title><description>UPDATE 12/6/2013: Kobe announced today that he would return Sunday against the Raptors and ticket prices are up 70% today alone. If the playoffs started today, the Lakers would not be in the post-season tournament for the first time in eight seasons. At 9-9, they sit three spots out of playoff [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>