<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7405">light therapy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:01:56" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7405-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7405_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:01:57">http://www.forbes.com/sites/carlapassino/2013/09/27/houses-for-sale-for-people-who-have-nearly-everything/</link><title>New Home Amenities For The Ultra-Rich: Beauty Therapy, Wine Tasting And Poker Rooms</title><description>These days, every mansion worth its name has a cinema room, a games room, a grand ballroom (or a dedicated party barn), a leisure complex with spa and pool and ‘his and her’ dressing rooms. However, a new breed of houses is adding a new dimension to the luxury real estate [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7405-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7405_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:03:08">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johnlamattina/2013/06/11/nejm-sheds-light-on-payments-to-doctors/</link><title>NEJM Sheds Light On Payments To Doctors</title><description>However, by far the biggest expenditure by pharma companies to Massachusetts doctors was for bona fide services, such as joint research projects, clinical trials, and advising on disease treatments. There were 8,432 payments made in this category amounting to $67.3 million – 88% of the total expenditure. In other words, pharmaceutical company [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7405-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7405_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:04:44">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jennchoi/2014/03/21/the-testing-games-can-teaching-kids-to-be-opportunistic-reduce-standardized-test-anxiety/</link><title>The Testing Games: Can Teaching Kids to Be Opportunistic Reduce Standardized Test Anxiety?</title><description>Videosee photosThinkFunClick for full photo gallery: Top Ten Games to Boost Test-Taking Skills As a writer of toy reviews, it's easy to find families who want to test products. However, at this time of the year, I have trouble getting my testers in the upper elementary grades to play with the [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7405-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7405_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:05:47">http://www.forbes.com/sites/emc/2014/04/10/faster-better-stronger-using-data-to-boost-athletic-performance/</link><title>EMC​Voice: Faster, Better, Stronger: Using Data To Boost Athletic Performance</title><description>By Kylie Jane Wakefield When Alex Guerrero, a body coach at the TB12 Sports Therapy Center in Foxborough, Mass., trains his clients, he turns to technology. He sets up beams of light that his athletes, which include New England Patriots quarterback Tom Brady, jump through. At the same time, video cameras [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7405-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7405_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:07:39">http://www.forbes.com/sites/larryhusten/2012/12/06/should-body-weight-influence-choice-of-antihypertensive-therapy/</link><title>Should Body Weight Influence Choice of Antihypertensive Therapy?</title><description>The hypertension field has been troubled by repeated observations that normal weight patients have more cardiovascular (CV) events than obese patients. Now a new analysis of a large hypertension trial confirms this finding but also suggests that it may be explained by either an adverse effect of diuretics or a protective [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7405-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7405_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:08:26">http://www.forbes.com/sites/larryhusten/2012/07/05/stem-cell-therapy-company-hypes-preliminary-results/</link><title>Stem Cell Therapy Company Hypes Preliminary Results</title><description>Update (July 6)--  I have heard from several investigators in the trial that the Osiris press release was issued without any input or consultation from the site investigators. In fact, the site investigators, including several who are  extremely experienced clinical trialists, have expressed frustration and disappointment because their input has [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7405-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7405_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:09:13">http://www.forbes.com/sites/lawrencelight/2013/04/04/how-to-get-tax-breaks-on-health-spending/</link><title>How to Get Tax Breaks on Health Spending</title><description>A good way to keep down medical costs and reduce your taxes is to open a healthcare flexible spending account. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7405-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7405_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:10:04">http://www.forbes.com/sites/singularity/2012/07/24/europe-takes-the-lead-toward-approval-of-first-gene-therapy-drug/</link><title>Europe Takes The Lead Toward Approval Of First Gene Therapy Drug</title><description>VideoIt's taken decades of work but the first gene therapy is on the verge of finally getting approval in Europe. A watershed moment in gene therapy has finally come to pass. This month, a committee from the European Medicines Agency recommended the approval of a gene therapy drug, named Glybera (alipogene [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7405-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7405_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:10:35">http://www.forbes.com/sites/matthewherper/2012/08/16/big-pharma-failures-light-the-way-to-change/</link><title>Big Pharma Failures Light the Way to Change</title><description>The pharmaceutical industry saw two very big drugs fizzle last week. Both wrecks show the way to real change. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7405-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7405_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:11:01">http://www.forbes.com/sites/larryhusten/2012/04/24/study-sheds-light-on-cardiac-device-infective-endocarditis/</link><title>Study Sheds Light on Cardiac Device Infective Endocarditis</title><description>A new study sheds light on a rare but highly dangerous complication associated with device implants: cardiac device infective endocarditis (CDIE). Approximately 10-23% of device infections result in CDIE, leading, in one estimate, to an overall rate of 1.14 cases per 1,000 device-years. In a paper published in JAMA, Eugene Athan and [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>