<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7406">does my child have adhd</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:12:03" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7406-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7406_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:12:04">http://www.forbes.com/sites/dailymuse/2013/08/27/adhd-women-and-work-what-its-like-and-ways-to-cope/</link><title>ADHD, Women, And Work: What It's Like And Ways To Cope</title><description>ADHD often goes undiagnosed in women—which can be a huge problem when they get to the workplace. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7406-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7406_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:13:20">http://www.forbes.com/sites/helaineolen/2012/10/09/the-new-york-times-reports-on-giving-adhd-drugs-to-children-who-dont-have-adhd/</link><title>The New York Times Reports On Giving ADHD Drugs to Children Who Don't Have ADHD</title><description>One of my more or less (depending on your viewpoint) attractive traits as a person is the ability to take a set of facts, and predict a negative outcome in the future.  It’s a side of my personality that I am simultaneously proud of and horrified by. On one hand, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7406-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7406_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:14:00">http://www.forbes.com/sites/emilywillingham/2013/09/05/if-a-parent-murders-an-autistic-child-who-is-to-blame/</link><title>If A Parent Murders An Autistic Child, Who Is To Blame?</title><description>No other condition draws this kind of judgment or leads people to blame the condition, the murdered, and everyone except the murderer for killing their own child. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7406-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7406_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:15:05">http://www.forbes.com/sites/alicegwalton/2013/03/05/time-to-pay-attention-what-the-newest-adhd-research-is-telling-us/</link><title>Time To Pay Attention: What The Newest ADHD Research Is Telling Us</title><description>ADHD is not just a kid thing: It raises the risk of serious psychiatric disorders in adulthood. But it's what we do what this information that's the real question. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7406-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7406_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:16:11">http://www.forbes.com/sites/alicegwalton/2012/07/25/how-parents-stress-can-hurt-a-child-from-the-inside-out/</link><title>How Parents' Stress Can Hurt A Child, From The Inside Out</title><description>Whether in utero or in the household, parental stress can damage a kid, from the genes up. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7406-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7406_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:17:12">http://www.forbes.com/sites/laurashin/2014/03/18/how-to-manage-your-biggest-investment-your-kids/</link><title>How To Manage Your Biggest Investment: Your Kids</title><description>A social scientist sifts through the data on 10 vexing parenting questions, from how far to space them to whether or not to bribe them.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7406-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7406_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:18:02">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jacobsullum/2014/02/20/hyperbole-hurts-the-surprising-truth-about-methamphetamine/</link><title>Hyperbole Hurts: The Surprising Truth About Methamphetamine</title><description>Alberto Gonzales, George W. Bush’s attorney general, called it “the most dangerous drug in America.” A physician quoted by The New York Times described it as “the most malignant, addictive drug known to mankind.” A police captain told the Times it “makes crack look like child’s play, both in terms [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7406-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7406_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:19:12">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johnosborn/2013/12/23/glaxosmithkline-may-be-motivated-by-scandal-but-changing-compensation-schemes-for-docs-and-sales-reps-is-the-right-move/</link><title>GlaxoSmithKline May Be Motivated By Scandal, But Changing Compensation Schemes For Docs And Sales Reps Is The Right Move</title><description>GlaxoSmithKline’s decision to stop paying doctors to speak about their products and to change sales representative compensation so that it is not tied directly to prescription volume is seen by some as a desperate attempt to deflect attention from recent scandals, including a $3 billion settlement of fraud and abuse [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7406-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7406_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:20:10">http://www.forbes.com/sites/nextavenue/2013/07/19/how-to-stay-motivated-and-accomplish-anything/</link><title>How To Stay Motivated And Accomplish Anything</title><description>It takes more than willpower. You need to have a strategy. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7406-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7406_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:21:13">http://www.forbes.com/sites/emilywillingham/2013/02/07/fox-news-asks-can-autism-be-prevented/</link><title>Fox News Asks, Can Autism Be Prevented?</title><description>It's happened again at Fox. After taking down a story last year that was packed with misinformation about genetically modified foods--headlined "What you need to know"--Fox has now offered up another similarly underevidenced article, this time headlined "Can autism be prevented?" Short answer: No, not usually. In spite of that, the article [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>