<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7407">kim kardashian pregnant</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:22:25" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7407-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7407_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:22:26">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markhendrickson/2013/05/02/kim-kardashian-ronny-porta-and-other-beautiful-people/</link><title>Kim Kardashian, Ronny Porta And Other Beautiful People</title><description>The great people who help to make the United States the amazing country that it is. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7407-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7407_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:23:47">http://www.forbes.com/sites/dorothypomerantz/2012/03/29/kim-kardashian-tops-our-list-of-the-most-overexposed-celebrities/</link><title>Kim Kardashian Tops Our List of the Most Overexposed Celebrities</title><description>Her sisters, Kourtney and Khloe also make the list. But being overexposed is not always a bad thing.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7407-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7407_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:25:12">http://www.forbes.com/sites/meghancasserly/2012/01/13/kim-kardashian-kashing-in-sorry-new-york-post/</link><title>Kardashian Klan Still Kashing In (Sorry New York Post)</title><description>see photosForbes ImagesClick for full photo gallery: Kim Kardashian “You may not have to keep up with the Kardashians much longer,” says Brian Niemietz in today’s New York Post, trashing the glossy-haired TV family for falling ratings, lost contracts and a decline in magazine covers that he says are a result [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7407-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7407_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:26:02">http://www.forbes.com/sites/deborahljacobs/2013/09/19/how-to-buy-your-first-hermes-birkin/</link><title>How To Buy Your First Hermès Birkin</title><description>Tips from a handbag authority on what to look for and how to get the best deal when buying a Birkin at auction.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7407-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7407_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:27:25">http://www.forbes.com/sites/bluecarreon/2013/07/11/kate-middletons-best-maternity-looks-and-how-she-pulls-it-off/</link><title>Kate Middleton's Best Maternity Looks And How She Pulls It Off</title><description>As we wait for news of the royal baby, here's a look at Kate Middleton's royal maternity style</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7407-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7407_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:28:17">http://www.forbes.com/sites/mariansalzman/2013/01/27/kate-middleton-and-the-branding-of-a-duchess/</link><title>Kate Middleton and the Branding of a Duchess</title><description>In what was undoubtedly old news to anyone who has been paying attention to the British royal family, St. James’s Palace issued an official statement last week to announce that “Their Royal Highnesses the Duke and Duchess of Cambridge are delighted to confirm they are expecting a baby in July.” [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7407-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7407_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:30:12">http://www.forbes.com/sites/meghancasserly/2012/12/03/kate-middleton-marissa-mayer-most-fascinating-women-of-2012/</link><title>Kate Middleton, Marissa Mayer And The Most Fascinating Women Of 2012</title><description>There’s no denying that 2012 has been a big year for women. We won the election, we made millions and we stood up to Rush Limbaugh. These are the women who made headlines--and history--in 2012.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7407-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7407_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:31:26">http://www.forbes.com/sites/lesleyanncoker/2012/05/09/good-morning-america-ends-todays-16-year-winning-streak/</link><title>Good Morning America Ends Today's 16-Year Winning Streak</title><description>ABC’s Good Morning America has enjoyed a remarkable ratings rise the last few weeks. According to Nielsen Media Research, GMA surpassed NBC’s Today for the first time in 16 years the week of April 9, 2012, by a total of 31,000 viewers. GMA repeated its victory the week of April [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7407-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7407_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:31:51">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kiriblakeley/2011/05/18/arnolds-baby-mama-mildred-baena-playing-against-type/</link><title>Arnold's Baby Mama Mildred Baena: Playing Against Type</title><description>I always find it fascinating when a rich, powerful or famous man takes as a mistress a woman who would never appear on the cover of Maxim magazine. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7407-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7407_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:33:04">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jennagoudreau/2012/01/24/mompreneur-jessica-alba-gets-honest-about-business/</link><title>Mompreneur Jessica Alba Gets Honest About Business</title><description>The actress sits down with Forbes to detail her new eco-friendly baby brand The Honest Company. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>