<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7408">tom cruise</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:34:04" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7408-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7408_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:34:05">http://www.forbes.com/sites/peterjreilly/2014/01/01/how-to-ranch-like-tom-cruise-on-a-lower-budget/</link><title>How To Ranch Like Tom Cruise On A Lower Budget</title><description>Video Not everybody can be Tom Cruise, but even without taking up Scientology, there are ways of participating in the Tom Cruise experience.  For example, it was reported that Tom Cruise was paying $400 in property tax on an $18 million getaway ranch in Colorado.  The great property tax deal was [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7408-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7408_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:35:15">http://www.forbes.com/sites/dorothypomerantz/2013/04/18/tom-cruise-still-matters/</link><title>Tom Cruise Still Matters</title><description>His film, 'Oblivion', is expected to top the box office this weekend with $42 million.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7408-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7408_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:36:15">http://www.forbes.com/sites/timtreadgold/2013/08/01/a-mission-impossible-job-for-tom-cruise-at-anglo-american/</link><title>A Mission Impossible Job For Tom Cruise At Anglo American</title><description>If Tom Cruise is not available for the next Mission Impossible movie the producers might be interested in recruiting Mark Cutifani, the recently appointed chief executive of Anglo American who is trying to “do a Cruise” by reviving the problem plagued mining giant Tom Cruise, probably not volunteering for the chief [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7408-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7408_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:37:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonbelzer/2014/03/27/sports-industry-mogul-darren-heitner-teaches-us-how-to-play-the-game/</link><title>Sports Industry Mogul Darren Heitner Teaches Us How To Play The Game</title><description>When Cuba Gooding Jr. got Tom Cruise to scream the words, “Show Me The Money!” during his Oscar winning performance in Jerry Maguire, he coined a phrase that would not only become synonymous with the business of sports for decades to come, but go on to inspire millions to try [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7408-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7408_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:38:51">http://www.forbes.com/sites/scottmendelson/2013/04/21/weekend-box-office-oblivion-opens-among-top-tom-cruise-debuts/</link><title>'Oblivion' Ranks Among Tom Cruise's Top Opening Weekends</title><description>Tom Cruise became a movie star during an era when a film's success was less predicated on opening weekend.  Like Harrison Ford and Tom Hanks, Tom Cruise made his name as Hollywood's biggest and most consistent star when a $15 million opening weekend was very good, a $25 million weekend [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7408-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7408_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:40:16">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markhughes/2012/12/10/watch-tom-cruise-in-oblivion-trailer/</link><title>Watch Tom Cruise In 'Oblivion' Trailer</title><description>VideoOne of the films high on my list of most anticipated films of 2013 is the sci-fi movie Oblivion starring Tom Cruise, which adapts a graphic novel of the same name. The first trailer has been released, and it looks pretty awesome, folks! The story is fascinating, the effects are eye-popping, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7408-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7408_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:41:46">http://www.forbes.com/sites/scottmendelson/2013/04/20/friday-box-office-tom-cruise-scores-near-record-opening-day-with-oblivion/</link><title>Friday Box Office: Tom Cruise Scores Near-Record Opening Day With 'Oblivion'</title><description>Tom Cruise may be among the biggest movie stars of the last thirty years, but his peak stardom occurred from the mid-80's to mid-2000's (Top Gun to War of the Worlds). That's an incredibly long run, but it was also mostly during an age where opening weekend wasn't quite as [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7408-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7408_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:43:00">http://www.forbes.com/sites/scottmendelson/2013/04/16/review-tom-cruises-oblivion-is-visually-beautiful/</link><title>Review: Tom Cruise's 'Oblivion' Presents a Beautiful Vision of the End of the World</title><description>I could easily spoil the vast majority of Oblivion merely by listing the various science fiction films from which it cribs.  From visual cues to plot beats and character arcs, it feels like a mash-up of the various high-profile science fiction thrillers from the last few decades.  But almost despite itself, the [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7408-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7408_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:44:14">http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidmonagan/2013/04/14/obamas-got-his-clinton-andtom-cruise-too-official-irish-heritage-certificates-for-one-and-all/</link><title>O'Bama's Got His, Clinton And Tom Cruise Too -- Official Irish Heritage Certificates For One And All</title><description>You too can be certified Irish like Tom Cruise. Official evidence of Irish ancestry available for a song! read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7408-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7408_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:45:34">http://www.forbes.com/sites/robertwood/2012/07/20/tom-cruise-scientology-isnt-only-about-taxes/</link><title>Tom Cruise: Scientology Isn't Only About Taxes</title><description>The Scientology symbol is composed of the letter S, which stands for Scientology, and the ARC and KRC triangles, two important concepts in Scientology. (Photo credit: Wikipedia) Most people are reluctant to criticize religious practices, let alone a church. Yet fear that Suri Cruise might be indoctrinated into Scientology's elite Sea Org may have [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>