<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7409">rihanna chris brown</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:46:26" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7409-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7409_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:46:27">http://www.forbes.com/sites/zillow/2014/03/28/celebrity-real-estate-rihanna-pink-sarah-michelle-gellar-and-zac-efron/</link><title>Celebrity Real Estate: Rihanna, Pink, Sarah Michelle Gellar And Zac Efron</title><description>It’s Buh-Bye L.A. For Rihanna Rihanna has left the building -- and L.A.. -- so it makes sense that the sultry songstress has put her luxurious Pacific Palisades mansion up for sale. The listing comes just months after she tried to rent the 10,000-square-foot manse for $65,000 a month. It appears that [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7409-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7409_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:48:07">http://www.forbes.com/sites/lizgarcia/2012/02/13/compassion-for-chris-brown-the-only-solution/</link><title>Compassion For Chris Brown The Only Solution</title><description>Chris Brown accepting an award at the 2012 Grammys. photo from NY Daily news Grammys producer Ken Erlich told ABC News Radio that Chris Brown was invited to perform on last night's show because "Everyone deserves a second chance." My feeling: No, they don't. Read the police report of Chris Brown's [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7409-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7409_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:48:40">http://www.forbes.com/sites/bluecarreon/2013/02/10/jennifer-lopez-justin-timberlake-rihanna-and-more-on-the-grammy-awards-red-carpet/</link><title>Jennifer Lopez, Justin Timberlake, Rihanna, Taylor Swift And More On The Grammy Awards Red Carpet</title><description>See what Taylor Swift, Jennifer Lopez, Beyonce, Drake, Pharell, Jennifer Lopez , Justin Timberlake and more on the red carpet of the 2013 grammy Awards,</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7409-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7409_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:49:19">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johnclarke/2012/09/09/coldplay-rihanna-and-jay-z-to-play-london-paralympics-closing-ceremonies/</link><title>Coldplay, Rihanna And Jay-Z To Play London Paralympics Closing Ceremonies</title><description>Jay Z Coldplay, Rihanna and Jay-Z are on deck to perform at the London Paralympics Closing Ceremony tonight. According to reports, Coldplay will play "Us Against The World," "Yellow," "Up In Flames," "42," "God Put A Smile On Your Face," "Clocks," and "Charlie Brown." Rihanna will join Coldplay's Chris Martin for a duet [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7409-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7409_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:50:27">http://www.forbes.com/sites/dorothypomerantz/2012/05/16/celebrity-100-rihanna-and-kim-kardashian-debut-on-our-list/</link><title>Celebrity 100: Rihanna and Kim Kardashian Debut On Our List</title><description>Today celebrity power is about more than talent. It's about knowing how to work a 24-hour persona.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7409-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7409_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:51:27">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markpasetsky/2011/03/22/chris-brown-defends-good-morning-america-outburst-via-twitter/</link><title>Chris Brown Defends Good Morning America Outburst Via Twitter</title><description>Chris Brown, who has been desperately trying to rehabilitate his image in order to sell his new album F.A.M.E, reportedly exploded behind the scenes at Good Morning America this morning, according to reports.  Apparently, he wasn't thrilled with GMA anchor Robin Roberts, who asked him on-air about the 2009 Rihanna [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7409-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7409_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:52:09">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markpasetsky/2011/02/12/news_chris_brown_snl_twitter_189189/</link><title>Chris Brown Tweets He's Nervous About Saturday Night Live</title><description>Was Chris Brown worried about his Saturday Night Live musical appearance? You bet. Earlier today, Brown shared with his fans via Twitter exactly how he was feeling: "I'm so nervous about tonight!!!!!" read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7409-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7409_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:53:16">http://www.forbes.com/sites/meghancasserly/2012/12/13/hillary-clinton-beyonce-10-most-talked-about-women-of-2012/</link><title>The 10 Most Talked-About Women Of 2012</title><description>Content curator News360 ran the numbers to track the news-making women of 2012—from celebrities to politicians, what ladies dominated the news cycle this year?</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7409-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7409_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:53:59">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jennagoudreau/2012/11/07/working-with-your-husbands-ex-and-the-worlds-most-awkward-business-partnerships/</link><title>Working With Your Husband's Ex And The World's Most Awkward Business Partnerships</title><description>Sometimes love and business tangle in unexpected ways. Whether working with your ex or your spouse's ex, these may be the world's most awkward business relationships.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7409-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7409_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 10:55:00">http://www.forbes.com/sites/danschawbel/2012/03/09/house-music-has-become-a-global-phenomenon/</link><title>House Music Has Become a Global Phenomenon</title><description>DJ's have taken over pop culture by producing for America's most prominent music figure heads and by immersing themselves in clubs and at major venues. Check out to see which masterminds are leading the global phenomenon.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>