<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7416">release date bioshock infinite</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:34:42" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7416-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7416_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:34:42">http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2013/10/25/bioshock-infinite-burial-at-sea-release-date-announced/</link><title>'BioShock Infinite: Burial At Sea' Release Date Announced</title><description>The 'Burial At Sea' DLC for 2K's 'BioShock Infinite' is coming this November.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7416-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7416_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:36:06">http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2014/04/22/dragon-age-inquisition-box-art-is-gender-neutral/</link><title>'Dragon Age: Inquisition' Box-Art Is 'Gender-Neutral'</title><description>The newly released box-art for 'Dragon Age: Inquisition' is intentionally vague. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7416-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7416_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:37:33">http://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2013/04/09/bioshock-infinite-review-xbox-360-version/</link><title>BioShock Infinite Review - Xbox 360 Version</title><description>BioShock Infinite, the "spiritual sequel" to 2007's highly-praised BioShock, itself the spiritual sequel to the highly-praised System Shock 2, has expectations as sky-high as its cloud-city setting. Can it deliver? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7416-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7416_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:38:19">http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2012/12/07/bioshock-infinite-delayed-yet-again/</link><title>Bioshock Infinite Delayed Yet Again</title><description>It's almost a running joke at this point how many times Bioshock Infinite has been delayed at this point, so it's no surprise to be writing another story like this one. That said, I've never been of the school of thought that delaying a game is necessarily a bad thing. [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7416-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7416_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:39:03">http://www.forbes.com/sites/danielnyegriffiths/2013/04/01/bioshock-infinite-spoiler-free-review/</link><title>The Shock Doctrine - BioShock Infinite (Spoiler-free) Review</title><description>At the dying of the light for the current gaming hardware cycle, Take-Two Interactive are finishing strongly: Grand Theft Auto 5 will be one of the biggest-selling games of 2013. But will BioShock Infinite be remembered as the best? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7416-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7416_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:39:45">http://www.forbes.com/sites/danielnyegriffiths/2013/11/04/irrational-ken-levine-golden-joystick-interview/</link><title>Irrational Decisions: Ken Levine Talks BioShock, Burial At Sea And The Future Of Storytelling</title><description>Ken Levine, cofounder and Creative Director of Irrational Games, talks to Forbes about BioShock Infinite, his greatest regret as a game designer, and how football (American or everywhere-else version) relates to the behavior of Elizabeth, the heroine of 'Burial at Sea'. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7416-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7416_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:40:31">http://www.forbes.com/sites/danielnyegriffiths/2013/01/22/bioshock-infinite-preview/</link><title>BioShock Infinite Preview - Oh, Amber Waves of Pain</title><description>BioShock Infinite's gown continues to slip - I spent some time in Columbia with producer Mike Soden. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7416-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7416_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:42:17">http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2012/05/09/bioshock-infinite-delayed-until-2013/</link><title>Bioshock: Infinite Delayed Until 2013</title><description>Bioshock Infinite was going to be one of the most anticipated releases of the holiday season, but now it looks like it’s going to be one of the most anticipated releases of early 2013. Irrational Games’ talked-about follow-up to Bioshock (which I had some problems with) sends the hero to the [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7416-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7416_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:43:11">http://www.forbes.com/sites/danielnyegriffiths/2013/08/19/in-retrospect-gone-home-designer-on-bioshock-bastion-and-the-indie-games-business/</link><title>In Retrospect: 'Gone Home' Designer On 'BioShock', 'Bastion' And The Indie Games Business</title><description>Although The Fullbright Company's Gone Home was something of an indie darling well before its release, the four-person studio is still reeling a little, it seems, from the commercial and critical reception it received at launch last week. In this interview, conducted earlier this year, founder and designer Steve Gaynor discussed the emotional and [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7416-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7416_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:44:19">http://www.forbes.com/sites/carolpinchefsky/2013/01/03/bioshock-infinites-sky-hook-is-guaranteed-to-put-the-steam-in-your-punk/</link><title>BioShock Infinite's Sky-Hook Is 'Guaranteed to Put the Steam in Your Punk'</title><description>How do you get from point A to point B in a city in the clouds? If you’re a citizen of Columbia, the floating city in the upcoming game BioShock Infinite, you use a Sky-Hook to transport you across Sky-Lines. And how do you attack enemies? A Sky-Hook, of course. Wait, it’s a method of transportation and a weapon? I need it. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>