<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7420">Badland game for iphone</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:56:38" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7420-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7420_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:56:39">http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2013/07/08/apple-giving-away-top-shelf-apps-and-games-for-five-year-app-store-anniversary/</link><title>Apple Giving Away Top-Shelf Apps And Games For Five Year App Store Anniversary</title><description>Video Mac App Store (Photo credit: Wikipedia) Apple's App Store celebrates its fifth anniversary this week, and Apple has some nice rewards for anyone that happens to be searching through the app store today. The company has put a suite of top-shelf apps and games on the ultimate sale today, knocking them [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7420-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7420_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:57:43">http://www.forbes.com/sites/terokuittinen/2013/07/01/why-price-an-app-at-4-because-it-makes-price-cut-campaigns-really-pop/</link><title>Why Price An App At $4? Because It Makes Price Cut Campaigns Really Pop</title><description>Finnish app vendor Frogmind made a contrarian decision by pricing its iOS game "Badland" at $4 last spring. The mobile game market has moved decisively towards free downloads over the past two years. There is only one paid app in the Top 20 revenue chart of iPhone apps today in America [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7420-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7420_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:58:23">http://www.forbes.com/sites/terokuittinen/2013/11/22/5-reasons-why-finnish-apps-are-beating-american-rivals-on-us-ipad-market/</link><title>5 Reasons Why Finnish Apps Are Beating American Rivals On US iPad Market</title><description>November 21 was another high point for Finnish app industry. FDG Entertainment's "Oceanhorn" reigned as #1 iPad download in America and Rovio's "Angry Birds Star Wars 2" held onto #5 slot. Supercell's two games were lodged as #2 and #3 grossing US iPad apps. This meant that three Finnish companies held [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7420-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7420_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 11:58:58">http://www.forbes.com/sites/terokuittinen/2013/10/31/nordic-start-up-funding-heating-up/</link><title>Nordic Start-up Funding Heating Up</title><description>Sweden has been long a focus of European start-up funding - in 2012, it attracted more venture capital money per capita than any other European country, absorbing nearly 20% of all European VC funding. But in 2013, Finland has also started showing a pulse as the country's role as a [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>