<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7430">conflict mali</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:36:21" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7430-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7430_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:36:22">http://www.forbes.com/sites/willyfoote/2013/03/14/mali-entrepreneurs-offer-path-to-peace/</link><title>Mali Entrepreneurs Offer Path to Peace</title><description>The day French fighters started bombing Mali in January, I was on edge.  Root Capital’s regional credit manager based in Dakar, Diaka Sall, was visiting clients in Mali that very day the French stepped in to stop the Northern rebels' southward march toward the capital city. “Don’t worry,” she told us, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7430-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7430_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:37:57">http://www.forbes.com/sites/eliseknutsen/2012/12/13/for-ngos-in-mali-life-goes-on-with-new-difficulties/</link><title>For NGOs in Mali, Life Goes On... With New Difficulties</title><description>An American working in Mali explains how the crisis has affected NGOs operating throughout the country. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7430-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7430_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:39:23">http://www.forbes.com/sites/willyfoote/2014/03/10/rep-joe-kennedy-on-the-healing-powers-of-entrepreneurship/</link><title>Rep. Joe Kennedy On The Healing Powers Of Entrepreneurship</title><description>When I sat down for lunch earlier this year with Massachusetts Congressman Joe Kennedy, I had conflict zones and refugees on my mind. It turns out, so did he. Over the holidays, my kids watched the 60 Minutes story on the Lost Boys of Sudan, young refugees who returned to [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7430-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7430_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:40:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/forbeswomanfiles/2014/04/15/why-we-all-should-care-about-the-womens-economy/</link><title>Why We All Should Care About The Women's Economy</title><description>When we look at women as a global economic force, a picture of unprecedented potential becomes visible. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7430-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7430_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:41:49">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ruthblatt/2013/12/13/rage-against-the-regime-how-young-people-are-using-music-to-create-social-change-in-the-middle-east/</link><title>Rage Against The Regime: How Young People Are Using Music To Create Social Change In The Middle East</title><description>A new MTV series shows how music creates conflict by expressing discontent with the established regime as well as how music can create healing connections between people who have historically been at conflict. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7430-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7430_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:42:30">http://www.forbes.com/2005/08/31/ivory-coast-civil-war-cx_0831oxan-ivorycoast.html</link><title>Ivorian Conflict Takes Toll On Region</title><description>Recent setbacks in advance of the planned October elections threaten to return the Ivory Coast to civil war. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7430-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7430_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:43:17">http://www.forbes.com/sites/richardminiter/2014/02/28/6-signs-that-the-white-houses-susan-rice-is-clueless-about-africa/</link><title>6 Signs That The White House's Susan Rice Is Clueless About Africa</title><description>Susan Rice said this Sunday she had “no regrets” about trotting out her flawed Benghazi talking points last year, touching off a predictable storm of controversy. Certainly Rice’s talking points deserved more scrutiny than they got from reporters. There are simple questions that Rice could have been asked: If the Benghazi [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7430-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7430_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:43:50">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ashoka/2012/12/05/a-son-of-slaves-is-still-fighting-for-human-rights/</link><title>A Son of Slaves Still Fights For Human Rights</title><description>The campaign to abolish slavery in the US might be over, but globally the problem persists. (Photo credit: Wikipedia) While "Lincoln" portrays the end of slavery in the U.S. as something from the past, slavery is still a threat to human dignity for millions across the globe. In Mali, one descendant [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7430-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7430_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:45:00">http://www.forbes.com/sites/christophercoats/2013/11/21/whats-standing-in-the-way-of-moroccan-oil-and-gas/</link><title>What's Standing In the Way of Moroccan Oil And Gas?</title><description>Morocco is emerging as a viable, or at least safe bet for energy exploration in North Africa - but the road ahead is not without its challenges. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7430-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7430_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:45:40">http://www.forbes.com/sites/taylorbrodarick/2013/09/30/black-hawk-again-what-the-kenya-mall-attack-means-for-africa-and-america/</link><title>Black Hawk Again? What The Kenya Mall Attack Means For Africa And America</title><description>The new face of terrorism is likely to be African. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>