<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7432">ticket to mars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:48:02" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7432-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7432_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:48:03">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jesselawrence/2014/04/03/sparse-primary-market-helps-drive-up-price-of-bruno-mars-tickets-on-secondary-market/</link><title>Sparse Primary Market Helps Drive Up Price of Bruno Mars Tickets on Secondary Market</title><description>Since halftime at the Super Bowl, there has been a lasting effect on secondary market prices for Bruno Mars tickets. Two months after the Super Bowl, prices on the secondary market aren’t quite at the astronomical levels they were immediately after the game, but ‘Moonshine Jungle’ remains one of the [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7432-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7432_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:49:01">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jesselawrence/2014/02/12/could-the-bruno-mars-act-change-the-way-tickets-are-bought-for-high-demand-concerts/</link><title>Could "The Bruno Mars Act" Change The Way Tickets Are Bought For High Demand Concerts?</title><description>When Bruno Mars finished his Super Bowl half-time show, America had found a new king of pop.  No state was more excited about his ascendency to the throne than his native Hawaii.  To celebrate, fans lined up on Monday after the Super Bowl to get Bruno Mars tickets for his [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7432-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7432_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:49:54">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jesselawrence/2014/04/01/as-bangerz-tour-reaches-halfway-point-prices-for-miley-cyrus-tickets-rising/</link><title>As Bangerz Tour Reaches Halfway Point, Prices For Miley Cyrus Tickets Rising</title><description>Miley Cyrus has 17 dates remaining on her ‘Bangerz’ Tour, passing the halfway point of her 40 show dates. After mixed reviews at the start the run, ‘Bangerz’ has gained momentum as the tour has rolled on. Through the first 23 performances, the average price for a ticket on the [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7432-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7432_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:51:16">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jesselawrence/2014/02/03/ticket-demand-and-prices-for-bruno-mars-moonshine-jungle-tour-skyrocking-after-super-bowl-performance/</link><title>Demand And Prices For Bruno Mars Tickets Skyrocket After Super Bowl Performance</title><description>After a season of buildup and two weeks of feverish hype, Super Bowl XLVIII was never really a game.  From the first snap, the Broncos seemed disoriented and over-matched. By halftime the game was over, and the only thing to look forward to was the halftime show.   Along with the [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7432-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7432_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:52:12">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jesselawrence/2014/03/10/2014-houston-rodeo-tickets-in-high-demand/</link><title>Behind Maroon 5, 2014 Houston Rodeo Tickets In High Demand</title><description>First held in 1931 as the Houston Fat Stock Show and Livestock Exposition, the Houston Livestock Show and Rodeo, or Houston Rodeo has been the signature event for its host city for over 80 years now. Held over 20 days at Reliant Stadium, the Houston Rodeo features a diverse program [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7432-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7432_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:52:38">http://www.forbes.com/sites/brucekasanoff/2014/04/17/five-ways-to-get-anyone-to-to-anything/</link><title>Five Ways To Get Anyone To Do Anything You Want</title><description>Many years ago when I was earning my MBA at Wharton, students raved about a course Dr. Charles Dwyer taught in the education department. (The course might as well have been taught on Mars, but Dr. Dwyer was good enough to attract vast hordes of MBA students.) The highlight of [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7432-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7432_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:53:08">http://www.forbes.com/sites/zackomalleygreenburg/2014/02/03/what-bruno-mars-super-bowl-show-means-for-his-earnings/</link><title>What Bruno Mars' Super Bowl Show Means For His Earnings</title><description>Unlike the players who took the field for the Seattle Seahawks and Denver Broncos at last night's Super Bowl, halftime performer Bruno Mars won't be paid for his efforts--as is customary for the year's biggest entertainment event in the U.S. For the Super Bowl's halftime acts, payment comes in the form of exposure--and in the case of Bruno Mars, [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7432-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7432_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:53:46">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jesselawrence/2014/02/05/luke-bryan-hopes-to-follow-bruno-mars-success-with-daytona-500-pre-race-concert/</link><title>Luke Bryan Hopes To Follow Bruno Mars Success With Daytona 500 Pre-Race Concert</title><description>When the Daytona International Speedway announced that Luke Bryan would be headlining the Datytona 500 pre-race show, the Super Bowl was still almost two weeks away.  While the Super Bowl was a dud, Bruno Mars electrified 115 million Americans with his 12-minute half-time show.  In a stroke of musical promotional [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7432-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7432_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:54:13">http://www.forbes.com/sites/zackomalleygreenburg/2014/01/31/how-bruno-mars-got-the-super-bowl-xlviii-halftime-gig/</link><title>How Bruno Mars Got The Super Bowl XLVIII Halftime Gig</title><description>How did the 28-year-old from Hawaii land the gig? He told FORBES the whole story during an interview for our annual 30 Under 30 issue, which hit newsstands earlier this month. It might surprise some to learn the NFL reached out to Mars first, not vice versa.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7432-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7432_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 12:55:06">http://www.forbes.com/sites/charleswarner/2014/02/06/addicted-to-commercials/</link><title>Addicted to Commercials - Corrected</title><description>I made stupid math error in my first post of this blog -- watching too many commercials, I guess.  I've corrected it below. Suspense took a holiday after the first quarter of the Super Bowl.  About 112 million viewers knew who was going to win, so why did they stick around? They [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>