<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7438">facebook privacy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:17:45" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7438-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7438_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:17:46">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kellyclay/2014/04/21/how-to-manage-facebook-privacy-for-the-entire-family/</link><title>How To Manage Facebook Privacy For The Entire Family</title><description>A few weeks ago, Facebook rolled out yet another layout of Timeline, causing a brief uproar from Facebook users. While most people settled down in a few days, those concerned with privacy noted that the new design explicitly made finding privacy settings more difficult than ever. Facebook has been known [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7438-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7438_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:18:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/parmyolson/2014/03/17/whatsapp-founder-defends-his-commitment-to-privacy-after-19-facebook-deal/</link><title>WhatsApp Founder Defends His Commitment To Privacy After $19B Facebook Deal</title><description>Jan Koum responds to ‘inaccurate and careless’ criticisms of how the messaging app might continue to handles user data, after Facebook agreed to buy it for $19 billion last month. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7438-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7438_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:19:25">http://www.forbes.com/sites/benkepes/2014/02/12/holy-ban-batman-facebook-takes-privacy-seriously-and-bans-sketchy-partner/</link><title>UPDATED - Holy Ban Batman - Facebook Takes Privacy Seriously And Bans Sketchy Partner</title><description>An interesting piece of news picked up from MyPermissions, a company doing interesting work giving consumers clarity over the third party services their social solutions have given authentication to. It seems that Facebook has started to take privacy violations seriously and has banned a couple of vendors from the platform Late [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7438-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7438_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:19:50">http://www.forbes.com/sites/amitchowdhry/2013/11/19/facebook-privacy-tips/</link><title>20 Tips On Increasing Your Facebook Privacy And Security</title><description>Let's face it, we all have an embarrassing photo that we don't want people to see on Facebook.  Maintaining privacy on Facebook is important because recruiters, teachers, bosses and college admission committees are highly likely to look at your profile and make judgments about your professionalism based on what they can see. [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7438-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7438_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:20:22">http://www.forbes.com/sites/larrymagid/2014/04/17/facebooks-nearby-friends-fearure-lets-you-share-your-location/</link><title>Facebook's 'Nearby Friends' Feature Lets You Share Your Location</title><description>Facebook is rolling out a new feature for its mobile app that allows you to  share your approximate location with friends. The opt-in feature (it's turned off by default) enables you to find and be found by nearby friends. The feature can be turned on or off at any time [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7438-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7438_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:20:53">http://www.forbes.com/sites/parmyolson/2014/04/17/facebook-to-ping-users-of-nearby-friends/</link><title>Facebook To Ping Users Of Nearby Friends</title><description>The social media giant finally moves into the 'people discovery' space. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7438-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7438_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:21:15">http://www.forbes.com/sites/drewhendricks/2013/10/21/what-does-the-facebook-teen-privacy-change-mean-for-businesses/</link><title>What Does The Facebook Teen Privacy Change Mean For Businesses?</title><description>(Photo credit: Wikipedia) Until recently, Facebookers between the ages of 13 and 17 operated in a vacuum. Only their friends could see their posts, whether they wanted to make a public impression or not. All of that is changing. Perhaps in competition with the growing popularity of its own Instagram service, Facebook [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7438-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7438_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:21:47">http://www.forbes.com/sites/shelisrael/2013/12/09/why-apple-google-facebook-must-fight-for-user-privacy/</link><title>Why Apple, Google &amp;amp; Facebook Must Fight for User Privacy</title><description>Apple, Google and Facebook, along with AOL, LinkedIn, Microsoft, Twitter and Yahoo! have signed a petition to the Federal government urging limits be imposed on the government's authority to collect customer data from Internet companies who must comply or face very serious penalties. These eight companies usually compete--often bitterly.  The last [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7438-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7438_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:22:28">http://www.forbes.com/sites/parmyolson/2014/04/10/regulators-to-facebook-and-whatsapp-were-watching-you/</link><title>Regulators To Facebook And WhatsApp: 'We're Watching You'</title><description>The Federal Trade Commission has publicly reminded Facebook and WhatsApp of their ‘obligations’ to privacy, and says it will monitor how they use people’s data. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7438-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7438_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:22:49">http://www.forbes.com/sites/leoking/2014/04/15/watch-out-paypal-the-real-meaning-of-a-facebook-money-transfer-business/</link><title>Watch Out PayPal? The Real Meaning Of A Facebook Money Transfer Business</title><description>The web-based money transfer market could be in for a large shakeup after it emerged Facebook is planning a money transfer business in Europe, expanding its existing options beyond the US. Expert opinions are split as to whether a foray into the market by Facebook would cause a headache for existing money transfer providers such as PayPal, [...]</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>