<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7440">barcelona real madrid</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:33:10" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7440-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7440_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:33:10">http://www.forbes.com/sites/bobbymcmahon/2014/02/02/there-are-a-lot-more-racing-santanders-than-real-madrids-and-barcelonas-spains-financial-quagmire/</link><title>There Are A Lot More Racing Santanders Than Real Madrids And Barcelonas - Spain's Financial Quagmire</title><description>Because for all the success achieved over the last 10 years or so Spain has an unsustainable system by which the top two teams – Real Madrid and Barcelona - siphon off so much money that the others are faced with accepting the inevitably of irrelevance or incurring so much debt that bankruptcy becomes just another milestone in the business plan. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7440-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7440_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:34:35">http://www.forbes.com/sites/bobbymcmahon/2013/10/26/the-first-clasico-of-the-season-seven-thoughts-on-barcelona-and-real-madrid/</link><title>The First Clásico Of The Season - Seven Thoughts On Barcelona And Real Madrid</title><description>Real Madrid had a very solid penalty claim turned down in the 72nd minute. Ronaldo was in the Barca penalty box looking to run on to a through ball when Mascherano hit him in the back. Down went Ronaldo but the referee was unmoved. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7440-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7440_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:35:03">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kurtbadenhausen/2013/07/15/barcelona-and-real-madrid-rule-social-media/</link><title>Barcelona And Real Madrid Rule Social Media</title><description>Need more proof of soccer's massive global following? Barcelona has 61 million Twitter followers and Facebook fans, which is more than the NFL's 30 most valuable teams combined. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7440-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7440_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:36:24">http://www.forbes.com/sites/mikeozanian/2013/12/02/by-targeting-real-madrid-and-barcelona-regulators-could-put-la-liga-at-disadvantage/</link><title>By Targeting Real Madrid And Barcelona Regulators Could Cripple La Liga</title><description>Perhaps it is their desperation for cash due to the country's dismal economy and declining tax revenue. Or perhaps they have decided that rules are rules--no exceptions. For whatever reason Spain's regulators are going after players and teams in La Liga, the country's top soccer league, in such a punitive [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7440-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7440_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:37:12">http://www.forbes.com/sites/bobbymcmahon/2014/04/20/why-jose-mourinho-needs-to-worry-about-his-head-when-chelsea-plays-atletico-madrid-in-uefa-champions-league/</link><title>Why Jose Mourinho Needs To Worry About His Head When Chelsea Plays Atletico Madrid In UEFA Champions League</title><description>"I'm not Tito! I'll rip your head off!" read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7440-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7440_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:37:45">http://www.forbes.com/sites/bobbymcmahon/2013/06/24/the-players-barcelona-and-real-madrid-decided-were-not-good-enough-part-two/</link><title>Players Barcelona (And Real Madrid) Decided Were Not Good Enough - Part Two</title><description>Part one  looked at the dilemma faced by Barcelona - give young players like Thiago Alcântara and Martin Montoya more playing time at the expense of more proven talent or risk losing them. Part two considers some La Masia players who have been allowed to leave and some big money transfers [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7440-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7440_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:38:21">http://www.forbes.com/sites/bobbymcmahon/2014/04/05/why-barcelonas-annus-horribilis-may-yet-turn-into-something-very-different/</link><title>Why Barcelona's Annus Horribilis May Yet Turn Into Something Very Different</title><description>Persistent questioning of the financial details of the deal by Barcelona club member Jordi Cases brought the same answers for weeks but eventually Rosell’s mantra of $74M was found to be a lie. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7440-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7440_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:38:59">http://www.forbes.com/sites/mikeozanian/2013/09/16/real-madrid-makes-ronaldo-highest-paid-soccer-player-with-200-million-deal/</link><title>Real Madrid Makes Ronaldo Highest Paid Soccer Player With $200 Million Deal</title><description>BARCELONA, SPAIN - AUGUST 23: Lionel Messi of FC Barcelona (2ndR) duels for the ball with Cristiano Ronaldo, Fabio Coentrao (2ndL) and Xabi Alonso of Real Madrid CF during the Super Cup first leg match between FC Barcelona and Real Madrid at Camp Nou on August 23, 2012 in Barcelona, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7440-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7440_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:39:40">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kellyphillipserb/2014/02/21/fc-barcelona-hit-with-another-superstar-tax-scandal-as-neymar-transfer-investigated/</link><title>FC Barcelona Hit With Another Superstar Tax Scandal As Neymar Transfer Investigated</title><description>What's the biggest soccer news to come out of FC Barcelona in recent months? Tax debt. Now that Messi has resolved his tax issues, the team has to grapple with questions over the Neymar transfer. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7440-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7440_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:40:36">http://www.forbes.com/sites/afontevecchia/2014/01/23/fc-barcelona-president-quits-over-neymar-corruption-scandal/</link><title>FC Barcelona President Quits Over Neymar Corruption Scandal: Barca Paid $150M For Brazilian Star</title><description>FC Barcelona president Sandro Rosell resigned after reports revealed the team paid more than 95 million euros to sign Brazilian superstar Neymar, well above the 57 million euros he originally disclosed.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>