<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7441">barcelona real madrid goal messi</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:41:44" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7441-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7441_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:41:45">http://www.forbes.com/sites/bobbymcmahon/2014/04/05/why-barcelonas-annus-horribilis-may-yet-turn-into-something-very-different/</link><title>Why Barcelona's Annus Horribilis May Yet Turn Into Something Very Different</title><description>Persistent questioning of the financial details of the deal by Barcelona club member Jordi Cases brought the same answers for weeks but eventually Rosell’s mantra of $74M was found to be a lie. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7441-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7441_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:42:29">http://www.forbes.com/sites/mikeozanian/2013/12/02/by-targeting-real-madrid-and-barcelona-regulators-could-put-la-liga-at-disadvantage/</link><title>By Targeting Real Madrid And Barcelona Regulators Could Cripple La Liga</title><description>Perhaps it is their desperation for cash due to the country's dismal economy and declining tax revenue. Or perhaps they have decided that rules are rules--no exceptions. For whatever reason Spain's regulators are going after players and teams in La Liga, the country's top soccer league, in such a punitive [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7441-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7441_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:43:41">http://www.forbes.com/sites/bobbymcmahon/2013/10/26/the-first-clasico-of-the-season-seven-thoughts-on-barcelona-and-real-madrid/</link><title>The First Clásico Of The Season - Seven Thoughts On Barcelona And Real Madrid</title><description>Real Madrid had a very solid penalty claim turned down in the 72nd minute. Ronaldo was in the Barca penalty box looking to run on to a through ball when Mascherano hit him in the back. Down went Ronaldo but the referee was unmoved. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7441-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7441_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:44:40">http://www.forbes.com/sites/afontevecchia/2014/01/23/fc-barcelona-president-quits-over-neymar-corruption-scandal/</link><title>FC Barcelona President Quits Over Neymar Corruption Scandal: Barca Paid $150M For Brazilian Star</title><description>FC Barcelona president Sandro Rosell resigned after reports revealed the team paid more than 95 million euros to sign Brazilian superstar Neymar, well above the 57 million euros he originally disclosed.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7441-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7441_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:45:42">http://www.forbes.com/sites/mikeozanian/2014/01/03/barcelona-becomes-first-sports-team-to-have-50-million-facebook-fans/</link><title>Barcelona Becomes First Sports Team To Have 50 Million Facebook Fans</title><description>FC Barcelona has become the first sports franchise in the world to have over 50 million fans on Facebook and the Spanish soccer power also claims it now has one of the 30 most popular Facebook pages in the world. The historic achievement comes after a 2013 in which Barcelona gained more than 11 [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7441-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7441_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:46:29">http://www.forbes.com/sites/mikeozanian/2013/09/16/real-madrid-makes-ronaldo-highest-paid-soccer-player-with-200-million-deal/</link><title>Real Madrid Makes Ronaldo Highest Paid Soccer Player With $200 Million Deal</title><description>BARCELONA, SPAIN - AUGUST 23: Lionel Messi of FC Barcelona (2ndR) duels for the ball with Cristiano Ronaldo, Fabio Coentrao (2ndL) and Xabi Alonso of Real Madrid CF during the Super Cup first leg match between FC Barcelona and Real Madrid at Camp Nou on August 23, 2012 in Barcelona, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7441-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7441_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:47:41">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ricardogeromel/2013/03/06/will-a-billionaire-buy-messis-left-foot/</link><title>Will A Billionaire Buy Messi's Left Foot?</title><description>A Japanese jeweler unveiled today, in a famous jewelry shop in Tokyo, a pure gold replica of Lionel Messi’s left foot. The unique 25 kilograms solid sculpture was created by Ginza Tanaka and will go on sale tomorrow for $5.25 million. “I'm honoured to have my foot recreated in pure gold," said [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7441-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7441_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:49:08">http://www.forbes.com/sites/bobbymcmahon/2013/01/02/december-2012-revisited-galaxy-repeats-villa-defence-spreads-xmas-cheer-to-others-messi-finishes-on-91-goals/</link><title>December 2012 - Revisited; Galaxy Repeats; Villa Defence Spreads Xmas Cheer To Others; Messi Finishes On 91 Goals;</title><description>In Spain Athletic Bilbao gets another 5-1 thumping at the start of the month – this whipping inflicted by Barcelona. As normal Real beats Atleti in the Madrid derby – this time 2-0. MLS Cup is won for the second consecutive year by Los Angeles Galaxy as they beat Houston Dynamo [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7441-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7441_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:50:30">http://www.forbes.com/global/2012/0507/soccer-valuations-12-feature-spain-financial-crisis-champions-barcelona-boom.html</link><title>The Barcelona Boom</title><description>The hottest soccer club in the world right now is thriving despite Spain's financial crisis--and one of the stranger ownership structures in sports. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7441-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7441_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 13:51:03">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kurtbadenhausen/2013/03/02/cristiano-ronaldo-and-lionel-messi-rule-the-world-but-not-the-u-s/</link><title>Cristiano Ronaldo And Lionel Messi Rule The World, But Not The U.S.</title><description>Messi and Ronaldo are the biggest stars in the world’s most popular sport, but their awareness levels in the U.S. are on par with Yu Darvish and Abby Wambach.</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>