<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7448">running shoes boston</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:28:09" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7448-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7448_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:28:09">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kurtbadenhausen/2013/05/20/brooks-running-shoes-hit-their-stride/</link><title>Brooks Running Shoes Hit Their Stride</title><description>Brooks Sports tried to go toe-to-toe with Nike across all sports, but couldn't keep pace. A renewed focus on performance running shoes helped the company take off. The subsidiary of Berkshire Hathaway is "on fire" says Warren Buffett. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7448-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7448_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:29:28">http://www.forbes.com/sites/learnvest/2013/08/02/running-the-numbers-whats-the-real-cost-of-your-workout/</link><title>Running The Numbers: What's The Real Cost Of Your Workout?</title><description>Meet the woman who does yoga three times a week—for six cents a workout. And the guy who pays $15,000 a year to stay in shape. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7448-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7448_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:31:24">http://www.forbes.com/sites/petercohan/2012/11/14/cobblers-shoes-strategy-guru-michael-porters-monitor-group-bankrupt/</link><title>Cobbler's Shoes: Strategy Guru Michael Porter's Monitor Group Bankrupt</title><description>Català: Michael Porter. Česky: Michael Porter. Dansk: Michael Porter. Deutsch: Michael Porter. Español: Michael Porter. Suomi: Michael Porter. Bahasa Indonesia: Michael Porter. Nederlands: Michael Porter. ‪Norsk (bokmål)â¬: Michael Porter. Polski: Michael E. Porter. Português: Michael Porter. Српски / Srpski: Majkl Porter. Svenska: Michael [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7448-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7448_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:32:27">http://www.forbes.com/sites/toddessig/2013/05/03/on-boylston-street-lessons-learned-at-the-boston-marathon-makeshift-memorial/</link><title>On Boylston Street: Lessons Learned At The Boston Marathon 'Makeshift' Memorial</title><description>Weeping Willow &amp; Pond at Boston Common (Photo credit: Jill Clardy) I just spent 4 days in Boston, at a conference titled “Global Psychoanalysis in a Social World.” The timing, so soon after the Marathon and lockdown, was a total coincidence. Nevertheless, what happened was still on everyone’s mind. Many talks [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7448-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7448_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:33:05">http://www.forbes.com/sites/bobcook/2011/12/07/excessive-excessive-celebration-penalties-are-a-pox-on-football-no-matter-what-bob-costas-says/</link><title>Excessive Celebration Penalties Are a Pox on Football, No Matter What Bob Costas Says</title><description>VideoThis is Billy "White Shoes" Johnson. If the 1970s-1980s-era NFL kick returner, the forefather of Devin Hester, was not the inventor of the end zone dance, he most certainly was the one who made it popular. Let's put it this way: my friends and I in North Muskegon, Mich., far from [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7448-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7448_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:33:43">http://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesstylefile/2014/02/20/designer-spotlight-25bedford-redefines-the-power-suit/</link><title>Designer Spotlight: 25Bedford Redefines The Power Suit</title><description>Leave it to a busy working mom to take a stand and lead the workwear revolution. Kudos. Keri McCarthy Ferry, founder of 25Bedford, is on a mission with her new online apparel brand to disrupt the corporate dress code in the best of ways by making getting dressed for work exciting [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7448-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7448_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:34:17">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kellyclay/2013/12/29/what-social-media-managers-need-to-know-about-facebook-in-2014/</link><title>What Social Media Managers Need To Know About Facebook In 2014</title><description>For many of us, it's hard to believe that 2013 is almost over. It was a big year for social media, as Twitter went public, Snapchat rejected a $3B offer from Facebook and the emergence of mobile as a primary device caused advertisers to scramble to reach their target audiences [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7448-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7448_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:35:02">http://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestravelguide/2012/03/01/americas-10-best-cities-for-runners/</link><title>America's 10 Best Cities For Runners</title><description>Forbes Travel Guides chooses the 10 best cities for runners to lace up and hit the road.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7448-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7448_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:35:28">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jjcolao/2012/11/01/newly-minted-billionaire-is-spinning-ebay-scraps-into-gold/</link><title>Newly-Minted Billionaire Is Spinning eBay Scraps Into Gold</title><description>Michael Rubin was running a real business at 14 and a public company at 23. Now 40, he has just become one of America?s youngest billionaires through entrepreneurial frenzy--and the ability to turn eBay scraps into the greatest deal you've never heard about. Watch out, Amazon. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7448-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7448_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:36:00">http://www.forbes.com/sites/tomvanriper/2013/10/22/want-to-make-those-day-care-bucks-teach-soccer/</link><title>Want To Make Those Day Care Bucks? Teach Soccer.</title><description>Gustavo Szulansky, an Argentinian-turned-New Yorker, has grown his Super Soccer Stars chain into 200 locations since 2000, with more to come. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>