<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7450">thailand individual travel</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:37:58" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7450-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7450_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:37:59">http://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestravelguide/2013/10/08/forbes-travel-guide-hot-20/</link><title>Forbes Travel Guide Hot 20</title><description>Where to be now in North America. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7450-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7450_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:38:47">http://www.forbes.com/sites/suzynam/2013/07/03/tourism-ipos-boost-fortunes-of-thailands-richest/</link><title>Tourism, IPOs Boost Fortunes Of Thailand's Richest</title><description>Record number of tourists are a boon for Thailand's richest. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7450-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7450_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:39:35">http://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesasia/2013/10/15/asias-travel-business-holiday-inn-targets-china-and-southeast-asia/</link><title>Asia's Travel Business: Holiday Inn Targets China and Southeast Asia</title><description>From China to India, millions of cost-conscious travelers are on the move in Asia. Here's how Holiday Inn Express set out to win this market. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7450-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7450_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:40:48">http://www.forbes.com/sites/morganhartley/2013/06/10/the-brutal-business-of-child-boxing-in-thailand/</link><title>The Brutal Business Of Child Boxing In Thailand</title><description>Chai in the red corner, moments before the start of his fight. Photos by Morgan Hartley Fight Night – 10:40PM Under the bright florescent lights of the boxing ring, the boy could barely see out beyond the elastic ropes that surrounded the fighting stage; the crowd and the festival that pressed in around [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7450-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7450_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:41:38">http://www.forbes.com/sites/nextavenue/2014/04/09/boomers-feed-growing-wellness-vacation-industry/</link><title>Boomers Feed Growing Wellness Vacation Industry</title><description>Trips to get your body and mind fit are popular, especially among boomers. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7450-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7450_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:42:14">http://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestravelguide/2013/08/14/five-international-dishes-to-try-in-london/</link><title>Five International Dishes To Try In London</title><description>London is one of the most multicultural destinations in the world: There are more than 300 languages spoken in the city, with foreign-born residents accounting for a third of the population—not to mention all the Londoners of foreign descent. The British capital is a cultural melting pot. This diverse range of [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7450-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7450_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:42:59">http://www.forbes.com/sites/simonmontlake/2012/01/20/in-thailand-a-rare-peek-at-his-majestys-balance-sheet/</link><title>In Thailand, A Rare Peek At His Majesty's Balance Sheet</title><description>Image by AFP via @daylife Thailand's King Bhumibol, who turned 84 last December, is the world's longest serving ruler. He is also the richest - by a comfortable margin. Last year Forbes estimated his net wealth in excess of $30 billion, beating oil-rich Brunei's Sultan Bolkiah into second place. A gaggle [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7450-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7450_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:44:19">http://www.forbes.com/sites/larryolmsted/2014/04/08/10-high-profile-luxury-hotel-openings-for-2014/</link><title>10 High Profile Luxury Hotel Openings For 2014</title><description>If you enjoys creature comforts and standout service when you travel, there are a number of new hotels debuting this year that you might want to keep on your radar read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7450-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7450_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:45:02">http://www.forbes.com/sites/larryolmsted/2011/08/14/todays-top-luxury-travel-trends/</link><title>Today's Top Luxury Travel Trends</title><description>The two biggest trends here are the return to travelers planning trips well in advance, while the past few years have seen much shorter lead times and last minute bookings, and the emergence (finally) of South America as a hot destination. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7450-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7450_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:46:12">http://www.forbes.com/sites/dominiqueafacan/2014/03/12/luxperience-with-lindy-andrews/</link><title>Luxperience With Lindy Andrews</title><description>Lindy Andrews is the Australian CEO of Luxperience, a high-end experiential travel event taking place in Sydney this August. I caught up with Lindy at the recent Luxperience London pop-up to quiz her about the latest travel trends and must-do destinations for 2014. Sum up Luxperience in a nutshell. Luxperience is the [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>