<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7451">buy animal farm</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:47:12" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7451-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7451_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:47:13">http://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesasia/2013/11/20/animal-lover/</link><title>Low Tuck Kwong Saves the Animals</title><description>Billionaire Low Tuck Kwong has a special hobby--his own private zoo. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7451-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7451_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:47:54">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jamesmcwilliams/2013/10/23/small-free-range-egg-producers-cant-escape-problems-of-factory-farms/</link><title>Small, Free-Range Egg Producers Can't Escape Problems Of Factory Farms</title><description>Conscientious consumers often assume that eggs sourced from small farms are eggs that are immune to the problems facing factory farms. This is not always the case. Pastured hens raised on small farms commonly suffer from predation, disease, welfare abuse, and over-medication. The alternatives to factory farming may, in the end, turn out to require [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7451-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7451_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:48:55">http://www.forbes.com/sites/timworstall/2013/07/05/if-farming-vicuna-saves-them-from-extinction-then-shouldnt-we-farm-elephants-and-tigers-too/</link><title>If Farming Vicuna Saves Them From Extinction Then Shouldn't We Farm Elephants And Tigers Too?</title><description>This little story about a property purchase in Argentina set me thinking: The 330 square miles (85,000 hectares) of high altitude grassland and mountain peaks are valuable to Loro Piana because they are home to 6,000 vicuna, whose “golden fleeces” provide the super-soft wool that the company uses to read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7451-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7451_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:49:59">http://www.forbes.com/sites/nadiaarumugam/2013/05/31/illegal-genetically-modified-wheat-found-in-oregon-farm-should-we-be-worried/</link><title>Illegal Genetically Modified Wheat Found In Oregon Farm: Should We Be Worried?</title><description>Unlike specially developed herbicide-tolerant and insecticide- resistant corn, cotton, and soy varieties grown prolifically in the United States, Wheat. (Photo credit: Wikipedia) genetically modified wheat has not been approved by the Food and Drug Administration. In fact, GM wheat isn't approved anywhere in the world. Despite this, a farmer in [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7451-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7451_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:50:22">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ashleaebeling/2012/06/06/how-to-farm-for-love-and-profit-and-save-the-farm/</link><title>How To Farm For Love And Profit--And Save The Farm</title><description>A photographic book of a Bucks County farm underscores the importance of farmland preservation.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7451-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7451_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:51:15">http://www.forbes.com/2010/09/07/animal-rights-farming-2020-opinions-contributors-peter-singer.html</link><title>Animal Advocates Surpass NRA In Political Influence</title><description>Farm animals will enjoy more rights than ever before. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7451-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7451_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:52:41">http://www.forbes.com/sites/gerganakoleva/2011/12/16/applegate-farms-amplifies-appeals-for-antibiotic-free-food/</link><title>Applegate Farms Amplifies Appeals for Antibiotic-Free Food</title><description>Video Three out of four Americans want government to do something to curb overuse of antibiotics on animal farms that supply most of the nation's meat, and nearly as many believe the rise of antibiotic-resistant bacteria - "superbugs" - as a result of the misuse is a serious threat to human [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7451-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7451_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:53:34">http://www.forbes.com/sites/bethhoffman/2012/11/19/all-natural-turkeys-one-huge-reason-to-buy-them/</link><title>'All Natural' Turkeys? One Huge Reason to Buy Them</title><description>There is a good chance you splurged this holiday and bought the 'all natural' turkey for your family.  More and more, consumers are wanting better, healthier food for their families and are willing to pay for it. But are "all natural" foods actually better? The survey says: consumers don't trust company labels A [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7451-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7451_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:54:01">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kerryhannon/2011/11/16/how-to-buy-a-racehorse/</link><title>How to Buy a Racehorse</title><description>“You would be an idiot to get into a racing partnership strictly as an investment,” drawls Campbell. “It’s the kind of thing that could shoot the moon and have incredible returns, but you’d better not count on it. The pleasure aspect has got to be strong. It’s a speculative deal. It’s something that might make money. It’s got good tax benefits if [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7451-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7451_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:54:40">http://www.forbes.com/2009/09/02/farm-agriculture-commodities-intelligent-investing-fertilizer.html</link><title>The State Of The Farm</title><description>The recession is hitting the American farm. Agricultural investments likely reflect these dismal numbers already. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>