<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7453">pc 2 games reviews</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:56:46" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7453-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7453_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:56:46">http://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2014/04/07/luftrausers-review-pc-mac-playstation-3-ps-vita-raus-party/</link><title>'Luftrausers' Review (PC, Mac, PlayStation 3, PS Vita) - Raus Party</title><description>Luftrausers, a hardcore, retro-styled physics-based shooter, puts the player in the cockpit of one of over a hundred possible buildouts of an experimental combat jet launched by a Ruritanian enemy against overwhelming. Using torpedoes, missiles, lasers or good old-fashioned giant, slow-moving arcade-game bullets, your mission is to kill, and kill, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7453-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7453_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:57:28">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonevangelho/2014/04/10/mad-catz-freq-4d-gaming-headphones-with-vivitouch-review/</link><title>Mad Catz FREQ 4D Gaming Headphones With ViviTouch Review</title><description>I've been a vocal evangelist for ViviTouch, a new haptic technology which elevates audio to crazy levels of immersion. Now Mad Catz has the distinction of being the first company to bring the technology to retail via their F.R.E.Q. 4D headphones. Do they deliver the magic? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7453-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7453_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:57:54">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonevangelho/2014/04/08/radeon-r9-295x2-review-amd-delivers-on-a-promise-with-exciting-liquid-cooled-gpu/</link><title>Radeon R9 295X2 Review: AMD Delivers On A Promise With Exciting Liquid-Cooled GPU</title><description>With the liquid cooled Radeon R9 295x2, AMD has delivered an exciting 4K-capable graphics card for PC gaming enthusiasts. They're also delivering on some important promises. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7453-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7453_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:58:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2014/03/31/out-there-review-ios-android-lost-in-space-perdu-en-espace/</link><title>'Out There' Review (iOS, Android) - Roguelikelike Lost In Space</title><description>Out there, by the French studio mi-clos, offers a solitary, existential and attractively simple vision of being lost in deep space. Can its quiet charms keep players hooked? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7453-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7453_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 14:59:03">http://www.forbes.com/sites/antonyleather/2014/03/12/msi-gt60-2pe-dominator-pro-gaming-laptop-review-a-2500-pc-killer-with-an-ultra-hd-screen/</link><title>MSI GT60 2PE Dominator Pro Gaming Laptop Review: A $2,500 PC-Killer With An Ultra HD Screen</title><description>Gaming laptops can represent something of a false economy. Compared to desktops, gamers generally get far less performance per buck for the simple reason so much more time and effort goes in to cramming some seriously powerful hardware into such a small place. However, there are still plenty of reasons you [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7453-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7453_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:00:24">http://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2013/12/16/world-of-warplanes-review-pc/</link><title>'World Of Warplanes' Review (PC)</title><description>Video The free-to-play MMO World of Warplanes is the high-flying follow-up to Wargaming’s World of Tanks. World of Warplanes continues the trend of placing players in historically accurate weapons of war, with faster-paced combat than Tanks and a progression system that allows players to build up an expansive hangar of highly customizable [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7453-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7453_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:00:52">http://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2014/03/11/titanfall-review-xbox-one-the-iron-giant/</link><title>'Titanfall' Review (Xbox One): The Iron Giant</title><description>VideoSpeed. It's been missing from the competitive FPS genre since the days of Quake. Call of Duty lets you sprint for mere seconds at a time. Gears of War has you run only when it leads to hiding behind a wall. Halo allows more mobility in the form of a power-armor [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7453-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7453_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:02:01">http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidewalt/2014/03/04/south-park-the-stick-of-truth-review/</link><title>'South Park: The Stick of Truth' Review</title><description>It's the most disgusting, deliberately offensive mass-market video game ever made... and also a joy to play.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7453-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7453_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:02:35">http://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2014/03/25/diablo-3-reaper-of-souls-review-through-the-fire-and-flames/</link><title>'Diablo 3: Reaper of Souls' Review: Through The Fire And Flames</title><description>VideoThe release of Diablo 3's expansion, Reaper of Souls, represents the culmination of what might be one of the most dramatic quality turnarounds in gaming history. When the original Diablo 3 launched, though it improved on some aspects of its immortal predecessor, it was mostly heralded as a huge disappointment. Loot, [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7453-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7453_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:03:22">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonevangelho/2014/03/12/its-actually-cheaper-to-buy-digital-storms-new-gaming-pc-than-to-build-it-yourself/</link><title>It's Actually Cheaper To Buy Digital Storm's New Gaming PC Than To Build It Yourself</title><description>In a sure sign that the world is ending -- or that perhaps a boutique PC vendor is actually making use of economies of scale to benefit their customers -- Digital Storm's newly released Vanquish II gaming rig is cheaper to buy off the shelf than it is to build yourself. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>