<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7456">gps reviews</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:06:20" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7456-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7456_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:06:20">http://www.forbes.com/sites/joefolkman/2013/10/29/understanding-feedback-the-gps-direction-to-leadership-success/</link><title>Understanding Feedback: The 'GPS Direction' To Leadership Success</title><description>One of the most frustrating parts of getting feedback from others is that perceptions of bosses are often much different than the perspective of peers and direct reports. From an individual’s perspective, they see themselves as behaving very consistently, but the ratings from others can be present a dramatically different [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7456-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7456_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:07:02">http://www.forbes.com/sites/sethporges/2013/12/08/review-how-smart-is-toshibas-mammoth-new-tv/</link><title>Review: How Smart Is Toshiba's Mammoth New TV?</title><description>The Pitch: The 65-inch Toshiba 65L7300U promises a seriously slim 1080p TV that pulls in an Internet's worth of streaming content and apps thanks to its "cloud TV" platform. The Truth: I've long been a skeptic of smart TVs. Not the concept behind an Internet-enabled television—that's been a inevitability for a few years now—but the idea [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7456-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7456_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:08:28">http://www.forbes.com/sites/danielnyegriffiths/2013/12/02/city-cynic-against-the-smart-city-by-adam-greenfield-review/</link><title>City Cynic: 'Against The Smart City' By Adam Greenfield (Review)</title><description>In 'Against the smart city', networks expert and urbanist Adam Greenfield cuts into the vision of the smart city, and has some choice words for its conception as a closed-source, ground-up pleasuredome for the technically and economically empowered. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7456-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7456_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:09:29">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonfogelson/2013/12/04/2013-suzuki-burgman-650-abs-test-drive-and-review-the-scooter-for-motorcyclists/</link><title>2013 Suzuki Burgman 650 ABS Test Drive And Review: The Scooter For Motorcyclists?</title><description>Is it time to trade in your cruiser for a mega scooter? The Suzuki Burgman 650 ABS is here to tempt you.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7456-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7456_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:11:04">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonfogelson/2013/10/23/2014-indian-chieftain-ride-and-review-indian-rides-again/</link><title>2014 Indian Chieftain Ride And Review: Indian Rides Again</title><description>Indian Motorcycle is back from the dead. Contributing Writer Jason Fogelson took a spin on the 2014 Indian Chieftain, an exciting new touring bike.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7456-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7456_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:11:46">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonevangelho/2013/07/30/skyrim-in-bed-the-nvidia-shield-review/</link><title>Skyrim In Bed: The NVIDIA SHIELD Review</title><description>SHIELD is a daring proposition fueled by a split personality. It's NVIDIA's flagship Tegra 4 device, a dedicated Android gaming console, and a machine promising ultra-low latency wireless streaming of your PC games to any room in the house. As a complete package, is it a success? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7456-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7456_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:12:17">http://www.forbes.com/sites/quora/2013/03/13/what-do-you-think-of-the-new-chromebook-pixel/</link><title>Review of Chromebook Pixel</title><description>What do you think of the new Chromebook Pixel? This was originally posted on Quora by Michael Wolfe. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7456-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7456_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:12:54">http://www.forbes.com/sites/carolpinchefsky/2013/03/09/tomb-raider-2013-review/</link><title>Tomb Raider (2013): Review</title><description>“I hate tombs,” Lara Croft says as she’s standing in the middle of, whaddya know, a tomb. Although we’ve seen many a crypt in her future, Lara in Tomb Raider (2013) is a younger, more squeamish version of herself in this thoroughly enjoyable origin story. Our tomb raider is almost a tomb afraider. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7456-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7456_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:13:34">http://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2012/10/22/forza-horizon-review/</link><title>'Forza Horizon' Review</title><description>If you enjoyed Burnout Paradise but craved that experience with insanely gorgeous scenery and real-world handling, Forza Horizon is an instant recommendation. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7456-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7456_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:14:20">http://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2013/03/05/tomb-raider-review-a-conquering-croft/</link><title>Tomb Raider Review: A Conquering Croft</title><description>This is Tomb Raider, but Lara Croft is not Lara Croft. She’s shivering and cold, alone on an island swarming with amorphous evil. She has a weak bow, a scavenged radio and nothing more. Shadows are everywhere. You can only feel so bad for her, though, because this is a [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>