<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7457">the music man lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:15:12" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7457-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7457_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:15:13">http://www.forbes.com/sites/natalierobehmed/2014/04/16/the-lyrical-portfolios-of-hip-hops-wealthiest-artists/</link><title>The Lyrical Portfolios Of Hip-Hop's Wealthiest Artists</title><description>From Beats by Dre to Roc Nation Sports, the portfolios of the Forbes Five include a diverse range of investments. But what would these artists’ portfolios look like if they reflected the assets most frequently mentioned in verse? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7457-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7457_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:16:18">http://www.forbes.com/sites/maxrobins/2013/11/19/les-brown-the-man-who-wrote-the-encyclopedia-of-television/</link><title>Les Brown: The Man Who Wrote 'The Encyclopedia of Television'</title><description>He was a pioneer in demystifying the business of TV and predicted the digital revolution. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7457-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7457_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:17:23">http://www.forbes.com/sites/walterpavlo/2013/08/28/singing-a-tune-from-federal-prison-karey-lees-music-hits-the-charts/</link><title>Singing A Tune From Federal Prison, Karey Lee's Music Hits The Charts</title><description>From federal prison, Karey Lee Woolsey has released an album of songs he recorded before starting a prison term of nearly 13 years. Billboard Biz likes the sound of his tune, and so will you. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7457-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7457_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:18:26">http://www.forbes.com/sites/moneybuilder/2011/03/03/10-money-lessons-from-music-lyrics/</link><title>10 Money Lessons from Music Lyrics</title><description>This post provided by GetRichSlowly.org. When you're looking for personal finance advice, you probably check out books and websites like GRS, but what about turning on the radio? Recently, I wrote about the cost of love and mentioned several songs with lyrics about love and money. This got me thinking about how [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7457-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7457_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:19:34">http://www.forbes.com/sites/zackomalleygreenburg/2013/06/26/toby-keith-cowboy-capitalist-countrys-500-million-man/</link><title>Toby Keith, Cowboy Capitalist: Country's $500 Million Man</title><description>Country superstar Toby Keith has some of the most loyal fans in music. And he owns enough product extensions to make sure they're also some of the most lucrative. Personal earnings so far: $500 million. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7457-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7457_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:20:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/nickmessitte/2014/02/28/g-i-r-l-meets-n-e-r-d-the-second-adolescence-of-pharrell/</link><title>G I R L meets N.E.R.D. - The Second Adolescence of Pharrell</title><description>Given that G I R L offers nothing new in terms of production, structure, or attitude (and given a plethora of other artists offering fresher approaches in all three arenas) why is this record poised to do so well? Why is Pharrell having such a moment? It can’t just be that hat, right? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7457-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7457_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:21:03">http://www.forbes.com/sites/arieladams/2014/02/13/why-talented-master-watchmakers-dedicate-their-lives-to-the-art/</link><title>Why Talented Master Watchmakers Dedicate Their Lives To The Art</title><description>In the world of high-end watchmaking there are men and women who make the pursuit of horology something intellectual and very interesting as opposed to the mere collection of luxury status items. Watchmaking has always been at heart a scientific endeavor, but one that has been mixed with art forms as well as the high-profile nature of producing [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7457-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7457_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:22:04">http://www.forbes.com/sites/karlshmavonian/2012/07/27/thoughts-on-country-western-music-and-the-hank-williams-syndrome/</link><title>Thoughts On Country &amp;amp; Western Music and the Hank Williams Syndrome</title><description>From left to right Kris Kristofferson, Johnny Cash, Waylon Jennings, Willie Nelson, who formed the country music supergroup, The Highwaymen (Photo credit: Wikipedia) Our theme for the Thoughts page this time is Country &amp; Western music, inspired by a Mar. 2, 1992 FORBES cover story, featuring Garth Brooks, on the growing [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7457-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7457_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:23:28">http://www.forbes.com/sites/zackomalleygreenburg/2012/10/19/power-of-music-part-2-lupe-fiasco-and-the-business-of-conscious-rap/</link><title>Power of Music Part 2: Lupe Fiasco And The Business Of 'Conscious Rap'</title><description>Fiasco is proof that musicians don’t need to fill their lyrics with empty words and clichés to be successful, and that it’s possible to make a healthy living on ‘conscious’ rap. As far as he’s concerned, making music with a message can differentiate an artist--and often, it makes them more commercially viable, not less.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7457-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7457_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:24:19">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ruthblatt/2013/11/04/lou-reed-and-the-problem-with-the-innovation-imperative/</link><title>Lou Reed And The Problem With The Innovation Imperative</title><description>People usually think it’s best to be the first to hit the market with a disruptive innovation. But more often than not, the advantages don’t pan out. The career of the late Lou Reed reveals the dark side of the innovation imperative and the disadvantages that come with being a first mover. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>