<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7458">rice recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:25:05" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7458-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7458_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:25:06">http://www.forbes.com/sites/michellemaisto/2012/04/30/from-brownies-to-pasta-8-recipes-for-eating-more-beans/</link><title>From Brownies to Pasta, 8 Recipes for Eating More Beans</title><description>Heidi Swanson promises that neither these Amazing Black Bean Brownies nor these Marathon Cookies (with navy beans, great northerns or white kidney beans) actually taste like beans. I believe her. But I still plan to find out for myself. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7458-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7458_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:25:49">http://www.forbes.com/sites/carolpinchefsky/2012/09/13/four-guild-wars-2-recipes-you-can-craft-in-your-kitchen/</link><title>Four 'Guild Wars 2' Recipes You Can Craft in Your Kitchen</title><description>I'm enjoying Guild Wars 2 (GW2) for its gorgeous graphics and its non-stop adventure. But playing GW2 has resulted in a strange side effect: It's making me hungry. That's because whenever I use the discovery tab to find new recipes, I think, "Mmm...tasty." read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7458-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7458_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:27:16">http://www.forbes.com/sites/nadiaarumugam/2011/09/08/the-rise-of-rice-new-yorks-eateries-dedicated-to-the-grain/</link><title>The Rise of Rice: New York Eateries Dedicated to the Grain</title><description>September is National Rice Month. 21 years ago the USA Rice Federation petitioned for the honor in recognition of the importance of the grain to the US, and to celebrate its role in the nation's diet. And quite a role it plays too. The average American chows down on 25 [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7458-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7458_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:28:22">http://www.forbes.com/2006/07/27/bbq-recipe-summer-cz_rm_0727food.html</link><title>Summer Barbecue Recipes</title></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7458-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7458_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:29:05">http://www.forbes.com/sites/williamarruda/2013/09/25/the-one-thing-that-will-destroy-your-brand/</link><title>The One Thing That Will Destroy Your Brand</title><description>This one thing will destroy your brand. Many strong personal brands have done major damage to their success by violating their brand promise. Learn how you can avoid a major brand disaster. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7458-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7458_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:30:23">http://www.forbes.com/sites/michellemaisto/2012/01/27/ultimate-comfort-food-or-healthy-boost-for-picky-eaters/</link><title>Ultimate Comfort Food, Or Healthy Boost for Picky Eaters?</title><description>Since its nutritional impact can be easily dialed up, rice pudding makes a perfect toddler food. Or more specifically: a perfect food for picky eaters. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7458-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7458_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:31:20">http://www.forbes.com/sites/nextavenue/2012/11/19/the-ghosts-of-thanksgivings-past/</link><title>The Ghosts Of Thanksgivings Past</title><description>(Photo credit: QUOI Media) This Thanksgiving holiday, seven Next Avenue staffers will take a look around the table, cherishing the moment and feasting on memories, despite the absence of someone or something special. And one will skip the gathering altogether. By Suzanne Gerber, Next Avenue Living &amp; Learning Editor My father was born [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7458-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7458_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:31:58">http://www.forbes.com/sites/theyec/2014/02/27/increase-your-business-performance-by-treating-your-body-better/</link><title>Increase Your Business Performance By Treating Your Body Better</title><description>Entrepreneurs have a tendency to leave the basics -- like good nutrition -- off of their to-do lists. But a few simple shifts over time can impact your body and your business. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7458-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7458_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:33:30">http://www.forbes.com/sites/juliewilcox/2012/08/07/the-triumph-of-tofu/</link><title>The Triumph Of Tofu</title><description>Although there has been controversy over whether or not tofu is healthy for us, this soy product is taking front stage in the world of edible delights. Last week, tofu made The New York Times most popular food articles, which I was happy to see. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7458-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7458_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:34:06">http://www.forbes.com/sites/moneybuilder/2012/02/29/want-to-save-on-groceries-cook-like-a-peasant/</link><title>Want to Save on Groceries? Cook like a Peasant</title><description>Image via Wikipedia Ever notice how most cultures have their own take on rice? Risotto in Italy, Spanish rice in Mexico, dirty rice in New Orleans, paella in Spain — all filling dishes that can satisfy a family with just a few ingredients. In fact, it could be argued that [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>