<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7463">hollywood actress</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:54:57" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7463-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7463_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:54:58">http://www.forbes.com/sites/trulia/2014/02/06/actress-jordana-brewster-selling-hollywood-home-once-owned-by-ellen-degeneres/</link><title>Actress Jordana Brewster Selling Hollywood Home Once Owned By Ellen Degeneres</title><description>‘The Fast and the Furious’ actress Jordana Brewster is selling her stunning Hollywood home for $3,795,000. Property records show that the Brazilian-American actress paid $3,375,000 for the 3 bedroom, 4 bathroom, 2,868 square foot architectural stunner in March 2011. Long before Brewster called the place home, Ellen DeGeneres walked the halls of [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7463-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7463_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:55:39">http://www.forbes.com/sites/judebrennan/2014/02/23/hollywood-swine-skewers-hollywood/</link><title>Hollywood &amp;amp; Swine Skewers Hollywood</title><description>More than a few movie moguls and mega-stars have slammed into the intersection of Hollywood &amp; Swine – the home of more EXCLUSIVES than any entertainment news site in history – particularly at Oscar time. There’s a reason for that. It’s the Onion of the showbiz world. Peel back the layers [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7463-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7463_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:56:22">http://www.forbes.com/sites/emc/2014/04/02/big-data-predicts-big-winners/</link><title>EMC​Voice: Big Data Predicts Big Winners In Sports, Politics And Hollywood</title><description>By Erin Richey How did your Academy Awards pool turn out this year? Did you accurately predict Jared Leto for Best Supporting Actor and Cate Blanchett for Best Actress? Chances are if you laid your bets based on data from past award ceremonies, social media and prediction markets, your picks won. Big [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7463-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7463_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:57:29">http://www.forbes.com/sites/zillow/2014/03/31/jodie-foster-cuts-price-on-hollywood-hills-abode/</link><title>Jodie Foster Cuts Price On Hollywood Hills Abode</title><description>While not exactly Greta Garbo, Hollywood stalwart Jodie Foster has made as much of a career of her privacy as she has as a lifelong model, actress and director. Now the 51-year-old Yale grad is in the spotlight – and not only for speculation about whether the new gold band she’s [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7463-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7463_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:58:14">http://www.forbes.com/video/3118057018001/</link><title>Glenn Close On Hollywood Today</title><description>The veteran actress of film and television shares her excitement about the way the entertainment industry has, and continues, to evolve.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7463-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7463_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 15:58:34">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kellyphillipserb/2012/09/10/when-politics-and-hollywood-intersect-actress-tweets-tax-policy-among-criticism/</link><title>When Politics and Hollywood Intersect: Actress Tweets Tax Policy Among Criticism</title><description>Actress Lindsay Lohan. Photo by Rafael Amado Deras. (Photo credit: Wikipedia) From Clint Eastwood to Scarlett Johansson, the 2012 presidential election is quickly becoming a celebrity studded affair. At both the Republican and Democratic conventions, celebrities stood up for their preferred candidate with albeit mixed reviews. Celebs have been [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7463-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7463_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:03:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jerryjao/2014/03/03/entrepreneurial-lessons-from-the-oscars/</link><title>Can Hollywood Teach Entrepreneurs A Thing Or Two?</title><description>Ahh…the Academy Awards. Undoubtedly the biggest night in Hollywood (and, apparently, Twitter), the ceremony brings together some of the most talented and entertaining people in the world. As I watched the Oscars unfold, the businessperson in me couldn’t help but think that it’s more than just a showbiz event. There [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7463-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7463_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:03:54">http://www.forbes.com/sites/dorothypomerantz/2014/02/16/why-ellen-page-coming-out-matters-in-hollywood/</link><title>Why Ellen Page Coming Out Matters In Hollywood</title><description>As more young stars come out, society will change with them. Hollywood needs more Ellen Pages.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7463-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7463_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:05:00">http://www.forbes.com/sites/michaellee/2014/02/14/how-hollywood-is-teaching-madison-avenue-a-lesson-in-marketing/</link><title>How Hollywood Is Teaching Madison Avenue A Lesson In Marketing.</title><description>I’ve been impressed recently in how Hollywood has been showing off some innovative marketing savvy and creativity when launching its latest movies. And I’m sure those launches are getting more than a few envious glances from the madmen and women of Madison Avenue. Beyond getting the stars of the movie or [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7463-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7463_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:05:57">http://www.forbes.com/sites/work-in-progress/2013/11/20/3-marketing-lessons-from-hollywood/</link><title>3 Marketing Lessons From Hollywood</title><description>Learn critical marketing lessons from Hollywood that apply to all businesses via producer and founder of Ambush Entertainment and Cold Iron Pictures, Miranda Bailey. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>