<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7470">is sugar poison</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:22:07" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7470-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7470_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:22:08">http://www.forbes.com/sites/timworstall/2013/08/04/a-new-front-opens-in-the-war-against-big-sugar/</link><title>A New Front Opens In The War Against Big Sugar</title><description>Sadly, this time it seems to be my native Britain that is being taken in by the propaganda. You know, this idea that sugar is uniquely evil, that in fact it's the fructose that's the really bad part of it and we must therefore tax, tax, tax in order to [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7470-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7470_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:22:56">http://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesleadershipforum/2013/06/21/why-the-amas-obesity-ruling-is-bad-medicine/</link><title>Why The AMA's Obesity Ruling Is Bad Medicine</title><description>This article is by Hank Cardello, a senior fellow at the Hudson Institute, a consultant on socially responsible products and practices, and the author of Stuffed: An Insider’s Look at Who’s (Really) Making America Fat. Darker states have higher obesity rates. (Photo credit: Wikipedia) The American Medical Association’s announcement this week that [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7470-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7470_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:23:25">http://www.forbes.com/sites/patrickmichaels/2014/04/11/obamacare-for-lunch/</link><title>Obamacare For Lunch?</title><description>We’re about to be fed a diet of political correctness. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7470-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7470_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:24:10">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ptc/2014/03/28/becoming-cyborgs-ear-based-wearable-tech-disrupts-healthcare/</link><title>PTC​Voice: Becoming Cyborgs: Wearable Tech Disrupts Healthcare</title><description>By Lydia Leavitt Health and healthcare have typically been a personal relationship between doctors and patients – kept private and behind closed doors. More recently, however, healthcare is being opened up by technology.  Medical questions are crowdsourced, records are electronic and doctors are connected directly with their patients –  before, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7470-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7470_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:25:55">http://www.forbes.com/sites/tommytomlinson/2013/11/27/alabama-vs-auburn-the-biggest-and-craziest-college-football-game-of-the-year/</link><title>Alabama Vs. Auburn: The Biggest (And Craziest) College Football Game Of The Year</title><description>The Auburn-Alabama game might decide this year's national title. But they're playing for something even bigger: Bragging rights in the state. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7470-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7470_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:27:08">http://www.forbes.com/sites/emilywillingham/2013/06/25/8-foods-the-usa-bans-but-other-nations-dont/</link><title>8 Foods The USA Bans But Other Nations Don't</title><description>Many factors that have nothing to do with scientific evidence drive decisions to ban or not to ban, and the US is really no better or worse than other similar nations as a watchdog for its people. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7470-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7470_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:28:06">http://www.forbes.com/2009/09/16/commodities-inflation-hedge-personal-finance-financial-investing-ideas-crude-oil.html</link><title>Choose The Right Commodities</title><description>Commodity investments may be an effective antidote for inflation, but take some time to pick your poison. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7470-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7470_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:28:57">http://www.forbes.com/2008/12/23/vodka-scotch-spirits-forbeslife-cx_ea_1223spirits_slide.html</link><title>In Depth: What The World Drinks</title><description>Where you live has a lot to do with what poison you prefer.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7470-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7470_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:29:35">http://www.forbes.com/sites/wlf/2013/03/18/desperate-to-foment-new-regulations-lawsuits-activists-ratchet-up-food-addiction-campaign/</link><title>Desperate To Foment New Regulations &amp;amp; Lawsuits, Activists Ratchet Up 'Food Addiction' Campaign</title><description>A woman takes a drink from a 26-ounce Caramel Frappuccino at a Starbucks on the Upper East Side of New York City March 11, 2013. (Image credit: AFP/Getty Images via @daylife) At a time when all their attempts to impose "sin taxes," more regulation of advertising, and bans on certain [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7470-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7470_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:30:23">http://www.forbes.com/sites/peterlipson/2013/02/12/prisoners-making-hooch-what-could-possibly-go-wrong/</link><title>Prisoners Making Hooch: What Could Possibly Go Wrong?</title><description>We may treat prison inmates like animals, but despite our moral biases, they are infinitely resourceful and intelligent. Just take a look how a prisoner can fashion a shank out of a styrofoam cup and toilet paper. And booze: prisoners aren't allowed to have it, of course, but that doesn't [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>