<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7475">software consultant work at home</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:42:19" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7475-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7475_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:42:20">http://www.forbes.com/sites/gregsatell/2014/03/15/now-its-the-big-time-consultants-that-are-getting-disrupted/</link><title>Now, It's The Big Time Consultants That Are Getting Disrupted</title><description>Clients don’t always need a big sales pitch, a hefty strategic document or to be schmoozed by senior executives. Sometimes, they just need work done. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7475-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7475_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:43:17">http://www.forbes.com/sites/theapothecary/2014/01/29/surprise-massachusetts-is-home-to-americas-worst-performing-obamacare-exchange/</link><title>SURPRISE: Massachusetts Is Home To America's Worst-Performing ObamaCare Exchange</title><description>Massachusetts is struggling under ObamaCare. In the state that “inspired” the Affordable Care Act (ACA), with almost universal coverage and a functional exchange, most would assume the transition to the federal law would be largely cosmetic. Yet many BayState insiders have been surprised by the number of brick walls the state has run into during [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7475-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7475_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:44:48">http://www.forbes.com/sites/truebridge/2013/10/22/software-revolution-part-iv-computing-in-a-mobile-world/</link><title>Software Revolution, Part IV: Computing in a Mobile World</title><description>Written by Josh Manchester (This is the final installment of a four-part series discussing large technology shifts and their impact on enterprise software and venture capital investments.  Click to access Part I, Part II and Part III.) What is Mobile Computing? Of the three trends highlighted throughout this series, the shift from desktop to [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7475-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7475_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:45:20">http://www.forbes.com/sites/victoriabarret/2013/02/13/box-aaron-levie-mobile-enterprise-software/</link><title>How The Kids At Box Are Disrupting Software's Most Lucrative Game</title><description>Box cofounder Aaron Levie has a humble goal in mind: beat Microsoft and Oracle, among others, in the most lucrative game in software. With over $300 million in venture money raised and a mobile perspective on the future, the 28-year-old has a fighting chance. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7475-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7475_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:45:57">http://www.forbes.com/sites/rawnshah/2011/02/14/can-consultants-save-us-money-by-doing-more-work-remotely/</link><title>Can Consultants Save Us Money By Doing More Work Remotely?</title><description>Vinnie Mirchandani’s book, The New Polymath: Profiles in Compound Technology Innovations, is an easy-to-read guide on how personalities create breakthrough innovations by bridging multiple disciplines. In it, he talks about the rise of new multi-talented leaders, the modern equivalent of the Renaissance Man—or Renaissance Person to be more [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7475-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7475_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:46:53">http://www.forbes.com/sites/calebmelby/2013/04/03/millennials-are-redefining-work-corporations-should-take-advantage/</link><title>Millennials Are Redefining Work, Corporations Should Take Advantage</title><description>Corporations treat post-collegiate grunts as cheap labor for mind-numbing tasks. But they should take a note from startups and give Milennials space to innovate. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7475-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7475_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:48:09">http://www.forbes.com/sites/learnvest/2013/09/19/a-peek-at-my-paycheck-how-3-households-allocate-their-earnings/</link><title>A Peek At My Paycheck: How 3 Households Allocate Their Earnings</title><description>We convinced three households to bravely share every detail of their monthly budgets. How does yours compare? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7475-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7475_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:49:05">http://www.forbes.com/sites/stevedenning/2011/04/04/ge-hope-at-last-or-imagination-not-yet-at-work/</link><title>GE: Hope At Last, Or Imagination Not Yet At Work?</title><description>The prospects of a turnaround at GE depend on shifting the culture from an inside-out production perspective to an outside-in customer perspective. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7475-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7475_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:50:02">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jacquelynsmith/2014/01/15/10-high-paying-flexible-jobs-2/</link><title>10 High-Paying Flexible Jobs</title><description>Looking for a career that offers job flexibility or a fat paycheck? Here are 10 that offer both.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7475-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7475_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:50:46">http://www.forbes.com/sites/chrisversace/2014/04/01/talking-big-data-and-analytics-with-ibm/</link><title>Talking Big Data And Analytics With IBM</title><description>While many think of IBM still as a computer and cash register company, the company has been transforming itself through internal efforts and acquisitions to become a Big Data and Analytics powerhouse that is ready to engage in the Internet of Everything. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>