<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7477">china bird flu</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:59:28" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7477-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7477_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 16:59:29">http://www.forbes.com/sites/junhli/2014/04/01/kfc-china-sees-robust-recovery-from-bird-flu-and-a-catastrophic-2013/</link><title>KFC China Sees Robust Recovery from Bird Flu and a Catastrophic 2013</title><description>In March 2014,  JL Warren Capital LLC, a New York-based China focused equity research firm, surveyed hundreds of consumers outside of KFC stores in 14 cities, ranging from first- to fourth-tier cities in China. Survey results show that KFC store traffic is steadily recovering to its level in 2012. This recovery follows [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7477-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7477_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:00:28">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kenrapoza/2013/04/12/chinas-bird-flu-a-problem-for-yum-brands-co-says/</link><title>China's Bird Flu A Problem For Yum! Brands, Co Says</title><description>Yum! Brands sales in trouble from China's bird flu woes.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7477-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7477_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:00:51">http://www.forbes.com/sites/scottgottlieb/2013/04/30/were-not-prepared-for-chinas-deadly-bird-flu/</link><title>We're Not Prepared For China's Deadly Bird Flu</title><description>In Asia, more than 120 people have been sickened, and 23 are dead, from a potent strain of bird flu that has the frightening markings of a potential pandemic strain. We have grappled with deadly pockets of potent flu outbreaks before. But this one has characteristics that make it different. There’s a [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7477-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7477_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:01:40">http://www.forbes.com/sites/russellflannery/2013/04/28/china-h7n9-bird-flu-cases-rise-by-five-four-provinces-report-illnesses-in-one-day/</link><title>China H7N9 Bird Flu Cases Rise By Five; Four Provinces Report Illnesses In One Day</title><description>The number of confirmed H7N9 bird flu cases in mainland China rose by five on Sunday, the country’s official Xinhua news agency reported. Four provinces -- Zhejiang, Shandong, Jiangxi and Fujian -- reported illnesses, the agency said. Premier Li Keqiang. (Photo credit: Wikipedia) Xinhua didn't provide a total number of cases. Based on a figure [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7477-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7477_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:02:05">http://www.forbes.com/sites/russellflannery/2013/04/28/china-h7n9-bird-flu-cases-keep-rising-mainland-total-reaches-120/</link><title>China H7N9 Bird Flu Cases Keep Rising, Mainland Total Reaches 120</title><description>The number of confirmed H7N9 bird flu cases in mainland China stood at 120 as of yesterday at 7 p.m. Beijing time, according to China National Radio. The number of dead was 23. The latest case of the deadly new flu includes the first illness in Hunan Province. Cases continued to rise [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7477-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7477_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:02:48">http://www.forbes.com/sites/russellflannery/2013/05/01/china-reports-more-h7n9-bird-flu-illnesses-deaths/</link><title>China Reports More H7N9 Bird Flu Illnesses, Deaths</title><description>Another two people have died in China in connection with from H7N9 bird flu, bringing the total number of deaths to 26 as of May 1 at 4 p.m. Beijing time, the official Xinhua news agency reported. The number of confirmed H7N9 bird flu cases in the mainland rose to 127, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7477-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7477_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:03:16">http://www.forbes.com/sites/russellflannery/2013/04/25/china-reports-three-new-h7n9-bird-flu-cases-jiangxi-has-1st-suspected-illness/</link><title>China Reports Three New H7N9 Bird Flu Cases; Jiangxi Has 1st Suspected Illness</title><description>The number of confirmed  H7N9 bird flu cases in China increased by three yesterday to 111 yesterday, the official Xinhua news agency reported. The total number of dead was 23. The number of new cases continued to rise after World Health Organization officials this week concluded a trip to China and [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7477-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7477_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:04:04">http://www.forbes.com/sites/russellflannery/2013/04/15/yum-drops-2-6-after-china-poultry-stocks-pummeled-on-bird-flus-spread/</link><title>Yum! Drops 2.6% After China Poultry Stocks Pummeled On Bird Flu's Spread</title><description>Shares in Yum!, whose KFC fried-chicken chain has relied on China for much its growth in sales in recent years, dropped 2.6% in U.S. trading last night as new cases of bird flu were reported in the country over the weekend.   With H7N9 bird flu cases expanding from eastern China [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7477-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7477_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:05:05">http://www.forbes.com/sites/russellflannery/2013/04/23/h7n9-bird-flu-cases-in-china-rise-to-108-shandong-province-has-first-illness/</link><title>H7N9 Bird Flu Cases In China Rise To 108; Shandong Province Has First Illness</title><description>The number of confirmed H7N9 bird flu cases in China increased by four to 108 yesterday, the official Xinhua news agency reported. The number of dead rose by one to 22. The first case of H7N9 illness was reported in Shandong Province,  the Shanghai Daily reported today. The province is a [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7477-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7477_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:05:57">http://www.forbes.com/sites/russellflannery/2013/04/22/h7n9-bird-flu-cases-in-china-rise-to-104-deaths-at-21/</link><title>H7N9 Bird Flu Cases In China Rise To 104; Deaths At 21</title><description>The number of confirmed H7N9 bird flu cases in China increased by two to 104 during the 24-hour period through 4 p.m. on Monday, according to the official Xinhua news agency.  Twenty-one of the sick have died. The two new cases were in Zhejiang Province, which has in recent days surpassed [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>