<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7478">protect kids online</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:06:44" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7478-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7478_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:06:45">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ericgoldman/2013/09/30/californias-latest-effort-to-protect-kids-online-is-misguided-and-unconstitutional/</link><title>California's Latest Effort To 'Protect Kids Online' Is Misguided And Unconstitutional</title><description>California recently enacted SB 568 (Business &amp; Professions Code 22580) to prevent certain types of online advertising from being shown to kids. Like so many other state efforts to regulate the Internet, the new law takes an understandable regulatory objective and turns it into a sloppily drafted and misguided law [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7478-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7478_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:07:33">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ericbasu/2014/04/11/heartbleed_five_steps_to_protect/</link><title>Heartbleed - Five Steps To Protect Yourself And Your Business</title><description>Cyber security threats, including brand new threats or "zero days" often don't make the headlines, but for anyone who has been perusing the news in the last couple of days the "Heartbleed" bug has been first and foremost in the news.  There are thousands of postings on this bug in [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7478-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7478_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:08:15">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ericgoldman/2013/09/24/californias-new-online-eraser-law-should-be-erased/</link><title>California's New 'Online Eraser' Law Should Be Erased</title><description>Most laws designed to "protect kids online" are ill-conceived...including this one. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7478-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7478_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:08:41">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jordanshapiro/2014/02/22/kids-headphones-soothe-parents-headaches-protect-little-ears/</link><title>Kids' Headphones Soothe Parents' Headaches, Protect Little Ears</title><description>Sometimes a dad just wants quiet. That’s when I ask my little gamer kids to put on headphones. I write this piece with trepidation. I have to put all my idealistic recommendations about active engaged parenting aside for a moment. Sometimes I want to eat breakfast without a soundtrack of beeps [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7478-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7478_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:09:26">http://www.forbes.com/sites/northwesternmutual/2014/03/13/got-credit-helping-kids-boost-their-own-credit-score/</link><title>Northwestern Mutual​Voice: Got Credit? Helping Kids Boost Their Own Credit Score</title><description>In response to the “college credit crisis,” the Credit Card Accountability, Responsibility and Disclosure Act of 2009 took significant steps to protect students against the perils of charging away their future. However, parents must also do their part. Your children will soon be surrounded by debts—college loans, car payments and, someday, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7478-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7478_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:10:35">http://www.forbes.com/sites/clareoconnor/2014/03/05/facebook-and-instagram-introduce-new-rules-to-stem-illegal-gun-sales-online/</link><title>Facebook and Instagram Introduce New Rules To Stem Illegal Gun Sales Online</title><description>Social media giant Facebook and photo sharing subsidiary Instagram today announced new rules aimed at cutting down illegal gun sales on both platforms after months of lobbying.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7478-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7478_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:11:20">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kellyphillipserb/2013/12/29/12-days-of-charitable-giving-committee-to-protect-journalists/</link><title>12 Days Of Charitable Giving: Committee To Protect Journalists</title><description>It’s the eleventh day of our 12 Days of Charitable Giving. Our featured charity, Committee to Protect Journalists, is an independent, nonprofit organization that promotes press freedom worldwide. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7478-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7478_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:12:48">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jordanshapiro/2014/01/24/your-kids-school-may-have-the-right-to-sell-student-data/</link><title>Your Kid's School May Have The Right To Sell Student Data</title><description>How much do you really know about education in terms of data and privacy? The landscape of edtech can be confusing, ambiguous, and contradictory. A new survey from Common Sense Media points out that adults, even those without children, are “intensely concerned about using personal data to market to children, inside [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7478-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7478_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:13:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/larrymagid/2013/09/13/survey-finds-internet-users-know-theyre-not-anonymous-online-but-take-steps-to-protect-privacy/</link><title>Most Online Adults Know They're Not Anonymous But Take Steps To Protect Privacy</title><description>A recent survey from the Pew Research Center found at the more than a fifth (21%) of adults have had an email or social media account hijacked and more than a tenth (11%) have had information important information stolen, such as a social security number, credit card or bank account [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7478-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7478_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:14:35">http://www.forbes.com/sites/larrymagid/2013/08/22/teens-avoid-mobile-apps-due-to-privacy-concerns/</link><title>Teens Take Measures To Protect Mobile Privacy</title><description>Nearly half of all teens and 59% of girls have turned off location sharing A new report from the Pew Research Center and Harvard's Berkman Center provides more evidence that teens are concerned about privacy when using mobile devices. This follows last week's report that American teens care about online privacy. The [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>