<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7479">dunbar number social networks</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:15:09" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7479-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7479_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:15:09">http://www.forbes.com/sites/michaelsimmons/2014/01/02/how-big-should-your-network-be/</link><title>How Big Should Your Network Be?</title><description>There is one fundamental challenge that I - and most of the people I interview - struggle with. How do we keep in touch with an ever-growing network given our limited time and cognitive ability? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7479-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7479_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:16:08">http://www.forbes.com/sites/tjmccue/2013/01/15/social-media-maximum-150-friends/</link><title>Social Media Maximum: 150 Friends</title><description>Dunbar's Number explains that most of us can only manage 150 relationships or connections. Now, most social media platforms like LinkedIn, Facebook, Twitter, and Pinterest make the case for increasing your social network as large as you can make it. More is always better, or so it seems. University of Oxford [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7479-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7479_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:17:12">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markfidelman/2013/05/21/why-this-companys-social-platform-just-made-salespeople-a-lot-smarter/</link><title>Why This Company's Social Platform Just Made Salespeople A Lot Smarter</title><description>Surprise, annoyance, anger, exhaustion, and rejection - the 5 stages of executives hanging up the phone in a cold calling situation. Times have changed but many salespeople haven’t received the memo. In the past, sales teams have relied on cold calling as a primary method to generate leads. Another relied on [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7479-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7479_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:17:34">http://www.forbes.com/sites/mikeisaac/2010/11/14/new-social-network-path-iphone-instagram-facebook-499999950-friends/</link><title>New Social Network Path = iPhone + Instagram + Facebook - 499,999,950 Friends</title><description>Facebook alums David Morin and Sean Fanning launch a new, exclusive way of getting social. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7479-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7479_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:18:19">http://www.forbes.com/sites/georgeanders/2012/07/18/oxford-scholar-facebook-wont-widen-your-social-circle/</link><title>Oxford Scholar: Your 1,000 Friends On Facebook Are A Mirage</title><description>Robin Dunbar, the Oxford scholar who famously declared that we can only sustain 150 friends, takes a look at Facebook and declares: Even with social media, the Dunbar number doesn't go up. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7479-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7479_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:19:00">http://www.forbes.com/sites/limyunghui/2013/04/30/a-simple-app-for-a-happier-life/</link><title>A Simple App For A Happier Life</title><description>There are more social apps out there these days drawing inspiration from social science researches - and maybe rightly so. For example, Path personal network is inspired by the Dunbar's number, which is the maximum and optimum number of friends a person can sustain stable inter-personal relationship with, at any [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7479-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7479_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:20:21">http://www.forbes.com/sites/elisadoucette/2012/12/28/make-your-facebook-news-feed-stop-the-rings-and-babies/</link><title>Make Your Facebook News Feed Stop The Rings And Babies</title><description>December of 2012 may be the most engagement action my Facebook has seen since I joined the site in 2007. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7479-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7479_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:21:41">http://www.forbes.com/sites/michaelsimmons/2013/09/30/the-1-relationship-building-habit-you-should-do-daily/</link><title>The #1 Relationship Building Habit You Should Do Daily</title><description>Introductions from your network to the right clients, employees, partners, and investors can change everything. However, most people leave this up to chance. One individual has found a way to remove the randomness. Imagine hiring an employee, not providing value back (i.e., a salary), and only randomly touching base once per [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7479-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7479_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:22:15">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kashmirhill/2011/06/08/woman-tattoos-her-facebook-friends-on-her-arm/</link><title>Woman Tattoos Her Facebook Friends On Her Arm</title><description>VideoLooking for a creative tattoo idea and a way to show your friends how much they mean to you? Consider the "social tattoo" of a woman in the Netherlands. The Facebook profile photos of 152 of her closest friends are now a permanent fixture on her arm. "Of course I gave [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7479-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7479_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:23:11">http://www.forbes.com/sites/danielnyegriffiths/2011/11/30/with-a-beautiful-new-ui-where-is-path-going/</link><title>With a Beautiful New UI, Where Is Path Going?</title><description>VideoWhen Path launched in November 2010,  it had three notable elements. First, it was Dave Morin's first CEO position. As the architect of the Facebook Connect APIs, which had made it frictionlessly simple to leave comments and use services using your Facebook ID, he was most definitely a hot property in [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>