<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7482">popular twitter stars</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:33:47" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7482-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7482_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:33:48">http://www.forbes.com/sites/maurybrown/2014/04/03/red-sox-slugger-david-ortiz-tops-most-popular-mlb-jersey-sales/</link><title>Red Sox Slugger David Ortiz Tops Most-Popular MLB Jersey Sales</title><description>With Major League Baseball's 2014 season underway, here's the top 20 list of which player jerseys sold the most between the end of the 2013 World Series and the start of this season. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7482-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7482_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:34:31">http://www.forbes.com/sites/dinagachman/2014/03/31/walking-dead-finale-kids-choice-awards-rule-twitter/</link><title>Walking Dead Finale, Kids' Choice Awards Rule Twitter</title><description>The Walking Dead’s highly anticipated season finale couldn’t top Nickelodeon’s 27th Annual Kids’ Choice Awards last week. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7482-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7482_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:35:30">http://www.forbes.com/sites/maxrobins/2014/04/07/killing-off-tv-stars-churns-prime-time-gold/</link><title>Why "The Good Wife," "Scandal," And "Sons of Anarchy" Kill Stars</title><description>When TV shows such as "The Good Wife," "Sons of Anarchy," and "Scandal" kill off key cast members they kill in the ratings too. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7482-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7482_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:36:04">http://www.forbes.com/sites/briansolomon/2014/03/26/meet-the-internet-fund-avoiding-facebook-twitter-the-rest-of-bubble-2-0/</link><title>Meet The Internet Fund Avoiding Facebook, Twitter, The Rest Of Bubble 2.0</title><description>Fourteen years ago Kinetics Internet Fund crashed when the dot-com bubble burst. Now it's killing it by deftly avoiding looming dot-bombs. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7482-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7482_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:36:52">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markfidelman/2013/12/14/twitter-these-are-the-most-popular-tweets-of-2013/</link><title>Twitter: Here Are The Most Popular Tweets of 2013</title><description>Tragedy and coming of age dominated the year’s most popular tweets. Twitter released some year-end stats today, and topping the list of most re-tweeted Tweets came from Glee’s Lea Michele after reporting the loss of co-star Cory Monteith. Another significant moment occurred after Fast and Furious Actor Paul Walker passed away and a statement [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7482-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7482_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:37:18">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kurtbadenhausen/2014/03/08/can-canelo-alvarez-be-a-ppv-star-for-showtime/</link><title>Can Canelo Alvarez Be a PPV Star For Showtime?</title><description>Canelo is looking at a $6 million payday for Saturday's fight. A big PPV audience will generate millions more. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7482-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7482_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:37:46">http://www.forbes.com/sites/cedricmuhammad/2014/03/18/the-law-of-250-joe-girards-sales-strategy-wins-the-millennial-vote-not-twitter-or-facebook/</link><title>The Law of 250. Joe Girard's Sales Strategy Wins The Millennial Vote, Not Twitter Or Facebook</title><description>Although the media and political analysts are dissecting it to no end, something has been glossed over in the new Pew Research report on Millennials - the power of a magical number in life which sales guru Joe Girard identified decades ago. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7482-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7482_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:38:17">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kurtbadenhausen/2014/02/17/the-nbas-endorsement-all-stars-2014/</link><title>The NBA's Endorsement All-Stars 2014</title><description>The NBA’ s biggest stars earned $155 million last year from endorsements thanks to huge shoe deals and the global reach of the sport. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7482-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7482_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:38:51">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markadomanis/2014/02/13/navalnys-reaction-to-sochi-shows-why-he-is-much-more-popular-than-other-russian-liberals/</link><title>Navalny's Reaction To Sochi Shows Why He Is Much More Popular Than Other Russian Liberals</title><description>My recent article about Viktor Shenderovich drew some, ahem, heated reactions from various parts of the Russian internet after it was translated and posted on Echo Moskvi's website. I found many of the comments entertaining, particularly those that simultaneously advocated and denied that Russia was equivalent to Hitler's Germany ("Mark, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7482-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7482_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:39:52">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jameslyne/2014/03/12/what-justin-biebers-twitter-hack-teaches-us-about-social-security/</link><title>What Justin Bieber's Twitter Hack Teaches Us About Social Media Security</title><description>Justin Bieber's 50 million follower strong Twitter account was hijacked briefly a couple of days ago and now that the dust has settled it seems like a good opportunity to review how these attacks happen and what all of us (pop stars included) should learn about Twitter security. I'll briefly recount [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>