<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7483">facebook paying?</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:40:18" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7483-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7483_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:40:19">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johnbuckingham/2014/04/10/value-investing-and-dividend-paying-bandwagons/</link><title>Value Investing And Dividend-Paying Bandwagons</title><description>Dividend-paying value stocks are gaining popularity. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7483-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7483_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:41:01">http://www.forbes.com/sites/petercohan/2014/03/26/why-oculus-vr-investor-is-bullish-on-facebook-shares/</link><title>Why Oculus VR Investor Is Bullish On Facebook Shares</title><description>Facebook spent $2 billion to buy Oculus VR -- maker of a "virtual reality headset for immersive gaming" called Oculus Rift. My March 26 interview with one of the Oculus VR investors, Santo Politi of Spark Capital, suggests that there may be a method to Facebook's madness in paying 77 times [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7483-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7483_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:41:51">http://www.forbes.com/sites/susanadams/2014/03/07/the-highest-paying-internships/</link><title>The Highest-Paying Internships</title><description>see photosClick for full photo gallery: The Highest-Paying Internships What do Palantir, VMware, Twitter, LinkedIn and Facebook have in common? Aside from all being tech companies based in the Bay Area, they pay their interns more than any other companies in America, according to a survey released by career website Glassdoor. Based [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7483-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7483_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:42:40">http://www.forbes.com/sites/parmyolson/2014/04/14/facebook-prepares-a-money-transfer-service-but-still-needs-trust/</link><title>Facebook Prepares A Money-Transfer Service, But Still Needs Trust</title><description>After getting 48 money-service licenses in the U.S., Facebook is now doing the same in Europe. But it could be a few years before people trust the platform enough to process their cash. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7483-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7483_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:43:41">http://www.forbes.com/sites/roberthof/2014/02/19/in-one-chart-heres-why-facebook-is-blowing-19-billion-on-whatsapp/</link><title>In One Chart, Here's Why Facebook Is Blowing $19 Billion On WhatsApp</title><description>Even in this era of multibillion-dollar valuations for tech startups that have barely moved out of the founders' parents' basement, the idea of Facebook paying $19 billion for a mobile messaging service seems simply insane. But that's what Facebook likely will be spending to acquire WhatsApp, the latest--well, not even actually the latest--social [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7483-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7483_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:44:39">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markrogowsky/2014/02/20/facebook-playbook-the-best-offense-is-a-good-defense/</link><title>Facebook Playbook: The Best Offense Is A Good Defense</title><description>It's hard to look past the $19 billion price tag Facebook is paying for WhatsApp, but to understand where CEO Mark Zuckerberg is coming from you really need to do just that. His company is always trying to build something new to improve the experience and value of using Facebook. [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7483-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7483_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:45:20">http://www.forbes.com/sites/drewhendricks/2014/02/27/could-your-facebook-ad-campaign-become-a-disaster/</link><title>Could Your Facebook Ad Campaign Become A Disaster?</title><description>For businesses seeking exposure, paying for Facebook ads has become a popular option. The site has 1.2 billion users, after all, making it an ideal outlet for ad placement. But through a complicated turn of events, some business owners are finding that their ad campaigns are backfiring on them, prompting [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7483-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7483_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:45:51">http://www.forbes.com/sites/nigamarora/2014/03/26/himax-glimpses-new-reality-with-facebook-google/</link><title>Himax Glimpses New Reality With Facebook, Google</title><description>Himax will certainly benefit in terms of revenues from the developments at Facebook and Google, but the increase in revenues will not result in proportionate increase in earnings. Here is a case where the company will grow but investors will be disappointed. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7483-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7483_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:46:49">http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidprosser/2014/04/02/does-facebooks-deal-for-oculus-spell-trouble-for-kickstarter/</link><title>Does Facebook's Deal For Oculus Spell Trouble For Kickstarter?</title><description>Facebook's $2bn purchase of Oculus has left some of the virtual company's early financial backers wondering why they're not earning any money from the deal read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7483-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7483_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 17:47:39">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markadomanis/2014/03/17/regardless-of-us-and-eu-sanctions-russia-is-already-paying-a-huge-price-for-invading-crimea/</link><title>Regardless of US and EU Sanctions, Russia Is Already Paying A Huge Price For Invading Crimea</title><description>We still have to wait and see precisely how bad things get between Russia and the West: quite a lot hinges on what happens over the next several weeks in Ukraine, particularly on how aggressively Russia acts in Eastern cities like Lugansk, Donetsk, and Kharkiv. Whether or not Moscow accept [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>