<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7486">board games teenagers</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:07:01" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7486-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7486_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:07:02">http://www.forbes.com/sites/parmyolson/2014/03/04/inside-the-facebook-whatsapp-megadeal-the-courtship-the-secret-meetings-the-19-billion-poker-game/</link><title>Inside The Facebook-WhatsApp Megadeal: The Courtship, The Secret Meetings, The $19 Billion Poker Game</title><description>Buying the world’s biggest and most reclusive messaging service took more than just money, but months of gaining its founders' trust and a promise of independence. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7486-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7486_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:07:51">http://www.forbes.com/sites/waynemcdonnell/2013/08/05/alex-rodriguezs-211-game-suspension-is-the-final-death-knell-in-a-career-once-destined-for-cooperstown/</link><title>Alex Rodriguez's 211-Game Suspension Is Death Knell Of A Career Once Destined For Cooperstown</title><description>After several months of rumors and speculation, Major League Baseball has officially announced that Alex Rodriguez has been suspended for 211 games due to his use and possession of performance enhancing substances and his attempts to “obstruct and frustrate” the Biogenesis investigation. The suspension will begin on Thursday unless Rodriguez [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7486-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7486_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:09:01">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johngaudiosi/2012/12/20/walt-disney-imagineers-explain-how-video-games-influenced-new-epcot-test-track-attraction/</link><title>Walt Disney Imagineers Explain How Video Games Influenced New EPCOT Test Track Attraction</title><description>VideoLAKE BUENA VISTA, Florida – In a way it’s ironic that EPCOT, which was designed as a world of the future, is one of the most dated theme parks at Walt Disney World Resort. But Disney is working on improving the park. While the Magic Kingdom recently doubled the size [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7486-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7486_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:09:45">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johngaudiosi/2011/04/21/while-supreme-court-mulls-ruling-on-violent-games-ftc-gives-game-retailers-high-scores/</link><title>While Supreme Court Mulls Ruling on Violent Games, FTC Gives Game Retailers High Scores</title><description>A lot can change over the course of a year. Last year, the game industry faced a harsh economy and increased scrutiny as the U.S. Supreme Court decided to formally consider the legality of a California law restricting the sales of violent video games. The industry was hedging its bets [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7486-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7486_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:10:34">http://www.forbes.com/2005/05/02/cx_dl_0502feat.html</link><title>Ten Smart Cars For Teenagers 2005</title><description>Our annual guide to the most affordable and safe cars for younger buyers. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7486-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7486_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:11:35">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jjcolao/2014/01/06/the-inside-story-of-snapchat-the-worlds-hottest-app-or-a-3-billion-disappearing-act/</link><title>The Inside Story Of Snapchat: The World's Hottest App Or A $3 Billion Disappearing Act?</title><description>Evan Spiegel, 23, and Bobby Murphy, 25, have turned Snapchat and its disappearing photos into the hottest app in America for teenagers. Hot enough, in fact, to spurn a $3 billion offer from Facebook. Will they become two of the youngest billionaires ever -- or fade quickly into business infamy? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7486-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7486_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:12:13">http://www.forbes.com/sites/steveschaefer/2014/04/21/lone-star-stockpicker-the-wit-and-wisdom-of-don-hodges/</link><title>Lone Star Stockpicker: The Wit And Wisdom Of Don Hodges</title><description>From selling television ads to a 50-year career in the equities business, Don Hodges has long found opportunity in odd places. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7486-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7486_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:13:40">http://www.forbes.com/2008/02/12/vintage-arcade-games-tech-personal-cx_ps_0213vintage.html</link><title>Arcade Games Make A Comeback</title><description>Yes, the Xbox is more high-tech. But a new wave of game players are bringing home something even more special--old-style arcade games. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7486-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7486_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:14:19">http://www.forbes.com/forbes/1999/1101/6411084a.html</link><title>Riggio's Game</title><description>Barnes &amp; Noble's chairman bet $25 million of his own money on an ailing videogame retailer. He just sold it at a fat profit. And the buyer is? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7486-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7486_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:15:45">http://www.forbes.com/2004/12/02/cx_de_1202kidphone.html</link><title>Dude, Ring Me Up A Game</title><description>Kids don't need to play on cell phones to kill time between meetings. That's why they're a big market. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>