<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7487">april fools day ideas</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:16:29" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7487-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7487_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:16:30">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kellyphillipserb/2014/04/01/irs-introduces-tax-return-vending-machines-april-fools-day-edition/</link><title>IRS Introduces Tax Return Vending Machines (April Fool's Day Edition)</title><description>Forget cupcake ATMs: the Internal Revenue Service has a better idea. Beginning with the 2014 tax year, the IRS will offer the opportunity for taxpayers in some metropolitan area to file simple income tax returns by using a vending machine. While a tax vending machine may seem out of the ordinary, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7487-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7487_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:16:54">http://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2014/04/01/a-quick-word-on-the-unexpected-business-benefit-of-april-fools-day/</link><title>SAP​Voice: A Quick Word On The Unexpected Business Benefit Of April Fools' Day</title><description>What started out as just a grade school excuse to wear your underwear outside your pants has spilled over into businesses around the globe. Yes, I am talking about that one day a year where techies and PR folks can come together to plan a goofy experience for their brand. [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7487-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7487_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:18:18">http://www.forbes.com/sites/schifrin/2014/01/06/guru-round-up-the-43-best-investment-ideas-for-2014/</link><title>Guru Round Up: The 43 Best Investment Ideas For 2014</title><description>What to buy in 2014? Here are what the experts like. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7487-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7487_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:19:18">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2013/04/01/why-im-logging-off-for-april-fools-day/</link><title>Why I'm Logging Off For April Fool's Day</title><description>Oh great, it's April Fools Day. I might as well not bother, because a tech commentator's lot is not a happy lot on a day like today. We deal in the dreams of developers, the impossibilities of the internet, and play with the emotions of the engaged... except today, where everyone just throws ideas at their PR teams and blogs like it's the pitch [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7487-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7487_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:20:14">http://www.forbes.com/sites/danielmitchell/2012/04/01/with-washington-now-imposing-the-worlds-highest-corporate-tax-rate-every-day-is-april-fools-day-for-american-companies/</link><title>With Washington Now Imposing the World's Highest Corporate Tax Rate, Every Day is April Fool's Day for American Companies</title><description>VideoLast year, I expressed skepticism that the White House was serious about reducing the corporate tax rate. And, sure enough, when the Obama Administration produced a plan earlier this year, it was a disappointing mix of a few good provisions and several unpalatable proposals. This is unfortunate because the United States [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7487-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7487_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:20:42">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johnwasik/2014/04/02/how-to-beat-the-rigged-flash-boys-stock-market/</link><title>How To Beat The Rigged, 'Flash Boys' Stock Market</title><description>This is not a post-April Fool's day joke, but it riffs on the furor caused by Michael Lewis's new book Flash Boys: A Wall Street Revolt. "How do you beat Wall Street at trading?" "Don't trade." That's my advice in a nutshell because it avoids the mostly true, but old news of Lewis's [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7487-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7487_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:21:17">http://www.forbes.com/sites/andygreenberg/2011/04/01/hack-your-ipad-to-see-through-clothes-an-april-fools-prank-with-a-real-physics-lesson/</link><title>Hack Your iPad To See Through Clothes? An April Fool's Prank With A Real Physics Lesson</title><description>Despite the latest hoax, an old infrared filter trick really can hack a camera to penetrate clothing. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7487-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7487_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:22:06">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kellyphillipserb/2012/07/19/a-dog-may-have-its-day-but-no-tax-perks/</link><title>A Dog May Have Its Day But No Tax Perks</title><description>I woke up on Monday morning to a strangely empty house. The dog was gone. My dog, a lab mutt, has been a part of my family for 13 years. He was a rescue from the SPCA in North Philadelphia. When we first picked him up, he weighed less than five [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7487-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7487_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:22:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/parmyolson/2013/04/05/microsoft-complains-facebook-home-is-a-lot-like-windows-phone-forgets-to-mention-its-also-free/</link><title>Microsoft Complains Facebook Home Is A Lot Like Windows Phone - Forgets To Mention It's Also Free</title><description>Microsoft says it had the idea for a people-centric-smartphone two years before Facebook. But that doesn't change the fact that Home is cheaper and easier to get hold of than Windows Phone. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7487-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7487_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:23:11">http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2013/08/04/see-the-trailer-for-the-legend-of-zelda-movie-that-never-was/</link><title>See The Trailer For The Legend of Zelda Movie That Never Was</title><description>With how beloved Nintendo franchises are by children, it's a wonder there aren't more movies made out of them. Yes, we have unfortunate "classics" like the '93 Super Mario Bros, and there have been a number of Pokemon films, but none are the sorts of blockbuster kids movies we see [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>