<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7492">oldest jokes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:35:23" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7492-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7492_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:35:24">http://www.forbes.com/sites/briansolomon/2012/04/16/94-year-old-billionaire-to-marry-for-the-5th-time-jokes-that-he-wants-more-kids/</link><title>94-Year-Old Billionaire To Marry For The 5th Time, Jokes That He Wants More Kids</title><description>Austrian retail tycoon Karl Wlaschek (net worth: $4.7 billion), who plans to get married in the next few days, is the fifth-oldest billionaire in the world. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7492-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7492_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:35:54">http://www.forbes.com/sites/steveforbes/2013/02/12/laugh-now-but-the-yankees-will-be-champs/</link><title>Laugh Now, But Here's Why The Yankees Will Be Champs</title><description>(New) Yankee Stadium, Jul 2009 - 14 (Photo credit: Ed Yourdon) The jokes about the aging New York Yankees – their prospective lineup is easily the oldest in Major League Baseball – are legion: The most expensive nursing home in the world is Yankee Stadium. The Yankees have replaced Gatorade in the dugout [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7492-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7492_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:36:48">http://www.forbes.com/sites/adamhartung/2014/03/25/the-race-to-communicate-was-malaysia-airlines-right-to-text-the-lost-plane/</link><title>The Race to Communicate - Was Malaysia Airlines Right to Text The Lost Plane?</title><description>You never know when a crisis might happen to your organization. But leaders need to plan for communications in advance of trouble so they maintain trust and not err when the message is difficult. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7492-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7492_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:37:23">http://www.forbes.com/sites/katyasoldak/2013/05/28/how-a-world-boxing-champion-turned-politician/</link><title>How A World Boxing Champion Turned Politician</title><description>To the world, Vitali Klitschko is known as a heavyweight WBC champion from Ukraine -- the oldest of the two famous Klitschko brothers, tough world-class boxers. In his mid-thirties, he decided to pick up a different kind of fight, no less rough than boxing—Ukrainian politics. Vitali Klitschko Beats Dereck Chisora, February [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7492-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7492_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:38:38">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jenniferrooney/2013/12/12/video-inside-cvs-headquarters-with-cmo-rob-price/</link><title>Video: Inside CVS Headquarters With CMO Rob Price</title><description>You may not see an abundance of its commercials on TV, but CVS/pharmacy, the retail division of CVS/Caremark, has been working hard in another way to get noticed—and distance itself from the competition: by creating a highly personalized shopping experience, both in-store and via digital channels. Senior VP and CMO Rob [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7492-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7492_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:39:14">http://www.forbes.com/sites/briansolomon/2014/02/12/king-of-craft-beer-how-sierra-nevada-is-winning-the-hops-war/</link><title>King Of Craft Beer: How Sierra Nevada Is Winning The Hops War</title><description>Decades before the boutique beer boom Ken Grossman tasted opportunity. Sierra Nevada is now a juggernaut--and he might be worth $800 million. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7492-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7492_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:39:37">http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2012/04/30/games-are-art-but-hilary-goldstein-is-still-right/</link><title>Games are Art, But Hilary Goldstein is Still Right</title><description>Tiny Wings (Photo credit: Wikipedia) It’s the oldest argument in the video game world. Are games art? People love to say yes, people love to say no. Hilary Goldstein has a great piece up on Venturebeat where he argues that games aren’t art, but despite the incendiary headline, I read a [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7492-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7492_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:40:21">http://www.forbes.com/sites/oreillymedia/2013/10/12/you-cant-legislate-away-the-time-money-and-features-law/</link><title>You Can't Legislate Away the Time, Money and Features Law</title><description>By James Turner Last week, I wrote in some detail about some of the specifics of how the Federal healthcare portal seems to have violated basic principles of good software delivery. Now I want to talk a bit about the more general factor that I think led to all those cut [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7492-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7492_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:40:59">http://www.forbes.com/sites/moneybuilder/2012/05/01/hunting-for-health-insurance/</link><title>Hunting for Health Insurance</title><description>see photosClick for full photo gallery: Health Secrets Of The World's Oldest People I am sick. For the past ten days, I’ve been wrestling with a high fever, a cough, a persistent sore throat, and a general malaise that’s kicking my ass. Basically, I’m the sickest I’ve been in [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7492-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7492_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:41:44">http://www.forbes.com/sites/karlmoore/2011/06/28/whartons-cappelli-on-why-older-workers-are-your-best-workers/</link><title>Wharton's Cappelli On Why Older Workers Do It Better</title><description>VideoThe book I am writing this summer is about young people - how we love them, nurture them and focus on them.  Wharton's Peter Cappelli, thinks we have got wrong.  Or at least somewhat. That our most valuable workers are often our oldest. One of things coming out of our research of younger people, what [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>