<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7493">islam discussions social media</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:42:17" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7493-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7493_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:42:18">http://www.forbes.com/sites/richardbehar/2013/01/25/there-he-goes-again-egypts-morsi-stuns-u-s-senators-in-meeting-with-jews-control-media-slur/</link><title>There He Goes Again: Egypt's Morsi Stuns U.S. Senators In Meeting With 'Jews-Control-Media' Slur</title><description>A Forbes exclusive: Egypt President Morsi called Jews apes and pigs. And then he stunned U.S. Senators in a Meeting With a 'Jews-Control-Media' Slur. Meanwhile, western major media continues to ignore Morsi's "NASA Problem." read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7493-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7493_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:43:34">http://www.forbes.com/sites/cedricmuhammad/2013/10/29/why-are-we-liberal-or-conservative-q-and-a-with-dr-avi-tuschman-author-our-political-nature-the-evolutionary-origins-of-what-divides-us/</link><title>Why Are We Liberal Or Conservative? -- Q and A With Dr. Avi Tuschman, Author, "Our Political Nature: The Evolutionary Origins Of What Divides Us"</title><description>An Evolutionary Anthropologist believes he has found the natural root of why we lean Right or Left read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7493-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7493_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:44:45">http://www.forbes.com/sites/robertwood/2013/10/16/sex-as-a-religion-ask-the-irs/</link><title>Sex As A Religion? Ask The IRS</title><description>Ever since our founding fathers, it’s hands-off for federal income taxes, property taxes and more. And despite the separation of church and state, the IRS is involved in determining what's a legitimate religion. If you've been following the IRS problems over the last year, you might think the beleaguered tax agency isn't always objective. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7493-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7493_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:45:25">http://www.forbes.com/sites/alexkantrowitz/2013/06/04/a-firsthand-look-at-the-changes-driving-turkeys-protests/</link><title>A Firsthand Look At The Changes Driving Turkey's Protests</title><description>A day before the demonstrations in Istanbul’s Gezi Park heated up, I stepped on a flight in the city’s soon to be overshadowed Ataturk Airport and headed out of the country. Protesters gather in Istanbul I had just spent three weeks meeting with business leaders, academics and friends in Turkey and left [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7493-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7493_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:46:11">http://www.forbes.com/sites/marketshare/2011/12/17/if-one-man-can-take-down-lowes-and-kayak-whats-next/</link><title>If One Man Can Take Down Lowe's and Kayak, What's Next?</title><description>Video Scott Goodson is the founder of StrawberryFrog, the world’s first cultural movement agency. His first book, Uprising exploring the phenomena of movements will be published by McGraw Hill soon.   “Forget anarchy. Today’ protests, revolts and riots are self-organizing, hyper-networked—and headed for a city near you,” as the latest edition [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7493-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7493_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:46:58">http://www.forbes.com/sites/knowledgewharton/2013/10/03/182013/</link><title>Was Jesus An Effective Leader? Insights From Reza Aslan's 'Zealot'</title><description>The following post was published on the Knowledge@Wharton website on October 1, 2013. In his bestselling new book, Zealot: The Life and Times of Jesus of Nazareth, author Reza Aslan’s goal was to write a biography of one of history’s most influential people, drawing on historical sources instead of the traditional Gospels to help people understand [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7493-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7493_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:47:36">http://www.forbes.com/sites/bruceupbin/2012/03/08/saudi-billionaire-alwaleed-this-end-of-america-talk-is-baloney/</link><title>Saudi Billionaire Alwaleed: This End Of America Talk Is Baloney</title><description>Forbes Wealth Editor Luisa Kroll and I sat down with Saudi Arabia’s Prince Alwaleed Bin Talal Alsaud during his recent trip to New York. The Prince, 57 years old and  No. 29 on the World’s Billionaires List at $18 billion, is the richest man in the Middle East and a [...]</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7493-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7493_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:48:07">http://www.forbes.com/sites/rahimkanani/2012/04/17/tony-blair-on-faith-governance-aid-and-philanthropy/</link><title>Tony Blair on Faith, Governance, Aid and Philanthropy</title><description>Tony Blair at the Global Philanthropy Forum. Yesterday at the 2012 Global Philanthropy Forum, former British Prime Minister and Philanthropist Tony Blair spoke on a range of global issues spanning faith and globalization, governance and leadership, and how 21st century philanthropy must continually innovate and adapt to our rapidly changing [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>