<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7494">cartoons festival</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:48:35" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7494-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7494_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:48:36">http://www.forbes.com/sites/scottmendelson/2014/01/13/top-5-underrated-disney-cartoons/</link><title>Top 5 Underrated Disney Cartoons</title><description>As you probably know, Walt Disney's Frozen ended its eighth weekend yesterday with $317 million in domestic grosses. That makes it officially the biggest-grossing single-release Disney Studios animated film in domestic history; surpassing the $312m original theatrical gross of The Lion King in 1994 (it was of course reissued in September 2011 and [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7494-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7494_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:49:19">http://www.forbes.com/sites/brandindex/2013/09/09/toyota-is-on-a-festival-tour-and-ramps-up-buzz-along-the-way/</link><title>Toyota Is On A Festival Tour And Ramps Up Buzz Along the Way</title><description>VideoToyota's SpongeBob car promotion Toyota has ended the summer on a high, as Buzz for the brand has risen since its festival-focused "Let’s Go Places" and kids-friendly "Happy Driving!" campaigns. The carmaker is currently second in terms of Purchase Consideration out of competitor brands Ford and Honda, following a duo of [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7494-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7494_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:49:49">http://www.forbes.com/sites/lizadonnelly/2013/04/25/ways-to-express-freedom-the-third-annual-international-festival-of-political-cartooning-in-caen-france/</link><title>Ways To Express Freedom: The Third Annual International Festival Of Political Cartooning In Caen, France</title><description>What happens when political cartoonists from around the world gather in one place for a week and share their passion for what they do?</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7494-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7494_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:50:20">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markhughes/2014/04/17/exclusive-interview-with-zack-snyder-director-of-batman-vs-superman/</link><title>Exclusive Interview With Zack Snyder, Director Of 'Batman Vs. Superman'</title><description>With the Man of Steel sequel about to start shooting in Detroit, fans have been hoping new information about the movie will drop soon, and desperately awaiting the reveal of the new batsuit and Wonder Woman costume. Well, dear readers, I had a chance to speak at length with the [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7494-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7494_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:50:44">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jacobsullum/2014/02/26/five-senators-demand-unconstitutional-restrictions-on-e-cigarette-ads-for-the-children/</link><title>Five Senators Demand Unconstitutional Restrictions On E-Cigarette Ads&amp;mdash;For The Children</title><description>Today five senators—Barbara Boxer (D-Calif.), Richard Durbin (D-Ill.), Tom Harkin (D-Iowa), Richard Blumenthal (D-Conn.), and Edward Markey (D-Mass.)—introduced “legislation to protect children from e-cigarettes." To be more precise, the bill aims to protect children from speech about e-cigarettes. The Protecting Children from Electronic Cigarette [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7494-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7494_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:51:35">http://www.forbes.com/sites/johngiuffo/2013/11/01/neil-gaimans-sandman-snuck-up-on-me-in-san-francisco/</link><title>Neil Gaiman's Sandman Snuck Up On Me In San Francisco</title><description>From Sandman #8, drawn by Mike Dringenberg, where we first meet Morpheus' sister, Death. Image used with persmission of the Cartoon Art Museum / copyright DC Comics - Vertigo. I like my experiences with serendipity to have a touch of cosmic significance – like, was this meant to happen? I always try [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7494-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7494_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:52:35">http://www.forbes.com/sites/michaelvenables/2013/06/19/andrew-rekvin-on-renewables-the-limits-of-information-and-the-dangerous-middle/</link><title>Andrew Revkin On Renewables, The Limits Of Information And Being In The Dangerous Middle</title><description>The Seattle Science Festival 2013 ended on Saturday with it's closing night program, Our 11th Hour: Straight Talk on Climate Change from People Who Know with world-leading experts on climate change: Dr. Kevin Trenberth, Dr. Richard Alley and New York Times journalist Andrew Revkin, followed by a 30-minute opera on environmental stewardship, Heron [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7494-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7494_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:53:28">http://www.forbes.com/sites/dougbandow/2014/01/06/the-more-wasteful-is-the-federal-government-program-the-more-essential-it-is-to-washington/</link><title>The More Wasteful Is The Federal Government Program, The More Essential It Is To Washington</title><description>Too many people expect to live at someone else’s expense through Washington. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7494-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7494_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:54:00">http://www.forbes.com/sites/dorothypomerantz/2011/01/24/from-undercover-boss-to-the-economic-crisis/</link><title>From 'Undercover Boss' to the Economic Crisis</title><description>A new documentary called 'The Flaw' looks at how income inequality helped fuel the financial crisis. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7494-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7494_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 18:54:33">http://www.forbes.com/sites/danielnyegriffiths/2013/09/05/pax-problems-censorship-and-sensibility-in-the-penny-arcade/</link><title>PAX Problems: Censorship And Sensibility In the Penny Arcade [Updated]</title><description>PAX Prime, another sold-out PAX gaming and geekdom convention, became unexpectedly controversial when an old wound was reopened on the last day. What happens next? read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>