<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7498">syria chemical weapons</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:19:21" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7498-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7498_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:19:21">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kenrapoza/2013/10/16/syrias-chemical-weapons-slowly-being-eradicated/</link><title>Syria's Chemical Weapons Slowly Being Eradicated</title><description>Unlike in Iraq, weapons inspectors getting the job done in Syria.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7498-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7498_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:20:00">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kenrapoza/2013/09/23/china-will-help-destroy-syrias-chemical-weapons/</link><title>China Will Help Destroy Syria's Chemical Weapons</title><description>China to help with Assad's chemical weapons dump, if asked.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7498-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7498_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:21:21">http://www.forbes.com/sites/markadomanis/2013/09/10/russias-proposal-to-take-control-of-syrias-chemical-weapons-probably-isnt-sincere-but-we-should-try-to-find-out/</link><title>Russia's Proposal To Take Control Of Syria's Chemical Weapons Probably Isn't Sincere, But We Should Try To Find Out</title><description>The debate over Syria has been particularly interesting because, for the first time I can remember, the neoconservatives have been totally ineffectual as a lobby for the use of military force. They've been outflanked and outfought on both the left and right, and it seems very likely that the authorization [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7498-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7498_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:21:58">http://www.forbes.com/sites/alexkantrowitz/2013/02/10/individual-intervention-u-s-connecting-with-syrian-officers-on-social-media-in-attempt-to-keep-chemical-weapons-safe/</link><title>The United States' Social Media Plan to Keep Syria's Chemical Weapons Safe</title><description>We have already seen social media used as a new wartime communication tool, but a fresh tactic being deployed by the United States government may be taking the practice to a new level. According to the Daily Beast's Eli Lake, the U.S. has been connecting with midlevel Syrian officers via [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7498-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7498_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:22:54">http://www.forbes.com/sites/rickungar/2013/09/10/breakthrough-syria-says-it-will-surrender-chemical-weapons-to-international-control/</link><title>Breakthrough? Syria Says It Will Surrender Chemical Weapons To International Control</title><description>(Photo credit: Wikipedia) The Syrian government has announced that it will accept Russia’s proposal whereby the al-Assad government will place its chemical weapons under the control of the international community. According to Interfax, Syrian minister Walid al-Moualem, said today— “We held a very fruitful round of talks with Foreign Minister [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7498-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7498_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:23:45">http://www.forbes.com/sites/stratfor/2013/09/12/analytic-guidance-the-syria-crisis/</link><title>Analytic Guidance: The Syria Crisis</title><description>Editor's note: Periodically, Stratfor publishes guidance produced for its analysis team and shares it with readers. This guidance sets the parameters used in our own ongoing examination and assessment of events surrounding Syria's use of chemical weapons as the crisis evolves into a confrontation between the United States and Russia. Given [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7498-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7498_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:24:31">http://www.forbes.com/sites/geoffreykabat/2014/02/19/sochi-syria-how-can-we-watch-the-olympics-knowing-what-is-going-on-a-few-hundred-miles-away-in-syria/</link><title>Sochi and Syria: How Can We Watch The Olympics Knowing What is Going on a Few Hundred Miles Away in Syria?</title><description>Day after day for the past 10 days, two realities have been unfolding virtually side-by-side with no apparent acknowledgement of a connection between them.  Every evening, we get to see the amazing feats of the world’s most talented athletes competing in the Winter Olympics at Sochi and providing a stage [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7498-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7498_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:25:33">http://www.forbes.com/sites/claudiarosett/2013/08/19/north-korean-syrian-chemistry-the-weapons-connections/</link><title>North Korean-Syrian Chemistry: The Weapons Connections</title><description>Is North Korea complicit in the use of chemical weapons in Syria? For a host of reasons, this question ought to be high priority for the United Nations chemical weapons experts who finally arrived in Syria this past weekend to investigate allegations of chemical weapons use in the conflict raging [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7498-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7498_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:26:22">http://www.forbes.com/sites/dougschoen/2014/02/06/john-kerry-admits-defeat-on-syria-but-whats-next-the-case-for-coercive-diplomacy/</link><title>John Kerry Admits Defeat On Syria, But What's Next? The Case For Coercive Diplomacy</title><description>The notion that we’re failing in Syria is just about the only thing both parties can agree on these days. In a recent interview for her MSNBC show, Andrea Mitchell went after a US State Department official on our flawed approach to dealing with Syrian President Assad and, by extension, the [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7498-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7498_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:27:25">http://www.forbes.com/sites/marketnewsvideo/2013/09/10/daily-wrap-september-10-2013/</link><title>Daily Wrap: September 10, 2013</title><description>The US markets rallied on Tuesday following the news that Syria would hand over its chemical weapon stockpiles, potentially avoiding the US committing itself to a military conflict in the already volatile Middle East region. In mid-afternoon trading, the Dow, Nasdaq and S&amp;P 500 were all in positive territory. Apple (AAPL) [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>