<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7499">gold price</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:27:58" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7499-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7499_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:27:59">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kitconews/2014/04/11/survey-participants-see-higher-gold-prices-next-week-5/</link><title>Survey Participants See Higher Gold Prices Next Week</title><description>(Kitco News) - Gold prices are expected to rise next week as a majority of participants in the weekly Kitco News Gold Survey forecast the yellow metal will build on the gains established in early April. Out of 33 participants, 22 responded this week. Fourteen see prices up, while four see prices [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7499-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7499_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:28:25">http://www.forbes.com/sites/roystonwild/2014/04/10/why-asian-shoppers-should-blast-gold-prices-sky-high/</link><title>Why Asian Shoppers Should Blast Gold Prices Sky High</title><description>Countries across Asia piled into gold last year as precious metal prices plummeted. But is buying activity from this region likely to remain bubbly looking ahead? read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7499-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7499_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:29:08">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kitconews/2014/04/04/survey-participants-see-higher-gold-prices-next-week-4/</link><title>Survey Participants See Higher Gold Prices Next Week</title><description>(Kitco News) - A majority of participants in Kitco News’ weekly gold survey look for the price of the metal to rise next week. Out of 33 participants, 18 responded this week. Eleven see prices up, while five see prices down and two see prices sideways or unchanged. Market participants include bullion [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7499-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7499_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:30:24">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kitconews/2014/04/07/second-quarter-will-not-be-a-great-time-for-gold-prices-analysts/</link><title>Second Quarter Will Not Be A Great Time For Gold Prices -- Analysts</title><description>(Kitco News) - Commodity analysts are expecting gold to remain weak in the next three months as seasonal factors, an improving U.S. economy and lack of bullish momentum drag prices down. Ole Hansen, head of commodity strategy at Saxo Bank, pointed out that the second quarter is usually a quiet time [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7499-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7499_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:30:59">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kitconews/2014/03/28/weaker-gold-prices-seen-for-next-week-survey-participants/</link><title>Weaker Gold Prices Seen For Next Week -- Survey Participants</title><description>(Kitco News) - Gold prices may continue to exhibit weakness following two weeks of softer values, said a majority of participants in the weekly Kitco News Gold Survey. In the Kitco News Gold Survey, out of 33 participants, 22 responded this week. Six see prices up, while 12 see prices down and [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7499-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7499_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:32:07">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kitconews/2014/03/17/gold-prices-ahead-of-game-iitraders-ilczyszyn/</link><title>Gold Prices Ahead Of Game: iiTrader's Ilczyszyn</title><description>(Kitco News) - Gold prices have pulled back slightly after hitting six-month high in early trading Monday and one trader says he wouldn’t be surprised to see the market continue to move lower. “Short-term, we are reaching a little overbought levels – we wouldn’t be surprised to see the market come back,” [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7499-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7499_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:33:20">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kitconews/2014/03/25/gold-prices-steady-firmer-on-short-covering-bargain-hunting/</link><title>Gold Prices Steady-Firmer On Short Covering, Bargain Hunting</title><description>(Kitco News) - Gold prices are steady to slightly higher in early U.S. trading Tuesday, on some short covering and bargain hunting after falling to a four-week low on Monday. Gold bulls are still on shaky technical ground. April gold was last up $1.00 at $1,312.00 an ounce. Spot gold was [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7499-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7499_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:34:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kitconews/2014/03/24/technical-selling-firmer-u-s-dollar-pressure-gold-prices/</link><title>Technical Selling, Firmer U.S. Dollar Pressure Gold Prices</title><description>(Kitco News) - Gold prices are moderately lower in early U.S. trading Monday, on technically related selling and amid a higher U.S. dollar index. Serious near-term chart damage has been inflicted on the gold market recently. April gold was last down $11.00 at $1,325.00 an ounce. Spot gold was last quoted [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7499-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7499_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:35:56">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kitconews/2014/03/26/difficult-to-quantify-but-iraqi-gold-purchase-helped-push-gold-prices-towards-1400-peter-hug/</link><title>Difficult To Quantify, But Iraqi Gold Purchase Helped Push Gold Prices Towards $1,400: Peter Hug</title><description>(Kitco News) - Following Tuesday’s news that the Central Bank of Iraq purchased $1.56 billion of gold in March, many were left wondering why gold was not moving upwards. Peter Hug, Kitco’s Global Trading Director says the impact of the purchase is difficult to quantify. He added though it makes sense that Iraq [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7499-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7499_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:36:43">http://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2014/03/18/low-silver-and-gold-prices-will-impact-silver-wheatons-year-over-year-profits/</link><title>Low Silver And Gold Prices Will Impact Silver Wheaton's Year-Over-Year Profits</title><description>Silver Wheaton links its dividend payment to cash generated by operating activities in the previous quarter. Low silver prices imply lower cash flows and hence lower dividends, which may put pressure on the company’s share price. read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>