<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7500">roof isolation</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:37:49" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7500-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7500_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:37:50">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jonbruner/2011/07/25/forbes-goes-camping-on-the-roof/</link><title>Forbes Goes Camping on the Roof</title><description>Seven intrepid Forbes staffers camped on the roof of the Forbes building in Manhattan through 96-degree heat.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7500-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7500_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:38:49">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jenniferhicks/2013/10/30/pioneers-festival-a-smarter-sxsw-takes-its-place-in-europe/</link><title>Pioneers Festival: A Smarter SXSW Takes Its Place In Europe</title><description>In a bold move, the third annual Pioneers Festival held in Vienna, Oct. 30 and 31, 2013 chose to do something different. They embraced the overlooked practices of science, robotics and AI. These are three of the fastest growing markets for technology globally  - and tossed them together under one roof [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7500-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7500_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:39:34">http://www.forbes.com/sites/lawtonursrey/2014/02/25/what-coworking-can-really-do-for-you/</link><title>What Coworking Can Really Do For You</title><description>There was a time when indie businesses, consultants, freelancers and the like were stuck alone in their home offices or fighting for space at the local coffee shop. Thanks to coworking, all that has changed – and it’s definitely for the better. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7500-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7500_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:40:22">http://www.forbes.com/sites/singularity/2013/01/14/for-women-things-really-havent-changed-even-in-medical-school/</link><title>For Women, Things Really Haven't Changed -- Even in Medical School</title><description>By Brooke Sachs (@MlleBrooklyn), an early-career social entrepreneur, third-year Medical student, and FutureMed alumni at Singularity University. For years, I insisted that the world had changed. That violence against women was decreasing. That I'd never felt it; never had it affect my life. I wasn't shouting from the roof-tops that I [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7500-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7500_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:41:34">http://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2013/10/01/how-microsoft-could-cope-with-the-differing-european-and-us-windows-phone-markets/</link><title>How Microsoft Could Cope With The Differing European And US Windows Phone Markets</title><description>The latest numbers from Kantar Worldpanel makes for good reading for the European arm of the Windows Phone team. Overall in the top five EU countries the platform is on 9.2% and Windows Phone is on course to break the 10% barrier before the start of 2014. The picture in the US is not so good with just 3.0% marketshare. What can Microsoft do to [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7500-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7500_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:42:25">http://www.forbes.com/sites/peterdetwiler/2013/09/11/designing-a-high-performance-building-it-takes-planning-to-do-it-right/</link><title>Designing A High Performance Building: It Takes Planning To Do It Right</title><description>Net zero buildings and high-performance buildings have on key trait in common - to do them right, you have to invest in an integrated planning process, and define the outcomes you want. The Parkland Hospital is an example of taking the time to integrate the various concerns and get it right, especially from the patient's point of view. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7500-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7500_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:43:14">http://www.forbes.com/sites/arieladams/2013/04/11/2013s-best-luxury-suv-land-rover-4th-gen-range-rover-review/</link><title>2013's Best Luxury SUV: Land Rover 4th Gen Range Rover Review</title><description>The Forbes hands-on review by Ariel Adams of the 2013 Land Rover Range Rover family of luxury SUVs. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7500-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7500_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:43:50">http://www.forbes.com/sites/deborahljacobs/2012/10/30/new-york-picks-up-the-pieces-live-blogging-as-we-bounce-back-from-hurricane-sandy/</link><title>How Do You Spell Resilience? New Yorkers Bounce Back From Hurricane Sandy</title><description>Hurricane Sandy was a whack on the side of the head. But New Yorkers are known for their resilience. I will be live blogging here about how we are coping.</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7500-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7500_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:44:32">http://www.forbes.com/sites/peterjreilly/2011/07/31/s-corporation-rental-income-not-passive-except-when-it-is/</link><title>S Corporation Rental Income Not Passive Except When It Is</title><description>Private Letter Ruling 201118011 A C corporation is a taxable entity.  Distributions that it makes to its shareholders are also, generally, taxable to them.  People who don't want to pay tax twice on the same income will make an S election.  The shareholders are taxed on whatever the earnings are regardless of [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7500-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7500_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:45:00">http://www.forbes.com/sites/nadiaarumugam/2012/04/26/taste-test-dunkin-donuts-fake-artisan-bagels-vs-real-artisan-bagels/</link><title>Taste Test: Dunkin' Donuts' Fake "Artisan" Bagels vs Real Artisan Bagels</title><description>Davidovich's Pumpernickel Bagel (right) vs Dunkin' Donut's Rendition (left) As promised in my last post on the complaints filed by Davidovich Bakery, NY, against Dunkin' Donuts for false and misleading usage of the descriptor "artisan" in relation to Dunkin's new line of bagels, I present the ultimate arbiter in the bagel [...] read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>