<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7505">ethnic myanmar</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:55:36" name="Forbes" id="FW14-e102"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e102-7505-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7505_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:55:37">http://www.forbes.com/sites/realspin/2012/11/15/myanmar-no-ethics-no-nation/</link><title>Myanmar: No Ethnics; No Nation</title><description>Obama is in the political and moral position to promote a new comity in Myanmar. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7505-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7505_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:56:19">http://www.forbes.com/sites/simonmontlake/2012/10/30/myanmars-ethnic-conflict-flares-in-shadow-of-asian-oil-investments/</link><title>Myanmar's Ethnic Conflict Flares In Shadow Of Asian Oil Investments</title><description>Rakhine State, Myanmar In a setback for reformers, ethnic violence has spread in western Myanmar (Burma), killing scores of civilians and displacing over 32,000 people. Following the latest fighting between Rakhine and Rohingya groups, satellite images released by Human Rights Watch appear to show the wholesale destruction last week of a [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7505-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7505_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:57:11">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jonspringer/2014/01/21/the-buzz-about-myanmars-future-prosperity-with-oliver-belfitt-nash/</link><title>The Buzz About Myanmar's Future Prosperity With Oliver Belfitt-Nash</title><description>Oliver Belfitt-Nash provides candid free news and analysis on the countries where he resides. In his previous job at Monet Capital in Mongolia, he was an early voice in making investors aware that the market would be receding in 2011 and 2012. He now works for Ronoc – an Irish [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7505-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7505_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:57:41">http://www.forbes.com/sites/jonspringer/2013/12/16/american-law-firm-grows-opportunities-in-myanmar/</link><title>American Law Firm Grows Opportunities In Myanmar</title><description>The law firm of Herzfeld, Rubin, Meyer &amp; Rose Limited (HRMR) announced itself as the first 100% American owned law firm in Myanmar on July 29, 2013. While the United States has reduced the number of sanctions it has against the former nation of Burma in the past year, there [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7505-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7505_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:58:22">http://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesasia/2014/02/01/the-golden-hour-for-the-golden-land-myanmars-need-for-u-s-public-private-partnerships/</link><title>The Golden Hour For The Golden Land: Myanmar's Need For U.S. Public-Private Partnerships</title><description>As Myanmar begins to show signs of progress, U.S. business leaders must seize the opportunity to ensure the country’s gains result in balanced and inclusive growth. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7505-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7505_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:58:42">http://www.forbes.com/sites/techonomy/2013/11/05/myanmars-promising-experiment-with-internet-freedom/</link><title>Myanmar's Promising Experiment With Internet Freedom</title><description>After decades of rule by a brutal regime known for imprisoning cyber-dissidents, Internet freedom in Myanmar expanded dramatically over the past year, according to a recent report by Freedom House. The report warns that the Internet in Myanmar is still “not free,” however, and that major obstacles remain to further improvement. One is a legacy of [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7505-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7505_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 19:59:17">http://www.forbes.com/sites/theoosborne/2013/06/10/travel-destination-of-the-day-myanmar-burma/</link><title>Hot Destination: Myanmar (Burma)</title><description>Sunset views in Myanmar (Forbes Image) Our hot destination at the moment is Myanmar. After a long period of inaccessibility, this once isolated nation at the cross roads to India and China has finally opened its doors to new frontier type travellers. Myanmar is now easily reachable from London by flying via [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7505-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7505_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 20:00:17">http://www.forbes.com/sites/realspin/2013/09/02/what-myanmar-must-do-to-free-itself-of-china/</link><title>What Myanmar Must Do To Free Itself Of China</title><description>One of the world's great democratic hopes emerges. read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7505-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7505_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 20:01:03">http://www.forbes.com/sites/lauriekahle/2013/07/16/orient-express-launches-orcaella-offering-new-myanmar-cruises/</link><title>Orient Express Launches Orcaella Offering New Myanmar Cruises</title><description>Orient Express' Orcaella launches on July 22 in Myanmar with new itineraries to remote regions. On July 22, Orient-Express will launch a new river cruiser, the Orcaella, which will sail on the Ayeyarwady (Irrawaddy) River in Myanmar, also known as Burma. Named for a species of dolphin that inhabits the river, [...] read »</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e102-7505-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e102/7505_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-23 20:02:07">http://www.forbes.com/sites/simonmontlake/2013/06/27/general-electrics-last-frontier-return-to-myanmar-burma/</link><title>General Electric's Last Frontier: Return To Myanmar (Burma)</title><description>The industrial giant is trying to do business in just-opened Myanmar, where they badly need the stuff it makes and sells. So why is this storied multinational struggling? read »</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>