<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7024">reinforcement learning</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:21:02" name="CNN" id="FW14-e101"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e101-7024-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7024_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:21:41">http://edition.cnn.com/2012/02/02/us/my-view-technology-and-engineering-the-forgotten-part-of-stem-education/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>My View: Technology and engineering, the forgotten part of STEM education</title><description>* Editor's note: Matt Walton a technology and engineering education teacher at Glen Allen High School in Henrico County, Virginia. He has a master's degree in education and a bachelor of science degree in technology education from North Carolina State University. 

http://www.cnn.com/2012/02/02/us/my-view-technology-and-engineering-the-forgotten-part-of-stem-education/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7024-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7024_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:22:38">http://edition.cnn.com/2012/08/04/tech/innovation/olympics-technology-debate-future/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>High-tech kit speeds athletes into new era</title><description>* From hydrodynamic swimwear in the pool to lightweight carbon-fiber bicycles slicing through the air at the velodrome, the Olympic Games is once again shining a spotlight not only on the athletes, but also their kit. 

http://www.cnn.com/2012/08/04/tech/innovation/olympics-technology-debate-future/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7024-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7024_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:23:30">http://edition.cnn.com/2014/04/03/opinion/mccutcheon-campaign-contribution-limits/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Why I fought campaign contribution limit</title><description>* The Supreme Court on Wednesday reinforced the nation's belief in freedom and its constitutional traditions with a ruling that upheld my challenge to a section of the federal election campaign law that restricted citizens' rights to express their views. 

http://www.cnn.com/2014/04/03/opinion/mccutcheon-campaign-contribution-limits/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7024-04"><link>http://www.cnn.com/2014/04/18/living/open-textbooks-online-education-resources/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>How some colleges are offering free textbooks</title><description>* College student Caitlin Ryen works two jobs to support herself and pay tuition at South Florida Community College. When a new semester rolls around, that usually means choosing which textbooks to buy, or not buying any at all, she says. 

http://www.cnn.com/2014/04/18/living/open-textbooks-online-education-resources/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7024-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7024_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:25:33">http://edition.cnn.com/2014/03/28/world/europe/russia-ukraine-troop-buildup/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>What do we know about Russia's troop buildup on Ukraine's border?</title><description>* Both Kiev and Washington say that Russian forces are massing in large numbers near Ukraine's eastern border -- and that they represent a threat to Ukraine and potentially to other former Soviet states. 

http://www.cnn.com/2014/03/28/world/europe/russia-ukraine-troop-buildup/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7024-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7024_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:26:47">http://edition.cnn.com/2014/03/26/travel/tsa-airport-security/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>In wake of LAX shooting, TSA recommends checkpoint changes</title><description>* The Transportation Security Administration is recommending a beefed-up police presence at TSA checkpoints and ticket counters during busy times at airports, the agency said in a report released Wednesday. 

http://www.cnn.com/2014/03/26/travel/tsa-airport-security/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7024-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7024_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:27:33">http://edition.cnn.com/2014/03/26/health/human-factor-max-aaron/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Hockey player breaks back, switches to figure skating</title><description>* I'm relaxing at home on the couch watching TV, and everything seems to be about the Olympics. I can't seem to avoid the constant reminder of where I would like to have been at this moment: in Sochi, Russia. 

http://www.cnn.com/2014/03/26/health/human-factor-max-aaron/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7024-08"><link>http://www.cnn.com/2014/03/26/politics/ukraine-crisis/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Obama: U.S. and Europe united over Ukraine crisis</title><description>* U.S. President Barack Obama on Wednesday again called for Russia to de-escalate the situation in Ukraine and warned of further isolation and "costs" if Moscow doesn't respond to the West's call for a change of course. 

http://www.cnn.com/2014/03/26/politics/ukraine-crisis/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7024-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7024_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:29:57">http://edition.cnn.com/2014/03/25/opinion/huffington-redefining-success/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Success is about more than money and power</title><description>* On April 6, 2007, I woke up in the morning in a pool of blood. I had collapsed from exhaustion and hit my head on the corner of my desk, cutting my eye and breaking my cheekbone. 

http://www.cnn.com/2014/03/25/opinion/huffington-redefining-success/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7024-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7024_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 16:31:06">http://edition.cnn.com/2014/03/04/health/ramprasad-depression/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Depression, anxiety: What worked for me</title><description>* For more than a decade of my life, I struggled with debilitating anxiety, panic attacks and depression. And, like millions of people around the world, I longed to discover a magic pill to cure my ills and promise me nirvana. 

http://www.cnn.com/2014/03/04/health/ramprasad-depression/index.html</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>