<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7034">sony vaio laptop</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:33:03" name="CNN" id="FW14-e101"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e101-7034-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7034_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:34:15">http://edition.cnn.com/2002/TECH/ptech/04/23/top.notebooks.idg/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Review: Dells tops list of best 15 notebook PCs</title><description>* Can't decide whether you like the eraserhead or the touchpad better? Two new Dells join the Top 15 this month, and both have dual pointing devices. The $2,625 Latitude C810, fourth on the power chart, can accommodate a pair of optical drives too, for easy copying of files between a DVD-ROM drive and a CD-RW drive. The $2,396 Latitude C610, Dell's l... 

http://www.cnn.com/2002/TECH/ptech/04/23/top.notebooks.idg/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7034-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7034_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:35:18">http://politicalticker.blogs.cnn.com/2010/07/01/political-hot-topics-thursday-july-1-2010/?iref=allsearch</link><title>POLITICAL HOT TOPICS: Thursday, July 1, 2010</title><description>* The CNN Washington Bureau’s morning speed read of the top stories making news from around the country and the world. WASHINGTON/POLITICAL For the latest political news: www.CNNPolitics.com CNNMoney: House OKs Wall Street reform bill The House voted... 

http://politicalticker.blogs.cnn.com/2010/07/01/political-hot-topics-thursday-july-1-2010/</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7034-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7034_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:36:03">http://edition.cnn.com/2002/US/11/03/sniper.case/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Police look for more sniper links</title><description>* Police in Prince George's County, Maryland, are trying to determine whether a September 5 shooting in Clinton is related to the recent Washington-area sniper rampage, a spokesman said Sunday. 

http://www.cnn.com/2002/US/11/03/sniper.case/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7034-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7034_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:36:37">http://edition.cnn.com/2008/TECH/ptech/09/10/sony.laptop/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Sony laptop a solid, if unspectacular, choice for school</title><description>* With its 14-inch display, the Sony Vaio CR510 sits right in the middle of Sony's laptop lineup, which runs from the 11-inch Vaio TZ to the 17-inch Vaio AR line. We happen to believe that a... 

http://www.cnn.com/2008/TECH/ptech/09/10/sony.laptop/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7034-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7034_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:37:14">http://edition.cnn.com/2007/TECH/ptech/08/16/hp.laptop/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Review: Solid construction, biz-friendly features from HP laptop</title><description>* Fans of ultraportable laptops have had a lot of products to be excited about in recent months, with two excellent models in particular standing out - -the Toshiba Portege R500 and the Sony VAIO TZ150. 

http://www.cnn.com/2007/TECH/ptech/08/16/hp.laptop/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7034-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7034_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:37:35">http://edition.cnn.com/2001/TECH/ptech/09/20/low.cost.laptop.idg/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Laptops: Low-Cost to Luxury</title><description>* Do you need a lightweight laptop that won't bust your budget? Have you finally decided to treat your best employees (or yourself) to a top-of-the-line, wireless-ready model? One of four new portables that we tested--Gateway's Solo 1200, Hewlett-Packard's Pavilion N5470 and Omnibook 6100, and Sony's http://www.cnn.com/2001/TECH/ptech/09/20/low.cost.laptop.idg/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7034-07"><link>http://www.cnn.com/2001/TECH/ptech/07/31/sony.vaio.idg/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>New sales model adopted for some Sony products</title><description>* In an effort to penetrate the North American corporate laptop computer market, Sony on Monday announced a major change in the way the company will build and sell its new Vaio GR-series mobile products. 

http://www.cnn.com/2001/TECH/ptech/07/31/sony.vaio.idg/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7034-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7034_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:39:15">http://edition.cnn.com/2002/TECH/ptech/01/25/sony.security.idg/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Sony issues security alert for some Vaio laptops</title><description>* Sony is urging some customers who have bought Vaio computers since November to upgrade their software after the discovery of a potentially serious software bug that could allow intruders access to their computers. The security advisory applies to customers in much of Asia and some Middle East an... 

http://www.cnn.com/2002/TECH/ptech/01/25/sony.security.idg/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7034-09"><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/01/10/living/steampunk-laptop/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Sony goes steampunk with gaming laptop</title><description>* What happens when you combine a laptop nicknamed The Beast with a subculture that is sweeping across the nation like a maelstrom? Sony has been steampunk'd, and the company asked for it. 

http://www.cnn.com/2012/01/10/living/steampunk-laptop/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7034-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7034_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:40:24">http://edition.cnn.com/2007/TECH/ptech/03/13/lenovo.thinkpad/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Review: Lenovo ThinkPad X60s a sweet laptop</title><description>* The latest model in the ThinkPad X series, the ultraportable X60s is almost imperceptibly lighter and thinner than its predecessor, the ThinkPad X41. 

http://www.cnn.com/2007/TECH/ptech/03/13/lenovo.thinkpad/index.html</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>