<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7078">count in korean</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:33:43" name="CNN" id="FW14-e101"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e101-7078-01"><link>http://www.cnn.com/ASIANOW/asiaweek/97/0801/nat1.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Asiaweek</title><description>* The popularity of the NKPs current leader, President Kim Young Sam, could hardly be lower. Corruption allegations stemming from the 1992 presidential election, together with the ongoing trial of his son and personal adviser Kim Hyun Chul for influence peddling, have severely weakened Kims position. Indeed, if his single, fiveyear term of office wer... 

http://www.cnn.com/ASIANOW/asiaweek/97/0801/nat1.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7078-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7078_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:35:31">http://edition.cnn.com/2014/04/21/world/asia/ship-captain-role/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Abandon ship? In recent maritime disasters, captains don't hang around</title><description>* When the HMS Birkenhead, a British ship carrying troops, began to sink off the coast of South Africa in 1852, the captain and military officers on board famously allowed women and children to board the lifeboats first. 

http://www.cnn.com/2014/04/21/world/asia/ship-captain-role/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7078-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7078_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:36:36">http://politicalticker.blogs.cnn.com/2014/04/16/cnns-gut-check-for-april-16-2014/?iref=allsearch</link><title>CNN's GUT CHECK for April 16, 2014</title><description>* CNN's GUT CHECK | for April 16, 2014 | 5 p.m. - n. a pause to assess the state, progress or condition of the political news cycle OBAMA SLAMS HOUSE GOP ON IMMIGRATION … Marking the one-year anniversary of the Senate’s passage of a comprehensive... 

http://politicalticker.blogs.cnn.com/2014/04/16/cnns-gut-check-for-april-16-2014/</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7078-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7078_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:38:19">http://edition.cnn.com/2014/04/16/opinion/hall-ukraine-russia-putin-nuclear/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Is Ukraine about to go nuclear again?</title><description>* As tensions escalate on the eastern border of Ukraine, President Barack Obama has called on Russian President Vladimir Putin and his government "to cease all efforts to undermine and destabilize" the sovereign nation after the movement of Russian troops into Ukraine and its annexing of Crimea. 

http://www.cnn.com/2014/04/16/opinion/hall-ukraine-russia-putin-nuclear/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7078-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7078_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:39:49">http://edition.cnn.com/2014/03/25/opinion/kane-malaysia-plane-international-effort/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Coming together: Flight 370 search unites global community</title><description>* "We must be on you but cannot see you." That was one of the very last voice signals transmitted by Amelia Earhart in the summer of 1937, somewhere over the vast Pacific Ocean during her ill-fated flight around the globe. 

http://www.cnn.com/2014/03/25/opinion/kane-malaysia-plane-international-effort/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7078-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7078_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:40:20">http://edition.cnn.com/2014/03/02/opinion/miller-ukraine-putin-mideast/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Putin's move could be costly to U.S., Middle East</title><description>* Ukrainian sovereignty won't be the only casualty of Russian President Vladimir Putin's efforts to assert Russian influence and interest in Crimea. 

http://www.cnn.com/2014/03/02/opinion/miller-ukraine-putin-mideast/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7078-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7078_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:41:16">http://edition.cnn.com/WORLD/9712/18/s.korea.outcome/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Kim apparent winner in S. Korean presidential election</title><description>* With more than threequarters of the votes counted, state television reported that Kim had received 40.3 percent of the vote compared to 38.6 percent for Lee, the governing party candidate. The third candidate in the race, Rhee Inje, received 19.6 percent of the vote. 

http://www.cnn.com/WORLD/9712/18/s.korea.outcome/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7078-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7078_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:42:15">http://edition.cnn.com/US/9707/11/briefs.pm/kim.sentencing/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Former Navy analyst gets prison term for spying</title><description>* U.S. District Judge Leonie Brinkema rejected leniency forKim, 57, a native South Korean who became a U.S. citizen in 1974. He had worked as a civilian computer specialist for the office of Naval Intelligence since 1978. He pleaded guilty in May to one count of conspiracy to commit espionage. 

http://www.cnn.com/US/9707/11/briefs.pm/kim.sentencing/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7078-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7078_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:43:15">http://edition.cnn.com/2010/WORLD/asiapcf/11/15/skorea.nkorea.defectors/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Report: N. Korean defectors reach 20,000 and counting</title><description>* The number of North Koreans who have defected to South Korea has passed 20,000, the Yonhap news agency said Monday. 

http://www.cnn.com/2010/WORLD/asiapcf/11/15/skorea.nkorea.defectors/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7078-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7078_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:43:55">http://edition.cnn.com/2014/02/18/sport/sochi-winter-olympics-day-11-wrap/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Sochi 2014: Dutch skaters clean up again to maintain spotless display</title><description>* It's becoming a familiar routine. 

http://www.cnn.com/2014/02/18/sport/sochi-winter-olympics-day-11-wrap/index.html</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>