<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7108">renting car seattle</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:13:09" name="CNN" id="FW14-e101"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e101-7108-01"><link>http://www.cnn.com/2010/TRAVEL/02/01/car.rental.tips/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Find a cheaper car rental away from the airport</title><description>* The best rate Darren Popik could find on a weekend car rental at Austin-Bergstrom International Airport recently was $114. So he decided to look elsewhere. 

http://www.cnn.com/2010/TRAVEL/02/01/car.rental.tips/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7108-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7108_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:14:38">http://edition.cnn.com/2014/04/15/travel/worlds-longest-bridges/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>10 of the world's longest bridges</title><description>* If you ever find yourself in Hunan, China, rent a car and drive the Jishou-Chadong Expressway: 18 tunnels under the Wuling mountains that culminate at the Aizhai Bridge, a gut-churning 1,150-foot-high suspension bridge over the Dehang Canyon. It's a man-made wonder, the world's highest (and mayb... 

http://www.cnn.com/2014/04/15/travel/worlds-longest-bridges/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7108-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7108_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:15:42">http://edition.cnn.com/2013/04/03/living/simplify-your-life-go-car-free/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Simplify your life: Go car-free</title><description>* When 25-year-old Emily Knies moved from Seattle to Chicago two years ago, being able to easily and happily live car-free was a key consideration. For one thing, she doesn't have a driver's license -- and from the time she was a kid, she never wanted to own a car. 

http://www.cnn.com/2013/04/03/living/simplify-your-life-go-car-free/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7108-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7108_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:16:55">http://edition.cnn.com/2008/BUSINESS/10/07/luxury.rental/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Keeping up appearances in the credit crunch</title><description>* So the credit crunch means this year's six-figure bonus has been put on hold, but you still need to keep up appearances at the country club -- what to do? Why not join the growing number of people who are choosing to rent, rather than buy, life's little luxuries? 

http://www.cnn.com/2008/BUSINESS/10/07/luxury.rental/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7108-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7108_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:17:53">http://edition.cnn.com/2008/TRAVEL/getaways/09/19/bainbridge.island/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Falling for Bainbridge Island</title><description>* Imagine yourself on a ferryboat deck with a latte in one hand, your overnight bag at your feet, and the dazzling Seattle, Washington, skyline filling the horizon behind you. While the boat churns across Elliott Bay, the Space Needle disappears from view and a shoreline materializes in the distance. 

http://www.cnn.com/2008/TRAVEL/getaways/09/19/bainbridge.island/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7108-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7108_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:18:48">http://edition.cnn.com/2011/11/09/travel/seattle-washington-too-nice/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Seattle was too nice for me</title><description>* Last time I was in Seattle I burned down an apartment. It wasn't arson; it was the faulty wiring on a trash-picked lamp. Or, from the look of the hard black puddle that used to be my stereo, a bad wall outlet. I never found out because two days later I left town to wait tables at Yellowstone National Park. 

http://www.cnn.com/2011/11/09/travel/seattle-washington-too-nice/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7108-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7108_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:19:31">http://edition.cnn.com/2001/LAW/07/02/millennium.bomb.trial/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Gov't witness reveals details of Y2K bomb plot</title><description>* A government witness Monday told a jury defendant Mokhtar Haouari asked him to travel to Seattle, Washington, in December 1999 to assist someone who would be carrying out a violent act in the United States. 

http://www.cnn.com/2001/LAW/07/02/millennium.bomb.trial/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7108-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7108_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:20:22">http://edition.cnn.com/2000/US/01/27/border.arrest.01/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Ressam pleads not guilty on bomb smuggling charges</title><description>* SEATTLE CNN Ahmed Ressam pleaded not guilty Thursday to charges ofbomb smuggling and conspiring to commit an act of international terrorism thatcarry a combined maximum prison sentence of 135 years. 

http://www.cnn.com/2000/US/01/27/border.arrest.01/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7108-09"><link>http://www.cnn.com/2000/TRAVEL/NEWS/02/14/vacation.rentals.lat/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Travel How to rent a vacation homeawayfromhome</title><description>* You can choose modern luxury apartments near shopping and cultural attractions in the worlds capitals, romantic retreats on secluded beaches, country cottages, mountainside chalets, historic manor houses and more. 

http://www.cnn.com/2000/TRAVEL/NEWS/02/14/vacation.rentals.lat/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7108-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7108_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:21:50">http://edition.cnn.com/2008/TRAVEL/11/04/seattle.localview1/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Seattle: A local's view</title><description>* Scott grew up in Texas and has lived in Seattle for 11 years. He runs the Central District News blog, which keeps tabs on the news in Quincy Jones's old neighborhood. Here he gives CNN the lowdown on life in Seattle. 

http://www.cnn.com/2008/TRAVEL/11/04/seattle.localview1/index.html</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>