<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7265">grassland plants</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:46:09" name="CNN" id="FW14-e101"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e101-7265-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7265_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:46:36">http://edition.cnn.com/2014/04/22/travel/nature-must-see-shows/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>15 of nature's most spectacular shows</title><description>* Fireworks are fantastic and human endeavor has its place, but sometimes Mother Nature outshines any performance we can produce. 

http://www.cnn.com/2014/04/22/travel/nature-must-see-shows/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7265-02"><link>http://www.cnn.com/2014/04/02/opinion/turner-wetlands-protection-epa/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Ted Turner: Time to finally protect wetlands, streams</title><description>* Clean water is vital to every single American. Families should be able to turn on the tap and have safe drinking water for their children, vacationers expect healthy rivers for fishing and swimming, and businesses need a steady supply of clean water to make products. 

http://www.cnn.com/2014/04/02/opinion/turner-wetlands-protection-epa/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7265-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7265_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:48:29">http://edition.cnn.com/TECH/science/9902/05/carbon.enn/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Carbon storage key to fighting global warming</title><description>* The storage of carbon in agricultural lands, forests and grasslands can play an important role in fighting global warming in the 21st century, energy and agricultural officials concluded at a recent workshop in St. Michaels, Md. 

http://www.cnn.com/TECH/science/9902/05/carbon.enn/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7265-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7265_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:49:07">http://edition.cnn.com/TECH/science/9805/26/prarire/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Fires role in prairie survival stressed</title><description>* ENN The smell of burning leaves has always been a sure sign of autumn. But springtime in the Kansas Flint Hills often confuses the olfactory senses because of the prescribed burning that takes place at the Konza Prairie Research Natural Area and area ranches. 

http://www.cnn.com/TECH/science/9805/26/prarire/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7265-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7265_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:49:30">http://edition.cnn.com/2012/09/21/living/oprah-rancher/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>An amateur rancher brings the wastelands of the Southwest back to life</title><description>* The land was parched and cracked and scattered with stones, as if the clouds had rained rocks in this part of the world. Small, thorny mesquites dotted the landscape, their taproots tunneling far beneath the soil to suck whatever water lay there. Creosote bushes fanned out from their mounds of chalky dirt and arroyos twisted this way and that, like... 

http://www.cnn.com/2012/09/21/living/oprah-rancher/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7265-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7265_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:50:37">http://edition.cnn.com/NATURE/9910/28/asia.quest/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>AsiaQuest</title><description>* As we head east along Marco Polos route, the cities are getting bigger and more modern. Here in Zhangye, we see fewer farmers, donkey carts, and horses and more modern apartment buildings, hotels and lights. Compared to Kashgar, its like Las Vegas Everyone has electricity and at night the restaurants and storefronts are lit up like Christmas trees.... 

http://www.cnn.com/NATURE/9910/28/asia.quest/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7265-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7265_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:50:59">http://edition.cnn.com/NATURE/9905/17/invasive.species.enn/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Invasive species threaten healthy ecosystems</title><description>* Even healthy ecosystems are vulnerable to invasions by exotic species, according to scientists with the U.S. Geological Survey. 

http://www.cnn.com/NATURE/9905/17/invasive.species.enn/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7265-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7265_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:51:19">http://edition.cnn.com/2009/TECH/science/03/19/endangered.birds.report/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Many bird populations in trouble, report says</title><description>* Bird populations native to several areas of the globe are in decline, with some teetering on the brink of extinction, according to a multi-agency report, the first of its kind, released Thursday. 

http://www.cnn.com/2009/TECH/science/03/19/endangered.birds.report/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7265-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7265_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:52:01">http://edition.cnn.com/2008/TECH/02/24/eco.biofuels/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Biofuels: 'Green gold' or problems untold?</title><description>* No subject appears to divide as many people in the climate change arena as biofuels. Their potential to positively impact greenhouse gas emissions is undoubtedly enormous. 

http://www.cnn.com/2008/TECH/02/24/eco.biofuels/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7265-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7265_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 20:52:30">http://edition.cnn.com/2007/TECH/science/10/25/env.environment.fires/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Warmer temperatures tied to wildfires, scientists say</title><description>* Huge wildfires, such as the ones that have charred more than 460,000 acres this week in Southern California, are becoming more common in the Western United States, and scientists say warming trends and other climate factors may be responsible. 

http://www.cnn.com/2007/TECH/science/10/25/env.environment.fires/index.html</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>