<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7490">convert wav mp3</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:08:03" name="CNN" id="FW14-e101"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e101-7490-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7490_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:08:28">http://edition.cnn.com/2000/TECH/computing/03/27/flashtrax.idg/hs~index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Technology Play MP3s on cassette with FlashTrax</title><description>* IDG MP3 tunes are great when youre hooked to your PC or if you have a portable player. But dont you wish you could play your MP3 tunes on your cars cassette player, or that oldbutstillserviceable Walkman A method is in development, and it wont involve laborious conversions from http://www.cnn.com/2000/TECH/computing/03/27/flashtrax.idg/hs~index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7490-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7490_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:08:46">http://edition.cnn.com/TECH/computing/9902/24/topsound.idg/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Top 10 sound tools</title><description>* IDG Whether you have a tincan sound card or one with cuttingedge fidelity, youll want to make the most of your PCs audio capabilities. You can download audio shareware that lets you play CDs, convert text to speech, and edit and record sound on a variety of different formats, including wavetable, MP3 http://www.cnn.com/TECH/computing/9902/24/topsound.idg/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7490-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7490_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:09:01">http://edition.cnn.com/2001/TECH/ptech/11/28/lp.to.cd.idg/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>How to turn your LPs into CDs or MP3s</title><description>* If you're a music fan, you probably already know that you can turn tracks from a store-bought CD into digital MP3 files. But if you still haven't left the analog age of vinyl LPs or cassettes behind, don't fret: You too can enjoy the fun of making your albums into CDs or putting them into an MP3... 

http://www.cnn.com/2001/TECH/ptech/11/28/lp.to.cd.idg/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7490-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7490_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:09:21">http://edition.cnn.com/TECH/computing/9906/07/topmp3.idg/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Top 10 MP3 utilities</title><description>* nALSOnnn Message Board MP3 The new wave nnnSign up for the Computer Connection email servicennnFor more computing storiesnn 

http://www.cnn.com/TECH/computing/9906/07/topmp3.idg/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7490-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7490_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:09:40">http://edition.cnn.com/2000/TECH/computing/03/07/top.mp3.idg/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Technology Top 10 MP3 tools</title><description>* IDG Beef up your music collection with this handy assortment of MP3 tools. With MP3 encoders and allinone players, you can compress or rip, in MP3 parlance music from audio CDs into MP3 files. You can use the players to compile a playlist of ... 

http://www.cnn.com/2000/TECH/computing/03/07/top.mp3.idg/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7490-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7490_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:10:01">http://edition.cnn.com/2000/TECH/computing/02/03/mp3.works.idg/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>How MP3 works</title><description>* IDG MP3 MPEG1, Layer 3 a compression standard that creates relatively small digital audio files with highfidelity sound. Highquality digital sound. Small file sizes. Most widely accepted digital audio standard. No system for protecting copyrights. 

http://www.cnn.com/2000/TECH/computing/02/03/mp3.works.idg/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7490-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7490_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:10:32">http://edition.cnn.com/2008/TECH/ptech/04/18/zoom.h2/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Zoom brings more muscle to everyday audio</title><description>* MP3 players and cell phones are fine for recording the occasional voice memo, but recording a music recital or broadcast-quality interview requires a product with more muscle. The Zoom H2 is not the smallest or best-sounding mobile audio recorder we've come across, but with an unbeatable street price of about $200 and a d... 

http://www.cnn.com/2008/TECH/ptech/04/18/zoom.h2/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7490-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7490_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:10:53">http://edition.cnn.com/2000/TECH/computing/11/29/top.mp3.idg/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Top 5 MP3 players</title><description>* 1\. Winamp: Listen to high-quality digital music with this popular--and free--utility, which supports an array of formats, including MP3, CD, WMA, Audiosoft, Mjuice, and MOD. It offers a skinnable interface and supports audio/visual plug-ins that allow you to create multimedia effects. With its extensive customization opti... 

http://www.cnn.com/2000/TECH/computing/11/29/top.mp3.idg/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7490-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7490_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:11:08">http://edition.cnn.com/2007/TECH/ptech/02/20/creative.zen.v.plus/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Review: Creative Zen V Plus a pocket-friendly player</title><description>* Creative Labs has a history of turning out great MP3 players, and the Zen V and the Zen V Plus -- available in July and August, respectively -- are no exception. 

http://www.cnn.com/2007/TECH/ptech/02/20/creative.zen.v.plus/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7490-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7490_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:11:49">http://edition.cnn.com/2000/TECH/computing/12/08/mp3.holiday.gadgets.idg/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Holiday gift guide: MP3 gadgets</title><description>* What it does: Place up to 32M bytes of MP3 music onto your watch. Connects to your PC via USB. Perfect for jogging, extreme mobility saves on other bulky gadgets. 

http://www.cnn.com/2000/TECH/computing/12/08/mp3.holiday.gadgets.idg/index.html</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>