<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7496">why IEEE member</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:32:08" name="CNN" id="FW14-e101"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e101-7496-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7496_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:32:21">http://edition.cnn.com/2012/09/18/tech/innovation/ieee-2040-cars/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>You won't need a driver's license by 2040</title><description>* The timeline for autonomous cars hitting the road en masse keeps getting closer. GM's Cadillac division expects to produce partially autonomous cars at a large scale by 2015, and the automaker also predicts it will have fully autonomous cars available by the end of the decade. Audi and BMW have also shown self-driving car concepts, with the former ... 

http://www.cnn.com/2012/09/18/tech/innovation/ieee-2040-cars/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7496-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7496_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:33:02">http://edition.cnn.com/2000/TECH/computing/08/01/10g.ethernet.idg/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Low-cost Ethernet at risk</title><description>* A low-cost option for 10-Gigabit Ethernet is meeting early resistance in the IEEE, potentially leaving users with only high-priced alternatives. 

http://www.cnn.com/2000/TECH/computing/08/01/10g.ethernet.idg/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7496-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7496_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:33:37">http://edition.cnn.com/2001/TECH/industry/10/31/usb.battle.idg/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>USB 2.0 prepares to battle for your PC</title><description>* One of the computing world's newest networking standards, USB 2.0, will be battling for the attention of visitors at the upcoming Comdex Fall show with IEEE 1394, an already established format that is spreading its wings to encompass a greater number of uses and a soon-to-come speed upgrade. The two formats have their roo... 

http://www.cnn.com/2001/TECH/industry/10/31/usb.battle.idg/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7496-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7496_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:33:55">http://edition.cnn.com/TECH/computing/9910/27/vlan.comeback.idg/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Are VLANs on the comeback trail</title><description>* IDG After stumbling out of the limelight a few years ago, virtual LANs may be poised for a comeback, thanks to the efforts of two standards bodies. 

http://www.cnn.com/TECH/computing/9910/27/vlan.comeback.idg/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7496-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7496_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:34:14">http://edition.cnn.com/2000/TECH/computing/01/25/wap.threat.idg/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Wireless standard threatened by GeoWorks claim of patent infringement</title><description>* IDG Just when everyone in the mobile industry thought it was safe to unite on a wireless standard the Wireless Application Protocol WAP GeoWorks is claiming infringement on its Intellectual Property Rights. n MESSAGE BOARDSmart cell phones n 

http://www.cnn.com/2000/TECH/computing/01/25/wap.threat.idg/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7496-06"><link>http://www.cnn.com/TECH/computing/9810/08/whorules.idg/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>The rules have changed</title><description>* IDG Four years ago, Network World published a series of three articles suggesting Microsoft was gaining control of the network through its ability to set de facto standards. The series made the case that Microsoft had sprinted ahead of plodding standards groups and used its market share to push its specifications so far into the market that even it... 

http://www.cnn.com/TECH/computing/9810/08/whorules.idg/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7496-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7496_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:35:07">http://whatsnext.blogs.cnn.com/2013/07/19/robots-the-future-of-elder-care/?iref=allsearch</link><title>Robots: The future of elder care?</title><description>* By Heather Kelly, CNN Would you let a robot take over as a live-in nurse for your aging parent or grandparent? In 2050, the elderly will account for 16 percent of the global population. That's 1.5 billion people over the age of 65, according to the... 

http://whatsnext.blogs.cnn.com/2013/07/19/robots-the-future-of-elder-care/</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7496-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7496_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:35:43">http://edition.cnn.com/2001/TECH/industry/09/14/tech.aid.idg/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Tech firms rush to get companies working again</title><description>* In the wake of Tuesday's terrorist attack, technology companies are rushing to aid disaster relief, the families of victims, and businesses affected by the tragedy. 

http://www.cnn.com/2001/TECH/industry/09/14/tech.aid.idg/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7496-09"><link>http://www.cnn.com/2000/TECH/computing/02/14/10gig.group.idg/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>10Gig Ethernet gets a voice</title><description>* IDG With momentum building around highspeed Ethernet, a group of vendors established the 10Gigabit Ethernet Alliance to propagate the technology. 

http://www.cnn.com/2000/TECH/computing/02/14/10gig.group.idg/index.html</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e101-7496-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e101/7496_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:36:31">http://edition.cnn.com/2014/01/15/tech/innovation/google-connect-home-nest/index.html?iref=allsearch</link><title>Google wants to run your home with Nest</title><description>* Google is knocking at your front door. It wants to come inside, make itself at home, and quietly turn all of your boring home devices into "smart" connected gadgets that learn about your patterns and preferences, talk to each other, collect data about your habits and make life easier by assisting with daily tasks. 

http://www.cnn.com/2014/01/15/tech/innovation/google-connect-home-nest/index.html</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>