<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7020">synovial joint</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:35:55" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7020-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7020_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:35:55">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x12gv1r_synovial-fluid-analysis-results-interpretation-sample-risks_tech</link><title>Synovial Fluid Analysis (Results Interpretation, Sample, Risks)</title><description>Synovial Fluid Analysis (Results Interpretation, Sample, Risks)

Toegevoegd door medsipodotcom laatste juli

The Synovial Fluid Analysis is used to identify if bacteria are present in an inflamed joint. To find out everything about this test and to interpret your test results, visit MedSipo - Medical Tests Interpreter: http://medsipo.com/details/joint-aspirate-for-culture Song credit: Earnest Kevin MacLeod (incompetech.com) Licensed under Creative Commons: By Attribution 3.0 http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/3.0/

56 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7020_01_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/CJog-/220x123-m4h.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7020-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7020_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:38:28">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xshv4w_treatment-options-for-synovial-cysts_school</link><title>Treatment Options For Synovial Cysts</title><description>Treatment Options For Synovial Cysts

Toegevoegd door paulwinston vorig jaar

http://www.ani-online.com/neurology-services-2.php - Many people wonder what the treatment options are for synovial cysts. However, spinal cysts are often completely painless and can go undetected for years.

65 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7020_02_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/Mf0E/220x123-92E.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7020-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7020_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:41:21">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xwj783_treatment-for-a-synovial-cyst-spine_school</link><title>Treatment For A Synovial Cyst Spine</title><description>Treatment For A Synovial Cyst Spine

Toegevoegd door shirleymarino11 vorig jaar

http://www.ani-online.com/neurology-services-2.php - A synovial cyst spine requires treatment as soon as possible, because it is an incredibly painful condition. Most people with synovial cysts on the spine find it hard to walk and function. Spinal cysts can be removed through surgical procedures, although they can also simply be drained. A medical professional will usually perform tumor resection, to check whether the cyst is benign or malignant.

210 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7020_03_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BBuX9/220x123-yk6.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7020-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7020_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:44:34">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xshv0s_various-synovial-cyst-spine-treatments_school</link><title>Various Synovial Cyst Spine Treatments</title><description>Various Synovial Cyst Spine Treatments

Toegevoegd door jennywalter vorig jaar

http://www.ani-online.com/neurology-services-2.php - Synovial cyst spine treatments are necessary if you want to rid yourself of lower back pain. If left untreated, synovial cysts can get bigger and just worsen over time.

120 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7020_04_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/MfTz/220x123-Rjd.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7020-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7020_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:45:27">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x16bqfs_joint-warrior-13-2-clap-de-fin_news</link><title>Joint Warrior 13-2 : clap de fin</title><description>Joint Warrior 13-2 : clap de fin

Toegevoegd door Armée de l'Air officiel laatste oktober

Bilan positif pour la France, le Royaume-Uni et les sept autres nations ayant participé à l'exercice Joint Warrior du 7 au 17 octobre 2013.

15 823 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7020_05_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CtZ76/220x123-JSs.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7020-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7020_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:48:46">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x171zfr_miley-cyrus-twerks-with-dwarf-smokes-joint-at-emas_news</link><title>Miley Cyrus twerks with dwarf, 'smokes joint' at EMAs</title><description>Miley Cyrus twerks with dwarf, 'smokes joint' at EMAs

Toegevoegd door reuters laatste november

ROUGH CUT - NO REPORTER NARRATION Miley Cyrus stole the show at the 2013 MTV EMA music awards on Sunday (November 10) by lighting what could have been a joint, in a nod to the host city's famously tolerant attitude towards soft drugs. She had earlier been photographed in one of Amsterdam's best-known coffeeshops where soft drugs are on the menu. When Cyrus picked up her best video award for "Wrecking Ball", she made a show of not finding the space for the bauble in her handbag. "You know I couldn't fit this award in my bag but I did find this," she said, pulling out a hand-rolled cigarette which she lit as she walked off the stage.

17 128 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7020_06_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/C3VSe/220x123-RPZ.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7020-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7020_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:51:31">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x16trom_joint-warrior-les-temps-forts_news</link><title>Joint Warrior : les temps forts</title><description>Joint Warrior : les temps forts

Toegevoegd door Armée de l'Air officiel laatste november

Revivez en vidéo les moments forts de l'exercice Joint Warrior qui s'est déroulé dans le courant du mois d'octobre au Royaume-Uni.

17 195 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7020_07_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CyUfm/220x123-Hr-.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7020-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7020_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:55:07">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1ntd0i_enfant-fume-un-joint_news</link><title>Enfant fume un joint</title><description>Enfant fume un joint

Toegevoegd door Spi0n een week geleden

La vidéo Vine qui fait scandale en ce moment aux États-Unis, est celle d'un enfant en bas âge aux toilettes, qui tire une taf sur un joint de cannabis, tendu par l'un de ses parents. C'est l'utilisateur du réseau social Vine "Chief Smokes" qui a publié la vidéo sur son compte puis qui fut re-uploadée par NikoWavy. Après avoir été retweetée plus de 40 000 fois et créée la polémique, elle fût supprimée. Depuis, des internautes disent avoir contacté les services de la protection de l’enfance en Californie afin de retrouver les parents responsables de cet acte.

2 545 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7020_08_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/EMqtq/220x123-oxG.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7020-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7020_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:58:10">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x17220i_mtv-european-awards-miley-cyrus-et-son-joint_news</link><title>MTV European Awards: Miley Cyrus et son "joint"</title><description>MTV European Awards: Miley Cyrus et son "joint"

Toegevoegd door euronews-fr laatste november

“Je n’ai pas de place dans mon sac pour le trophée mais j’ai trouvé ça…”, dixit Miley Cyrus après avoir reçu le prix de la Meilleure vidéo lors des MTV European Music Awards hier à Amsterdam aux Pays-Bas. “Ça”, c‘était un joint ou ce qui ressemblait à un joint que la chanteuse pop américaine a fumé sur scène. Miley Cyrus a été récompensée pour le clip “Wrecking Ball”. Le prix de la Meilleure artiste féminine, lui, est revenu à Katy Perry. La star américaine avait auparavant chanté dans les airs “Unconditionally”.Eminem a été le grand vaiinqueur de la soirée en remportant deux prix, celui du meilleur artiste hip hop et celui “d’icône planétaire”. Le rappeur americain avait été récompensé une semaine auparavant par les premiers Youtube Music Awards.Avec AFP et Reuters

12 074 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7020_09_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/C3XxS/220x123-3Q6.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7020-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7020_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:01:55">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x160xgw_joint-warrior-13-2-cooperation-franco-britannique_news</link><title>Joint Warrior 13-2, coopération franco-britannique</title><description>Joint Warrior 13-2, coopération franco-britannique

Toegevoegd door Armée de l'Air officiel laatste oktober

Le 07 octobre 2013 a marqué le coup d’envoi de l’exercice Joint Warrior 13.2 dans le ciel britannique, concrétisant la coopération franco-britannique établie en 2010 par la signature du traité de Lancaster House. Pendant 10 jours, la France et le Royaume-Uni participent avec sept autres nations (Allemagne, Australie, Canada, Danemark, Etats-Unis, Italie, Norvège) à un exercice centré sur des manœuvres aéromaritimes, dans lesquelles une quarantaine d’aéronefs et une quinzaine de bâtiments sont engagés.

13 135 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7020_10_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/Cpn1A/220x123-wTG.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>