<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7023">calculate jordan normal form</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:55:40" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7023-01"><link>http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1itpvy_hindi-microsoft-access-pt-5-form-create-tab-navigation-form-calculate-fields_school</link><title>(Hindi) Microsoft Access pt 5 (Form, Create Tab, Navigation form, Calculate fields)</title><description>(Hindi) Microsoft Access pt 5 (Form, Create Tab, Navigation form, Calculate fields)

Toegevoegd door Puneet 4 weken geleden

1 view</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7023_01_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/D9r3a/220x123-9TG.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7023-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7023_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:57:38">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xs84t4_tian-lavii-normal-feat-osb-crew-jordan-corentin_music</link><title>Tian - LavIi normal - feat OSB crew &amp; jordan corentin</title><description>Tian - LavIi normal - feat OSB crew &amp; jordan corentin

Toegevoegd door tex2005 vorig jaar

167 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7023_02_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/ArXHk/220x123-m35.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7023-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7023_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:01:44">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x19sv2t_turbotax-premier-2013-mac-cracked-download_tech</link><title>TurboTax Premier 2013 MAC Cracked DOWNLOAD</title><description>TurboTax Premier 2013 MAC Cracked DOWNLOAD

Toegevoegd door SecurityCode04 laatste januari

TurboTax Premier 2013 MAC Cracked DOWNLOAD Visit: http://www.new-cracked-softwares.info/

11 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7023_03_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DbHHq/220x123-Nui.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7023-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7023_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:04:37">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x19svar_turbotax-deluxe-2013-mac-download_tech</link><title>TurboTax Deluxe 2013 MAC DOWNLOAD</title><description>TurboTax Deluxe 2013 MAC DOWNLOAD

Toegevoegd door SecurityCode04 laatste januari

TurboTax Deluxe 2013 MAC DOWNLOAD Visit: http://www.new-cracked-softwares.info

6 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7023_04_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DbHLH/220x123-PKZ.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7023-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7023_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:07:46">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xqbvu3_what-are-irs-tax-forms-all-about-using-irs-tax-forms_school</link><title>What are IRS Tax Forms? All About Using IRS Tax Forms</title><description>What are IRS Tax Forms? All About Using IRS Tax Forms

Toegevoegd door Turbo Tax vorig jaar

http://turbotax.intuit.com What are IRS tax forms? Learn all about using IRS tax forms to help calculate your income taxes this year with this tax tips video from TurboTax.

17 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7023_05_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/Y8uN/220x123-nnB.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7023-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7023_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:11:41">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xghfjh_dingoo-test-hexcite-shapes-of-victory-game-boy-color_videogames</link><title>Dingoo Test - Hexcite Shapes of Victory Game Boy Color</title><description>Dingoo Test - Hexcite Shapes of Victory Game Boy Color

Toegevoegd door alamass 3 jaren geleden

Dingoo test de Hexcite Shapes of Victory (Glocal Hexcite) sur Game Boy Color par Satanos.

51 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7023_06_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/AZ15F/220x123-ySk.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7023-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7023_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:14:46">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xpp4il_jordan-tanner_music</link><title>JORDAN TANNER</title><description>JORDAN TANNER

Toegevoegd door BalconyTV 2 jaren geleden

http://www.BalconyTV.com‬ 'Like' uns auf Facebook - http://on.fb.me/mhECp2Sound Engineer - Nick SmithAudio &amp; Video production by Joe LynchPRESENTED BY LEE ANN McADOOJordan Tanner is an American singer, musician, songwriter, and producer. Born and raised in Roanoke, VA, Jordan attended the College of Charleston in South Carolina and earned a Bachelor of Arts in Philosophy. In the summer of 2006, he played guitar on tour for the Charleston-based band, The Working Title, opening for such acts as The Fray, Counting Crows, and The Goo Goo Dolls.Upon relocating to Austin, TX in February of 2007 he has been a full-time working musician. Constantly performing solo in and around the Austin area, Tanner is known for his employment of on-the-fly sampling, layering of vocal harmonies, excessive use of ambience and delay, and a dynamic vocal style. Jordan Tanner fronted The Vincents, an alternative rock trio including drummer Stephen Roberts and bassist Brandon Hill, from mid 2008 to mid 2009. The short-lived project yielded a recording, The Vincents EP (released March 16, 2009), which Tanner engineered and produced. The six-track EP featured an early version of "Visions of a Girl," which would later appear on his solo album.In late 2010, Tanner announced that he would be releasing this debut solo record in early 2011. Released March 16, 2011, "All of the Night" reflects more musical maturity and higher production quality than the previous Vincents EP. Playing all the instruments and singing all the vocals, Jordan assembled a record that is fairly calculated, while still diverse enough to boast ambient beauties ("Life to Lose"), organic rants ("Wake of Your Love") and radio-ready gems ("Taking Out the Love," "Visions of a Girl"). Jordan is currently in the process of forming a band around "All of the Night" with a CD release show in the works and future dates to support sales of the record.In addition to performing and recording music, Jordan's other career pursuits to date have involved acting, graphic design, and education.www.jordantanner.net/kickstarterwww.jordantanner.netTUNE IN AGAIN SOON FOR MORE FROM BALCONYTV AUSTIN!!!

50 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7023_07_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/Ap2mh/220x123-LyZ.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7023-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7023_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:15:42">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xvehk6_trust-your-driver_shortfilms</link><title>Trust Your Driver</title><description>Trust Your Driver

Toegevoegd door Brenton Oechsle vorig jaar

Never trust anyone who always tells the truth.He was engaged to the love of his life. Two weeks before the wedding she cheated on him. This sent him into a tailspin - he had to escape. How could he learn to trust anyone anymore? He started hitchhiking across the country - forcing himself to trust those around him. He changed himself on the outside but his heart was still broken on inside. He fears of truly trusting someone else as much as he did his fiancé. Over time and through the people that he meets - he learns that he does not have to hide behind a shroud of lies to seem normal and cultivate trust in others.In its simplest form this film depicts one hitchhiker being picked up by five drivers. If you met this hitchhiker - you would not be likely to meet one similar again. He is very open on a first impression but on the inside is very guarded. He will answer any question that you have for him until a line is crossed which he will proceed to direct the conversation back towards you. He will lie if he has to. He is not crazy but calculated and manipulative. When someone picks up a hitchhiker or is a hitchhiker being picked up - there is an invisible contract of trust that is entered into. This film explores that dynamic of trust. Ultimately, the hitchhiker serves as a microcosm for the nature of trust that people have for one another today in our ever discreet society.

30 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7023_08_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/Alz5T/220x123-Abr.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7023-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7023_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:17:54">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xxalig_jordan-tanner_music</link><title>JORDAN TANNER</title><description>JORDAN TANNER

Toegevoegd door BalconyTV vorig jaar

Like' us on Facebook - http://on.fb.me/mhECp2 Follow us on Twitter - http://bit.ly/tGop1yPRESENTED BY LAUREN PETREE Jordan Tanner (born June 14, 1982) is an American singer, musician, songwriter, and performer. Jordan is currently making a full-length album with platinum producer Rick Beato (Shinedown, Needtobreathe). Slated for release in late summer 2012, the new record is a milestone for Tanner's career and songwriting.Born and raised in Roanoke, VA, Jordan attended the College of Charleston in South Carolina and earned a Bachelor of Arts in Philosophy. In the summer of 2006, he played guitar on tour for the Charleston-based band, The Working Title, opening for such acts as The Fray, Counting Crows, and The Goo Goo Dolls. Upon relocating to Austin, TX in February of 2007 he has been a full-time working musician. Constantly performing solo in and around the Austin area, Tanner is known for his employment of on-the-fly sampling, layering of vocal harmonies, excessive use of ambience and delay, and a dynamic vocal style. Jordan Tanner fronted The Vincents, an alternative rock trio featuring Stephen Roberts and Brandon Hill, from mid 2008 to mid 2009. The short-lived project yielded a recording, The Vincents EP (released March 16, 2009), which Tanner engineered and produced. The six-track EP featured an early version of "Visions of a Girl," which would go on to be released on some future recordings.Jordan's first solo record, released in 2011, "All of the Night" reflects more musical maturity and higher production quality than the previous Vincents EP. Playing all the instruments and singing all the vocals, Jordan assembled a record that is fairly calculated, while still diverse enough to boast ambient beauties ("Life to Lose"), organic rants ("Wake of Your Love") and radio-ready gems ("Taking Out the Love," "Visions of a Girl"). Tune in again to BalconyTV //

26 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7023_09_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/BGFMX/220x123-OmJ.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7023-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7023_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:20:01">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xut735_new-wolfteam-hack-2013-download-aimbot-etc_videogames</link><title>[New] WolfTeam Hack 2013 Download Aimbot etc.</title><description>[New] WolfTeam Hack 2013 Download Aimbot etc.

Toegevoegd door WolfteamCheats vorig jaar

Download:http://goo.gl/3LbEF FREE HACK FEATURE LIST Aimbot * Auto Aim/Auto Shoot * Full 360 FOV Aimbot, can even see behind you * Bone Scan, Find a bone to hit when the player hides * Aim key, Select and use any aimkey you want to use * Choose from different Hitboxes to aim for; Head/Neck/Chest/Waist * Select Enemies, Friends, or Everyone as your target * Smooth Aim, Makes you look like a normal player * Visibility Checks, Aimbot only locks on when player can be hit * Knifebot with boneaim to target any area of the enemy * Auto Pistol, Hold down the fire key and watch it auto unload * Target by closest to distance or closest to crosshair * Full No Spread, All bullets hit dead on center * Auto Knife, Will knife as soon as enemy is in range ESP * Smart Bounding Boxes, Enemy is red, Target is yellow * Name Tags, Show names of all friendlies and enemies * Health Tags, Show health of all friendlies and enemies * Visual Tags, Shows an icon or frame around enemies * Class Tags, Show class of all enemies and friendlies * Distance Tags, Show the distance to all players MiniMap * Reveals enemy positions on the Minimap Misc * Trigger Bot, Only fires when your crosshair hovers over the enemy * Two Tone Chams, Shows the players in bright colors * Show FPS, Show how many frames per second you’re running * Show Time, Display the current time in game * Visual Toggle, Makes many ingame objects disappear * No Post Production, Removes Smoke, Fire, Etc Config Menu * Save up to 3 configurations and load them anytime Full Ingame Menu * Access the Hack Menu During Gameplay and Change Options on the Fly That’s it, have fun hacking. The ballistics aimbot is able to calculate the exact angle for a clean kill, even from the other side of the map! It does not mater if you are using normal weapons, turrets or tank. It is capable of controlling any vehicle turret with pinpoint accuracy “

1 944 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7023_10_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/tJD-/220x123-qMz.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>