<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7027">prefered or preferred</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:47:22" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7027-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7027_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:47:23">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1dz9vy_why-amadeus-system-is-one-of-the-most-preferred-gds-systems-today-call-us-at-91-80-50006556-or-email_tech</link><title>Why Amadeus System is one of the most preferred GDS Systems today (Call Us at +91.80.50006556 or email us at info@provab.com)</title><description>Why Amadeus System is one of the most preferred GDS Systems today (Call Us at +91.80.50006556 or email us at info@provab.com)

Toegevoegd door David Mathew laatste maart

Why Amadeus System is one of the most preferred GDS Systems today (Call Us at +91.80.50006556 or email us at info@provab.com) Travel Portal Development Company – http://www.provab.com GDS Systems are one of the most preferred ways for travel management companies to connect to online travel contents, flights, hotels, cars, cruise, transfers, sightseeing and similar things. Amadeus system is one of the leading GDS today. In only 20 years, Amadeus has become the largest global distribution system provider in the world. It had great reach to travel contents worldwide, in terms of buyers and sellers. It is a leading transaction processor for the global travel and tourism industry. Amadeus system has all the core competencies and merits to succeed in the long run, not only because it’s a comprehensive travel management system, but also its diversity in aggregating the travel contents. Over 90,000 travel agencies globally, use the Amadeus system. Amadeus is structured around two major competencies, GDS and travel IT solutions. Amadeus as a technology provider for airlines have the below functionalities In Inventory Management Reservation process PNR Generation Passenger Profiling Amadeus, which is a leading travel technology partner and transaction processor for the global travel and tourism industry, has also emerged as the technology provider of choice for the hotel booking platform in the MENA i.e. Middle East and North African region. To know more about us, please visit www.provab.com. You can call us at +91.80.50006556 and email us at info@provab.com. With Regards, David Mathew Business Manager PROVAB TECHNOSOFT http://www.provab.com

30 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7027_01_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/Dxjum/220x123-F4j.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7027-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7027_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:49:32">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1kyi7l_best-price-kids-preferred-lion-king-hand-rattle-simba_auto</link><title>best price Kids Preferred Lion King Hand Rattle Simba</title><description>best price Kids Preferred Lion King Hand Rattle Simba

Toegevoegd door Libigarlo1971 3 weken geleden

best price Kids Preferred Lion King Hand Rattle Simba Click on the discount link below: http://www.amazon.com/dp/B008S0BFXU/?tag=60percentoff2-20 Disclaimer: I am a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon. Amazon and the Amazon logo are trademarks of Amazon, Inc. or its affiliates.

0 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7027_02_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/EEQcN/220x123-KyO.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7027-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7027_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:50:03">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xp42nd_preferred-chrysler-dodge-jeep-near-holland-mi-2012-jeep-liberty_auto</link><title>Preferred Chrysler Dodge Jeep near Holland, MI 2012 Jeep Liberty</title><description>Preferred Chrysler Dodge Jeep near Holland, MI 2012 Jeep Liberty

Toegevoegd door PreferredAuto 2 jaren geleden

http://PreferredChryslerDodgeJeep.com 888-279-4277 The 2012 Jeep Liberty is powered by a 3.7-liter V6 that produces 210 hp and 235 pound-feet of torque. A four-speed automatic is the only transmission offered. Rear-wheel drive is standard and there are two different four-wheel-drive systems available, including the part-time Command-Trac and the full-time Selec-Trac. A properly equipped Liberty can tow as much as 5,000 pounds.

7 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7027_03_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/YRoU/220x123-u2r.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7027-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7027_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:51:46">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xp3av2_preferred-ford-of-grand-haven-mi-and-a-2012-ford-focus-electric_auto</link><title>Preferred Ford of Grand Haven, MI and a 2012 Ford Focus Electric</title><description>Preferred Ford of Grand Haven, MI and a 2012 Ford Focus Electric

Toegevoegd door PreferredAuto 2 jaren geleden

http://PreferredFord.com 888-283-6402 The 2012 Ford Focus Electric gets all of its power from an advanced 23kWh, high-voltage, lithium-ion battery system, which means you'll never need a drop of gas. It features an advanced liquid heating and cooling system to regulate battery temperature and help maximize battery life, so you can get the most miles out of each charge. The all-electric motor is designed to help reduce energy loss and heat generation while reducing your carbon footprint. To charge the high-voltage, lithium-ion battery system quickly, you can have an optional 240-volt charging station installed. It gives you a full charge in approximately 3 to 4 hours (about half the time of the Nissan Leaf).

4 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7027_04_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BIk3/220x123-Ni7.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7027-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7027_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:52:59">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xo4lpp_preferred-ford-near-ferrysburg-mi-and-the-2012-ford-expedition_auto</link><title>Preferred Ford near Ferrysburg, MI and the 2012 Ford Expedition</title><description>Preferred Ford near Ferrysburg, MI and the 2012 Ford Expedition

Toegevoegd door PreferredAuto 2 jaren geleden

http://PreferredFord.com 888-283-6402 The 2012 Ford Expedition is quite simply the do-it-all SUV. A standard 5.4L V8 delivers 310 horsepower and 365 lb.-ft. of torque, enough to pull up to 9,200 lbs. when properly equipped. When the road goes from dry to filled with snow, ice or gravel, the available Control Trac Four-Wheel-Drive (4WD) System helps provide more sure-footed traction. The independent rear suspension helps ensure your trips are comfortable, on smooth and rough roads alike. Capability. It defines what the 2012 Ford Expedition is all about for Ferrysburg, MI citizens.

6 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7027_05_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/ZD-G/220x123-8UT.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7027-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7027_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:54:18">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xocjf7_2012-ford-flex-near-spring-lake-mi-from-preferred-ford-michigan_auto</link><title>2012 Ford Flex near Spring Lake, MI from Preferred Ford Michigan</title><description>2012 Ford Flex near Spring Lake, MI from Preferred Ford Michigan

Toegevoegd door PreferredAuto 2 jaren geleden

http://PreferredFord.com 888-283-6402 Every 2012 Ford Flex comes standard with a 3.5-liter V6 that produces 262 horsepower and 248 pound-feet of torque. A six-speed automatic transmission and front-wheel drive are standard, but all-wheel drive is optional. In Edmunds performance testing, a front-wheel-drive Flex went from zero to 60 mph in 8.9 seconds. EPA-estimated fuel economy is 17 mpg city/24 mpg highway and 19 mpg combined with front-wheel drive. AWD drops those estimates to 16/22/18. Optional on the Flex Limited and Titanium is a turbocharged 3.5-liter V6 (dubbed EcoBoost) that produces 355 hp and 350 lb-ft of torque. All-wheel drive and a six-speed automatic with paddle shifters are standard. The EcoBoost-equipped Flex hits 60 mph in a swift 6.6 seconds. Despite the power increase, fuel economy drops just a tick to 16/21/18.

23 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7027_06_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/ZUBk/220x123-UPb.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7027-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7027_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:56:05">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xo38pc_preferred-ford-of-grand-haven-michigan-and-the-2012-ford-fusion_auto</link><title>Preferred Ford of Grand Haven Michigan and the 2012 Ford Fusion</title><description>Preferred Ford of Grand Haven Michigan and the 2012 Ford Fusion

Toegevoegd door PreferredAuto 2 jaren geleden

http://PreferredFord.com 888-283-6402 The 2012 Ford Fusion gas-powered and hybrid models deliver plenty of performance. Impressive fuel economy, 2011 EPA-estimated 23 city/33 highway/26 combined mpg. So you can enjoy a car that is responsive to the driving enthusiast within you and all the while be assured that you're doing right by the environment.

4 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7027_07_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/ZRyL/220x123-zgB.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7027-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7027_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 13:59:17">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xnbf17_used-jeep-liberty-at-preferred-auto-imports-in-muskegon-mi_auto</link><title>Used Jeep Liberty at Preferred Auto Imports in Muskegon, MI</title><description>Used Jeep Liberty at Preferred Auto Imports in Muskegon, MI

Toegevoegd door PreferredAuto 2 jaren geleden

http://PreferredAutoImports.com 866-924-9139 The road can be a threatening place, but with Hill Descent Control and Hill Start Assist, Liberty has the agility to help you navigate life's ups and downs. Hill Descent Control with grade sensing allows a smooth and controlled hill descent on rough or slippery terrain without the driver needing to touch the brake pedal. This system applies the brakes to each wheel individually when needed to reduce forward motion while negotiating down steep grades.

3 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7027_08_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/9eKi/220x123-MLT.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7027-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7027_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:01:35">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1njxpj_volkswagen-vento-preferred-edition-launched_auto</link><title>Volkswagen Vento Preferred Edition Launched !</title><description>Volkswagen Vento Preferred Edition Launched !

Toegevoegd door Indian Drives een week geleden

Since after a long time, Volkswagen launched an exclusive Vento in India, called the Vento Preferred Edition. This assorted sedan of Volkswagen is garnished with features like alloy wheels, side door protectors, chrome embellishment on the window lines, door visors, boot spoiler and a ‘Preferred’ badge on the bootlid. Meanwhile, on interiors, the car receives a reverse camera display which doubles up as a navigation system. Thus, this new exclusive sedan of VW is rolled out in order to beef up the sales against the new Honda City. In fact, the Vento Preferred can be bought in both the fuel trims - petrol as well as diesel. Both of the powertrains will come displaced with the 1.6 Liter engine mated to a five-speed manual gearbox.

28 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7027_09_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/EL45p/220x123-B9a.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7027-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7027_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 14:03:20">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xn46xz_2012-ford-transit-connect-ev-at-preferred-ford-of-grand-haven_auto</link><title>2012 Ford Transit Connect EV at Preferred Ford of Grand Haven</title><description>2012 Ford Transit Connect EV at Preferred Ford of Grand Haven

Toegevoegd door PreferredAuto 2 jaren geleden

http://PreferredFord.com 888-283-6402 To create the Ford Transit Connect Electric, Azure integrates its proven Force Drive electric powertrain into the award-winning Ford Transit Connect. Utilizing an advanced lithium-ion battery from Johnson Controls, the Transit Connect Electric can achieve a range of 50-80 miles depending on auxiliary usage and drive cycle, and has a top speed of 75 mph. The battery is rechargeable using either a 240-volt or standard 120-volt outlet.

9 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7027_10_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/X0wT/220x123-e5p.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>