<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7046">tuning fork</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:01:38" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7046-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7046_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:01:38">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1a93vp_adc-aluminum-alloy-tuning-fork-512-cps-review_news</link><title>ADC Aluminum Alloy Tuning Fork , 512 CPS Review</title><description>ADC Aluminum Alloy Tuning Fork , 512 CPS Review

Toegevoegd door ErminiaEarline567 laatste januari

ADC Aluminum Alloy Tuning Fork , 512 CPS ReviewRead Morehttp://tinyurl.com/q8oyt8c ADC Aluminum Alloy Tuning Fork , 512 CPS Medical grade tuning fork

4 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7046_01_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/DdVYA/220x123-x2f.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7046-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7046_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:02:17">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x19r0y3_planet-waves-tuning-fork-key-of-a-review_news</link><title>Planet Waves Tuning Fork, Key of A Review</title><description>Planet Waves Tuning Fork, Key of A Review

Toegevoegd door AudreaSherlene966 laatste januari

Planet Waves Tuning Fork, Key of A ReviewRead Morehttp://tinyurl.com/oy8gyn3 Planet Waves Tuning Fork, Key of A

0 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7046_02_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/Da1jf/220x123-dYW.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7046-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7046_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:03:05">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x19r0z5_planet-waves-tuning-fork-key-of-e-review_news</link><title>Planet Waves Tuning Fork, Key of E Review</title><description>Planet Waves Tuning Fork, Key of E Review

Toegevoegd door AzaleeRyann938 laatste januari

Planet Waves Tuning Fork, Key of E ReviewRead Morehttp://tinyurl.com/pbpddba Planet Waves Tuning Fork, Key of E

8 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7046_03_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/Da1jy/220x123-bq0.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7046-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7046_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:03:32">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xya9ep_viral-video-recap-cat-supercuts-and-licking-tuning-forks_tech</link><title>Viral Video Recap: Cat Supercuts and Licking Tuning Forks</title><description>Viral Video Recap: Cat Supercuts and Licking Tuning Forks

Toegevoegd door Tech News vorig jaar

On this week’s Viral Video Recap: Edison and Tesla’s epic rap battle, a hapless seal, and jerks getting what’s coming to them.

142 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7046_04_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/BPJ2C/220x123-MkL.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7046-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7046_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:04:20">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1gbz2o_tuning-tips-electronic-vs-fork-what-s-required-to-be-in-tune-andalusian-flamenco-guitar-cfg-tuning-f_music</link><title>Tuning Tips: Electronic Vs Fork &amp; What's Required To Be In Tune...? / Andalusian Flamenco Guitar CFG Tuning Flamenco Guitars / Santos Hernandez Marcelo Barbero Andalusian New Generation Fret board Division The Most Accurate Ever</title><description>Tuning Tips: Electronic Vs Fork &amp; What's Required To Be In Tune...? / Andalusian Flamenco Guitar CFG Tuning Flamenco Guitars / Santos Hernandez Marcelo Barbero Andalusian New Generation Fret board Division The Most Accurate Ever

Toegevoegd door Ruben Diaz laatste maart

Tuning Flamenco Guitars http://youtu.be/XpQzqdOtNfA How to put the Strings On (Restring) http://youtu.be/WSE5OgccMto Verify Your Fret-board http://www.rdiaz.org/rdvideo1251.html Know if the Fret-board (Neck) is Bent http://youtu.be/GP5YYm2vJBc How Often Change Strings http://youtu.be/YejdVncPKyw ........ Ex.1/ 00:14 (Buleria el Chorruelo by Paco de Lucia) Ex.2/ 01:14 Tip

20 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7046_05_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/D4CzP/220x123-EgI.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7046-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7046_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:04:58">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x15y5dd_used-guitars-for-sale-1967-gretch-viking-with-tuning-fork-515-864-6136_music</link><title>Used Guitars For Sale 1967 Gretch Viking with Tuning Fork 515.864.6136</title><description>Used Guitars For Sale 1967 Gretch Viking with Tuning Fork 515.864.6136

Toegevoegd door lawmanguitar02 laatste oktober

Used Guitars for Sale 1967 Gretsch Viking with Tuning Fork Bridge Gold Bigsby and Original Hardshell Case. This Gretsch is a Beauty. A completely Unaltered 1967 Gretsch Viking with virtually no binding rot. This Gretsch still has the Original Gold Hardware to include the elusive Tuning Bar Bridge System. The only thing we did to this guitar besides set it up with awesome playing low action, is to add some new muting material on the Original Mute System. Completely Original from there to include the excellent shape Gretsch Deluxe Gray Hardshell Case. Most guitars players abandoned the system for it was not user friendly, quickly throwing the tuning fork away and moving the bridge over the tuning fork hole to intonate. A very short sided decision. Chet Adkins used several of these unique systems guitars and loved them. The Tuning Fork floated in the hole and added extra harmonics. I have played this guitar both ways. It was set up without the Tuning Fork when I got it and then when Jeff the Tech brought it back complete. I could hear a difference. Subtle but its there. The Tuning Fork pickups up additional string harmonics and feeds them back through the pickups and sound holes. Very Cool. You should change your strings one at a time to make sure the Tuning Fork doesn’t move. It’s perfectly aligned now for intonation. Put the string thru the fork at a steep angle so that it doesn’t crimp, they will break. I would keep this guitar as shown but a player may want to go back to the bridge over the hole.Used Guitars for Sale Now for the rest of the guitar….it is Beautiful. I was shocked at the appearance when I first saw it. So many of these mid 60′s Gretsch’s have binding rot. This one has none. Most are missing the original Pickguard, this one is present. It was cracked but Jeff repaired it for another life-time of use. Gold Hardware including the original Gretsch Bigsby Whammy Tailpiece and original Whammy bar. Very little wear on the original frets but some pitting from play on the cowboy chord area of the top of the frets. This Guitar sounds magnificent, the original Gretsch Pickups are very strong. This Guitar is a pleasure to hear. Lawman Guitars specializes in Vintage and Rare Acoustic and Electric Guitars, If you are looking for a Guitar that is out of the ordinary give us a call or stop in. If you’ want to see more Used Guitars for Sale contact us. Lawman Guitars 6750 Westown Parkway #200 West Des Moines, IA 50266 (515) 864-6136 This video was produced by Tiller Productions, Des Moines, Iowa TillerProductions.com | TillerMediaGroup.com © Copyright 2012 Tiller Productions &amp; Lawman Guitars. All Rights Reserved. Topic: Used Guitars for Sale

44 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7046_06_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CokPk/220x123-C5X.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7046-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7046_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:05:57">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x19wsen_american-diagnostic-corporation-tuning-fork-c4096-504096-review_news</link><title>American Diagnostic Corporation Tuning Fork, C4096 504096 Review</title><description>American Diagnostic Corporation Tuning Fork, C4096 504096 Review

Toegevoegd door CatherynRaeann923 laatste januari

American Diagnostic Corporation Tuning Fork, C4096 504096 ReviewRead Morehttp://tinyurl.com/pjoxoxg American Diagnostic Corporation Tuning Fork, C4096 504096 Non-magnetic, corrosion resistant aluminum alloy constructionWeighs 1/3 of comparable steel tuning forksProduced from 3/8" x 1" bar stock for superior performance and consistent frequency accuracyExtra long 2" handle of turned smooth aluminum to facilitate bone conduction tests

1 view</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7046_07_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DbnsL/220x123-ZK2.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7046-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7046_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:06:48">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1jw0ol_best-price-medical-style-tuning-fork-set-6-piece-steel-with-case-review_auto</link><title>Best Price Medical Style Tuning Fork Set 6 Piece Steel with Case Review</title><description>Best Price Medical Style Tuning Fork Set 6 Piece Steel with Case Review

Toegevoegd door Anovinbreed1985 4 weken geleden

Best Price Medical Style Tuning Fork Set 6 Piece Steel with Case Review Click on the link below for the best price of this product: http://www.amazon.com/dp/B008OIWC4W/?tag=sonsfas0d-21 Disclaimer: I am a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon. Amazon and the Amazon logo are trademarks of Amazon, Inc. or its affiliates.

0 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7046_08_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/EAYrE/220x123-NbV.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7046-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7046_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:07:28">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1a5f6t_medical-professional-c256-hz-tuning-fork-c-256-review_news</link><title>Medical Professional c256 hz TUNING FORK C 256 Review</title><description>Medical Professional c256 hz TUNING FORK C 256 Review

Toegevoegd door EmmalineEla180 laatste januari

Medical Professional c256 hz TUNING FORK C 256 ReviewRead Morehttp://tinyurl.com/o3kekgb Medical Professional c256 hz TUNING FORK C 256 Professional High Grade Solid Aluminum-alloyc256 Hz PitchedExtra long 2" handle of turned smooth aluminum to facilitate bone conduction tests

5 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7046_09_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DcvIR/220x123-g38.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7046-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7046_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:08:15">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1nw83g_best-price-eta-hand2mind-octave-tuning-forks-set-of-8-review_lifestyle</link><title>Best Price ETA hand2mind Octave Tuning Forks (Set of 8) Review</title><description>Best Price ETA hand2mind Octave Tuning Forks (Set of 8) Review

Toegevoegd door Tratbicestpilg1983 een week geleden

Best Price ETA hand2mind Octave Tuning Forks (Set of 8) Review Click on the link below for the best price of this product: http://www.amazon.com/dp/B008AK89TG/?tag=60percentoff2-20 Disclaimer: I am a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon. Amazon and the Amazon logo are trademarks of Amazon, Inc. or its affiliates.

1 view</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7046_10_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/EM3Ub/220x123-rMV.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>