<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7051">dinosaur names</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:38:56" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7051-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7051_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:38:57">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1evlln_newly-named-dinosaur-was-europe-s-largest-jurassic-predator_news</link><title>Newly Named Dinosaur Was Europe's Largest Jurassic Predator</title><description>Newly Named Dinosaur Was Europe's Largest Jurassic Predator

Toegevoegd door wochit laatste maart

A newly identified dinosaur, built like T. Rex and equipped with blade-like teeth and larger arms and claws, was the largest predator in Europe during the late Jurassic period, researchers say. The new species, was smaller than tyrannosaurs, and may lived off a bit of hunting and a bit of scavenging 150 million years ago. After they were found in 2003, the fossils were first identified as a sister theropod species.

49 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7051_01_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/D0Rdr/220x123-IqG.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7051-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7051_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:39:43">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x16ztfs_new-predatory-dinosaur-discovered-named-king-of-gore_travel</link><title>New Predatory Dinosaur Discovered, Named 'King of Gore'</title><description>New Predatory Dinosaur Discovered, Named 'King of Gore'

Toegevoegd door Geo Beats laatste november

The discovery of a new species of dinosaur has been announced that scientists have named Lythronax argestes. The discovery of a new species of dinosaur that scientists have named Lythronax argestes, meaning king of gore, has been announced.It was the largest predator on land during the time it was alive. Related to the infamous Tyrannosaurus rex, the king of gore lived in an earlier time period, and grew to around 30 feet in length.Fossils of the dinosaur were first found in 2009, but it was only a partial skeleton with bones from the skull and other parts of the body. (1,8,1)Randall Irmis, co-author of the study at the Natural History Museum of Utah said: “There's a whole diversity of different branches of the Tyrannosaur family tree that are waiting to be found out there. We think that when the sea level was high it was isolating areas in western North America that caused different species to evolve in isolation and that's why we're finding so many different species.” (1,14,1)Research analysis of the fossils revealed that it was closely related to the T.rex, but had characteristics that evolved an estimated 10 million years earlier in the fossil record. What do you think about the discovery of the king of gore dinosaur?

76 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7051_02_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/C1L44/220x123-ums.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7051-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7051_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:40:49">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xqrczf_ice-age-dawn-of-the-dinosaurs-clip-the-name-s-buck_shortfilms</link><title>Ice Age: Dawn of the Dinosaurs - Clip - The Name's Buck</title><description>Ice Age: Dawn of the Dinosaurs - Clip - The Name's Buck

Toegevoegd door MyMovies_International vorig jaar

The most unlikeliest herd are back and this time they're having to face up to some pretty terrifying interlopers!

337 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7051_03_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/uwMR/220x123-UoJ.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7051-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7051_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:41:22">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x159pdh_almanac-dinosaurs_news</link><title>Almanac: Dinosaurs</title><description>Almanac: Dinosaurs

Toegevoegd door CBS News laatste september

On December 18th, 1892 Sir Richard Owen, the British scientist who gave dinosaurs their name, died at the age of 88. "Sunday Morning" opens its almanac to look back at what we have learned about those terrible lizards since their discovery.

12 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7051_04_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/CgLkU/220x123-v6n.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7051-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7051_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:42:10">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1bfacm_des-poulets-munis-de-protheses-pour-etudier-la-demarche-des-dinosaures_news</link><title>Des poulets munis de prothèses pour étudier la démarche des dinosaures</title><description>Des poulets munis de prothèses pour étudier la démarche des dinosaures

Toegevoegd door Le Monde.fr laatste februari

Prenant en compte le fait que les oiseaux sont de lointains descendants des dinosaures, des scientifiques de l'université du Chili ont inventé une prothèse dont ils équipent les poulets, rapporte le site io9. L'objectif de cette fausse queue de tyrannosaure : observer comment l'animal s'adapte à son nouvel appendice et ainsi mieux comprendre de quelle manière les dinosaures se déplaçaient. « Ces résultats indiquent un passage d'une locomotion bipède dont l'articulation se fait niveau des genoux, typique des oiseaux, à une locomation davantage gérée au niveau des hanches, typiques des crocodiles, des mammifères et, théoriquement, des dinosaures bipèdes non-aviaires », expliquent les auteurs de l'étude, dont on peut retrouver les conclusions sur le site PLOSOne.

25 901 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7051_05_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DiECH/220x123-wJx.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7051-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7051_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:42:55">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x8ughd_ice-age-3-dawn-of-the-dinosaurs-ful_news</link><title>Ice Age 3: Dawn of the Dinosaurs - Full Trailer</title><description>Ice Age 3: Dawn of the Dinosaurs - Full Trailer

Toegevoegd door JVT 5 jaren geleden

Ice Age 3: Dawn of the Dinosaurs - Full Trailer www.dvdenlared.com/cine

104 988 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7051_06_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/AI2K0/220x123-jey.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7051-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7051_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:43:45">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x17s6x9_barney-the-dinosaur-killed-during-1997-macy-s-thanksgiving-day-parade_news</link><title>Barney The Dinosaur ‘Killed’ During 1997 Macy’s Thanksgiving Day Parade</title><description>Barney The Dinosaur ‘Killed’ During 1997 Macy’s Thanksgiving Day Parade

Toegevoegd door MisterSexyBuzz laatste november

In 1997, thousands of kids were traumatized while watching the Macy’s Thanksgiving Day Parade. Due to powerful winds, Barney the purple dinosaur hit a lamp post, and eventually was torn to shreds as kids and families shrieked in terror. “Give the kids nightmares,” noted one spectator. Appropriately, this clip from the past parade, posted by DelhiTheCat, is going viral this Thanksgiving weekend.

528 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7051_07_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/DFLIs/220x123-0jb.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7051-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7051_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:44:39">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xsrqim_velociraptor-dans-melbourne-walking-with-dinosaurs_news</link><title>Velociraptor dans Melbourne (Walking With Dinosaurs)</title><description>Velociraptor dans Melbourne (Walking With Dinosaurs)

Toegevoegd door Spi0n vorig jaar

Un énorme Velociraptor a été découvert dans la ville de Melbourne en Australie. Le dinosaure se serait échappé du show Walking With Dinosaurs. Un chouette déguisement !

77 138 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7051_08_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/L0dH/220x123-zJc.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7051-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7051_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:45:27">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1lvs4o_des-paleontologues-recreent-en-3d-un-chemin-d-empreintes-de-dinosaures_news</link><title>Des paléontologues recréent en 3D un chemin d'empreintes de dinosaures</title><description>Des paléontologues recréent en 3D un chemin d'empreintes de dinosaures

Toegevoegd door Gentside 2 weken geleden

http://www.maxisciences.com/dinosaure/dinosaure-les-traces-d-une-course-poursuite-entre-deux-geants-recreees-en-3d_art32308.html

585 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7051_09_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/EHRvi/220x123-JOO.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7051-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7051_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 17:46:15">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x3637j_sur-la-terre-des-dinosaures-les-ine_news</link><title>Sur la terre des dinosaures - Les Inédits (5/5)</title><description>Sur la terre des dinosaures - Les Inédits (5/5)

Toegevoegd door www.vodeo.tv 6 jaren geleden

Nigel Marven, zoologiste et aventurier, a pendant des années parcouru le monde en quête d'animaux spectaculaires. Dans cet épisode, il termine son exploration des mondes sous-marins préhistoriques par la rencontre avec les plus dangereux prédateurs. En voir plus sur : http://www.vodeo.tv/5-67-4364-sur-la-terre-des-dinosaures---les-inedits-5-5.html?PARTID=9084

91 104 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7051_10_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/_49a/220x123-0fT.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>