<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7069">Eames chair</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:49:34" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7069-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7069_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:49:36">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xk7r0m_la-lounge-chair-ottoman-eames-vitra-www-ideesboutique-com_creation</link><title>La Lounge Chair Ottoman Eames Vitra - www.ideesboutique.com</title><description>La Lounge Chair Ottoman Eames Vitra - www.ideesboutique.com

Toegevoegd door Mathieu Potin 2 jaren geleden

Le Lounge Chair allie depuis 1956 un confort absolu et une qualité du plus haut niveau tant dans les matériaux que dans la fabrication, Charles et Ray Eames s’étant inspirés du traditionnel fauteuil club anglais. C’est pourquoi ils créèrent le Lounge Chair, à l’origine avec un placage sombre et recouvert de cuir noir, mais ils le dotèrent, de bonne heure, d’une variante avec des coussins en cuir clair. La nouvelle interprétation du Lounge Chair, conçue en collaboration avec l’Eames Office, s’inscrit dans cette continuité ; ce classique est maintenant disponible dans une version au placage en noyer à pigments blancs, en aluminium poli et cuir blanc, qui se marie parfaitement avec les intérieurs clairs. La Lounge Chair est désormais également disponible dans une version offrant un confort optimal aux personnes de grande taille. La lounge chair est éditée par Vitra pour l'europe.http://www.ideesboutique.com/fauteuils/5273-lounge-chair-a-ottoman-cuir-noir-et-coque-palissandre-vitra.html

463 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7069_01_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/a1Ut/220x123-REL.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7069-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7069_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:50:29">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1n5p42_chelsea-eames-style-dsw-daw-molded-plastic-dining-side-chair-arm-chair_lifestyle</link><title>Chelsea Eames Style DSW &amp; DAW Molded Plastic Dining Side Chair &amp; Arm Chair</title><description>Chelsea Eames Style DSW &amp; DAW Molded Plastic Dining Side Chair &amp; Arm Chair

Toegevoegd door Hot Products In The Market Reviews! 2 weken geleden

Buy it on Amazon: http://boxvimo.com/affiliate-link/ These are fun chairs that are so easy to put together and are light weight, so they are easy to move. But even being light weight, they are still very sturdy and can hold an adults weight easily. The plastic they are made of is very thick, and is easy and comfortable to sit on. Their base is made from wood and it bolts into the bottom of the chair. These chairs serve a very helpful purpose for us. My husband works in job that has him stopping home a few times each day throughout his shift for lunch and such. He's in law enforcement and he wears a deep blue uniform that almost looks black. We also have a house full of pets, most of them with light colored fur. Sitting down in the house in his uniform is so complicated, because our chairs all have fabric on them (which is bound to have some lint or a stray dog hair on it) or they have narrow arms on the sides. When in his uniform, he's wearing a duty belt packed with gear that makes him wider than usual. So he can't sit down in any chairs with arms or else his belt doesn't fit. And the way the uniform works, he can't just slip off his belt. So between fabric chairs getting lint and hair on his uniform and our chairs with arms being to narrow to fit into with his gear on, coming home to relax on break or during his lunch hour gets complicated. These chairs were the solution!

3 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7069_02_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/EK1tw/220x123-fbC.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7069-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7069_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:52:01">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x15rktz_enjoy-comfort-with-eames-chairs_news</link><title>Enjoy comfort With Eames chairs</title><description>Enjoy comfort With Eames chairs

Toegevoegd door Jeffrey Moore laatste oktober

Points You Want To Know about eames chairs Eames chairs (http://www.eamesdsw.com/charles-eames-dsw-classic-colection)

17 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7069_03_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/CmSwI/220x123-p5m.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7069-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7069_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:53:58">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xlbrl3_eames-lounge-chair-ottoman-replica-herman-miller_lifestyle</link><title>Eames Lounge chair &amp; ottoman - Replica - Herman Miller</title><description>Eames Lounge chair &amp; ottoman - Replica - Herman Miller

Toegevoegd door manhattanhomedesign 2 jaren geleden

This Eames style Lounge Chair &amp; Ottoman is a timeless classic. In continuous production since the Bauhaus 50's movement, the Eames Lounge Chaise style and ottoman is widely considered one of the most significant designs of the modern classics.

223 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7069_04_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/2jzP/220x123-Z6q.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7069-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7069_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:55:28">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xjgqy1_eames-lounge-chair-reproduction_lifestyle</link><title>Eames Lounge chair reproduction</title><description>Eames Lounge chair reproduction

Toegevoegd door manhattanhomedesign 2 jaren geleden

This Eames style Lounge Chair &amp; Ottoman is a timeless classic. In continuous production since the Bauhaus 50's movement, the Eames Lounge Chaise style and ottoman is widely considered one of the most significant designs of the modern classics.It represents the epitome of armchair comfort. The precise lines of the plywood shell and the soft fullness of the leather form a restful seat that involves you like a real glove. This Eames lounge style chair and matching ottoman takes comfort and style to another level.

112 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7069_05_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/AEVzs/220x123-X37.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7069-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7069_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:56:23">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xppr01_eames-lounge-chair_news</link><title>Eames Lounge chair</title><description>Eames Lounge chair

Toegevoegd door ModecorFurnitures 2 jaren geleden

Our online furniture store consistently sold the top quality contemporary and classic furniture from some of famous designer like: Le Corbusier, George Nelson, Isamu Noguchi, Arne Jacobsen, Charles and Ray, Eero Aarnio, Eero Saarinen, Mies van der Rohe and many more. Our collection include only those range of product that reflects quality and unique design.

23 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7069_06_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/AB72T/220x123-mCK.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7069-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7069_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:58:08">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x15rqgj_any-size-and-shapes-of-dining-chairs-eames-chair_news</link><title>Any Size And Shapes Of Dining Chairs-Eames Chair</title><description>Any Size And Shapes Of Dining Chairs-Eames Chair

Toegevoegd door Walter Thomas laatste oktober

Eames chair (http://eamesdsw.com/) is available in a number of colors and so you will find a color that will fit the color of your dining or any place that you want keep them.

12 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7069_07_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CmWCe/220x123-pzq.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7069-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7069_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 20:59:10">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xju8ye_eames-soft-pad-management-chair-review_news</link><title>Eames Soft Pad Management Chair Review</title><description>Eames Soft Pad Management Chair Review

Toegevoegd door ChairReport 2 jaren geleden

Quick Eames Soft Pad Management Chair Review. For more detailed information on the chair, visit http://chairreport.com/eames-soft-pad-management-chair-review-an-icon-of-stylish-comfort/. For more objective chair reviews visit http://chairreport.com/.

87 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7069_08_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/ajyp/220x123-Qlq.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7069-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7069_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:00:40">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xibda9_eames-lounge-chair-replica_lifestyle</link><title>Eames Lounge chair Replica</title><description>Eames Lounge chair Replica

Toegevoegd door manhattanhomedesign 3 jaren geleden

free shipping, furniture sale, Manhattan Home Design Discounts, Coupon Codes, Free Shipping Codes, Promo Offers, Promotional Codes, and Manhattan Home Design Discount Coupons, Money Off Coupon Codes, Deals, Gift Coupons, Promo Codes, Free Shipping Codes and Online Printable Coupons when you shop at the Manhattan Home Design website. Easily save money and time with our coupon codes when purchasing from Manhattan Home Design.

198 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7069_09_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/0eOB/220x123-p0q.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7069-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7069_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 21:01:31">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xiest0_eames-aluminum-group-style-softpad-management-chair_lifestyle</link><title>Eames Aluminum Group Style Softpad Management Chair</title><description>Eames Aluminum Group Style Softpad Management Chair

Toegevoegd door manhattanhomedesign 2 jaren geleden

eames office chair, eames aluminum office chair, eames lounge chair, aluminum office chair reproduction, office leather chair, office chair sale, charles eames, hang it all, charles eames lounge chair, charles eames lounge, charles eames chair, free shipping, furniture sale, Manhattan Home Design Discounts, Coupon Codes, Free Shipping Codes, Promo Offers, Promotional Codes, and Manhattan Home Design Discount Coupons, Money Off Coupon Codes, Deals, Gift Coupons, Promo Codes, Free Shipping Codes and Online Printable Coupons when you shop at the Manhattan Home Design website. Easily save money and time with our coupon codes when purchasing from Manhattan Home Design.

86 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7069_10_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/7b-F/220x123-A8L.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>