<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7086">falsifying pictures 21st centurie</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:48:57" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7086-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7086_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:48:58">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x3jt8m_21st-century-pictures-logo-2007_shortfilms</link><title>21st Century Pictures logo (2007)</title><description>21st Century Pictures logo (2007)

Toegevoegd door Danny J. Palmer 6 jaren geleden

The new opener for 21st Century Pictures, as seen on recent DVD releases here in Australia. The company deals mainly in straight-to-DVD releases, such as National Lampoons Dorm Daze 2, where this logo comes from.

448 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7086_01_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/Ji1k/220x123-Kvr.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7086-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7086_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:50:17">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x3ju20_21st-century-pictures-1990s_shortfilms</link><title>21st Century Pictures (1990s)</title><description>21st Century Pictures (1990s)

Toegevoegd door Danny J. Palmer 6 jaren geleden

The old 21st Century Pictures logo, as seen on many a direct-to-video tape, as well as early DVD releases. Taken from Mike Bassett: England Manager.

344 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7086_02_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/Jk0N/220x123-TYN.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7086-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7086_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:51:21">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x195ktf_miley-cyrus-wildest-party-pics_people</link><title>Miley Cyrus' Wildest Party Pics</title><description>Miley Cyrus' Wildest Party Pics

Toegevoegd door revnewmedia laatste januari

2013 was the year Miley turned 21! In honor, let's look back at her best partying pics!

3 549 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7086_03_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/DX0OO/220x123-QJz.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7086-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7086_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:52:23">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x15ax2f_oracle-ceo-larry-ellison-took-an-18-pay-cut-for-this-fiscal-year_news</link><title>Oracle CEO Larry Ellison took an 18% pay cut for this fiscal year.</title><description>Oracle CEO Larry Ellison took an 18% pay cut for this fiscal year.

Toegevoegd door 3 Minute Update laatste september

Business Weekend Wrap Up… News Corp’s 4th quarter revenue exceeded expectations, $2.13 billion, $40 million more than expected. Paramount Pictures suing JPMorgan. Plus Hertz now carrying Telsa automobiles!

84 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7086_04_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/Cgis4/220x123-M5N.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7086-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7086_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:53:04">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xcftts_justice-for-khojaly-the-world-shoul_news</link><title>JUSTICE FOR KHOJALY-The world should know the whole truth.</title><description>JUSTICE FOR KHOJALY-The world should know the whole truth.

Toegevoegd door Hayordipu 4 jaren geleden

Khojali is the tragedy of the Azerbaijani authorities. Write a story through fraud is not morally and disgraceful. In Azerbaijan, forget that the 21st century already and that does not falsify but not so easy. All lies, sooner or later discovered.

381 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7086_05_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/AG-F8/220x123-zCH.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7086-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7086_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:54:24">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xmt3th_thala-thala-rolix-rangam_fun</link><title>Thala Thala Rolix:Rangam</title><description>Thala Thala Rolix:Rangam

Toegevoegd door MaaMusic 2 jaren geleden

Ashwin (Jeeva), a young, energetic photojournalist working for the private newspaper Neti Vartha, witnesses Naxalites robbing a local bank. He chases them and manages to click photos of the robbers. When he tries to escape, he is stopped by a young woman (Karthika Nair) who assumes he is the culprit and helps the robbers to take his camera. However, he is able to secure the memory card of the camera and to prove that he is a press photographer he shows the photos to the police, who identify everyone except the gang leader (whose face is covered by a mask). At his office, he meets Renuka 'Renu', the woman who earlier mistook him, who has newly joined as Article Editor. Saraswathi 'Saro' (Piaa Bajpai) also works in his office who has feelings for Ashwin. After finding out that Ashwin likes Renuka, she sacrfices her love. Vasanthan Perumal (Ajmal Ameer), a recent graduate and engineer, strives hard to enter the political field. He is in contest against his rivals who capture the people at the time of elections by giving freebies and money. No one cares about Vasanthan and his team of graduates, who promise a healthy government to people. Their group name happens to be 'Siragugal'. Meanwhile, Renuka writes a cover story about politician Aalavandhan (Kota Srinivasa Rao), describing his attempt to marry a minor. Enraged by this, Aalavandhan barges into the newspaper office and shouts at Renuka. The audio recording of her interview disappears, and she is fired from her job for falsified reporting. Ashwin now risks his life to capture the pictures of Aalavandhan who actually engages in child marriage. Later the story with the photos is printed in their newspaper and this makes Renuka to fall in love with him. Vasanthan organizes a political campaign meeting. Ashwin receives a text message from Saro that states there is a bomb underneath the stage where Vasanthan and his political party is. Ashwin manages to save Vasanthan, while he finds Saro seriously injured and fighting for her life amidst the riot, eventually dies from her injuries. Ashwin, through a video clip recorded by another photographer, finds out that Saro was intentionally killed by someone. He later notices a resemblance between the leader of the bank robbery and this unknown killer, concluding that it is the same person. Vasanthan wins in the elections taking majority, gaining the title of Central Minister and his party raises to the secretariat. He orders the release of 20 naxals on Republic Day, citing humanity. Hearing this, Ashwin rushes to meet Vasanthan. In Vasanthan's office, he finds the leader of the bank robbery who had also killed Saro. He tells Vasanthan about it, but he ignores him and pretends to be busy. Ashwin then follows the leader to his hideout.At the same time, the CM (Vasanthan) orders Tamil Nadu Police to go kill the naxals at the address Vasanthan gave and the Police Commandos surrounds the perimeter. There he learns that it was Vasanthan who, with the help of the naxals, planted the bomb and killed Saraswati as she saw the bomb being planted. In the end Vasanthan gets killed by a blast. Ashwin never reveals the relationship between Vasanthan and the killer to the media. Ashwin feared that if he does so, other party members who won along with Vasanth in election will lose their seats because of people. Ashwin tells the press that Vasanth sacrificed himself to kill the naxals.&amp;nbsp;

220 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7086_06_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/AQwCT/220x123-eio.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7086-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7086_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:55:04">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x17j2ik_ex-chemist-gets-3-5-years-for-tampering-with-drug-tests_shortfilms</link><title>Ex-Chemist Gets 3-5 Years For Tampering With Drug Tests</title><description>Ex-Chemist Gets 3-5 Years For Tampering With Drug Tests

Toegevoegd door Web TV laatste november

A former Massachusetts chemist pleaded guilty Friday to tampering with evidence and falsifying drug tests.

10 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7086_07_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DBPFK/220x123-J3r.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7086-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7086_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:55:40">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x14wjxl_south-africa-police-lied-over-marikana-massacre_news</link><title>South Africa police 'lied' over Marikana massacre:...</title><description>South Africa police 'lied' over Marikana massacre:...

Toegevoegd door euronews-en laatste september

South African police lied about the mass shooting of striking miners at Marikana last year, according to a commission of inquiry.It accuses police of falsifying and hiding documents, as well as giving false accounts of events....http://www.euronews.net/

15 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7086_08_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CcDsM/220x123-cFb.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7086-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7086_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:56:21">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x134nqc_u-s-charges-two-men-with-fraud-in-london-whale-scandal_news</link><title>U.S. charges two men with fraud in 'London Whale' scandal</title><description>U.S. charges two men with fraud in 'London Whale' scandal

Toegevoegd door wochit laatste augustus

U.S. prosecutors in Manhattan have accused two former JPMorgan Chase &amp; Company employees who worked in London of wire fraud and conspiracy. The two are suspected of falsifying books and records in criminal charges related to the bank's $6.2 billion trading losses last year, now known as the 'London Whale' scandal.

29 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7086_09_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/COwJe/220x123-2ob.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7086-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7086_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-24 23:56:54">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xzygkj_rcmp-members-found-hunting-on-the-job-falsifying-details_news</link><title>RCMP Members Found Hunting on the Job, Falsifying Details</title><description>RCMP Members Found Hunting on the Job, Falsifying Details

Toegevoegd door tvnportal laatste mei

From falsifying information to the abuse of police resources — including an airplane — CBC News has been digging through the discipline files of Manitoba RCMP members who faced hearings between 2010 and fall of 2012.Powered by NewsLook.com Producer : CBC

7 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7086_10_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/Be6yk/220x123-XrZ.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>