<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7092">How much was a gallon of gas during depression</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:41:57" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7092-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7092_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:41:58">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xg1dmv_gas-prices-rise-by-as-much-as-a-dime-per-gallon_news</link><title>Gas Prices Rise by as Much as a Dime per Gallon</title><description>Gas Prices Rise by as Much as a Dime per Gallon

Toegevoegd door Local News 3 jaren geleden

Gas Prices Rise by as Much as a Dime per Gallon Wed, 30 Jun 2010 01:47:00 EDT

61 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7092_01_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/zhiP/220x123-k6J.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7092-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7092_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:42:28">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xyg8cz_the-rcmp-have-confirmed-a-second-canadian-was-killed-during-an-attack-on-a-gas-plant-in-algeria-in-j_news</link><title>The RCMP Have Confirmed a Second Canadian Was Killed During an Attack on a Gas Plant in Algeria in January, Louise Martin Reports</title><description>The RCMP Have Confirmed a Second Canadian Was Killed During an Attack on a Gas Plant in Algeria in January, Louise Martin Reports

Toegevoegd door tvnportal vorig jaar

The remains of a second Canadian allegedly part of an attack on a gas plant in January have been identified by Algerian authorities, the RCMP has confirmed.Powered by NewsLook.com Producer : CBC

20 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7092_02_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BQzCg/220x123-Luv.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7092-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7092_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:43:02">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1nbqfn_how-ups-trucks-save-money-by-turning-right_travel</link><title>How UPS Trucks Save Money by Turning Right</title><description>How UPS Trucks Save Money by Turning Right

Toegevoegd door Geo Beats 2 weken geleden

While an individual person may not save much by only making right turns, a huge corporation like UPS has proven since 2004 how avoiding left turns in its trucks can significantly increase its bottomline while reducing emissions and accidents. With nearly 100,000 trucks and hundreds of aircraft, UPS averages 15.8 million packages delivered daily worldwide. While an individual person may not save much by only making right turns, since UPS implemented a right turn policy in 2004, they have significantly increased profits while reducing emissions and accidents.UPS estimates the right-turn-heavy policy, combined with its routing software, shortens routes by 20.4 million miles and saves 10 million gallons of gas while delivering an additional 350,000 packages and reducing CO2 emissions by about 20,000 metric tons each year.UPS engineers noticed how waiting to turn left caused trucks to fall behind on their schedules, consume more gas, and increase the probability of accidents. Their software maps routes with only right-hand turns unless it’s quicker or easier to proceed with a left-hand turn. A driver estimates they do about 90% right-hand turns.The television show Mythbusters tested the policy with one route using 8 left and 4 right turns, and another route using 1 left and 23 right turns. The UPS-like route was just over 1 mile and 9 minutes longer, but it reduced gas consumption from 6.8 to 4 pounds. UPS’ software probably would’ve added one or two more left-hand turns to be more efficient on time while still saving gas.

24 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7092_03_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/ELPyQ/220x123-76-.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7092-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7092_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:43:31">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1dfvjb_top-4-business-stories-of-the-day_news</link><title>Top 4 Business Stories of the Day</title><description>Top 4 Business Stories of the Day

Toegevoegd door wochit laatste februari

Spring is a terrible time to buy gas. The closer we get to May 1 -- the day that every fuel station in the country has to switch to summer-blend gasoline -- the higher prices typically go. That's because the supply of "regular" gas gets scarcer as refineries ratchet down production in advance of the changeover. With regular unleaded gasoline currently hovering around $3.43 per gallon, it's likely that we'll be flirting with $4 prices before long. U.S. stocks were mixed in mid-morning trading Tuesday as investors reacted to an unexpectedly steep decline in consumer confidence this month. The weak start came a day after the Standard &amp; Poor's 500 index came within a point of closing at another record high. The Conference Board's index of consumer confidence fell to 78.1 in February from 80.7 the month before. That was below the 80.1 level economists polled by FactSet were expecting. The report is a closely watched indicator of how likely consumers are to spend money and keep the economy moving forward. Britain's Tesco, the world's third-largest retailer, is to focus on cheaper pricing as it relaxes its view on operating margins and steps up its store revamp program and investment in online and convenience channels. Outlining his plans at an investor and analyst seminar on Tuesday, Chief Executive Philip Clarke said the measures accelerate a turnaround plan aimed at countering increased competition in the British retail market, but which has so far failed to boost its languishing sales. Clarke explained "This doesn't signal a need for a new strategy, simply to go faster." IMF Managing Director Christine Lagarde sounded the trumpet on rising income disparities for the second time this month, in a speech at Stanford University. This comes after also broaching the issue during a lecture at the BBC. She said "Rising inequality and economic exclusion can have pernicious effects," pointing to IMF research that shows income gaps can lead to slower and less sustainable growth. The World Economic Forum also warned this month that the chronic gap between rich and poor is getting wider, posing the single biggest risk to the world this year.

10 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7092_04_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/Dvg8v/220x123-x9S.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7092-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7092_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:44:26">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1p8jx2_portland-pee-water-drunk-urinates-in-reservoir-so-city-will-flush-38-million-gallons-of-water_news</link><title>Portland pee water: drunk urinates in reservoir so city will flush 38 million gallons of water</title><description>Portland pee water: drunk urinates in reservoir so city will flush 38 million gallons of water

Toegevoegd door NMAtv vorig vrijdag

Check out our official website: http://us.tomonews.net/Check out our Android app: http://goo.gl/PtT6VDCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f----------------------------------------­----------------------------------------­----------------The city of Portland, Oregon flushed 38 million gallons of drinking water on Wednesday after its Number 5 reservoir was contaminated with human urine. Exactly how much human urine? Well, after a teenager relieved himself into the reservoir, we could be talking about up to 20 ounces. But exactly to what extent could 20 ounces of urine contaminate a reservoir? Twenty ounces is about four times the size of a normal human micturition. But the kid had been drinking, so lets just give 'em that one.Time for some math! As you know, there are 128 ounces in a gallon. And with 38 million gallons in the reservoir, that means we'd be drinking 1 part per 243,200,000 of pee. At those levels, he could have diluted 20 ounces of liquid cyanide into the reservoir, and it still would have posed no risk to humans. Also, don't forget that these are open reservoirs, with all kinds of stuff dropping in there over time. It is Oregon after all, so think "roaches" — and I'm not talking about an insect. Still, the Water Bureau's David Shaff says that with all the city's reservoirs 100 percent full, Portland can afford to flush the pee water. Speaking of what it can afford, when Portland flushed and cleaned a reservoir one fifth of this volume in 2011, it cost the city US$35,000. Sounds like you better start hugging some dollar bills out of those trees, Portland.----------------------------------------­----------------------------------------­----------------Welcome to TomoNews, where we animate the most entertaining news on the internets. Come here for an animated look at viral headlines, US news, celebrity gossip, salacious scandals, dumb criminals and much more! Subscribe now for daily news animations that will knock your socks off.Check out our Android app: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.nextmedia.ganCheck out our iOS app: https://itunes.apple.com/app/tomonews/id633875353For news that's fun and never boring, visit our channel:https://www.youtube.com/user/TomoNewsUSSubscribe to stay updated on all the top stories:https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCt-WqkTyKK1_70U4bb4k4lQ?sub_confirmation=1Stay connected with us here:Facebook http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSTwitter @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSGoogle+ http://plus.google.com/+TomoNewsUS/Instagram @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus

1 632 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7092_05_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/ER6T7/220x123-xDP.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7092-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7092_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:45:22">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x7dpg1_amazing-tips-to-save-gas-that-can-i_news</link><title>Amazing Tips to Save Gas That Can Increase Your Gas Mileage!</title><description>Amazing Tips to Save Gas That Can Increase Your Gas Mileage!

Toegevoegd door alternative 5 jaren geleden

http://www.alternativefuelstips.comThe most fuel-efficient engine in the automotive world can only do so much in saving precious gasoline. Maximizing a vehicle’s fuel mileage is not a task for the engine alone; getting the most mileage out of a vehicle also requires the driver’s efforts. Fortunately for drivers, the question on how to save gas is easy to answer. To drive more miles per gallon of gasoline, all a driver needs is an updated set of driving habits. If it all possible, avoid driving during rush hours. The added starts and stops of rush hour traffic will cut into your gas mileage. http://www.alternativefuelstips.com

33 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7092_06_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/AWrGZ/220x123-jBg.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7092-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7092_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:46:12">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xcdnzm_baby-elephant-named-in-melbourne_news</link><title>Baby Elephant Named in Melbourne</title><description>Baby Elephant Named in Melbourne

Toegevoegd door NTDTelevision 4 jaren geleden

This baby elephant is the first-ever born at the zoo here in Melbourne.And to come up with a fitting name, Victoria residents took part in a naming competition.And the winning name was “Mali,” the Thai word for jasmine.Today she was officially named during a Buddhist ceremony at the zoo.[Katie Pahlow, Zoo Spokesperson]:"Just as a demonstration of how much she's captured the hearts and minds of so many Victorians, we had 34,000 entries into the competition."Zookeepers say Mali is drinking around three and a half gallons of milk each day and is putting on about three to four pounds of weight.She’s only the second elephant to be born in an Australian zoo and is the first female.

254 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7092_07_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/5lpi/220x123-8U0.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7092-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7092_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:47:11">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x5zzbn_1-way-to-improve-gas-mileage-in-yo_news</link><title>#1 way to Improve gas mileage in your current car</title><description>#1 way to Improve gas mileage in your current car

Toegevoegd door igtm8wwlm9 5 jaren geleden

Do you want to know what the oil companies and the top 5 Automobile manufactures don't want you to know about Hydrogen, and the power of its gases?Do you want to know how you can truly receive the lowest gas prices from the pump by force..Do you want to know The Info Inside...http://GasSaving.TheINFOinside.comhttp://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N_7Og3r_JcAWe Test the TipsThe good news is that you can drastically improve your gas mileage. The caveat is that you have to change your driving habits. If you are willing to change, ...www.edmunds.com/advice/fueleconomy/articles/106842/article.html - 47k - Cached - Similar pages - Note thisTips to improve your Gas MileageGas Mileage Tips. Here are some tips to help you reduce the amount of gas ... MPG and offers tips on how to improve fuel economy MotorWeek Video (5.6 MB) ...www.fueleconomy.gov/FEG/drive.shtml - 11k - Cached - Similar pages - Note thisTips to improve your Gas MileageFixing a car that is noticeably out of tune or has failed an emissions test can improve its gas mileage by an average of 4 percent, though results vary ...www.fueleconomy.gov/feg/maintain.shtml - 17k - Cached - Similar pages - Note thisMore results from www.fueleconomy.gov »Sneaky Ways To Get Better Gas Mileage - Forbes.comThat's because more frequent air filter changes can improve your vehicle's gas mileage by as much as 10%, the Car Care Council says. ...www.forbes.com/2008/04/22/cars-mpg-gas-forbeslife-cx_jm_0422cars.html - 47k - Cached - Similar pages - Note this» Hack Your MPG: How to Improve Gas Mileage by 15 ...A few weeks ago, I mentioned that I was going to experiment with my driving style to see if I could improve my mileage. With gas prices topping $4/gallon, ...www.fivecentnickel.com/2008/06/17/hack-your-mpg-improve-gas-mileage-by-15/ - 56k - Cached - Similar pages - Note thisAcetone In Fuel Said to Increase MileageMany products claiming to improve mileage are expensive and do not really ... Take a mileage check

210 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7092_08_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/AU0Ie/220x123-9ec.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7092-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7092_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:47:40">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1pdftm_panda-given-tv-to-cure-boredom-and-depression_travel</link><title>Panda Given TV to Cure Boredom and Depression</title><description>Panda Given TV to Cure Boredom and Depression

Toegevoegd door Geo Beats vorig vrijdag

Staffers at Yunnan Wild Animal Park recently set up a television in a panda exhibit to help the animal get over depression and boredom. For some, a good TV show can be therapeutic for a troubled mind. Staffers at Yunnan Wild Animal Park seem to think that statement is true, as they recently set up a television in a panda exhibit.The employees hope the TV will help rid boredom and cure the animal’s depression. The panda in question is named Scarlett. Two of her companions, called Macy and Qianqian previously stayed at the Yunnan Wild Animal Park after their former homes in Sichuan were destroyed by an earthquake.During their time together, the three pandas became very close. Qianqian was transported back to Sichuan in 2012 and on March 31st of this year, Scarlett’s last remaining friend Macy was taken back to her original home. Scarlett was left alone and the sadness proved to be a little too much for the panda to handle. Right after Macy left, Scarlett refused to go back to her room, wouldn’t eat and ignored the staffers’ attempts to play and engage her. That’s when the staff wondered if a TV would help to console her. They installed one and played footage of Scarlett and Macy playing together when they were younger.Scarlett is responding beautifully to it. She now sits in front of the TV and munches her food while observing the video.

38 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7092_09_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/ESiu1/220x123-iaG.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7092-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7092_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 00:48:29">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xzi3bi_coffee-amount-in-tv-show-friends-enough-to-kill_travel</link><title>Coffee Amount in TV Show 'Friends' Enough to Kill</title><description>Coffee Amount in TV Show 'Friends' Enough to Kill

Toegevoegd door Geo Beats laatste mei

The caffeinated coffee amounts in the hit TV show 'Friends' are enough to kill.If there was one thing you saw in the hit TV show ‘Friends’ more than the 6 friends, it was coffee. The six companions were commonly together at a java establishment called Central Perk. An article on Scientific American's blog delves into the massive amounts of caffeine the friends took in over the course of the show. The telltale black mug frequently seen in the hands of Chandler, Ross, Phoebe, Joey, Rachel and Monica holds 20 ounces of coffee. Assuming that each of the characters filled and drank two of those giant cups per episode, that totals to a whopping 445 gallons of coffee ingested between all of the cast members. Using Starbucks as a guide, the writer concluded that the six friends took in 3 pounds of caffeine during the show’s run. It was further established that if the caffeine taken in over the 10 seasons was immediately distributed, the high potency would be enough to hospitalize, if not kill 300 hundred people. That’s some seriously disturbing ‘Friends’ trivia.How much coffee do you drink?

109 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7092_10_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/Ba1DE/220x123-_Np.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>