<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7106">active learning survey</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:43:13" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7106-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7106_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:43:13">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xxt3ua_flixercise-fun-active-learning-for-kids_lifestyle</link><title>Flixercise - Fun Active Learning for Kids</title><description>Flixercise - Fun Active Learning for Kids

Toegevoegd door flixercise vorig jaar

Flixercise is an interactive video activity library for kids! It is the goal of Flixercise to partner with parents/families and educators with a solution for inactivity in children. The Flixercise site provides teachers and families with anytime access to a large variety of fun and engaging physical activities with an academic focus. Each video activity is designed to promote movement, brain functioning, and learning! Flixercise activities have children jumping, clapping, singing, and having fun to enhance learning!! Our active learning videos can also help fight obesity and promote enhance learning and memory skills in a fun interactive environment for children. Kids can improve their reading and math skills to a variety of fitness activities and music styles: hip hop, cheerleading, kickboxing and more! To find out more about Flixercise visit http://www.flixercise.com/.

262 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7106_01_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BKVOS/220x123-MxJ.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7106-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7106_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:44:10">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1blckt_treehouse-nursery-school-active-learning-for-early-years_lifestyle</link><title>Treehouse Nursery School | Active Learning for Early Years</title><description>Treehouse Nursery School | Active Learning for Early Years

Toegevoegd door Treehouse Nursery School laatste februari

Treehouse Nursery School recognises the importance of education for the under-fives, which is why as well as a full care team, they also employ a full time infant teacher.

8 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7106_02_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/Dj8fL/220x123-R5E.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7106-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7106_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:44:49">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xz1zji_optimal-convex-optimization-under-tsybakov-noise-through-reduction-to-active-learning-aarti-singh-ca_tech</link><title>Optimal convex optimization under Tsybakov noise through reduction to active learning (Aarti SINGH-Carnegie Mellon University)</title><description>Optimal convex optimization under Tsybakov noise through reduction to active learning (Aarti SINGH-Carnegie Mellon University)

Toegevoegd door IHES Institut des Hautes Études Scientifiques vorig jaar

Optimal convex optimization under Tsybakov noise through reduction to active learning We demonstrate that the complexity of convex minimization is only determined by the rate of growth of the function around its minimizer, as quantified by a Tsybakov-like noise condition (TNC) with exponent k. Specifically, we demonstrate optimal first-order stochastic optimization rates that depend precisely on the TNC exponent k which include as special cases the classical rates for convex (k tending to infinity), strongly convex (k=2) and uniformly convex optimization (k &gt; 2). Even faster rates (nearly exponential) can be attained if the exponent 1 &lt; k &lt; 2\. Our analysis is based on a reduction of convex optimization to active learning as both problems involve minimizing the number of queries needed to identify the minimizer or the decision boundary, respectively,  by using feedback gained from prior queries. Our results demonstrate that the complexity of convex optimization in d-dimensions is precisely the same as the complexity of active learning in 1 dimension. First, we port a lower bound proof from active learning to demonstrate the complexity of optimizing convex function satisfying TNC, under both stochastic first-order oracle as well as derivative-free (zeroth order) setting. We then demonstrate that the optimal rate with TNC exponent under first-order oracle can be achieved by an epoch-gradient descent algorithm, as well as a coordinate descent algorithm that uses a 1-dimensional active learning algorithm as subroutine. We also show that it is possible to adapt to the unknown TNC exponent and hence the degree of convexity.

151 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7106_03_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/BWlTQ/220x123-zRA.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7106-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7106_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:46:05">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1ihoj5_best-price-exersaucer-delux-active-learning-circus_tech</link><title>best price ExerSaucer Delux Active Learning Circus</title><description>best price ExerSaucer Delux Active Learning Circus

Toegevoegd door Corsuhighform1986 laatste maart

best price ExerSaucer Delux Active Learning Circus Click on the discount link below: http://www.amazon.com/dp/B0096ICOW4/?tag=sonsfas0d-21 Disclaimer: I am a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon. Amazon and the Amazon logo are trademarks of Amazon, Inc. or its affiliates.

0 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7106_04_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/DvVNy/220x123-j0w.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7106-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7106_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:47:02">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1if451_cute-evenflo-exersaucer-triple-fun-active-learning-center-review_lifestyle</link><title>Cute Evenflo Exersaucer Triple Fun Active Learning Center Review!</title><description>Cute Evenflo Exersaucer Triple Fun Active Learning Center Review!

Toegevoegd door Chuchachuchin laatste maart

Best Offers/ Best Sale Price On: http://amzn.to/1pdza13

4 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7106_05_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/D8Lhj/220x123-VnE.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7106-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7106_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:47:57">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1debdl_clearance-exersaucer-delux-active-learning-circus_lifestyle</link><title>Clearance ExerSaucer Delux Active Learning Circus</title><description>Clearance ExerSaucer Delux Active Learning Circus

Toegevoegd door Luicapafea1974 laatste februari

Clearance ExerSaucer Delux Active Learning Circus Click on the discount link below: http://www.amazon.com/dp/B0096ICOW4/?tag=60percentoff-20 Disclaimer: I am a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon. Amazon and the Amazon logo are trademarks of Amazon, Inc. or its affiliates.

2 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7106_06_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/DvVNy/220x123-j0w.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7106-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7106_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:48:45">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x18uv0p_active-learning-of-constraints-for-semi-supervised-clustering_school</link><title>Active Learning of Constraints for Semi-Supervised Clustering</title><description>Active Learning of Constraints for Semi-Supervised Clustering

Toegevoegd door ecwaytechnologies laatste december

ECWAY TECHNOLOGIES @ IEEE EMBEDDED PROJECTS ECWAY TECHNOLOGIES @ IEEE MECHANICAL PROJECTS ECWAY TECHNOLOGIES @ IEEE VLSI PROJECTS ECWAY TECHNOLOGIES @ IEEE ROBTICS PROJECTS ECWAY TECHNOLOGIES @ IEEE POWER ELECTRONICS PROJECTS ECWAY TECHNOLOGIES @ IEEE JAVA PROJECTS ECWAY TECHNOLOGIES @ IEEE .NET PROJECTS ECWAY TECHNOLOGIES @ IEEE NS2 PROJECTS ECWAY TECHNOLOGIES @ IEEE MATLAB PROJECTS ECWAY TECHNOLOGIES @ IEEE ANDROID PROJECTS SUMMARY: Final Year IEEE Projects for BE, B.Tech, ME, M.Tech,M.Sc, MCA &amp; Diploma Students latest Java, .Net, Matlab, NS2, Android, Embedded,Mechanical, Robtics, VLSI, Power Electronics, IEEE projects are given absolutely complete working product and document providing with real time Software &amp; Embedded training...... ---------------------------------------------------------------- JAVA &amp; .NET PROJECTS: Networking, Network Security, Data Mining, Cloud Computing, Grid Computing, Web Services, Mobile Computing, Software Engineering, Image Processing, E-Commerce, Games App, Multimedia, etc., EMBEDDED SYSTEMS: Embedded Systems,Micro Controllers, DSC &amp; DSP, VLSI Design, Biometrics, RFID, Finger Print, Smart Cards, IRIS, Bar Code, Bluetooth, Zigbee, GPS, Voice Control, Remote System, Power Electronics, etc., ROBOTICS PROJECTS: Mobile Robots, Service Robots, Industrial Robots, Defence Robots, Spy Robot, Artificial Robots, Automated Machine Control, Stair Climbing, Cleaning, Painting, Industry Security Robots, etc., MOBILE APPLICATION (ANDROID &amp; J2ME): Android Application, Web Services, Wireless Application, Bluetooth Application, WiFi Application, Mobile Security, Multimedia Projects, Multi Media, E-Commerce, Games Application, etc., MECHANICAL PROJECTS: Auto Mobiles, Hydraulics, Robotics, Air Assisted Exhaust Breaking System, Automatic Trolley for Material Handling System in Industry, Hydraulics And Pneumatics, CAD/CAM/CAE Projects, Special Purpose Hydraulics And Pneumatics, CATIA, ANSYS, 3D Model Animations, etc., CONTACT US: ECWAY TECHNOLOGIES 15/1 Sathiyamoorthi Nagar, 2nd Cross, Thanthonimalai(Opp To Govt. Arts College) Karur-639 005. TamilNadu , India. Cell: +91 9894917187. Website: www.ecwayprojects.com | www.ecwaytechnologies.com Mail to: ecwaytechnologies@gmail.com.

4 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7106_07_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DUphA/220x123-a81.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7106-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7106_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:49:46">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1m63jb_best-price-evenflo-exersaucer-triple-fun-active-learning-center-life-in-the-amazon_shortfilms</link><title>best price Evenflo Exersaucer Triple Fun Active Learning Center Life in The Amazon</title><description>best price Evenflo Exersaucer Triple Fun Active Learning Center Life in The Amazon

Toegevoegd door Thercavivent1970 2 weken geleden

best price Evenflo Exersaucer Triple Fun Active Learning Center Life in The Amazon Click on the discount link below: http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00AJSJE6O/?tag=60percentoff2-20 Disclaimer: I am a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon. Amazon and the Amazon logo are trademarks of Amazon, Inc. or its affiliates.

8 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7106_08_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/EIE9v/220x123-gH4.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7106-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7106_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:50:23">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1dq9ei_clearance-evenflo-exersaucer-triple-fun-active-learning-center-life-in-the-amazon_lifestyle</link><title>Clearance Evenflo Exersaucer Triple Fun Active Learning Center Life in The Amazon</title><description>Clearance Evenflo Exersaucer Triple Fun Active Learning Center Life in The Amazon

Toegevoegd door Menkeraka1974 laatste februari

Clearance Evenflo Exersaucer Triple Fun Active Learning Center Life in The Amazon Click on the discount link below: http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00AJSJE6O/?tag=60percentoff-20 Disclaimer: I am a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon. Amazon and the Amazon logo are trademarks of Amazon, Inc. or its affiliates.

25 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7106_09_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/Dw-nv/220x123-WFO.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7106-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7106_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 02:51:12">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xs38x2_steelcase-education-solutions-introduces-new-active-learning-solutions-video_news</link><title>Steelcase Education Solutions Introduces New Active Learning Solutions - Video</title><description>Steelcase Education Solutions Introduces New Active Learning Solutions - Video

Toegevoegd door tvnportal vorig jaar

Introducing VerbPowered by NewsLook.com Producer : MultiVu

61 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7106_10_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/ZkSj/220x123-Y1Y.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>