<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7109">best place to eat pho in new york</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:07:59" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7109-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7109_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:08:00">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1ddj4a_best-places-to-travel-in-new-york_travel</link><title>Best Places To Travel In New York</title><description>Best Places To Travel In New York

Toegevoegd door Nasser ALI laatste februari

Hotels Checkout is a site which offers honest and unbiased travel reviews from nomadic travel writers who have a deep love for exploration and wandering to different lands and destinations. All blog contributors of Hotels Checkout give valuable travel tips and well-researched advice on how to spend less while travelling and how to find the best hotels that will make your travel experience more enjoyable and successful. Hotels Checkout envisions to help its blog readers to become wiser in choosing their accommodations, destinations, and even in planning every detail of their travels and tours. Hotels Checkout will help you know the best travel destination for every season. Visit http://hotelscheckout.com/ for more information.

7 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7109_01_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DvMne/220x123-a4v.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7109-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7109_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:08:51">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x12snr2_phillip-roy-wasserman-best-places-to-visit-in-new-york_travel</link><title>Phillip Roy Wasserman - Best Places to Visit in New York</title><description>Phillip Roy Wasserman - Best Places to Visit in New York

Toegevoegd door Phillip Roy Wasserman laatste augustus

Phillip Roy Wasserman shares a video Best Places to Visit in New York. Phillip Roy Wasserman shares this video to show you the beauty of New York. Phillip Roy Wasserman

32 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7109_02_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/CMRf6/220x123-NAU.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7109-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7109_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:09:30">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x16sx9o_best-infiniti-dealership-around-york-pa-best-place-to-buy-a-new-infiniti-near-york-pa_auto</link><title>Best Infiniti Dealership around York, PA| Best place to buy a new Infiniti near York, PA</title><description>Best Infiniti Dealership around York, PA| Best place to buy a new Infiniti near York, PA

Toegevoegd door dm_525d470fe41e5 laatste november

Visit us on the web at http://www.nationwideinfiniti.com/ or call us at 410-561-1000 Nationwide Infiniti, located near York, PA, is the premier provider of new and pre-owned Infiniti automobiles. Our new and pre-owned inventories hold a wide assortment of vehicles to suit every taste and need. At Nationwide Infiniti, we strive to make buying or leasing a new or pre-owned vehicle a pleasant and rewarding experience. Come down to Nationwide Infiniti, located near York, PA, today and let us get you in the car of your dreams!

1 view</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7109_03_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/CyHQ8/220x123-cx2.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7109-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7109_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:10:32">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x16sykw_best-kia-dealership-in-york-pa-where-is-the-best-place-to-buy-a-kia-near-york-pa_auto</link><title>Best Kia Dealership in York, PA| Where is the best place to buy a Kia near York, PA</title><description>Best Kia Dealership in York, PA| Where is the best place to buy a Kia near York, PA

Toegevoegd door dm_525d44553c898 laatste november

Visit us on the web at www.nationwide-kia.com or call us at (410) 561-9000 Nationwide Kia, located near York, PA, is the premier provider of new and pre-owned Kia automobiles. Our new and pre-owned inventories hold a wide assortment of vehicles to suit every taste and need. At Nationwide Kia, we strive to make buying or leasing a new or pre-owned vehicle a pleasant and rewarding experience. Come down to Nationwide Kia, located near York, PA, today and let us get you in the car of your dreams!

0 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7109_04_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CyHtq/220x123-mys.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7109-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7109_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:11:44">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xayalz_best-place-to-watch-baseball-new-yo_sport</link><title>best place to watch baseball New York vs Philadelphia</title><description>best place to watch baseball New York vs Philadelphia

Toegevoegd door michaelsanford71 4 jaren geleden

http://WatchMLBOnline.net best place to watch baseball New York vs Philadelphia by visiting the above link

18 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7109_05_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/Asp8L/220x123-skg.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7109-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7109_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:12:30">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xayaqq_best-place-to-watch-a-baseball-game_sport</link><title>best place to watch a baseball game New York vs Philadelphia</title><description>best place to watch a baseball game New York vs Philadelphia

Toegevoegd door baow21 4 jaren geleden

http://WatchMLBOnline.net best place to watch a baseball game New York vs Philadelphia by visiting the above link

29 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7109_06_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/AsqA4/220x123-YLf.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7109-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7109_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:13:18">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xi6xxw_eat-the-best-pizza-in-new-york_news</link><title>Eat The Best Pizza In New York</title><description>Eat The Best Pizza In New York

Toegevoegd door Local News 3 jaren geleden

(New York, NY) High gas prices have travelers taking cars less often, but News 4 New York's Cat Greenleaf shows you how a quick subway ride could take you to pizza paradise.

55 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7109_07_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/U2aL/220x123-HQj.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7109-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7109_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:13:51">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xg2l5q_brazilian-model-and-tv-host-fernanda-motta-grabs-a-bite-to-eat-with-friends-in-new-york_people</link><title>Brazilian model and TV host Fernanda Motta grabs a bite to eat with friends in New York</title><description>Brazilian model and TV host Fernanda Motta grabs a bite to eat with friends in New York

Toegevoegd door Celeb News 3 jaren geleden

NEW YORK, NEW YORK - Thursday May 21 2009. Brazilian model and TV host Fernanda Motta grabs a bite to eat with friends in New York.

1 151 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7109_08_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/VZtc/220x123-flY.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7109-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7109_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:14:24">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x18tvf4_top-10-amazing-places-to-visit-in-new-york_travel</link><title>Top 10 Amazing Places To Visit in New York</title><description>Top 10 Amazing Places To Visit in New York

Toegevoegd door Gnxtgroup laatste december

Empire State Building Tired of staring up at New York City skyscrapers? Check out the view of New York City from atop the Empire State Building. A classic New York City attraction, it offers visitors wonderful views of New York City and the surrounding area. Our advice: cut your waiting time by purchasing your tickets in advance. Statue of Liberty The Statue of Liberty was a gift to the United States in honor of the friendship established during the French Revolution. It has become an American symbol of freedom and welcome to the immigrants who come to the USA looking for a better life. While the interior of the Statue of Liberty is closed for improvements, you can still visit Liberty Island and nearby Ellis Island. The Museum of Modern Art (MoMA) Founded in 1929 as the first museum dedicated entirely to contemporary art, the MoMA is host to an impressive collection of modern artistic efforts. From painting and sculpture to film and architecture, the Museum of Modern Art's diverse collection has something for everyone, including kids. Central Park Central Park has offered a welcome escape from the concrete jungle of New York City for over 150 years. Take a walk, a boat ride or just enjoy a picnic in Central Park and discover for yourself why Central Park is so popular.

228 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7109_09_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DUZtm/220x123-2YS.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7109-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7109_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 03:15:34">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xzgu5x_top-5-places-to-propose-in-new-york-city_creation</link><title>Top 5 Places To Propose In New York City</title><description>Top 5 Places To Propose In New York City

Toegevoegd door VideojugCreativeCulture laatste april

VideoJug user Ryan Ride5 brings us a great guide on the top five places to propose in New York City. Watch this film for some truly romantic inspiration for when you take the plunge.

281 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7109_10_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/Bafow/220x123--2X.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>