<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7118">part time jobs texas city</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:13:22" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7118-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7118_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:13:23">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1onhmd_part-time-work-at-home-jobs-in-agoura-hills-ca-california_people</link><title>Part Time Work At Home Jobs In Agoura Hills CA California</title><description>Part Time Work At Home Jobs In Agoura Hills CA California

Toegevoegd door Armando Lima een week geleden

Part Time Jobs In Agoura Hills CA http://bit.ly/jobs-part-time https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X68jcuywkQ4

1 view</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7118_01_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/EPDvP/220x123-60Y.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7118-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7118_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:14:03">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1ifvxx_part-time-jobs-in-malta_people</link><title>Part Time Jobs In Malta</title><description>Part Time Jobs In Malta

Toegevoegd door Avaaddison5 laatste maart

Read More About Part Time Jobs In Malta : http://caterermalta.com/key-approaches-for-finding-part-time-jobs-in-malta/

7 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7118_02_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/D8N-H/220x123-Ovj.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7118-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7118_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:14:41">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1g6njq_part-time-jobs-by-jobsupermart_music</link><title>Part Time Jobs by Jobsupermart</title><description>Part Time Jobs by Jobsupermart

Toegevoegd door Kittyenedinay7 laatste maart

Part Time Jobs http://www.jobsupermart.com/ (65) 67339136 JobSupermart.com 111 North Bridge Road 27-01 Peninsula Plaza Singapore 179098 With unstable economy and increasing prices of necessary commodities it has become difficult for common workers and employees to meet basic monthly needs. Towards the end of a month nothing is left in pocket after paying home rent, utility bills and medical expenses. Also unexpected issue may arise anytime that requires urgent cash. That is why most people plan to save some money by doing part-time jobs. Rest assured you are not the only one who feels that manner. Many people look for part time work. However, JobSupermart is an online job solutions provider looking to help those who are looking for part-time jobs in Singapore and neighboring areas. It focuses on providing online recruitment services at an extremely cost effective rate to help both the employers as well as job hunters. For more information go to JobSupermart.com now.

3 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7118_03_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/D3Jc6/220x123-WGg.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7118-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7118_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:15:35">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1bzu5f_part-time-jobs-from-home-300-a-day-online-watch-this_lifestyle</link><title>Part Time Jobs From Home - $300+ a Day Online! (WATCH THIS)</title><description>Part Time Jobs From Home - $300+ a Day Online! (WATCH THIS)

Toegevoegd door Frank laatste februari

http://MyNoBsIncomeFormula.com/go Are you looking for part time jobs from home? Part time jobs from home have become a new norm when life has challenges that prevent you from working a typical 9 to 5 or you are unable to meet your income demands and family needs. Have you heard of the part time jobs from home available on the Internet? Many people who have a full-time job are taken advantage of these part time opportunities and are dedicating time to building a small fortune. Do you want to learn how you can start doing it as well? I am a successful Internet marketer and I do enjoy helping others to find success in the world of Internet marketing. If you want to know how you can begin a part time job from home within just a few days, no experience necessary - here is your special course: http://MyNoBsIncomeFormula.com/go It is a proven system to make money online. I have tested it and it made me $1000 in first week of using it. It has video modules that will teach you each and every thing even if you are a newbie. Check it out and let me know what you think! See you there, - Frank

8 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7118_04_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/Dnnpm/220x123-7e_.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7118-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7118_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:16:07">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1c4pk0_isis-found-a-part-time-job-isis-love-johnny-sins-2014-full-and-free-brazzers-porn_shortfilms</link><title>Isis Found a Part Time Job Isis Love , Johnny Sins 2014 Full and Free Brazzers Porn</title><description>Isis Found a Part Time Job Isis Love , Johnny Sins 2014 Full and Free Brazzers Porn

Toegevoegd door Watchxxxhd laatste februari

Isis Found a Part Time Job Isis Love , Johnny Sins 2014 Full and Free Brazzers Porn

4 102 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7118_05_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/DoepP/220x123-a8_.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7118-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7118_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:16:39">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x13s9y7_do-part-time-low-paid-jobs-have-a-future_news</link><title>Do Part Time Low Paid Jobs Have a Future?</title><description>Do Part Time Low Paid Jobs Have a Future?

Toegevoegd door tvnportal laatste augustus

We talk to Prof. Michael C. Burda from the economics faculty at Berlin's Humboldt University.Powered by NewsLook.com Producer : Deutsche Welle

20 048 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7118_06_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CHYM8/220x123-LYt.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7118-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7118_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:17:34">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x13sh8v_do-part-time-low-paid-jobs-have-a-future-made-in-germany_news</link><title>Do part-time low-paid jobs have a future? | Made in Germany</title><description>Do part-time low-paid jobs have a future? | Made in Germany

Toegevoegd door DW (English) laatste augustus

Talk with Prof. Michael C. Burda from the economics faculty at Berlin's Humboldt University.

18 831 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7118_07_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CToNE/220x123-bc0.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7118-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7118_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:18:33">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x13shcl_working-before-work-the-boom-of-low-paid-part-time-jobs-made-in-germany_news</link><title>Working before work - the boom of low-paid part-time jobs | Made in Germany</title><description>Working before work - the boom of low-paid part-time jobs | Made in Germany

Toegevoegd door DW (English) laatste augustus

They're care providers, project managers or consultants by profession, but they also drive bicycle taxis. Nearly 10% of Germans have a second job. What’s not clear is whether it’s out of necessity or to increase their spending-power, as the German ministry of labor suggests.

23 401 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7118_08_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CToQQ/220x123-hRm.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7118-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7118_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:19:22">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x13s9y9_working-before-work-the-boom-of-low-paid-part-time-jobs_news</link><title>Working Before Work the Boom of Low Paid Part Time Jobs</title><description>Working Before Work the Boom of Low Paid Part Time Jobs

Toegevoegd door tvnportal laatste augustus

They're care providers, project managers or consultants by profession, but they also drive bicycle taxis. Nearly 10% of Germans have a second job. Whats not clear is whether its out of necessity or to increase their spending-power, as the German ministry of labor suggests.Powered by NewsLook.com Producer : Deutsche Welle

133 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7118_09_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CHYM8/220x123-LYt.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7118-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7118_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 04:19:58">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x18c464_greeks-earning-less-trapped-in-part-time-low-wage-jobs_news</link><title>Greeks earning less, trapped in part-time low wage jobs</title><description>Greeks earning less, trapped in part-time low wage jobs

Toegevoegd door euronews-en laatste december

Unemployment in Greece remains stuck near record highs, but even many of those with a job are struggling financially. Newly released figures show nearly 30 percent of workers in the private sector are earning less that 600 euros a month.Theodoros Anastasopoulos left university three years ago, but the only job he can get is as a public opinion pollster: He told euronews: “Two years after I completed my studies, I found this part-time job which pays me 250 to 300 euros a month. Obviously, I cannot afford to rent anywhere to live, I stay with my mother and my sister and the money we make covers only the food, utility bills and taxes.” The Greek Labour Ministry says there are 1,371,450 people employed by private companies in the country. Twenty percent of them – 274,000 – earn less that 500 euros a month, mostly working part time. Another eight percent – that’s 100,000 people – have a monthly income of 500 to 600 euros. Most of the rest earn between 1,000 and 2,000 euros. Labour costs have fallen as unemployment has been rising. Anna Hatzioannidou told us: “I finished my architecture studies a year ago. I have sent out over 100 CVs, I have only had a couple of job interviews. Now, I work as a part time photographer, taking pictures at night clubs and bars, for 240 euros per month.”Dramatically lower wages have not meant more people in work. In September unemployment inched up to 27.4 percent of the workforce from 27.3 percent in the previous two months. Almost 52 percent of young people are without a job.Euronews reporter in Athens Symela Touchtidou said: “Even when people are poorly paid, often it takes a long time for them to get their money. Research by the Greek Confederation of Trade Unions shows nearly half of all companies are paying wages at least one month late.”

7 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7118_10_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/DNRRC/220x123-XmI.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>