<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7135">Ahmed Dogan assassination</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:21:11" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7135-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7135_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:21:12">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xww2b7_assassination-attempt-on-bulgarian-opposition-leader-ahmed-dogan-mrf_news</link><title>Assassination Attempt on Bulgarian Opposition Leader Ahmed Dogan (MRF)</title><description>Assassination Attempt on Bulgarian Opposition Leader Ahmed Dogan (MRF)

Toegevoegd door Amazing Videos vorig jaar

A man jumped on stage and pointed a gun at the leader of Bulgaria's ethnic Turkish party before security guards wrestled him to the ground during a televised conference on Saturday.Ahmed Dogan, the long-time leader of the Movement for Rights and Freedoms (MRF) escaped unscathed, and it was not immediately clear why the attacker had targeted him at the party congress in downtown Sofia.Television footage showed the man jumping out of the audience and interrupting a speech by 58-year-old Dogan, who has led the party for almost a quarter of a century. Security guards were seen beating and kicking the attacker."Ahmed Dogan is in good health. Everything is under control," MRF official Ceyhan Ibryamov told journalists.Police said they had arrested a 25-year-old man from the Black Sea town of Burgas who was also carrying two knives.The liberal MRF party represents ethnic Turks and other Muslims who make up about 12 percent of Bulgaria's 7.3 million-strong population.Dogan is

1 347 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7135_01_thumb.png">http://s2.dmcdn.net/no-such-asset.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7135-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7135_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:22:09">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xwzc60_ahmed-dogan-assassination-attempt-incredible-video-bulgaria-review_news</link><title>Ahmed Dogan Assassination Attempt. INCREDIBLE VIDEO - Bulgaria (REVIEW)</title><description>Ahmed Dogan Assassination Attempt. INCREDIBLE VIDEO - Bulgaria (REVIEW)

Toegevoegd door tdancetv2 vorig jaar

COPYRIGHT DISCLAIMER Under Section 107 of the Copyright Act 1976, ALLOWANCE IS MADE FOR FAIR USE PURPOSES such as CRITICISM, COMMENT, news reporting, teaching, scholarship, and RESEARCH. Fair use is a use permitted by copyright statute that might otherwise be infringing. Non-profit, educational or personal use tips the balance in favor of fair use.--I have no ads on this video.any copyright issues, please just send a msg.SOFIA, Bulgaria — Bulgarian police detained a man after he pointed a gas pistol at an ethnic Turkish party leader as he was delivering a speech at a party caucus in the capital Saturday. No shots were fired.The video from the Saturday event in Sofia shows the man climbing the podium where Ahmed Dogan, the leader of the Movement for Rights and Freedoms, was speaking, and pointing the gun to his face.Dogan struck the man before he could pull the trigger, while other delegates wrestled the assailant to the ground. TV footage showed several people punching, kicking and stomping on the man when he was on the ground.Police arrested him and took him to a hospital. It wasn't immediately clear if he sustained serious injuries, or how he got past security to enter the hall with nearly 3,000 people attending.Eventually, the attacker was identified by police as 25-year-old Oktai Enimehmedov, a Bulgarian national and ethnic Turk, from the coastal city of Burgas. He was carrying the gas pistol and two knives. A gas pistol is a non-lethal weapon used for self-defense, but experts say when fired from close range it can cause life-threatening injuries.Interior Minister Tsvevtan Tsvetanov told journalists that the assailant had a criminal record for drugs possession, robberies and hooliganism.The liberal MRF party mainly represents ethnic Turks and other Muslims in Bulgaria, who make up 12 percent of its 7.3-million population.The conference had to elect a new leader to succeed Dogan, who is one of the Balkan country's most influential political figures. The 58-year-old has been at the helm of the party since founding it in 1990.Lyutvi Mestan, who was expected to become the new party leader, said "the true reason for the assault was the language of hatred and confrontation."Saturday's assault was the gravest attack on a politician in post-communist Bulgaria after the 1996 killing of ex-prime Minister Andrei Lukanov.

223 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7135_02_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/BEi9_/220x123-xLu.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7135-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7135_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:23:13">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xwvv2g_tentative-d-assassinat-sur-ahmed-dogan_news</link><title>Tentative d'assassinat sur Ahmed Dogan</title><description>Tentative d'assassinat sur Ahmed Dogan

Toegevoegd door Spi0n vorig jaar

Ce matin en Bulgarie, le président du parti libéral bulgare Ahmed Dogan, a échappé de peu à une tentative d’assassinat en public lorsqu'un homme armé d'un pistolet est monté sur la scène du congrès, a brandi une arme sur l'homme et tiré à plusieurs reprises. L'arme se serait alors enraillée et l'agresseur a pu être rapidement maitrisé par les gardes du corps. Cette tentative de meurtre raté s'est déroulée ce 19 Janvier 2013 lors du congrès du parti Mouvement des droits et libertés de la ville de Sofia en Bulgarie. Selon les premières information, l'assassin ferait parti de la mafia Bulgare.

509 786 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7135_03_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/BEFqx/220x123-zP2.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7135-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7135_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:23:46">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xwwelz_gun-jam-turkish-politician-ahmet-dogan-survives-failed-assassination-attempt-moments-ago_news</link><title>GUN JAM: Turkish Politician Ahmet Dogan Survives Failed Assassination Attempt Moments Ago</title><description>GUN JAM: Turkish Politician Ahmet Dogan Survives Failed Assassination Attempt Moments Ago

Toegevoegd door Amazing Videos vorig jaar

Heartstopping moment would-be assassin aims gun at Bulgarian opposition leader's head and pulls the trigger... but victim survives after weapon misfiresA Bulgarian politician today survived an assassination attempt when a gunman approached him on the stage where he was speaking.Fortunately for Ahmed Dogan, leader of the Movement for Rights and Freedoms, the gun misfires giving him time to react and hit the would-be assassins hand out of the way.Before he can fire a second shot the unidentified suspect is tackled to the ground by people at the conference in Sofia and security guards.

162 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7135_04_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BEIB_/220x123-9u8.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7135-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7135_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:24:44">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xwvt4z_ahmed-dogan_news</link><title>Ahmed Dogan</title><description>Ahmed Dogan

Toegevoegd door stefanelonikitelo vorig jaar

Ahmed Dogan

41 883 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7135_05_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/BEElZ/220x123-c9i.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7135-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7135_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:25:54">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xwvxxw_ahmed-dogan-a-echappe-de-peu-a-un-assassinat-en-direct_news</link><title>Ahmed Dogan a échappé de peu à un assassinat en direct !</title><description>Ahmed Dogan a échappé de peu à un assassinat en direct !

Toegevoegd door Gentside vorig jaar

http://www.gentside.com/bulgarie/bulgarie-l-039-incroyable-tentative-d-assassinat-sur-ahmed-dogan-filmee-en-direct_art47784.html

648 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7135_06_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/BJI94/220x123-jCu.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7135-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7135_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:26:40">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xwvy61_ahmed-dogan-a-echappe-de-peu-a-un-assassinat-en-direct_news</link><title>Ahmed Dogan a échappé de peu à un assassinat en direct !</title><description>Ahmed Dogan a échappé de peu à un assassinat en direct !

Toegevoegd door Gentside vorig jaar

http://www.gentside.com/bulgarie/bulgarie-l-039-incroyable-tentative-d-assassinat-sur-ahmed-dogan-filmee-en-direct_art47784.html

551 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7135_07_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/BEFf_/220x123-scU.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7135-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7135_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:27:34">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xiso1u_ahmed-dogan-and-kasim-dal-djebel-19-05-2011_news</link><title>Ahmed Dogan and Kasim Dal - Djebel - 19.05.2011</title><description>Ahmed Dogan and Kasim Dal - Djebel - 19.05.2011

Toegevoegd door Bulgaria Times 2 jaren geleden

Ahmed Dogan and Kasim Dal - Djebel - 19.05.2011

875 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7135_08_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/AbY5M/220x123-5jL.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7135-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7135_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:28:33">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xwz2zk_failed-assissination-attempt-ahmed-dogan-full-length-and-possible-motives-hydroelectric-power-scam_news</link><title>Failed assissination attempt Ahmed Dogan FULL LENGTH and possible motives, hydroelectric power scam</title><description>Failed assissination attempt Ahmed Dogan FULL LENGTH and possible motives, hydroelectric power scam

Toegevoegd door StarCrypt101 vorig jaar

41 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7135_09_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BEb86/220x123-UPR.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7135-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7135_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:29:11">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xwxfk5_failed-assassination-captured-during-televised-event_news</link><title>Failed Assassination Captured During Televised Event</title><description>Failed Assassination Captured During Televised Event

Toegevoegd door OneMinuteNews vorig jaar

A Bulgarian politician is extremely lucky to be alive after a man points a gun at his head and pulls the trigger during a televised conference.

584 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7135_10_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BEN-z/220x123-8VA.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>