<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7136">Soccer trick</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:30:02" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7136-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7136_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:30:03">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1a5z0t_amazing-backflip-soccer-trick_fun</link><title>Amazing Backflip Soccer Trick!</title><description>Amazing Backflip Soccer Trick!

Toegevoegd door RumbleVideo laatste januari

Pro football freestyler, Daniel Cutting, shows us his incredible kick and flip soccer trick. Bet you haven't seen that before!

15 759 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7136_01_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/Dc0U6/220x123-z04.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7136-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7136_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:31:02">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x155w9x_soccer-football-trick-shots-on-basketball-court-liam-coyte_fun</link><title>Soccer/Football Trick Shots on Basketball Court | Liam Coyte</title><description>Soccer/Football Trick Shots on Basketball Court | Liam Coyte

Toegevoegd door JukinVideo laatste september

JukinMember and soccer/football trickshot master Liam Coyte shows off his awesome skills once again, but this time on a basketball court (and some other places too)! Check his channel here: http://jukinvideo.com/members/liam-co... SUBSCRIBE: http://bit.ly/JukinVideodm LIKE us on FACEBOOK: http://facebook.com/JukinVideo FOLLOW us on TWITTER: http://twitter.com/JukinVideo REGISTER and UPLOAD on our WEBSITE: http://JukinVideo.com

2 109 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7136_02_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CfA66/220x123-7wV.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7136-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7136_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:31:50">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x11u3ve_soccer-groundmove-soccer-tricks_sport</link><title>soccer groundmove - Soccer Tricks</title><description>soccer groundmove - Soccer Tricks

Toegevoegd door Footballtricksonline laatste juli

Website: http://www.footballtricksonline.com FB: https://www.facebook.com/footballtricksonlineofficial Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/guidofto do you want to learn how to football? here you have a demonstration on how to do the "around the world" football/soccer trick to improve your football-soccer skills. Step 1 : Push the soccer ball with the inner part of your foot Step 2: Do a fake football/soccer move , swing your leg around the football to do it. Step 3 : Strike to the opposite way with a fast sprint! I hope this helps you in your football/soccer training. Try to improve your tricks and skills as much as you can. All these soccer moves are perfect as football training exercices. Watch the next football skills online tutorials to keep improving your soccer skills and have fun ;) Now you can do the popular tricks like football players like Cristiano ronaldo, neymar, messi, robinho, ronaldinho, carlitos tevez, etc The advanced step over can be used in futsal, street soccer, freestyle ,Street soccer anywhere! it´s an awsome football trick and not hard to learn ! learn this soccer skill now! football panna fotbalové triky サッカートリック 足球技巧 เทคนิคฟุตบอล футбольные трюки

3 160 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7136_03_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CDLem/220x123-n8G.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7136-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7136_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:32:54">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x11s8b0_pop-up-callejero-soccer-tricks_sport</link><title>Pop up Callejero - Soccer Tricks</title><description>Pop up Callejero - Soccer Tricks

Toegevoegd door Footballtricksonline laatste juli

Website: http://www.footballtricksonline.com FB: https://www.facebook.com/footballtricksonlineofficial Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/guidofto aquí tienes una demostración de cómo hacer EL "Pop up Callejero" un truco de futbol famoso para mejorar sus habilidades de futbolista. El truco de fútbol paso a paso : Paso 1 coloca el balón entre los dos pies.con tu pie dominante rueda el balón hacia arriba por tu pierna opuesta Paso 2 Rápidamente gira tu pie de apoyo completamente hacia atras y controla el balón Vean los siguientes vídeos tutoriales para seguir mejorando sus habilidades de fútbol y divertirse;) Espero que esto le ayude en su fútbol / entrenamiento de futbol. Trate de mejorar sus trucos y habilidades de futbol tanto como sea posible. Todos estos movimientos del fútbol son perfectos como ejercicios de entrenamiento de fútbol. Ahora usted puede hacer los trucos más populares como los jugadores de fútbol como Cristiano Ronaldo, Neymar, Messi, Robinho, Ronaldinho, Tevez carlitos, etc

2 591 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7136_04_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/CCsJY/220x123-oB7.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7136-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7136_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:33:33">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x11s87o_neymar-ball-pop-soccer-tricks_sport</link><title>Neymar ball pop - Soccer Tricks</title><description>Neymar ball pop - Soccer Tricks

Toegevoegd door Footballtricksonline laatste juli

Website: http://www.footballtricksonline.com FB: https://www.facebook.com/footballtricksonlineofficial Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/guidofto do you want to learn how to football? here you have a demonstration on how to do the "Neymar ball pop" football/soccer trick to improve your football-soccer skills. STEP1 Roll the ball with your non dominant foot STEP 2 Hit the ball with a fast tap in the inferior part, the harder the tap the higher the ball will reach Tip Thissoccer trick is used to pop the ball over the opponent, you will measure the strength depending on the height you wish Now you can do the popular trick like football players like Cristiano ronaldo, neymar, messi,etc. Very famous football trick,mostly used in freestyle and also used to improve football/soccer skills and strengthen the thighs of football players fotbalové triky サッカートリック 足球技巧 เทคนิคฟุตบอล футбольные трюки

2 147 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7136_05_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CCsF0/220x123-LV9.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7136-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7136_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:34:22">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x11s7z9_how-to-kick-like-cristiano-ronaldo-cr7-soccer-tricks_sport</link><title>How to kick like Cristiano Ronaldo cr7 - Soccer Tricks</title><description>How to kick like Cristiano Ronaldo cr7 - Soccer Tricks

Toegevoegd door Footballtricksonline laatste juli

Website: http://www.footballtricksonline.com FB: https://www.facebook.com/footballtricksonlineofficial Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/guidofto do you want to learn how to football? here you have a demonstration on how to kick/shoot like cristiano ronaldo CR7, this soccer tutorial will help you to improve your football-soccer skills. step 1 Place the ball on the ground with the valve facing your foot step 2 take a distance of about 3-7 steps depending on the comfort of each person and the distance at which the goal is. step 3 Hit the ball with the area between the inner and the instep. (Do not hit full instep) try kicking strong or the effect will not work Now you can do the popular trick like football players like Cristiano ronaldo, neymar, messi,etc. Very famous football trick,mostly used in freestyle and also used to improve football/soccer skills and strengthen the thighs of football players

3 470 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7136_06_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/CCr8Q/220x123-k13.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7136-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7136_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:35:04">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x11s8dd_ronaldinho-karaoke-soccer-tricks_sport</link><title>Ronaldinho Karaoke - Soccer Tricks</title><description>Ronaldinho Karaoke - Soccer Tricks

Toegevoegd door Footballtricksonline laatste juli

Website: http://www.footballtricksonline.com FB: https://www.facebook.com/footballtricksonlineofficial Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/guidofto do you want to learn how to football? here you have a demonstration on how to implement an awesome soccer technique! EXPLANATION STEP 1-roll the ball with your dominant foot STEP 2-stop the ball with the sole of your non-dominant foot (the ball should stop right next to your other foot) STEP 3- drag the ball back with your sole and then flick it up with your toes STEP 4- finally control the ball learn these soccer/football tips and tricks to get better Now you can do the popular trick like football players like Cristiano ronaldo, neymar, messi,etc. fotbalové triky サッカートリック 足球技巧 เทคนิคฟุตบอล футбольные трюки Very famous football trick,mostly used in freestyle and also used to improve football/soccer skills and strengthen the thighs of football players

1 083 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7136_07_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CCsLE/220x123-pNy.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7136-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7136_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:35:41">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x11u3wj_street-hook-soccer-tricks_sport</link><title>Street hook - Soccer Tricks</title><description>Street hook - Soccer Tricks

Toegevoegd door Footballtricksonline laatste juli

Website: http://www.footballtricksonline.com FB: https://www.facebook.com/footballtricksonlineofficial Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/guidofto do you want to learn how to football? here you have a demonstration on how to do the soccer "street soccer hook" football/soccer trick to improve your football-soccer skills on the streets or not! step 1 Place the ball between your feet, then press it against your non dominant ankle, now roll the ball up, when you get to your calves height, roll it behind the calf until you reach the outer side of the calf. step 2 now roll the ball upwards with power and finally control it. Now you can do the popular trick like football players like Cristiano ronaldo, neymar, messi,etc. Very famous football trick,mostly used in freestyle and also used to improve football/soccer skills and strengthen the thighs of football players

3 198 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7136_08_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/CDLfQ/220x123-sqc.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7136-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7136_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:36:15">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x11s80l_knee-akka-soccer-tricks_sport</link><title>Knee akka - Soccer Tricks</title><description>Knee akka - Soccer Tricks

Toegevoegd door Footballtricksonline laatste juli

Website: http://www.footballtricksonline.com FB: https://www.facebook.com/footballtricksonlineofficial Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/guidofto do you want to learn how to football? here you have a demonstration on how to do the soccer "knee akka" football/soccer trick to improve your football-soccer skills. Explanation Control the ball. when you are ready,kick the ball upwards and hit it with the side of your knee to the outside, then quickly kick the ball back in with your foot Tip Try to hit the soccer ball with the side of your knee and softly, if you do it rough the ball will be far from your control area. Now you can do the popular trick like football players like Cristiano ronaldo, neymar, messi,etc. Very famous football trick,mostly used in freestyle and also used to improve football/soccer skills and strengthen the thighs of football players fotbalové triky サッカートリック 足球技巧 เทคนิคฟุตบอล футбольные трюки

570 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7136_09_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CCr-w/220x123-XPC.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7136-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7136_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:37:02">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x12bsea_top-5-ronaldinho-tricks-epic-soccer-training_news</link><title>TOP 5 RONALDINHO TRICKS (Epic Soccer Training)</title><description>TOP 5 RONALDINHO TRICKS (Epic Soccer Training)

Toegevoegd door QueenieAnamaria960 laatste juli

Go To The Link Below To Downloadhttp://tinyurl.com/n65rorxTOP 5 RONALDINHO TRICKS (Epic Soccer Training) TOP,5,RONALDINHO,TRICKS,Epic,Soccer,Traininghttp://tinyurl.com/n65rorx

870 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7136_10_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CIPmS/220x123-iCu.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>