<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7137">Cat movies</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:37:54" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7137-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7137_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:37:55">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x15s547_it-s-just-a-cat-in-suspense-movies-supercut-alien-buffy-scary-movie-friday-13-halloween_shortfilms</link><title>"It's just a cat!!" in suspense movies supercut!!! Alien, Buffy, Scary Movie, Friday 13, Halloween...</title><description>"It's just a cat!!" in suspense movies supercut!!! Alien, Buffy, Scary Movie, Friday 13, Halloween...

Toegevoegd door MisterSexyBuzz laatste oktober

Eerie suspense followed by a cat bursting out from the darkness is one of the most cliche horror movie gimmicks. But that doesn’t stop unoriginal directors from using the tactic over and over. The It’s Just A Cat trick has been used so many times, cinema-obsessed Slacktory had no trouble creating this super cut of cats scaring people in the movies.

266 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7137_01_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/CmsOU/220x123-v_B.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7137-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7137_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:38:32">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xmegiv_maltin-on-movies-african-cats_shortfilms</link><title>Maltin on Movies - African Cats</title><description>Maltin on Movies - African Cats

Toegevoegd door ReelzChannel 2 jaren geleden

Leonard Maltin takes a closer look at African Cats

381 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7137_02_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/AcqDL/220x123-BIa.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7137-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7137_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:39:24">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x185tra_cat-movies-cd_animals</link><title>cat movies cd</title><description>cat movies cd

Toegevoegd door Thomas Swe laatste december

85 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7137_03_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DKfNK/220x123-Hzq.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7137-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7137_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:40:29">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x13zuo6_uncharted-mass-effect-metal-gear-solid-movies-update_shortfilms</link><title>Uncharted, Mass Effect &amp; Metal Gear Solid Movies Update</title><description>Uncharted, Mass Effect &amp; Metal Gear Solid Movies Update

Toegevoegd door ClevverMovies laatste augustus

http://bit.ly/clevvermovies - Click to Subscribe!http://Clevver.com - Visit our site!http://Facebook.com/ClevverMovies - Become a Fan!http://Twitter.com/ClevverMovies - Follow Us!Avi Arad is one of the main guys who helped bring comic book characters like Spiderman and Iron Man on to the big screen. And, he is at it again, but this time he's working on some video game properties that you're gonna want to know about. Producer, Avi Arad is busy working on adapting several video game properties like Metal Gear Soild, Uncharted, and Mass Effect. And in past videos many of you out there were begging for updates on the progress of these movies, so we're bringing those to you right here. But before we jump into the details...Many of us want to know why it has taken so long for video game properties to become movie franchises. Arad says that video games are a tough sell , because you have creative talent meeting financial decision makers, and sometimes its hard for both sides to agree on something that will satisfy both of their interests. However, Arad said that this same struggle happened when he started pitching comic book movies to studios and once one blows up, then it makes it easier for all of the others. So lets look at why Arad thinks these three video games are worthy of hitting the big screen. Starting with the Uncharted video game series, Arad thinks that this game has the most potential at being the first big success. He told China daily quote "It's a father and son game. There are things about it that are interesting. I think the world of antiquities theft, there are many countries in the world that realized they're being robbed and they're trying to recoup these important pieces. Now, the script has a lot of character [and] I think that has a shot at being the first one [to succeed." So theres no word on where this this project is in development, but at least there's a script! Which is a great place to start. But what about those games that have audiences but just aren't selling well in stores. Does that mean it wont work on the big screen? Arad says, no and that is because story is what really matters, and Metal Gear Solid is a perfect example of a video game that Arad says is full of story telling. The development on this property is still in it's early stages, with Arad saying that we may be 3 years or so away from seeing the film, but he does has a meeting with Metal Gear director, Kojima soon. So things are definitely moving in the right direction. But what about Mass Effect, many of you out there have asked about updates on this movie adaptation specifically, and while there is a lot to get excited about, Arad hints that it could take about 5 to 6 years before we will ever see it on the big screen. He said quote, "Love the project, it's getting there, it's been a lot of work; some movies take five, six years before they're ready." So, I know that these timelines maybe aren't exactly what some of you were hoping for, but are you all excited that these properties are at least in development? And do you trust Avi Arad with your favorite video game properties? Sound off below, or over on Facebook or Twitter. And whether you're a gamer or not, we love and appreciate you all here at ClevverMovies. From our studio, in Hollywood, Im Erin White. Thanks for tuning in.

928 321 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7137_04_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CUzWy/220x123-Vr5.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7137-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7137_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:41:28">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x155qwq_hot-movies-sin-sister-2-2010-full-movie_shortfilms</link><title>[Hot Movies] Sin sister 2 (2010) Full Movie</title><description>[Hot Movies] Sin sister 2 (2010) Full Movie

Toegevoegd door Digitaltvthai laatste september

ฉากจากหนัง

159 220 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7137_05_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/Ce_KG/220x123-332.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7137-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7137_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:41:58">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x162i8i_top-10-torture-porn-movies_shortfilms</link><title>Top 10 Torture Porn Movies</title><description>Top 10 Torture Porn Movies

Toegevoegd door WatchMojo laatste oktober

Warning: Viewer discretion is advised!These films take their time showing the creative dismemberment of their casts. Join http://www.WatchMojo.com as we count down our picks for the top 10 torture porn movies.

78 216 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7137_06_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CqKtU/220x123-VS_.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7137-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7137_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:42:51">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xvjpb5_muzi-v-nadeji-2011-all-trailer-full-movies-1080p-part-4-14_shortfilms</link><title>Muzi v nadeji (2011) all trailer &amp; full movies 1080p part 4/14</title><description>Muzi v nadeji (2011) all trailer &amp; full movies 1080p part 4/14

Toegevoegd door langamene vorig jaar

START WATCHING NOWhttp://tinyurl.com/c8vzbwu or http://megamovs.net/it is here that the newest movies you are looking for; Watch Online &amp; DOWNLOAD DivX Stage watch online &amp; full free hd dvd movie divxhttp://megamovs.net/ or http://tinyurl.com/c8vzbwu *** and +18 ***

268 768 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7137_07_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/dph7/220x123-6dZ.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7137-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7137_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:43:50">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xzheba_top-10-sexy-female-aliens-from-movies-and-tv_shortfilms</link><title>Top 10 Sexy Female Aliens From Movies and TV</title><description>Top 10 Sexy Female Aliens From Movies and TV

Toegevoegd door WatchMojo laatste mei

They might not be real, but it's not like you would have had a chance with em' anyway. Join http://www.WatchMojo.com as we count down the top 10 hottest aliens from movies and TV.

136 459 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7137_08_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/BapRc/220x123-qDU.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7137-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7137_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:44:49">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x19cq1b_the-most-gore-paul-verhoeven-movies_shortfilms</link><title>The most gore Paul Verhoeven movies</title><description>The most gore Paul Verhoeven movies

Toegevoegd door Eklecty-City.fr laatste januari

Le samedi 11 Janvier à Roest à Amsterdam à partir de 21.00 jusqu’à 3.00, une exposition d’art intitulée R-Rated Memories va rendre hommage au cinéaste Paul Verhoeven.http://www.eklecty-city.fr/tag/r-rated-memories/

68 025 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7137_09_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DZVxa/220x123-gbg.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7137-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7137_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 06:45:29">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x190i22_adult-movies-online-hot-adult-videos-adult-channel-how-to-watch-adult-movies_shortfilms</link><title>Adult Movies Online,Hot Adult Videos,Adult Channel,How to Watch Adult Movies</title><description>Adult Movies Online,Hot Adult Videos,Adult Channel,How to Watch Adult Movies

Toegevoegd door Twinkle Bajaj7 laatste december

Adult Movies Online,Hot Adult Videos,Adult Channel,How to Watch Adult Moviesand Adult Videos Online on Youtube. CLICK TO WATCH : www.freeonlinemovies.tv Watch Adult Movies and Hot Adult Videos Online. We have uploaded 1000 of Adult Movies Online on our website. Including all Latest Adult Movies, Adult Videos, Adult English Movies and all other Hot Adult Movies Online So If You are Looking for Some HD Hot Adult Movies Online..?? If yes than Find lots of Hot Adult Movies, Adult Videos, English Adult Videos Online at this website. All these Adult Videos and Adult Movies are free and you can easily Watch these Adult movies Online. So Now you can Watch 1000 of Adult Movies Online on our website. We have so many Adult movies, Adult videos on our Site. These all Adult movies are of High Definition and of Good Quality. So Watch Adult Movies Online Now. Hot Adult Movies online just for you. We have uploaded all latest Hot Adult Movies, So that you can watch them Online without downloading. These Adult videos and adult movies are in High definition and full length. So enjoy these hot adult movies online TAGS : Adult Movies Online How to Watch Adult Movies Adult English Movies Online Hot Adult Videos Online Hot Adult Movies Online Hot Adult movies Adult Movies Online How to Watch Adult Movies Hot Adult movies Hot Adult videos Adult videos

52 804 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7137_10_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/DWZHA/220x123-tg9.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>