<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7155">ted talk mooc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:04:12" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7155-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7155_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:04:13">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xtmedf_ted-talk-theo-jansen-creates-new-creatures_creation</link><title>TED Talk: Theo Jansen Creates New creatures</title><description>TED Talk: Theo Jansen Creates New creatures

Toegevoegd door TED vorig jaar

http://www.ted.com Artist Theo Jansen demonstrates the amazingly lifelike kinetic sculptures he builds from plastic tubes and lemonade bottles. His creatures are designed to move -- and even survive -- on their own.

26 900 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7155_01_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/Ahxu9/220x123-uE4.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7155-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7155_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:04:46">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xtmeas_ted-talk-einstein-the-parrot-talks-and-squawks_animals</link><title>TED Talk: Einstein the Parrot Talks and Squawks</title><description>TED Talk: Einstein the Parrot Talks and Squawks

Toegevoegd door TED vorig jaar

http://www.ted.com This whimsical wrap-up of TED2006 -- presented by Einstein, the African grey parrot, and her trainer, Stephanie White -- simply tickles. Watch for the moment when Einstein has a moment with Al Gore.

5 583 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7155_02_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/AvAn1/220x123-qZn.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7155-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7155_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:05:23">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xsugvx_ted-talk-handspring-puppet-co-the-genius-puppetry-behind-war-horse_creation</link><title>TED Talk: Handspring Puppet Co.: The genius puppetry behind War Horse</title><description>TED Talk: Handspring Puppet Co.: The genius puppetry behind War Horse

Toegevoegd door TED vorig jaar

http://www.ted.com "Puppets always have to try to be alive," says Adrian Kohler of the Handspring Puppet Company, a gloriously ambitious troupe of human and wooden actors. Beginning with the tale of a hyena's subtle paw, puppeteers Kohler and Basil Jones build to the story of their latest astonishment: the wonderfully life-like Joey, the War Horse, who trots (and gallops) convincingly onto the TED stage.

6 802 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7155_03_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/B9ex/220x123-EZa.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7155-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7155_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:05:50">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xn8cg8_ted-talk-kevin-slavin-how-algorithms-shape-our-world_tech</link><title>TED Talk: Kevin Slavin: How algorithms shape our world</title><description>TED Talk: Kevin Slavin: How algorithms shape our world

Toegevoegd door TED 2 jaren geleden

http://www.ted.com http://www.ted.com Kevin Slavin argues that we're living in a world designed for -- and increasingly controlled by -- algorithms. In this riveting talk from TEDGlobal, he shows how these complex computer programs determine: espionage tactics, stock prices, movie scripts, and architecture. And he warns that we are writing code we can't understand, with implications we can't control.

11 353 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7155_04_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/AWed2/220x123-Hee.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7155-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7155_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:06:24">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xr45rz_ted-talk-bart-weetjens-how-i-taught-rats-to-sniff-out-land-mines_animals</link><title>TED Talk: Bart Weetjens: How I Taught Rats to Sniff Out Land Mines</title><description>TED Talk: Bart Weetjens: How I Taught Rats to Sniff Out Land Mines

Toegevoegd door TED vorig jaar

http://www.ted.com At TEDxRotterdam, Bart Weetjens talks about his extraordinary project: training rats to sniff out land mines. He shows clips of his "hero rats" in action, and previews his work's next phase: teaching them to turn up tuberculosis in the lab.

5 898 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7155_05_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/APc-h/220x123-enk.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7155-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7155_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:06:56">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xsggkv_ted-talk-paul-sereno-digs-up-dinosaurs_animals</link><title>TED Talk: Paul Sereno Digs Up Dinosaurs</title><description>TED Talk: Paul Sereno Digs Up Dinosaurs

Toegevoegd door TED vorig jaar

http://www.ted.com Strange landscapes, scorching heat and (sometimes) mad crocodiles await scientists seeking clues to evolution's genius. Paleontologist Paul Sereno talks about his surprising encounters with prehistory -- and a new way to help students join the adventure.

2 245 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7155_06_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/GkO5/220x123-c63.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7155-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7155_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:07:28">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xljazp_ted-talk-ken-kamler-medical-miracle-on-everest_sport</link><title>TED Talk: Ken Kamler: Medical miracle on everest</title><description>TED Talk: Ken Kamler: Medical miracle on everest

Toegevoegd door TED 2 jaren geleden

http://www.ted.com When the worst disaster in the history of Mount Everest climbs occurred, Ken Kamler was the only doctor on the mountain. At TEDMED, he shares the incredible story of the climbers' battle against extreme conditions and uses brain imaging technology to map the medical miracle of one man who survived roughly 36 hours buried in the snow. TEDTalks is a daily video podcast of the best talks and performances from the TED Conference, where the world's leading thinkers and doers give the talk of their lives in 18 minutes. Featured speakers have included Al Gore on climate change, Philippe Starck on design, Jill Bolte Taylor on observing her own stroke, Nicholas Negroponte on One Laptop per Child, Jane Goodall on chimpanzees, Bill Gates on malaria and mosquitoes, Pattie Maes on the "Sixth Sense" wearable tech, and "Lost" producer JJ Abrams on the allure of mystery. TED stands for Technology, Entertainment, Design, and TEDTalks cover these topics as well as science, business, development and the arts. Closed captions and translated subtitles in a variety of languages are now available on TED.com, at http://www.ted.com/translate. Watch a highlight reel of the Top 10 TEDTalks at http://www.ted.com/index.php/talks/top10

10 976 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7155_07_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/OG7g/220x123-uxt.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7155-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7155_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:08:02">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xsugdy_ted-talk-graham-hill-why-i-m-a-weekday-vegetarian_lifestyle</link><title>TED Talk: Graham Hill: Why I'm a weekday vegetarian</title><description>TED Talk: Graham Hill: Why I'm a weekday vegetarian

Toegevoegd door TED vorig jaar

http://www.ted.com We all know the arguments that being vegetarian is better for the environment and for the animals -- but in a carnivorous culture, it can be hard to make the change. Graham Hill has a powerful, pragmatic suggestion: Be a weekday veg.

3 099 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7155_08_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/B8xl/220x123-pCA.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7155-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7155_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:08:40">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xsggca_ted-talk-david-griffin-on-how-photography-connects-us_shortfilms</link><title>TED Talk: David Griffin on How Photography Connects Us</title><description>TED Talk: David Griffin on How Photography Connects Us

Toegevoegd door TED vorig jaar

http://www.ted.com The photo director for National Geographic, David Griffin knows the power of photography to connect us to our world. In a talk filled with glorious images, he talks about how we all use photos to tell our stories.

3 790 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7155_09_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/GjK3/220x123-z_F.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7155-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7155_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 09:09:08">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xrolam_ted-talk-frans-de-waal-moral-behavior-in-animals_animals</link><title>TED Talk: Frans de Waal: Moral behavior in animals</title><description>TED Talk: Frans de Waal: Moral behavior in animals

Toegevoegd door TED vorig jaar

http://www.ted.com Empathy, cooperation, fairness and reciprocity -- caring about the well-being of others seems like a very human trait. But Frans de Waal shares some surprising videos of behavioral tests, on primates and other mammals, that show how many of these moral traits all of us share.

3 143 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7155_10_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/fFhK/220x123-KBk.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>