<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7167">aluminium extrusion</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:28:21" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7167-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7167_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:28:22">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x171sr2_hallmarks-of-exceptional-quality-aluminium-extrusions_lifestyle</link><title>Hallmarks of Exceptional Quality Aluminium Extrusions</title><description>Hallmarks of Exceptional Quality Aluminium Extrusions

Toegevoegd door Christialawrence laatste november

The demand of aluminium extrusions in various industries is high. However, not all vendors are experienced to provide great quality extrusions. 4 signs of a great extrusions are quality of raw material used, uniformity of metal thickness, adequate streamlining of junction points and smooth surface finish. More complex the cross section, more expertise is required to maintain the quality. One vendor that has the skill, the team, and the experience to provide high quality extrusions is P&amp;A International. For more information log on to http://www.pa-international.com/products/diecasting-extrusions-china

7 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7167_01_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/C3Nbc/220x123-GfG.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7167-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7167_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:28:47">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x10kyyc_how-to-polish-aluminium-profiles-like-a-shining-mirror_tech</link><title>How to polish aluminium profiles like a shining mirror</title><description>How to polish aluminium profiles like a shining mirror

Toegevoegd door Wei Judy laatste juni

The acid brightening polishing,electrolytic polishing,polishing sliver anodizing,polishing electrophoresis, polishing nickeling. All of these surface need to be processed by mechanical polishing. Its purpose is to remove the natural oxide film and eliminate the extrusion scratching mark,aluminum profiles surface can be smooth and shining like a mirror. After processed by mechanical polishing with different kinds of chemical treatment, profile surface will have a bright,shinning. If it is equipped with aluminum profile coloration treatment, aluminum profile surface can be achieved various beautiful colors;it not only can be used at the simple architectural aluminum profiles, but also can process different kinds of complicated cross sectional profiles(flat, incline, arc face, tube, with grooves noodles) for furniture, bathroom, bags, home appliance, aluminium tile trim, wooden floor trim, stairs edge trim, door edge trim and other profiles.More details, welcome email: xixilyly@gmail.com

430 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7167_02_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BkWWy/220x123-uF8.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7167-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7167_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:29:27">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1208xj_kontraktor-aluminium-composite-panel_lifestyle</link><title>KONTRAKTOR Aluminium Composite Panel</title><description>KONTRAKTOR Aluminium Composite Panel

Toegevoegd door Heirman Simbolon laatste juli

155 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7167_03_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/CE9I4/220x123-p_o.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7167-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7167_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:30:11">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x18810g_understanding-aluminium-die-casting_auto</link><title>Understanding Aluminium Die Casting</title><description>Understanding Aluminium Die Casting

Toegevoegd door Christialawrence laatste december

Aluminium casts are lightweight &amp; strong and therefore used extensively across industries. The process includes putting molten aluminium in alloy steel molds or die and then extracting it once it takes shape of the die. Specialized skills and expertise are required to get the work done. A leading producer of aluminium die casts is P&amp;A International. To learn more Log on to http://www.pa-international.com.au/

29 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7167_04_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/DLfZY/220x123-rDh.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7167-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7167_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:30:57">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x10l11q_how-to-brush-the-hairlines-on-aluminum-profiles_tech</link><title>How to brush the hairlines on aluminum profiles</title><description>How to brush the hairlines on aluminum profiles

Toegevoegd door Wei Judy laatste juni

Aluminum Profile Lines Brushing Machine Aluminium Profile Lines Brushing machine is used for scratching or brushing the hairlines on the aluminum profile surface by nylon wheels in high rotation speed, after the anodizing and coloring process, aluminum profiles surface will be colorful, beauty and decorated; if it is equipped with acid brightening process, aluminum profiles surface will be brighter. With the aluminum extrusion industrial developping, you also can carve different kinds of decorative pattern on others side, so the whole aluminum profiles will be more beauty and increase the value of aluminum profiles.For more details, welcome to contact: info@fsnenghong.com

162 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7167_05_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/BkXIU/220x123-lga.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7167-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7167_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:31:41">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x133tmx_formal-aluminyum-tanitim-filmi_tech</link><title>FORMAL ALÜMİNYUM TANITIM FİLMİ</title><description>FORMAL ALÜMİNYUM TANITIM FİLMİ

Toegevoegd door Formal_Aluminyum laatste augustus

Formal Alüminyum Sanayi ve Ticaret A.Ş. 28 yıllık alüminyum profil üretim tecrübesiyle 16.000 m² kapalı alanda faaliyet göstermektedir. İnşaat sektöründen beyaz eşyaya, sigma profillerinden güneş enerjisi profillerine kadar çok geniş bir ürün yelpazesine sahiptir. Firmaların ihtiyaçlarına göre özel tasarlanan butik profil üretimine ek olarak, Doğrama ve Cephe profillerinde seri üretimi vardır. FORMAL kalitesi ile tanışmak için profil kataloğumuzu mutlaka inceleyiniz....

82 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7167_06_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/COnfk/220x123-2fe.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7167-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7167_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:32:27">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xx25ex_automatic-aluminum-profile-puller-from-brightstar-aluminum-machinery_tech</link><title>Automatic Aluminum profile puller from Brightstar Aluminum Machinery</title><description>Automatic Aluminum profile puller from Brightstar Aluminum Machinery

Toegevoegd door alumachine vorig jaar

aluminum profile puller operation video from Brightstar Aluminum Machinery,www.brightstaralu.com, aluminum extrusion single puller, aluminum profile double puller, simple aluminum profile puller, puller for aluminium extrusion, automatic aluminium profile puller, energy saving aluminium puller, aluminium puller machinery, aluminum extruson profile puller

141 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7167_07_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BE6oS/220x123-vr1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7167-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7167_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:32:59">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xazrcp_tuna-aluminium_lifestyle</link><title>TUNA ALUMINIUM</title><description>TUNA ALUMINIUM

Toegevoegd door haburaf 4 jaren geleden

TUNA ALUMINIUM EXTRUSION FACTORY IN CERKEZLOY TEKIRDAG TURKEY

602 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7167_08_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/XNcB/220x123-W1H.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7167-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7167_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:33:43">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xss8mx_we-are-chinasavyy_tech</link><title>We are Chinasavyy</title><description>We are Chinasavyy

Toegevoegd door Chinasavvy vorig jaar

http://www.chinasavvy.comAn review to Chinasavvy. What we do. How we work. What makes us special. The processes we work with: Sand casting; Diecasting; Permanent mold casting; Investment casting; Aluminum extrusion; CNC milling; CNC lathe; CNC laser cutting; CNC bending; CNC punching; Metal sheet fabrication; Powder coating; etc

56 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7167_09_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/Ap548/220x123-fke.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7167-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7167_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:34:51">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xsoppu_aluminum-extrusion_tech</link><title>Aluminum Extrusion</title><description>Aluminum Extrusion

Toegevoegd door Chinasavvy vorig jaar

http://www.chinasavvy.com/industrial/aluminum-extrusion.phpChinasavvy generates both small and big aluminum extrusions for clients in the automotive and industrial markets. Using typical extrusion process process a variety of profiles and channels in aluminium extrusions could be accomplished.

91 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7167_10_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/AHH6M/220x123-izh.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>