<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7168">fabric glue</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:35:09" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7168-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7168_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:35:10">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1ceqfl_clearance-mod-podge-cs11218-8-ounce-glue-fabric_lifestyle</link><title>Clearance Mod Podge CS11218 8-Ounce Glue Fabric</title><description>Clearance Mod Podge CS11218 8-Ounce Glue Fabric

Toegevoegd door Cepenreusor1985 laatste februari

Clearance Mod Podge CS11218 8-Ounce Glue Fabric Click on the discount link below: http://www.amazon.com/dp/B001681Z8Q/?tag=60percentoff-20 Disclaimer: I am a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon. Amazon and the Amazon logo are trademarks of Amazon, Inc. or its affiliates.

1 view</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7168_01_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/Dp4G7/220x123-SNg.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7168-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7168_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:35:41">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xz39ht_stoff-kleben-mit-textilkleber_creation</link><title>Stoff Kleben mit Textilkleber</title><description>Stoff Kleben mit Textilkleber

Toegevoegd door model-maker vorig jaar

Stoff Kleben mit Anjas Textilkleber

274 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7168_02_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BW6PO/220x123--OO.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7168-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7168_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:36:34">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xya6ie_hightack_creation</link><title>Hightack</title><description>Hightack

Toegevoegd door dm_5145db03474fa vorig jaar

hightack is a water based eco friendly glue with low VOC to paste fancy material like, beads, stone, lace, gota etc on fabrics with water resistant properties

5 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7168_03_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/BPIJK/220x123-bPh.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7168-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7168_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:36:59">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xc721f_tear-mender-instant-fabric-leather_shortfilms</link><title>Tear Mender Instant Fabric &amp; Leather Adhesive</title><description>Tear Mender Instant Fabric &amp; Leather Adhesive

Toegevoegd door vat19com 4 jaren geleden

Holes in your jeans (that you didn't pay extra money for) are no longer a reason to stop wearing them. With Tear Mender Instant Fabric and Leather Adhesive, you can fix tears, cuts, holes, and snags in nearly any fabric (including leather) in a matter of minutes. Tear Mender is a non-toxic, waterproof, and UV resistant compound that forms a permanent bond within minutes. In fact, within 15 minutes of using Tear Mender, you can toss the repaired clothing into the washing machine! Each six ounce bottle of Tear Mender will make hundreds of repairs such as fixing a frayed shoelace, repairing a ripped pocket, reinforcing a loose button, or reattaching a belt loop. http://www.vat19.com/dvds/tear-mender-instant-fabric-adhesive.cfm?adid=youtube

1 039 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7168_04_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/OOcC/220x123-vyz.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7168-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7168_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:37:41">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xbdw1k_blue-velvet-door-panels-custom-dash_auto</link><title>Blue Velvet Door Panels Custom Dash Part 1 (Project BLUE)</title><description>Blue Velvet Door Panels Custom Dash Part 1 (Project BLUE)

Toegevoegd door jkamakaze 4 jaren geleden

This is the continuation of the Crown Vic Project Car this video covers the custom door panels being finished and features my photoshoot with Noir Kss Productions you can check them out at (http://www.noirkss.com) The door panels are painted black with a Blue Velvet-like fabric. The speakers in the door panels are Pioneer 4way 6.5 inch speakers Hey Everyone Exclusive Lifestyle back and starting a new project car Its a 2002 Crown Vic, tons of installs are going to be made on this car so ill try to keep you up to date. You can follow me on Twitter @iamJDM You can find me on Facebook or Myspace under JM Exclusive You can msg or we can chat on BBM or phone if you have any questions

626 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7168_05_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/AN9Db/220x123-toj.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7168-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7168_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:38:12">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x11af7f_top-boy-s01-e01-fabric-of-life-vost_tv</link><title>Top Boy - S01 E01 - Fabric of life - VOST</title><description>Top Boy - S01 E01 - Fabric of life - VOST

Toegevoegd door TOP BOY laatste juni

Retrouvez plus de séries TV inédites sur www.dailymotion.com/seriestv « Top Boy », la série britannique écrite par Ronan Bennet (Public Ennemies) distribuée par DRG, suit les aventures de jeunes dealers d’un quarter défavorisé de l'est londonien cherchant à étendre leur territoire. Entre barres d’immeubles, guerre de gangs, règlements de compte et la hantise de la police, la série montre la réalité telle qu'elle est perçue par les jeunes de ces quartiers. Souvent comparée à la série culte « The Wire », « Top Boy » a déjà remporté de nombreux prix et n’a encore jamais été diffusée en France.

48 227 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7168_06_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BrWUW/220x123-UqR.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7168-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7168_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:38:50">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x12sffz_how-to-create-fabric-effect-in-adobe-photoshop-cs6-in-urdu-and-hindi_tech</link><title>How to Create Fabric Effect in Adobe Photoshop CS6 in Urdu and Hindi</title><description>How to Create Fabric Effect in Adobe Photoshop CS6 in Urdu and Hindi

Toegevoegd door Muhammad Niaz laatste augustus

In This Tutorial You can Learn How to Create Fabric Effect in Adobe Photoshop CS6 i n Urdu and Hindi Language By Sir Muhammad Niaz from www.MuhammadNiaz.Net for Previous Tutorial: http://muhammadniaz.net/2013/06/01/learnadobephotoshop/ YouTube: http://www.YouTube.com/MrMuhammadNiaz Facebook: http://www.Facebook.com/MrMuhammadNiaz Twitter: http://www.Twitter.com/MrMuhammadNiaz

1 906 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7168_07_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CMNyi/220x123-34h.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7168-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7168_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:39:35">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xb320c_new-discovery-about-the-fabric-of-s_tech</link><title>New Discovery about the Fabric of Space-Time</title><description>New Discovery about the Fabric of Space-Time

Toegevoegd door SpaceRip 4 jaren geleden

Scientists have turned up rare evidence that space-time is smooth as Einstein predicted, while pushing closer to a complete theory of gravity. From NASA Goddard Space Flight Center.

60 056 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7168_08_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/AK4Pu/220x123-JCx.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7168-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7168_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:40:02">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1jvw68_razor-blades-found-glued-to-equipment-in-public-park_travel</link><title>Razor Blades Found Glued to Equipment in Public Park</title><description>Razor Blades Found Glued to Equipment in Public Park

Toegevoegd door Geo Beats 4 weken geleden

Police in East Moline, Illinois are asking members of the public to keep an eye out for suspicious activity at parks because approximately a dozen razor blades were recently discovered at a local playground. Police in East Moline, Illinois are asking members of the public to keep an eye out for suspicious activity at parks because approximately a dozen razor blades were recently discovered at a local playground. Law enforcement authorities had been alerted of the sharp blades after a 2-year-old child was injured while playing at Millennium Park. The cut was spotted on the male toddler’s hand, so the father brought him home and treated him there before contacting police and going with officers to the park to point out where the blades were located.The blades had been glued to playground equipment, meaning the act was intentional. Lieutenant Brian Foltz commented ‘I've seen a lot of things, but not razor blades glued to equipment at a park. East Moline parks are safe, but it's just a bad situation, bad instance where somebody, or maybe a group of kids.... figured this would be a fun prank to do.’ Officers removed the blades and other evidence before checking other parks for signs of vandalism. Nothing was found at any other playgrounds, but police have launched an investigation into the incident at Millennium Park. No suspects have yet been named.

10 133 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7168_09_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/EAXHi/220x123-nl5.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7168-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7168_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 10:40:33">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xpxmly_katherine-heigl-takes-mom-fabric-shopping_people</link><title>Katherine Heigl Takes Mom Fabric Shopping!</title><description>Katherine Heigl Takes Mom Fabric Shopping!

Toegevoegd door hollywoodtv 2 jaren geleden

http://Facebook.com/HollywoodTV - Become a Fan!http://Twitter.com/HollywoodTV - Follow Us!Katherine Heigl and mom are out for an afternoon in the sun, and after stopping for some lunch hit up a fabric store for some new threads (no pun intended, haha!). Katherine is looking mighty fresh today, and appears to be in a lovely mood.C62BBAD6

51 732 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7168_10_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BQL3/220x123-wIN.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>