<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7212">mud pumps</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:26:59" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7212-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7212_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:27:00">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x17i5pl_erke-dis-ticaret-ltd-toyo-mud-pump-material-transporting-www-erkegroup-com_tech</link><title>ERKE Dış Ticaret ltd., TOYO Mud Pump - Material Transporting - www.erkegroup.com</title><description>ERKE Dış Ticaret ltd., TOYO Mud Pump - Material Transporting - www.erkegroup.com

Toegevoegd door ERKE-LTD laatste november

19 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7212_01_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/DA1LG/220x123-lKq.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7212-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7212_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:27:41">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x17i5zw_erke-dis-ticaret-ltd-toyo-mud-pump-material-transporting-2-www-erkegroup-com_tech</link><title>ERKE Dış Ticaret ltd., TOYO Mud Pump - Material Transporting 2 - www.erkegroup.com</title><description>ERKE Dış Ticaret ltd., TOYO Mud Pump - Material Transporting 2 - www.erkegroup.com

Toegevoegd door ERKE-LTD laatste november

13 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7212_02_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DA1Xs/220x123-xUV.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7212-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7212_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:28:16">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xrcdhm_ivac-underground-mining-sump-mud-pumping-movie-360p_tech</link><title>IVAC Underground Mining Sump Mud Pumping Movie_(360p)</title><description>IVAC Underground Mining Sump Mud Pumping Movie_(360p)

Toegevoegd door zereko vorig jaar

IVAC Industrial Vacuum Systems provide portable and diverse units the world over. These industrial vacuum units units are capable of handling the most difficult of materials, and feature a unique delivery system as well as a powerful industrial vacuum. Powered by compressed air, the pnuematic units easily move products such as gravel, sand, rocks, and sludge, and is capable of moving them to any desired location. Our vacuums have been used in a number of applications, from mining solutions to factory spill clean-ups. There are endless possibilities for the IVAC industrial vacuum systems! We pump the “unpumpable!” see: http://industrialvacuumunit.com

112 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7212_03_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/t-L3/220x123-ADa.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7212-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7212_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:29:26">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x18iysr_excavator-pompa-sedot-pasir-lumpur_tech</link><title>excavator pompa sedot pasir lumpur</title><description>excavator pompa sedot pasir lumpur

Toegevoegd door SWAMP EXCAVATOR laatste december

JUAL pompa dredger cutting section yang bisa dipasang pada excavator, digerakkan oleh hydraulic excavator. Dengan goyangan arm excavator akan menghasilkan sedotan pasir / lumpur yang lebih maksimal. Hubungi : 081241346651 , email : abd.lathif@yahoo.co.id

76 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7212_04_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DQLsy/220x123-hW-.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7212-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7212_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:30:15">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x18u4sc_comisioning-excavator-pump-dredger-cutter-section-pompa-sedot-pasir-lumpur-di-pelabuhan-manado_tech</link><title>comisioning Excavator pump dredger cutter section pompa sedot pasir lumpur di Pelabuhan Manado</title><description>comisioning Excavator pump dredger cutter section pompa sedot pasir lumpur di Pelabuhan Manado

Toegevoegd door SWAMP EXCAVATOR laatste december

JUAL pompa sedot pasir, sedot lumpur, dredging pump cutter section. Bisa dipasangkan dengan excavator sehingga mendapatkan hasil yang lebih maksimal. Digerakkan oleh hidrolik excavator, sehingga tidak perlu penambahan powerpack lagi. Hubungi : 081241346651 / 081241888131, Email: abd.lathif@yahoo.co.id

69 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7212_05_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DUaUw/220x123-K5P.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7212-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7212_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:31:01">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x18uti2_install-dan-test-excavator-pompa-sedot-pasir-di-pelabuhan-manado_tech</link><title>install dan test excavator pompa sedot pasir di Pelabuhan Manado</title><description>install dan test excavator pompa sedot pasir di Pelabuhan Manado

Toegevoegd door SWAMP EXCAVATOR laatste december

JUAL POMPA SEDOT PASIR LUMPUR , bisa digabungkan dengan excavator, tidak perlu powerpack lagi. Dilengkapi dengan cutter section, sehingga dengan goyangan arm excavator akan menambah hasil lebih maksimal. Hubungi : 081241346651 , email: abd.lathif@yahoo.co.id.

56 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7212_06_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/DUo6A/220x123-9EQ.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7212-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7212_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:31:50">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xy8tl9_water-removal-middletown-nj-call-732-956-3900-water-damage-repairs-service-in-middletown-nj_lifestyle</link><title>Water Removal Middletown NJ Call -732-956-3900 Water Damage Repairs Service in Middletown NJ</title><description>Water Removal Middletown NJ Call -732-956-3900 Water Damage Repairs Service in Middletown NJ

Toegevoegd door dm_509338e7217cb vorig jaar

http://youtu.be/ZQ66Gl6BH0w - 732-956-3900 Water Damage Middletown If you're searching for a Flood Damage Middletown NJ, You in the right place!!! Thank you on behalf of deciding on Middletown the premier water damage clean up group serving Middletown New jersey, you have come to the right place! As a specialist flood damage and basement waterproofing repair contractor, I have myself called on many property owners with sewage water damage in New Jersey over the years. While you come upon water damage, sewage backup, or mold damage in your residence or business in Middletown NJ, it is necessary that you choose a well experienced and accountable remediation company in Middletown New Jersey. 60 Minutes to Arrive! Assess and Evaluate Damage to Contents and Structure Soot Damage Remediation in Middletown Flooded Wet carpet removal Drying Services in Middletown NJ Sewage Pump-out and Removal Mould Restoration as well as Mold Testing and Mold Inspections Books and Documents Drying in Middletown NJ Residential and Commercial Services We invite you to call us at: 732-956-3900 Water Removal Middletown New jersey 1 Kings Highway Middletown, NJ 07748, United States

3 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7212_07_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/BOuoq/220x123-ZJ9.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7212-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7212_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:32:36">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xst699_water-damage-shrewsbury-basement-water-removal_news</link><title>Water Damage Shrewsbury : Basement Water Removal</title><description>Water Damage Shrewsbury : Basement Water Removal

Toegevoegd door dm_502a3a32b31fd vorig jaar

http://youtu.be/bMsEQrjFnbg - (732) 993-6622 Water Damage Shrewsbury If someone is looking for water damage repair company in Shrewsbury NJ, You in the right place!!!Are you a Shrewsbury NJ resident whose home or firm has suffered both minor or major water damage? If you clarified “yes” to that question, next your seek out for an expedient and accountable water damage restoration corporation is over, you have come to the right place! As a trained flood damage and basement waterproofing service provider, I have personally called on many house owners with crawl space water damage in New Jersey over the many years. Having experienced a flooded sewage crisis myself, I be able to relate to what you are going through. Considering a lot of your prized possessions being damaged by wet carpet removal water damage in Shrewsbury NJ. 24/7 HelpLine - Immediate Response Pack-out, Cleanup and Remediation of Personal Belongings Soot Remediation and Smoke Cleanup in Shrewsbury Flooded Crawl space Drying Services in Shrewsbury New Jersey Sewage Clean up and Restoration Services in Shrewsbury Mold and mildew Removal &amp; Mold Test and Free Mold Inspections Insurance Claims Specialist in Shrewsbury NJ Direct insurance billing

5 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7212_08_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/r4WI/220x123-otz.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7212-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7212_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:33:08">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xufhmc_dj-david-guetta-pumps-up-your-battery-twizy-electric_music</link><title>DJ David Guetta pumps up your battery: Twizy electric</title><description>DJ David Guetta pumps up your battery: Twizy electric

Toegevoegd door The Ad Show vorig jaar

Cathy &amp; David Guetta plug into the positive energy… Music is energy / Thanks to David Guetta Country: France Brand: Renault Year: 2012 Agency: Publicis Conseil Director: So ME Producer: Iconoclast Plus de Pubs : http://www.dailymotion.com/CulturePub ... Tous droits réservés. Pour toute information, contacter culturepub@wizdeo.com

6 262 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7212_09_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/PW-4/220x123-fak.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7212-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7212_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 15:33:58">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x15hiri_petrol-pumps-shut-in-quetta-03-oct-2013_news</link><title>Petrol Pumps Shut in Quetta-03 Oct 2013</title><description>Petrol Pumps Shut in Quetta-03 Oct 2013

Toegevoegd door Geo News laatste oktober

1 025 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7212_10_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/CiqlK/220x123-PDu.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>