<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7250">collagen vascular disease</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:50:44" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7250-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7250_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:50:45">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x14pnhe_hypertensive-vascular-disease-symptoms-what-are-symptoms-of-hypertensive-vascular-disease_lifestyle</link><title>Hypertensive Vascular Disease Symptoms, What Are Symptoms Of Hypertensive Vascular Disease</title><description>Hypertensive Vascular Disease Symptoms, What Are Symptoms Of Hypertensive Vascular Disease

Toegevoegd door dm_523498f4e7f01 laatste september

Hypertensive Vascular Disease Symptoms, What Are Symptoms Of Hypertensive Vascular Disease? http://heartnews365.com/detorex33281997 Hypertensive heart disease refers to heart problems that occur because of high blood pressure. These problems include: Coronary artery disease and angina; Heart failure; and Thickening of the heart muscle. High blood pressure means the pressure inside the blood vessels is too high. As the heart pumps against this pressure, it must work harder. Over time, this causes the heart muscle to thicken. Without treatment, symptoms of heart failure may develop. Sometimes the muscle can be so thick that it does not get enough oxygen. This can cause angina. High blood pressure also leads to thickening of the blood vessel walls. When combined with cholesterol deposits in the blood vessels, the risk of heart attacks and stroke increases. Looking for a natural treatment to lower high blood pressure that work? We advise you to check out Detorex at http://www.detorex.com before you buy treatment for high blood pressure. Learn How You Can Easily &amp; Effortlessly Lower Your High Blood Pressure &amp; Eiminate The Risk Of Heart Attack or Stroke With This 100% NATURAL Remedies Your Doctors Hope You'll NEVER FIND OUT

34 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7250_01_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CaH86/220x123-v_s.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7250-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7250_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:51:21">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xztjtr_angioplasty-for-peripheral-vascular-disease_lifestyle</link><title>Angioplasty For Peripheral Vascular Disease?</title><description>Angioplasty For Peripheral Vascular Disease?

Toegevoegd door Chris Chris laatste mei

http://www.angirx.com - Angioplasty For Peripheral Vascular Disease? Looking for a natural remedy to reverse coronary heart disease that work? We advise you to check out Angirx at www.angirx.com before you buy any supplement to clear clogged arteries

79 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7250_02_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BdsSG/220x123-s2H.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7250-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7250_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:52:01">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xa4ujy_silverhawk-atherectomy-for-peripher_tech</link><title>Silverhawk Atherectomy for Peripheral vascular disease</title><description>Silverhawk Atherectomy for Peripheral vascular disease

Toegevoegd door interventional 4 jaren geleden

80 yr old man with acute severe lower limb ischemia underwent silverhawk atherectom. the vascularity restored and limb salvaged.

2 440 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7250_03_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/ycq9/220x123-S-e.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7250-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7250_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:52:27">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xxyasd_medicine-book-review-handbook-of-patient-care-in-vascular-diseases-lippincott-williams-wilkins-handb_creation</link><title>Medicine Book Review: Handbook of Patient Care in Vascular Diseases (Lippincott Williams &amp; Wilkins Handbook Series) by Todd E. Rasmussen, W. Darrin Clouse, Britt H. Tonnessen</title><description>Medicine Book Review: Handbook of Patient Care in Vascular Diseases (Lippincott Williams &amp; Wilkins Handbook Series) by Todd E. Rasmussen, W. Darrin Clouse, Britt H. Tonnessen

Toegevoegd door MedicineBook vorig jaar

Visit www.MedicineBookMix.com for more medicine book audio reviews! This is an audio summary of Handbook of Patient Care in Vascular Diseases (Lippincott Williams &amp; Wilkins Handbook Series) by Todd E. Rasmussen, W. Darrin Clouse, Britt H. Tonnessen.

30 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7250_04_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/BLxS8/220x123-P55.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7250-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7250_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:53:10">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1jj4pn_the-most-beneficial-facial-moisturizer-that-has-a-collagen-booster_lifestyle</link><title>The Most Beneficial Facial Moisturizer That Has A Collagen Booster</title><description>The Most Beneficial Facial Moisturizer That Has A Collagen Booster

Toegevoegd door dm_5191650b02522 laatste maart

http://www.amazon.com/Moisturizer-Rejuvenation-Pentapeptides-Significantly-Imperfections/dp/B00FJE4K94/ie=UTF8?m=ASPVTZ2LYYLG4&amp;keywords=facial+moisturizersVellumay Anti Aging Moisturizer is actually fortified with the collagen maximizing compound Matrixyl. This clinically proven ingredient helps you to rebuild the collagen we all lose as we age. Collagen supplies the skin with elasticity, which reduces facial lines.This superior facial cream also features green tea, shea butter along with peppermint oil to make a luxurious face moisturizer created for all skin types.This product is especially good for dealing with puffiness, wrinkles and fine lines related to aging and solar damage.Used as a part of an overall skin regimen, this potent face care cream will take years off aged and UV harmed skin.http://www.amazon.com/Moisturizer-Rejuvenation-Pentapeptides-Significantly-Imperfections/dp/B00FJE4K94/ie=UTF8?m=ASPVTZ2LYYLG4&amp;keywords=facial+cream

5 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7250_05_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/D_CwM/220x123-F7f.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7250-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7250_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:53:45">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1fdqz1_boost-collagen-level-to-look-your-best-at-every-age_lifestyle</link><title>Boost Collagen Level To Look Your Best At Every Age!</title><description>Boost Collagen Level To Look Your Best At Every Age!

Toegevoegd door MarthaLawinga laatste maart

Wrinkles, fine lines and other signs of aging occur due to decline in collagen level in our skin. Increase its production with Collagen Face Serum and forget all aging signs forever http://collagenfaceserumfacts.com/

6 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7250_06_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/D1mFn/220x123-ush.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7250-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7250_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:54:11">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1ddz37_best-collagen-supplements-colvita-dietary-supplements-for-s_lifestyle</link><title>best collagen supplements Colvita, dietary supplements for s</title><description>best collagen supplements Colvita, dietary supplements for s

Toegevoegd door Blo13817ti laatste februari

http://naturalcollagen.in dietary supplements Colvita a complex natural collagen supplement. One of the best collagen supplements because the collagen is lyophilized collagen. When you hear the word "collagen", do you think about all those celebrities having collagen plastic surgery disasters? Collagen can actually be found in your body naturally. It is a protein that incorporates 70% of the skin. As you age, your collagen starts losing its firmness and flexibility and your first wrinkles appear. Having plastic surgery is unnatural, expensive and can't guarantee good results. If you believe in natural options, then the best natural option is Colvita Natural Collagen Supplements! A powerful dietary supplement with many health benefits of this product include: - Skin nourishment from the inside - No more wrinkles! Thanks to the sea algae and its Vitamin E - It gives a boost to the structure of your skin - And its fish collagen helps relieving joint and other structural pains Give your skin a healthy, young glow with Colvita Natural Collagen Supplements and enjoy your newly found youth and energy again! Order your collagen supplements today! http://naturalcollagen.in/product/colvita-natural-collagen/

15 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7250_07_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/DvRJR/220x123-oQ4.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7250-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7250_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:55:08">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1d9f5l_%E0%B8%9A-%E0%B9%80%E0%B8%88%E0%B8%99%E0%B8%84%E0%B8%AD%E0%B8%A5%E0%B8%A5%E0%B8%B2%E0%B9%80%E0%B8%88%E0%B8%99-bigen-collagen-%E0%B9%81%E0%B8%A5%E0%B8%B0-%E0%B8%9A-%E0%B9%80%E0%B8%88%E0%B8%99%E0%B8%AA%E0%B9%81%E0%B8%A5%E0%B8%99%E0%B8%97-bigen-slan-2_lifestyle</link><title>บีเจนคอลลาเจน BIGEN COLLAGEN และ บีเจนสแลนทู BIGEN SLAN 2</title><description>บีเจนคอลลาเจน BIGEN COLLAGEN และ บีเจนสแลนทู BIGEN SLAN 2

Toegevoegd door Pasangyasorn TV laatste februari

โปรโมชั่นสินค้า เบอร์โทรติดต่อ 0925149990 - 3 SET 2,690 บาท จากเดิมราคา 4,700 บาท ถูกกว่าเดิม 2,010 บาท ประกอบด้วย - บีเจนคอลลาเจน 30 ซอง ราคาเต็ม 2,900 บาท - บีเจนสแลนทู 2 กระปุกๆละ 900 บาท ราคาเต็ม 1,800 บาท ( 1 กระปุกมี 30 เม็ด )

16 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7250_08_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/DuhRD/220x123-ruE.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7250-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7250_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:55:44">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x16if5w_cellulite-and-collagen_lifestyle</link><title>Cellulite and Collagen</title><description>Cellulite and Collagen

Toegevoegd door Robin Williams laatste oktober

Pressure Therapy: works to improve circulation, is a complement to other treatments and aids cellulite, varicose veins and slimming. For more information about any treatment go here: http://biothecareestetika.com/exeter/index.php/treatments/

10 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7250_09_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/CvR3W/220x123-S6G.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7250-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7250_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-25 19:56:46">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x18hr6k_dellure-collagen-mask-review-decrease-all-the-unwanted-skin-appearance-in-face_lifestyle</link><title>Dellure Collagen Mask Review - Decrease All The Unwanted Skin Appearance In Face</title><description>Dellure Collagen Mask Review - Decrease All The Unwanted Skin Appearance In Face

Toegevoegd door Dellure laatste december

http://getdellure.com/ Try dellure collagen mask now! :)

37 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7250_10_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DPu2q/220x123-hYu.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>