<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7307">causes of the cold war</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:10:29" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7307-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7307_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:10:30">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xju6qb_severe-cold-and-blinding-snowfall-kills-12-and-causes-travel-chaos-across-northern-europe-while-floo_news</link><title>Severe cold and blinding snowfall kills 12 and causes travel chaos across northern Europe while floods devastate parts of the Balkans</title><description>Severe cold and blinding snowfall kills 12 and causes travel chaos across northern Europe while floods devastate parts of the Balkans

Toegevoegd door tvnportal 2 jaren geleden

Europe hit by wintry blast, floods Powered by www.newslook.com Producer : CBC

15 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7307_01_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/AQf69/220x123-GsV.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7307-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7307_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:11:09">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xqh8qw_the-causes-of-war_news</link><title>The Causes of War</title><description>The Causes of War

Toegevoegd door MrsMorganatMeisler vorig jaar

6 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7307_02_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/tQ12/220x123-hCq.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7307-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7307_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:11:38">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xoevfg_the-causes-of-the-korean-war-the-cobra-strikes-u-s-army-documentary-film_shortfilms</link><title>The Causes of the Korean War: The Cobra Strikes - U.S. Army Documentary Film</title><description>The Causes of the Korean War: The Cobra Strikes - U.S. Army Documentary Film

Toegevoegd door thefilmarchive 2 jaren geleden

http://thefilmarchive.org/ One of the more significant impacts of containment was the outbreak of the Korean War. In June 1950, Kim Il-Sung's North Korean People's Army invaded South Korea. To Joseph Stalin's surprise, the UN Security Council backed the defense of South Korea, though the Soviets were then boycotting meetings in protest that Taiwan and not Communist China held a permanent seat on the Council. A UN force of personnel from South Korea, the United States, the United Kingdom, Turkey, Canada, Australia, France, South Africa, the Philippines, the Netherlands, Belgium, New Zealand and other countries joined to stop the invasion. http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cold_War

631 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7307_03_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/HL6A/220x123-bhu.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7307-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7307_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:12:12">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1nxqaq_french-and-indian-war-as-a-cause-of-the-revolution_tech</link><title>French and indian war as a cause of the revolution</title><description>French and indian war as a cause of the revolution

Toegevoegd door Arminda Arena een week geleden

French and indian war as a cause of the revolution - Get free French and indian war as a cause of the revolution - 2014French and indian war as a cause of the revolution - French and indian war as a cause of the revolutionFrench and indian war as a cause of the revolution ( LINK ): http://softwaregratuit.fr/app.php?id=TWpJME5EQXRNVEF6TkRFPQ==___________________________________________________French and indian war as a cause of the revolution ( LINK ) : http://softwaregratuit.fr/app.php?id=TWpJME5EQXRNVEF6TkRFPQ==___________________________________________________French and indian war as a cause of the revolution - French and indian war as a cause of the revolutionDownload ( LINK ) : http://softwaregratuit.fr/app.php?id=TWpJME5EQXRNVEF6TkRFPQ==French and indian war as a cause of the revolution is a good thing. Our team of has worked extensively to find the latest and working version of French and indian war as a cause of the revolution. You can download from French and indian war as a cause of the revolution.The latest and ONLY working French and indian war as a cause of the revolution. The system will generate unique download link for you to download French and indian war as a cause of the revolution! TOTALLY FREE!100% guaranteed!Steps :1. Open the link .2. Download: French and indian war as a cause of the revolution .3. Open French and indian war as a cause of the revolution.4. Enjoy the French and indian war as a cause of the revolution !How to get your free French and indian war as a cause of the revolution ?Just go to the link above, or click here ( LINK ) : http://softwaregratuit.fr/app.php?id=TWpJME5EQXRNVEF6TkRFPQ==It is the latest version of French and indian war as a cause of the revolution. Just download it, open and enjoy!

0 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7307_04_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/D66LA/220x123-o65.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7307-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7307_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:12:40">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1qqs00_cold-war-2-0-and-the-threat-of-nuclear-warfare-grtv-backgrounder_news</link><title>Cold War 2.0 and the Threat of Nuclear Warfare - GRTV Backgrounder</title><description>Cold War 2.0 and the Threat of Nuclear Warfare - GRTV Backgrounder

Toegevoegd door Alex Jones, Webster Tarpley vorig woensdag

3 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7307_05_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/EZP8-/220x123-aRz.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7307-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7307_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:12:59">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x18bzhn_echoes-of-the-cold-war-in-ukraine-unrest_news</link><title>Echoes of the Cold War in Ukraine unrest</title><description>Echoes of the Cold War in Ukraine unrest

Toegevoegd door CBS News laatste december

Flash Points: CBS News National Security Correspondent Bob Orr talks with CBS News Senior National Security Analyst Juan Zarate about the unrest in Ukraine as that country debates whether to move closer to the West or fall back into Russia's orbit.

14 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7307_06_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/DNNSC/220x123-D-3.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7307-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7307_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:13:27">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1enk6m_lifeblood-of-the-state-trade-war-cold-war-hot-war-alex-jones-infowars_news</link><title>Lifeblood of the State — Trade War, Cold War, Hot War - ALEX JONES, INFOWARS</title><description>Lifeblood of the State — Trade War, Cold War, Hot War - ALEX JONES, INFOWARS

Toegevoegd door Alex Jones, Webster Tarpley laatste maart

4 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7307_07_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DzkML/220x123-GBT.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7307-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7307_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:13:55">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1cjy8r_the-post-cold-war-tug-of-war-is-not-helping-ukraine-quijano-evans_news</link><title>The post-Cold War tug of war is not helping Ukraine - Quijano-Evans</title><description>The post-Cold War tug of war is not helping Ukraine - Quijano-Evans

Toegevoegd door Business from Grab Networks laatste februari

The post-Cold War tug of war is not helping Ukraine - Quijano-Evans

8 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7307_08_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/Dqe1B/220x123-lmF.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7307-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7307_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:14:16">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x18bmip_kyiv-protesters-brave-the-cold-as-political-tug-of-war-continues_news</link><title>Kyiv protesters brave the cold as political tug-of-war continues</title><description>Kyiv protesters brave the cold as political tug-of-war continues

Toegevoegd door euronews-en laatste december

Ukrainian anti-government protesters stood their ground in Kyiv’s Independence Square on Thursday. They rebuilt barricades after the police tried to clear the area the previous day.They have been protesting for more than two weeks after President Viktor Yanukovych rejected an EU trade deal in favour of closer ties with Russia.One of the protesters, Sergei, told euronews:“In Moscow, they think that what is happening here is anti-Russian. In Europe they think that what we are fighting for is pro-European. As a matter of fact, our actions are against the bandits (of the Ukrainian government). Most of the protesters who can be seen here are demonstrating for themselves.”Meanwhile the EU’s foreign policy chief, Catherine Ashton, has said that Yanukovych “intends to sign” the EU trade and cooperation agreement, which would be an about-face for the president.However, Yanukovych will meet Russia’s Vladimir Putin at bilateral interstate commission session scheduled for December 17 in Moscow. Protesters fear he will sign an agreement with Russia at that meeting. They have vowed to stay in Independence Square braving the cold, and the police, until this political tug-of-war is resolved to their satisfaction.

18 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7307_09_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/DND-o/220x123-4Hd.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7307-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7307_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 01:14:45">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xye9ob_cyprus-runs-to-russia-could-this-be-the-start-of-a-new-cold-war_news</link><title>Cyprus Runs to Russia: Could This Be the Start of a New Cold War?</title><description>Cyprus Runs to Russia: Could This Be the Start of a New Cold War?

Toegevoegd door tvnportal vorig jaar

The papers are split on whether Barack Obama's speech to Israelis was an engine for action or an excuse not to take any. Cyprus is in search of a suitor, but what happens when she is driven into the arms of Russia? One paper warns of a possible new Cold War!Powered by NewsLook.com Producer : France 24

11 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7307_10_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BFbZF/220x123-Ugc.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>