<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7403">usc trojans</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:28:40" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7403-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7403_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:28:41">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1jxvrj_paypal-18-cheap-wholesale-replica-ncaa-football-usc-trojans-ronnie-lott-home-game-jersey-42-white_sport</link><title>Paypal 18$ Cheap Wholesale replica NCAA FootBall USC Trojans Ronnie Lott home Game Jersey #42 White</title><description>Paypal 18$ Cheap Wholesale replica NCAA FootBall USC Trojans Ronnie Lott home Game Jersey #42 White

Toegevoegd door Dialogteldhx 4 weken geleden

Check http://made-in-putian.com you will find an amazing website to get your USC Trojans ##42 Ronnie Lott Jerseys. Besides, such a good web which can also provide whatever jerseys you guys needed. As a big sports fan, you can't miss it.

2 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7403_01_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/D_W1i/220x123-n3l.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7403-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7403_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:28:57">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1jm8x5_cod-replica-ncaa-football-jersey-usc-trojans-2-cheap-robert-woods-red-jersey-cheap-wholesale_sport</link><title>COD replica NCAA FootBall Jersey USC Trojans 2 Cheap Robert Woods Red Jersey Cheap Wholesale</title><description>COD replica NCAA FootBall Jersey USC Trojans 2 Cheap Robert Woods Red Jersey Cheap Wholesale

Toegevoegd door Subvertfpzntp laatste maart

Go and visit http://xhgy.cn for NCAA FootBall USC Trojans Robert Woods 2 Red Jerseys with authentic quality at discount. The player's number, name embroidered on center of back, chest and shoulders,Team Logo embroidered on sleeves. It is suitable, and the price is very favorable.

0 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7403_02_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/D_VSk/220x123-Mzp.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7403-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7403_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:29:28">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1jmfvi_18-usd-cheap-replica-ncaa-football-jersey-usc-trojans-33-marcus-allen-jersey-wholesale_sport</link><title>18 USD Cheap replica NCAA FootBall Jersey USC Trojans 33 Marcus Allen Jersey Wholesale</title><description>18 USD Cheap replica NCAA FootBall Jersey USC Trojans 33 Marcus Allen Jersey Wholesale

Toegevoegd door Subvertfpzntp laatste maart

http://sosfeel.ru for USC Trojans #33 Marcus Allen Jerseys with the player's number, name embroidered on center of back, chest and shoulders, Team Logo embroidered on sleeves. The price is really cheap and quality is very good.

3 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7403_03_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/D_Wy7/220x123-C4v.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7403-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7403_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:29:44">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1ct02e_stanford-cardinal-vs-usc-trojans-pick-prediction-ncaa-college-basketball-odds-preview-2-20-2014_sport</link><title>Stanford Cardinal vs. USC Trojans Pick Prediction NCAA College Basketball Odds Preview 2-20-2014</title><description>Stanford Cardinal vs. USC Trojans Pick Prediction NCAA College Basketball Odds Preview 2-20-2014

Toegevoegd door tonytssportsbets laatste februari

The USC Trojans will hit the road in PAC 12 conference action as they meet the Stanford Cardinal in an NCAA college basketball game set for Thursday night. Start time from Stanford is slated for 11PM Eastern Time with national television coverage provided by the PAC 12 Network. The wagering odds from this contest have the home side Stanford Cardinal favored by -14 points. USC has lost six straight and nine of their past ten games following the 83-74 home defeat on Sunday to the Colorado Buffaloes as a +4 point wagering underdog. The game total went over 142 ½ points. The Trojans have true road record this season of 1-7 straight up. In recent PAC 12 conference road contest the team has losses at Utah, Colorado, Oregon St and Oregon. USC is poor offensively in two areas as they make just 29.4% from three and 65.5% of their free throws.

5 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7403_04_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DsVBN/220x123-1rT.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7403-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7403_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:29:58">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x175fq1_usc-trojans-vs-stanford-cardinal-pick-prediction-college-football-odds-preview-11-16-2013_sport</link><title>USC Trojans vs. Stanford Cardinal Pick Prediction College Football Odds Preview 11-16-2013</title><description>USC Trojans vs. Stanford Cardinal Pick Prediction College Football Odds Preview 11-16-2013

Toegevoegd door tonytssportsbets laatste november

The Stanford Cardinal will hit the road in PAC 12 conference action to face the USC Trojans in an NCAA college football game set for Saturday night. Kick off time from USC is scheduled for 8PM Eastern Time with national television coverage provided by ABC TV. The college football point spread from this game has the road team Stanford Cardinal favored by -3 ½ points. Stanford is 8-1 on their season following a 26-20 home victory last week to the Stanford Cardinal as a +10 point underdog. The game total went under 60 ½ points. The Cardinal jumped out to the 17-0 first half lead. The team produced 377 offensive yards with 274 running for over 4 yards a carry. Kevin Hogan hit on 7 of 13 throws for 103 yards. The team had no turnovers and forced two away from Oregon. Stanford held a 25 minute time of possession advantage. Defensively the Cardinal gave up 312 yards to the Oregon offense with 62 rushing for 2 ½ yards per carry. Stanford got off the field 7 of 10 times on the Ducks third down plays. USC has won three straight to go to 7-3 on the season following a 62-28 road defeat last week to the California Golden Bears as a -18 ½ point betting favorite. The game total came in at over 57 points. The Trojans jumped out to the 41-14 first half lead. The Trojans gained 499 yards offensively with 256 running on 29 carries. Cody Kessler hit on 14 of 17 throws for 170 yards with two touchdowns.

20 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7403_05_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/C59qk/220x123-TCk.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7403-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7403_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:30:23">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x14wiw5_usc-trojans-vs-utah-st-aggies-pick-prediction-ncaa-college-football-odds-preview-9-21-2013_sport</link><title>USC Trojans vs. Utah St Aggies Pick Prediction NCAA College Football Odds Preview 9-21-2013</title><description>USC Trojans vs. Utah St Aggies Pick Prediction NCAA College Football Odds Preview 9-21-2013

Toegevoegd door tonytssportsbets laatste september

The Utah St Aggies will head to the west coast to face the USC Trojans in an NCAA college football game scheduled for Saturday afternoon. Kick off time for this week four game is set for 3:30PM Eastern Time with national television coverage provided by ABC TV. The betting odds from this college football game have the home side USC Trojans favored by -6 ½ points with an over under line set at 51 ½ points. Utah St is 2-1 on the year after a 70-6 home victory last week to non-FBS school Weber St Wildcats as a -39 point betting favorite. The game finished at over 64 ½ points. Utah St put this one away with a 49-0 lead at the half.

22 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7403_06_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/CcDWm/220x123-VW5.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7403-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7403_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:30:38">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x14nu72_usc-trojans-vs-boston-college-eagles-pick-prediction-ncaa-college-football-odds-preview-9-14-2013_sport</link><title>USC Trojans vs. Boston College Eagles Pick Prediction NCAA College Football Odds Preview 9-14-2013</title><description>USC Trojans vs. Boston College Eagles Pick Prediction NCAA College Football Odds Preview 9-14-2013

Toegevoegd door tonytssportsbets laatste september

The Boston College Eagles will make the long road trip out west to face the USC Trojans in an NCAA college football game scheduled for Saturday afternoon. Start time from USC is set for 3PM Eastern Time with national television coverage provided by the PAC 12 Network. The college football odds from this contest have the home team USC Trojans favored by -14 points with an over under line set at 42 ½ points. The Trojans will return -500 odds with the return on the road underdog Boston College Eagles at +400 odds on the money line.

32 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7403_07_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/CZsvI/220x123-D-s.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7403-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7403_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:31:10">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1473is_usc-trojans-vs-washington-st-cougars-pick-prediction-ncaa-college-football-odds-preview-9-7-2013_sport</link><title>USC Trojans vs. Washington St Cougars Pick Prediction NCAA College Football Odds Preview 9-7-2013</title><description>USC Trojans vs. Washington St Cougars Pick Prediction NCAA College Football Odds Preview 9-7-2013

Toegevoegd door tonytssportsbets laatste september

From week two PAC 12 conference play the Washington St Cougars will travel out west to face the USC Trojans in an NCAA college football game scheduled for Saturday night. Kick off time from USC is set for 10:30PM Eastern Time with national television coverage provided by Fox Sports 1. The NCAA college football odds from this contest have the home team USC Trojans favored by -16 points with an over under line set at 56 points. Those wagering the USC Trojans on the money line will lay -800 odds with the return on the road underdog Washington St Cougars at +550 odds on the money line.

20 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7403_08_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CWZxI/220x123-cNb.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7403-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7403_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:31:39">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1jrais_cod-cheap-replica-ncaa-football-jersey-usc-trojans-43-troy-polamalu-home-game-jersey-red-wholesale_sport</link><title>COD Cheap replica NCAA FootBall Jersey USC Trojans 43 Troy Polamalu Home Game Jersey Red Wholesale</title><description>COD Cheap replica NCAA FootBall Jersey USC Trojans 43 Troy Polamalu Home Game Jersey Red Wholesale

Toegevoegd door Dormantstdjub 4 weken geleden

Come and visit http://yhcb.cn for NCAA FootBall USC Trojans Troy Polamalu 43 Red Jerseys, they are with high qualities and raw material. Also we can offer best and timely services for every customer's order.

2 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7403_09_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/D_W2x/220x123-37W.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7403-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7403_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 08:32:12">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1jmdpp_18-ncaa-football-usc-trojans-reggie-bush-replica-jersey-wholesale-5-white-home-game-jersey_sport</link><title>18$ NCAA FootBall USC Trojans Reggie Bush replica Jersey Wholesale 5 White Home Game Jersey</title><description>18$ NCAA FootBall USC Trojans Reggie Bush replica Jersey Wholesale 5 White Home Game Jersey

Toegevoegd door Phobiarwflq laatste maart

Look at http://made-in-putian.com ,this NCAA FootBall USC Trojans Reggie Bush 5 White Jersey, it with a tackle twill team logo on the front and the play's name and number on the back, keep you pulling for a Blackhawks victory no matter what the score!

0 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7403_10_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/D_VUH/220x123-zix.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>