<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7416">release date bioshock infinite</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:19:46" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7416-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7416_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:19:47">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xtw5o0_bioshock-infinite-official-release-date_videogames</link><title>Bioshock Infinite Official Release Date</title><description>Bioshock Infinite Official Release Date

Toegevoegd door TheGUNNShop vorig jaar

Related article, http://www.joystiq.com/2012/03/01/bioshock-infinite-release-date-october-16/

92 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7416_01_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/TM55/220x123-yWD.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7416-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7416_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:20:08">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xzo3fp_release-bioshock-infinite-keygen-generator-pc-ps3-xbox360-direct-link_videogames</link><title>[Release] Bioshock Infinite Keygen Generator [PC PS3 XBOX360] [Direct Link]</title><description>[Release] Bioshock Infinite Keygen Generator [PC PS3 XBOX360] [Direct Link]

Toegevoegd door jhamiltonnov90 laatste mei

Download Here: http://bit.ly/1099TaS Copy the Above Link and Paste in your BROWSER.

37 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7416_02_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/BcTNO/220x123-fjn.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7416-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7416_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:20:28">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xybxp6_march-2013-skidrow-cracked-bioshock-infinite-free-download-pc-xbox-360-and-ps3_videogames</link><title>[March 2013][Skidrow Cracked] BioShock Infinite Free Download PC XBOX 360 and PS3</title><description>[March 2013][Skidrow Cracked] BioShock Infinite Free Download PC XBOX 360 and PS3

Toegevoegd door Strahinjin Boss vorig jaar

Hello Everyone! If you are looking for BioShock Infinite for Xbox 360 or PC or PS3, your on right place! Take a look on my website. Im sharing Free Game Cracks. Please say thanks and like video! For download visit: http://www.skidrowgamingcracks.com extra tags: BioShock Infinite PC BioShock Infinite download BioShock Infinite download free BioShock Infinite free download free download BioShock Infinite download BioShock Infinite free download BioShock Infinite download for free BioShock Infinite free BioShock Infinite at download free BioShock Infinite to download how get BioShock Infinite get BioShock Infinite free how i get BioShock Infinite free descargar BioShock Infinite BioShock Infinite Free download Xbox 360 download free BioShock Infinite for xbox360 how to download BioShock Infinite for xbox360 BioShock Infinite Free download PC download free BioShock Infinite for PC how to download BioShock Infinite for PC BioShock InfiniteFree download PS3 download free BioShock Infinite for PS3 how to download BioShock Infinite for PS3 release bioshock infinite bioshock release date bioshock infinite trailer

118 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7416_03_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BPoRC/220x123-mMu.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7416-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7416_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:20:50">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xykocz_direct-live-bioshock-infinite-x360_videogames</link><title>Direct Live Bioshock Infinite ( X360 )</title><description>Direct Live Bioshock Infinite ( X360 )

Toegevoegd door Hooper vorig jaar

Toutes mes vidéos sur http://www.hooper.fr Des vidéos inédites, un forum actif, des concours et des tournois originaux, rejoins la communauté sur http://www.hooper.fr

56 668 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7416_04_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/BSFiW/220x123-Iwe.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7416-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7416_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:21:16">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xys9ax_videotest-bioshock-infinite-hd-360_videogames</link><title>VideoTest Bioshock Infinite (HD)(360)</title><description>VideoTest Bioshock Infinite (HD)(360)

Toegevoegd door bibi300 vorig jaar

ATTENTION, SPOILERS !! Quand on attend énormément un jeu, on se dit qu'on peut être plus facilement déçu car nos espoirs sont tels que le jeu n'a finalement pas le droit à l'erreur, ou presque. J'attendais ce jeu comme un fouf furieux, après un 1er épisode monumental et quasi-parfait sur beaucoup de points et après un 2e sympa mais loin de me satisfaire complètement. J'ai aimé ce jeu. Mais...je n'ai pas eu la claque escomptée, la gifle que j'esperais et honnêtement, ça s'est joué à pas grand chose, mais suffisamment pour justifier cela. La 1ere moitié du jeu est juste sensationnel, une maitrise parfaite de l'exploration et de l'action sans que jamais l'un vienne prendre le pas sur l'autre, une ambiance de dingue, des thèmes abordés très intéressants (quoiqu'un peu sous-développés), une direction artistique phénoménale qui en jette, un scénario profond, agréable, cohérent et crédible...et ce personnage d'Elizabeth, réussie, vivante et bourré d'émotions, un vrai régal. Mais voila, en passant sur la 2e moitié du jeu, j'ai eu l'impression d'avoir une aventure qui s'essouflait, une qualité en dent de scie avec de bons passages mais aussi énormément d'allers-retours bien gonflants, une I.A. pas si énorme que cela et de l'action à ne plus en finir (le dernier quart du jeu est un vrai calvaire avec des vagues incesssantes d'une dizaine d'ennemis, voire plus...). Si bien qu'à un moment donné je me suis dit : quand est-ce que cela se termine ? Alors une fois de plus je l'ai pas détesté ce jeu au contraire, je le trouve bien plus réussi que le 2, mais à mon sens, il n'égale pas le 1. On sent que les problèmes de développement du jeu ont pesés sur celui-ci, et notamment dans cette 2e moitié du jeu où on a la sensation de jouer "à la va-vite". Quel dommage, car franchement, il était pas loin de m'emballer totalement grâce à cette 1ere partie magistrale. Je suis arrivé aux portes du Paradis...mais celles-ci sont restées fermées. Bonne vidéo à tous, et rejoignez-moi sur http://bibi300.overblog.com ! Facebook Officiel : https://www.facebook.com/pages/Bibi300fr-La-Passion-du-Jeu-Vid%C3%A9o/174703095915403 Twitter Officiel : http://twitter.com/PtitBibi300

15 191 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7416_05_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BUD7W/220x123-S9l.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7416-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7416_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:21:40">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xujfa0_revamped-playstation-store-pulled-bioshock-infinite-ultimate-edition-treyarch-admits-lack-of-innovat_videogames</link><title>Revamped PlayStation Store Pulled, Bioshock Infinite Ultimate Edition, Treyarch Admits Lack of Innovation - Nick's Gaming View Episode #85</title><description>Revamped PlayStation Store Pulled, Bioshock Infinite Ultimate Edition, Treyarch Admits Lack of Innovation - Nick's Gaming View Episode #85

Toegevoegd door TheGamerAccess vorig jaar

Coming up today on Nick’s Gaming View, revamped PlayStation Store taken down, Bioshock Infinite: Ultimate Songbird Edition announced, and Treyarch admits to lack of innovation with the original Call of Duty: Black Ops, THIS IS NICK’S GAMING VIEW!Hello everyone and welcome to Nick’s Gaming View, you are here with your host, Nick McCandless. Sony’s very own PlayStation Store has recently underwent numerous behind-the-scenes improvements and visual enhancements in various regions outside of North America including Australia, Sweden, Belgium, Denmark, and more, delivering a fresh new experience that PlayStation have fans have fallen in love with. While the new design is very welcome to the PlayStation platform and PlayStation fans are eagerly anticipating its release here in the states, Sony has admitted to hiccups such as not being able to add funds to one’s wallet causing Sony to reissue the previous PlayStation Store design. Nice to see Sony taking action to satisfy their customers, but let’s hope they are able to work out the kinks in time for their North American launch.Bioshock: Infinite, the once 2012 holiday season release pushed back to February 26th of 2013, recently uncovered its premium edition offering a 3-inch baby version keychain of the sold-out Murder of Crows vigor bottle replica, 5x7 inch lithograph by Jorge Lacera, 25 millimeter resin-cast Handyman miniature from the upcoming Bioshock Infinite board game, mini art book full of Bioshock Infinite concept art and commentary, various digital goodies, and a copy of Bioshock Infinite. Wondering how much this massive package will set you back? Bioshock Infinite’s Ultimate Songbird Edition will weigh in at the price of $149.99 on all three platforms including PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC requiring dedicated fans of the series to consider their purchase an investment.Continuing on massively successful franchises, the original Call of Duty: Black Ops was recently demoted by its very own developer, Treyarch, stating that the 2010 release did not significantly innovate as much of the press agreed with. Good news for those expecting more out of the successor, Black Ops II, Treyarch continued on by stating that Call of Duty: Black Ops II will indeed innovate and offer an experience no other Call of Duty has successfully accomplished. Is Treyarch truly going to deliver the revamp of Call of Duty we have all been waiting for, or are they simply running the hype train? Come November 13th when the action-packed first-person shooter hits store shelves gamers should find out, but let’s all hope we have a surprise awaiting us.Well that concludes today’s episode of Nick’s Gaming View but be sure to follow me on Twitter @NickMcCandless and check back daily for Nick’s Gaming View for your daily access pass for all things gaming.E-mail: admin@thegameraccess.comTwitter: https://twitter.com/NickMcCandlessGoogle+: https://plus.google.com/101731558093991354166Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/OfficialNickMcCandless

26 062 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7416_06_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/zK9G/220x123-Y7i.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7416-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7416_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:22:09">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xyz0il_bioshock-infinite-pc-02_videogames</link><title>Bioshock Infinite - PC - 02</title><description>Bioshock Infinite - PC - 02

Toegevoegd door Iti63 vorig jaar

Missions présentées : La tombola Vidéo disponible jusqu'en : 1080p Ma page Facebook : https://www.facebook.com/pages/Iti63/166081103477984?sk=wall FTJ sur facebook : http://www.facebook.com/pages/Frapstesjeux/186058341420736?ref=ts/ Dons et Goodies : http://boutique.frapstesjeux.fr/ Page Twitter : http://twitter.com/Frapstesjeux/ Ma page Twitter : https://twitter.com/Iti_sforyou Cette vidéo vous est proposée par Frapstesjeux www.frapstesjeux.fr

4 651 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7416_07_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DSH8w/220x123-hGE.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7416-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7416_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:22:31">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xz1urw_bioshock-infinite-pc-03_videogames</link><title>Bioshock Infinite - PC - 03</title><description>Bioshock Infinite - PC - 03

Toegevoegd door Iti63 vorig jaar

Missions présentées : L'odre du grand corbeau Vidéo disponible jusqu'en : 1080p Ma page Facebook : https://www.facebook.com/pages/Iti63/166081103477984?sk=wall FTJ sur facebook : http://www.facebook.com/pages/Frapstesjeux/186058341420736?ref=ts/ Dons et Goodies : http://boutique.frapstesjeux.fr/ Page Twitter : http://twitter.com/Frapstesjeux/ Ma page Twitter : https://twitter.com/Iti_sforyou Cette vidéo vous est proposée par Frapstesjeux www.frapstesjeux.fr

4 213 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7416_08_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DSH96/220x123-32c.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7416-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7416_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:23:02">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1ah4pn_bioshock-infinite-tombeau-sous-marin-episode-2-exclusive-preview-clip-vf_videogames</link><title>BioShock : Infinite - Tombeau Sous-Marin Episode 2 - Exclusive Preview Clip (VF)</title><description>BioShock : Infinite - Tombeau Sous-Marin Episode 2 - Exclusive Preview Clip (VF)

Toegevoegd door Gamekult laatste januari

BioShock : Infinite - Tombeau Sous-Marin Episode 2 (Xbox 360) - Exclusive Preview Clip (VF)

3 827 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7416_09_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/DefLG/220x123-RsT.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7416-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7416_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:23:23">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xyjslo_bioshock-infinite-pouvoirs_videogames</link><title>Bioshock Infinite - Pouvoirs</title><description>Bioshock Infinite - Pouvoirs

Toegevoegd door Millenium_TV vorig jaar

Bioshock Infinite - Pouvoirs Retrouvez toutes les informations dans notre dossier Bioshock Infinite : http://www.millenium.org/bioshock-infinite/accueil/test/bioshock-3-infinite-pc-xbox360-ps3-bioshock-3-infinite-pc-xbox-360-ps3-trailer-astuces-cheat-soluce-guide-test-84237

5 398 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7416_10_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BRwZ2/220x123-0yl.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>