<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7423">postdoc jobs european university biotech</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:44:25" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7423-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7423_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:44:26">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xppckf_ph-diva-and-the-mystery-band-animation-of-life-in_tech</link><title>“Ph.Diva and the Mystery Band” - Animation of Life in ...</title><description>“Ph.Diva and the Mystery Band” - Animation of Life in ...

Toegevoegd door Lifetechnologies 2 jaren geleden

April Brite, (aka the Ph.Diva) is a biotech Postdoc. April is thrilled when her abstract is picked for an oralpresentation, and starts preparing her presentation. When her PCR does not go exactly as planned, shesets off on a journey filled with frustrations, anticipation, fascination and determination. Will our Ph.Divamake it in time for her conference?Acknowledgements: This video is inspired by all the dedicated everyday-heroes-of-science. Invitrogenrecognizes your passion and admires your perseverance!

88 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7423_01_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/AVVDB/220x123-47k.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7423-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7423_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:44:45">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1r8ukn_verhofstadt-s-liberal-recipe-for-europe_news</link><title>Verhofstadt's liberal recipe for Europe</title><description>Verhofstadt's liberal recipe for Europe

Toegevoegd door euronews-en 20 uur geleden

For the first time in the European elections political groups have put forward candidates for the presidency of the European Commission. The choice will be made after the election of the new Parliament. In this edition of Europe’s choice the focus is on the candidate of the liberal group. Guy Verhofstadt chairs the Alliance of Liberals and Democrats for Europe.Born 11 April 1953 in Dendermonde, Belgium, he grew up in the Flanders region. While studying law at the University of Ghent, he became head of the Flemish Liberals Student’s Union A city councillor in Ghent by 23, his rapid rise continued as he became President of the Flemish liberal party at 29, then an MP in 1985. In the same year he became deputy prime minister and budget minister. But darker times followed. He lost the presidency of his party, then in opposition. He took a break in Tuscany to, as he said, reflect.Once dubbed Baby Thatcher, Verhoffstadt tempered his radical liberalism and returned to lead an overhauled Liberal party to victory in 1999, becoming premier of three successive governments.During this period he developed his passion for European politics, and his European Commission ambitions. In between campaign trips, we caught up him in Ghent doing one of his favourite pastimes – cycling. “The European tour is during the week, and the tour of Flanders is at the weekend,” he told us as we drove alongside while he peddled energetically along a cycle path. Since he was first elected to the European Parliament in 2009, Verhofstadt has fought to increase its weight in relation to that of the European Council.His staff say his seemingly tireless capacity for work sets an example. “He’s brought a completely new dynamism to the parliament . Since he arrived he’s politicised the institution much more than it ever was. But we’re always running around him and working 110 percent every day.There’s never a dull moment,” says Neil Corlett, Head of Press and Communication ALDE Group.It is perhaps as a champion of a federal Europe that Verhofstadt has made his name. He laid out his vision in his book ‘The United States of Europe’ in 2006 and last year co-authored a manifesto for a federal Europe with Daniel Cohn-Bendit of the Greens. Whether its the Budget, debt, taxation, or energy Verhofstadt wants deeper integration to cover all domains of government. “We need a much more integrated Europe. And this integration will be the engine to create more jobs and economic growth for years to come.The solution is really to use more Europe to get out of the crisis!” Verhofstadt says.“It is only our politicians who don’t have the courage to do it! And as a consequence people fall into disarray; they’re afraid, and they believe the lies of the nationalists. That’s the tragedy of Europe at the moment,” he adds.Fascinated by Europe’s diverse cultures, he speaks 5 languages ​, and says he feels at home everywhere on the continent, but has a particular connection to Italy.Sardinian Maria Landis, runs the kitchens of the Belgian government. It was Verhofstadt, as PM, who first hired her . Now his friend, her risotto with lobster and asparagus is among his favourite dishes. He’s not a bad cook himself, she says:“Lemon chicken is a speciality of his. So are chips!“I think he could have been a great chef; because he’s very creative, very curious, and has good taste; that’s important in cooking, but also in politics!“They say he’s visionary, but it takes vision to have good creativity; and he has that, perhaps sometimes a little too much,” she says. Through his support for a common socio-economic policy, a European army, Turkish membership of the EU, Verhofstadt has a habit of making waves. .So, what would his first act as Commission President, a role that’s already evaded him twice?“It would be to change the working method and directly use the European Commission as a true European government, which takes leadership of operations, which develops a vision and puts legislative packages on the tables of the Parliament and the Council. Precisely to force the states, to force the European Council to take up its responsibilities, which is not the case at the moment.“What Mr. Barroso does is to first phone Paris and then Berlin;(actually) usually it is the other way – first Berlin, then Paris. And it’s only when he has the green light from those two countries that he dares present something. But this isn’t how we will overcome the crisis!” he says.For the N-VA Flemish nationalist party’s lead candidate in the European elections Verhofstadt lacks realism. “His former Dutch liberal colleague Fritz Bolkestein compared Mr Verhofstadt to someone who is barking at the moon . It may be a little bit exaggerated , but I think the image is quite correct.“Mr Verhofstadt is focusing very much on the very long term issues, and on the European Union on the very long run . People will not go for these long term issues if

5 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7423_02_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/EczMW/220x123-SjT.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7423-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7423_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:45:12">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1rcby7_verhofstadt-s-liberal-recipe-for-europe_news</link><title>Verhofstadt's liberal recipe for Europe</title><description>Verhofstadt's liberal recipe for Europe

Toegevoegd door euronews-en 13 uur geleden

For the first time in the European elections political groups have put forward candidates for the presidency of the European Commission. The choice will be made after the election of the new Parliament. In this edition of Europe’s choice the focus is on the candidate of the liberal group. Guy Verhofstadt chairs the Alliance of Liberals and Democrats for Europe.Born 11 April 1953 in Dendermonde, Belgium, he grew up in the Flanders region. While studying law at the University of Ghent, he became head of the Flemish Liberals Student’s Union A city councillor in Ghent by 23, his rapid rise continued as he became President of the Flemish liberal party at 29, then an MP in 1985. In the same year he became deputy prime minister and budget minister. But darker times followed. He lost the presidency of his party, then in opposition. He took a break in Tuscany to, as he said, reflect.Once dubbed Baby Thatcher, Verhoffstadt tempered his radical liberalism and returned to lead an overhauled Liberal party to victory in 1999, becoming premier of three successive governments.During this period he developed his passion for European politics, and his European Commission ambitions. In between campaign trips, we caught up him in Ghent doing one of his favourite pastimes – cycling. “The European tour is during the week, and the tour of Flanders is at the weekend,” he told us as we drove alongside while he peddled energetically along a cycle path. Since he was first elected to the European Parliament in 2009, Verhofstadt has fought to increase its weight in relation to that of the European Council.His staff say his seemingly tireless capacity for work sets an example. “He’s brought a completely new dynamism to the parliament . Since he arrived he’s politicised the institution much more than it ever was. But we’re always running around him and working 110 percent every day.There’s never a dull moment,” says Neil Corlett, Head of Press and Communication ALDE Group.It is perhaps as a champion of a federal Europe that Verhofstadt has made his name. He laid out his vision in his book ‘The United States of Europe’ in 2006 and last year co-authored a manifesto for a federal Europe with Daniel Cohn-Bendit of the Greens. Whether its the Budget, debt, taxation, or energy Verhofstadt wants deeper integration to cover all domains of government. “We need a much more integrated Europe. And this integration will be the engine to create more jobs and economic growth for years to come.The solution is really to use more Europe to get out of the crisis!” Verhofstadt says.“It is only our politicians who don’t have the courage to do it! And as a consequence people fall into disarray; they’re afraid, and they believe the lies of the nationalists. That’s the tragedy of Europe at the moment,” he adds.Fascinated by Europe’s diverse cultures, he speaks 5 languages ​, and says he feels at home everywhere on the continent, but has a particular connection to Italy.Sardinian Maria Landis, runs the kitchens of the Belgian government. It was Verhofstadt, as PM, who first hired her . Now his friend, her risotto with lobster and asparagus is among his favourite dishes. He’s not a bad cook himself, she says:“Lemon chicken is a speciality of his. So are chips!“I think he could have been a great chef; because he’s very creative, very curious, and has good taste; that’s important in cooking, but also in politics!“They say he’s visionary, but it takes vision to have good creativity; and he has that, perhaps sometimes a little too much,” she says. Through his support for a common socio-economic policy, a European army, Turkish membership of the EU, Verhofstadt has a habit of making waves. .So, what would his first act as Commission President, a role that’s already evaded him twice?“It would be to change the working method and directly use the European Commission as a true European government, which takes leadership of operations, which develops a vision and puts legislative packages on the tables of the Parliament and the Council. Precisely to force the states, to force the European Council to take up its responsibilities, which is not the case at the moment.“What Mr. Barroso does is to first phone Paris and then Berlin;(actually) usually it is the other way – first Berlin, then Paris. And it’s only when he has the green light from those two countries that he dares present something. But this isn’t how we will overcome the crisis!” he says.For the N-VA Flemish nationalist party’s lead candidate in the European elections Verhofstadt lacks realism. “His former Dutch liberal colleague Fritz Bolkestein compared Mr Verhofstadt to someone who is barking at the moon . It may be a little bit exaggerated , but I think the image is quite correct.“Mr Verhofstadt is focusing very much on the very long term issues, and on the European Union on the very long run . People will not go for these long term issues if

5 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7423_03_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/EdT4-/220x123-K7-.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7423-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7423_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:45:47">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1qsn3p_president-guebuza-of-mozambique-the-eu-has-no-magic-solution-for-africa_news</link><title>President Guebuza of Mozambique: 'The EU has no magic solution for Africa'</title><description>President Guebuza of Mozambique: 'The EU has no magic solution for Africa'

Toegevoegd door euronews-en vorig woensdag

Mozambique has grown on average around 8 percent in recent years, partly because of large energy reserves, but half of the country’s 25 million population still live in poverty. Euronews correspondent Isabel Marques da Silva spoke with President Armando Guebuza about these issues during the EU-Africa summit in Brussels .Isabel Marques da Silva, euronews: “This EU – Africa summit wants to change the aid model to a model of investment and trade, particularly with the private sector. What will it mean in practical terms?”Armando Guebuza, President of Mozambique: “One of our traditional sectors is agriculture, where productivity has been increasing. This is already an important step and generates the need to develop the agro-industry and to have infrastructure in place that feeds this process. Also important to Africa is tourism because Africa, as you know, is a major tourist centre, not only because of the beaches but because of its nature and wildlife.”euronews: “And what is the role of Europeans in terms of investment and trade? Which model would be desirable to optimise growth?”President Guebuza: “What Europe can and must do is continue to support us, especially in infrastructure, training and fighting dangerous diseases. Mozambique is working at it, although only since relatively recently. We’ve been searching for a cholera vaccine for children. Europe has really lent a hand in the creation of new institutions. Mozambique now has more than 40 higher education institutions, distributed throughout the country’s provinces”.euronews: “The fact is that the rate of poverty has not decreased as hoped and half of the population still live in poverty. Transport, access to water and electricity are there for the elite. But if there is more income available, why aren’t there more services?”President Guebuza: “People’s attitudes don’t change just because there is a sudden 10 or 15-percent growth rate. The distribution of wealth is not just mathematical, it depends on the creation of jobs, hospitals, infrastructure and so on. Each one takes a long time to build. Despite the growth that Africa is experiencing, to build a 100 or 200-kilometre road, for example, needs a major investment that’s not available. Even in Europe, and in other developed countries, the crisis has to do with a lack of employment. You can’t say there’s a lack of money or of resources! They exist here but are not enough to absorb all the workforce. We’re starting to grow, but obviously we can’t see development like that from one minute to the next!”euronews: “We’re still seeing large numbers of people migrating from Africa to Europe despite the difficulties. Many people still die on their way to Europe and there are many human trafficking networks. How do you think this problem should be solved?”President Guebuza: “The problem is socio-economic. More jobs should be created, there should be investments in improving living conditions, further strengthening of technical and vocational training, as well as university education and infrastructure. These changes would stop people from migrating from Africa to Europe or to any other continent in search of better living conditions.”euronews: “Lets speak about natural resources as a source of wealth. Mozambique is often called the new “El Dorado” due to the recent discovery of large energy reserves. But these so-called “blessings” have in many other countries become a “poisoned gift” that has lead to an escalation in corruption, more armed conflicts and ecological devastation. “How can Mozambique and other countries prevent these discoveries from causing problems? Can partnerships with European companies help prevent that from happening?”President Guebuza: “The problem shown by these great discoveries is, in essence, that we still have major shortcomings in knowledge, science and technology. These energy reserves should have been discovered long ago. We have large deficiencies in access to capital. We should have already made use of it a long time ago. Now what we have to do is use these discoveries – with the support of European investment – in a way that creates more income. Whatever is earned through taxes and business opportunities should be used to strengthen our budget.”euronews: “Lets talk now about peace on the African continent. The EU is a major contributor to peacekeeping missions with recent examples seen in the Central African Republic, but also in Mali. During the last decade, the EU gave 1.2 billion euros for the so-called “African Peace Facility”, but the continent seems unable to prevent and resolve armed conflict.”President Guebuza: “Africa is aware that there are problems, Africa moves when there are problems and tries to anticipate and prevent them as they arise, but obviously these are human issues related to socio-economic problems and ancestral cultural conflicts between certain sectors of the population. You don’t solve them by just handing ove

13 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7423_04_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/EZeij/220x123-JuX.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7423-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7423_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:46:20">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1ijix1_copernicus-offers-a-flood-of-disaster-data_news</link><title>Copernicus offers a flood of disaster data</title><description>Copernicus offers a flood of disaster data

Toegevoegd door euronews-en laatste maart

The recent floods in the UK saw a lot of the management of that disaster made possible by using information from satellites. But how? In this edition of Space we find out.Flooding affects thousands of people every year across Europe, and this year one of them just happened to be a flood scientist – Spanish Research Fellow at Reading University in England, Javier García-Pintado.His back garden looks onto the Thames, he explains: “This is the bank of the Thames, and this areas was severely affected by the recent flooding. Specifically in this little bit of land we are a tiny bit higher, and we didn’t have any problems, but our neighbours around here certainly did.”García-Pintado knew his young family was safe at home, because he could count on his expert knowledge; his day job is using satellite data to improve flood models.“As hydrologists we were pretty confident that this property wouldn’t have a problem, and we told our neighbours,” he told euronews.Not everyone has a neighbour as knowledgeable as Javier, nor were they as lucky.The whole area west of London was affected as England and Wales lived through their wettest winter in almost 250 years.Across England alone 6,500 homes were flooded.The British government looked to space for help. Satellite images showed the extent of the disaster. However those images were not available quickly. In fact they took around 30 hours to be processed. Javier and his colleague David Mason at the University of Reading can use that data for post-flood analysis, but they want to go further, to get information faster, and be one step ahead of the floodwaters. “Just like they’ve improved weather forecasting, they know when it’s going to rain pretty accurately, up to three days ahead. Now we are hoping to get flood forecasting more accurate in the short term,” says Professor Mason.That vision of flood forecasting will move towards reality with the launch of ESA’s Sentinel satellites. They promise a real step change in disaster monitoring. The first, called Sentinel-1, launches in April 2014. “When we get to the Sentinel 1 satellites, they will be able to give us imagery in near real time, an hour or so after the download to the ground station, and then you get to the sort of situation where you can use this imagery in a flood prediction mode, in a flood forecasting mode,” explained Mason.The Sentinel satellites promise more than a deluge of data on flooding. The fleet comprises seven different satellites, and each will scan the Earth in different ways.The project is overseen by the Director of the Copernicus Space Office, Josef Aschbacher, at ESA’s Earth Observation base near Rome.“Once the system is set up we really have a very wide variety of satellites and instruments that measure a magnitude of parameters, really everything that you can measure from space, from land parameters for flooding, for forest fires, for volcanic eruptions, damage after earthquakes, but also oil spills, ocean parameters, sea surface height, sea surface temperatures, climate parameters, air quality, ice coverage, and so on. So really whatever can be measured more or less will be measured by this constellation of Sentinel satellites which are being built up right now,” he says. Funding for the Sentinels comes from taxpayers through the ‘Copernicus’ programme, formerly known as GMES. It is led by the European Commission, in partnership with ESA and the European Environment Agency. Everyone will be able to enjoy the view from these new eyes in the sky.“The data policy, which was decided recently, is open and free, because this data is also something on which we can build a lot of business development, also for European companies, in Europe and also outside Europe, and this is only possible if the raw data are free. It’s a little bit like the navigation signal – you have a free signal from space, and then a lot of businesses are founded based on that on the ground,” says ESA’s Director of Earth Observation Volker Liebig. The Copernicus programme is already up and running, but will expand greatly in the next two years as the Sentinels launch, and begin offering many terabytes of data per day. “In the best case we are coming down to about half a metre resolution, which is quite precise. Then you go to a range of about five metres resolution, where you can measure different parameters, typically agricultural information, agricultural fields, yield predictions. Then you go to about 200 metres, 250 metres, which is used for global mapping of the oceans, really parameters at a global scale which of course have a different type of user and a different type of interest,” promises Aschbacher.Back in England, Javier García-Pintado believes the near real-time flow of Sentinel-1 satellite data will make a difference. Flood forecasting is an emerging field in science, and it will grow with more timely and accurate information.“With the ESA satellite we will be able t

10 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7423_05_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/D8lo7/220x123-TwP.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7423-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7423_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:46:49">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x18h38q_find-a-new-career-by-retracing-your-steps_news</link><title>Find a new career by retracing your steps</title><description>Find a new career by retracing your steps

Toegevoegd door euronews-en laatste december

In a country where the school drop-out rate is around twice the European average, Generation Y met those swimming against the tide. We went to Barcelona to talk to young people who have decided to go back school.Almost 10 years ago, Lucas Martos decided to quit school. He says he couldn’t see the point in continuing: “Before, I wasn’t interested in school. I was younger, that’s true, but I didn’t see any point in it, it wasn’t producing any results. And I knew that outside school, as a 16-year-old, I could be making money. At that time, I just thought school was a waste of time.”Lucas worked in construction and manual jobs. But a health problem forced him to stop temporarily. Then he decided to finish high school and study to become a lab technician. “Even the idea of coming back frightened me. But I’m more mature now, so I decided to try. It’s like work: you have to persevere, you have to keep it together. It’s the same thing here,” Lucas says. “Whenever I was around people who went to university and the conversation turned to culture or education, I felt out of it. When I finally finished high school, I told my girlfriend: now I can play Trivial Pursuit and answer some questions.”Mar Corredor had also been also looking for answers for almost a year.“I started to skip classes and finally I stopped going. I had no motivation, I didn’t like it, I didn’t understand where it was leading,” she says.A volunteering experience made her think about kick-starting her education, this time training to work with people with special needs.“You have to, because employers are always asking for more degrees, more masters, more whatever, just to be able to work somewhere,” she says.Lucas and Mar decided to go back to school themselves, but many in their situation don’t. It is they who are the focus of a new European Erasmus Plus programme aimed at bringing the drop-out rate below 10% by 2020. However, that is a very ambitious target concedes Xavier Chavarria Navarro, head of the Prevention School Drop-Out project: “Now, in Spain, it’s around 30%. Until recently there was lots of work in construction, now it’s tourism. Most are jobs that don’t require specific training and you don’t have to have qualifications to make money.”The crisis, particularly in construction, left many youngsters without a job and some had little education. Xavier Chavarria Navarro works to keep 16-24 year-olds in or bring them back to the education system. “We can adjust the curricular programme according to their interests, providing an interesting and attractive educational process that makes sense to them,” he says.“If they’re helping you to go down the path of returning to study, showing you what steps to take to make it easier, I think it can be very positive,” says Lucas Martos.Xavier Chavarria Navarro says every case is treated individually. “We can guide young people, and the schools that integrate them, to a customised type of orientation, diversifying the curricula in order to make it more attractive to them.”The Generation Y stories continue on our social media pages.

15 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7423_06_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/DPcym/220x123-icx.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7423-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7423_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:47:09">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1lvhsn_jobs-data-isn-t-enough-to-boost-market_news</link><title>Jobs Data Isn't Enough to Boost Market</title><description>Jobs Data Isn't Enough to Boost Market

Toegevoegd door WSJ Live 3 weken geleden

Employers added 192,000 jobs in March but a selloff in biotech and health lead exchanges lower. Alexandra Scaggs reports on the News Hub. Photo: Getty Images. Copyright 2014, Dow Jones &amp; Company, Inc.

4 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7423_07_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/EHP1-/220x123-tzG.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7423-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7423_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:47:32">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xn5n2r_eu-calls-for-alleviating-high-youth-unemployment_news</link><title>EU calls for alleviating high youth unemployment</title><description>EU calls for alleviating high youth unemployment

Toegevoegd door PressTV 2 jaren geleden

The numbers are alarming. Twenty-one percent of young people in the EU, on average, are unemployed. The situation is most difficult in Southern Europe. In Spain, for example, over 40 percent of youngsters have no jobs. Increasingly, this group includes university graduates, not just low-skilled Europeans. In Brussels, the European Commission called for immediate action to alleviate this problem. It proposed the creation of more apprenticeships with funding from the EU institutions.

7 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7423_08_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/aFXq/220x123-vWv.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7423-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7423_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:47:50">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xirf85_post-study-work-visa-s-to-end_news</link><title>POST-STUDY WORK VISA'S TO END</title><description>POST-STUDY WORK VISA'S TO END

Toegevoegd door tvnportal 2 jaren geleden

STORY: POST-STUDY WORK VISA'S TO END DATELINE: FEB. 17, 2011 LENGTH: 0:02:47 LOCATION: LONDON INTRO: Foreign university graduates in the United Kingdom may soon have to leave the country as soon as their college career ends. The reason? The country is planning to stop awarding two-year post-study work visa's to students from abroad, which has a lot of people upset. Lifestyles explains. PKG The UK Home Office is planning to pass a bill which will end the two-year Post-study Work visa in the country. What does that mean? All students who do not hail from the European Union will have to leave Britain as soon as they graduate. Non-EU students and student societies at universities have expressed their opposition to the new policy and are pushing the Home Office to re-think the decision. SOUNDBITE: SIMEON UNDERWOOD, ACADEMIC REGISTRAR "One of the arguments it is sometimes used against PSW is that, it is taking jobs from British graduates. But what we found out from employers Powered by www.newslook.com Producer : Xinhua News Agency

48 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7423_09_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/APQZS/220x123-AGF.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7423-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7423_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 09:48:21">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1no58b_top-4-business-stories-of-the-day_news</link><title>Top 4 Business Stories of the Day</title><description>Top 4 Business Stories of the Day

Toegevoegd door wochit 2 weken geleden

Weaker earnings at JPMorgan Chase are dragging bank stocks lower in early trading. Technology and biotech stocks also fell, a day after the worst rout for the Nasdaq composite index since 2011. The Nasdaq fell another 12 points, or 0.3 percent, to 4,042 in the first few minutes of trading Friday. It's down 7 percent from its recent high reached March 5. JPMorgan Chase led a decline in bank stocks after reporting weaker earnings because of a decline in bond trading and mortgages. Dollar bulls expecting to score on the back of diverging rates between a hawkish Federal Reserve and dovish European Central Bank are now in full retreat. With the release of the dovish Federal Open Market Committee’s March meeting minutes, and Fed Chair Janet Yellen’s recent remarks highlighting “considerable slack” in the economy, many long-dollar positions are being squeezed as the market drastically prices out an early rate hike by the Fed. Wells Fargo Wells Fargo had a solid start in 2014 reporting a record quarterly income. Net income came in at $5.9 billion. That’s up 14% from last year when income was $5.2 billion. Wells Fargo quarterly revenue fell in line with estimates at $20.6 billion, a slight drop from last year’s $21.3 billion. Growth was driven by increases in equity gains in the market, mortgage servicing income and brokerage advisory fees, Wells Fargo noted. Gold prices are steady to firmer and hovering near a three-week high in early U.S. trading Friday. The market is hanging on to Thursday’s decent gains and the bulls have gained a bit of upside near-term technical momentum. June gold was last up $0.70 at $1,321.10 an ounce. Spot gold was last quoted up $3.30 at $1,322.00. May Comex silver last traded down $0.061 at $20.03 an ounce.

1 view</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7423_10_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/EMLJp/220x123-Ek_.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>