<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7430">conflict mali</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:12:24" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7430-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7430_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:12:25">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x12h50n_conflicting-claims-in-mali-presidential-election_news</link><title>Conflicting claims in Mali presidential election</title><description>Conflicting claims in Mali presidential election

Toegevoegd door euronews-en laatste juli

There was an air of expectancy on the streets of Bamako the capital of Mali. They are waiting for the first provisional results of the presidential election aimed at uniting the north and south of the country....http://www.euronews.net/

3 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7430_01_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CJrcA/220x123-hfj.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7430-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7430_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:12:47">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x11w34h_raw-bastille-day-honors-mali-conflict-forces_news</link><title>Raw: Bastille Day Honors Mali Conflict Forces</title><description>Raw: Bastille Day Honors Mali Conflict Forces

Toegevoegd door associatedpress laatste juli

Troops from 13 African countries that took part in the French-led war against al-Qaida-linked extremists in Mali, marched with the French military during the Bastille Day parade in Paris on Sunday to honor their role in the conflict. (July 14)Copyright 2013 The Associated Press

325 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7430_02_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/CDzfI/220x123-k2U.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7430-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7430_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:13:16">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xz8diy_mali-conflict-once-the-french-have-gone-part-2_news</link><title>Mali Conflict: Once the French Have Gone... (Part 2)</title><description>Mali Conflict: Once the French Have Gone... (Part 2)

Toegevoegd door NewsLook vorig jaar

French lawmakers gave the green lite to keeping troops in Mali. Operation serval began in January and since then al Qaeda linked jihadists have been chased out of Mali's towns and cities. Prime Minister Jean-Marc Ayrault says its mission accomplished. French troops have already begun to leave and the government says that just 1000 soldiers will remain until the end of the year for training purpose. Laura Baines and her guests discuss whether Mali is really on the path for peace.Video provided by France 24 Producer : France 24

50 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7430_03_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BYPJS/220x123-S1v.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7430-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7430_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:13:40">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x105ztb_niger-suicide-attacks-fuel-fears-mali-conflict-could-spread_news</link><title>Niger suicide attacks fuel fears Mali conflict could spread</title><description>Niger suicide attacks fuel fears Mali conflict could spread

Toegevoegd door Euronews laatste mei

There are fears that militant violence in West Africa is spreading after a double suicide attack in Niger which left more than 20 people dead, mostly soldiers.They are the first such attacks experienced by the country which is involved in a French-led offensive in neighbouring Mali against Islamist rebels....No Comment | euronews: watch the international news without commentary | http://www.euronews.net/nocomment/

43 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7430_04_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/Bg0gY/220x123-fpG.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7430-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7430_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:13:59">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xwyz9y_oxfam-counts-the-cost-of-mali-conflict_news</link><title>Oxfam counts the cost of Mali conflict</title><description>Oxfam counts the cost of Mali conflict

Toegevoegd door Agence France-Presse (AFP) vorig jaar

Oxfam says that at least 400,000 people have fled the conflict in Mali to seek shelter in neighbouring countries. Duration: 01:27

19 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7430_05_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/BEbFF/220x123-IQn.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7430-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7430_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:14:26">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xxn7cd_in-the-french-papers-understanding-the-conflict-in-mali-with-satellite-images_news</link><title>IN THE FRENCH PAPERS - Understanding the conflict in Mali with satellite images</title><description>IN THE FRENCH PAPERS - Understanding the conflict in Mali with satellite images

Toegevoegd door FRANCE 24 English vorig jaar

FRENCH PAPERS, Weds. 20/02/13: French media react to news that a French family was taken hostage in Cameroon. Aujourd’hui en France has an interview with an eyewitness. Slate, meanwhile, tries to understand the French intervention in Mali using satellite images and the rare press photos that are published. By Florence VILLEMINOT Get the France 24 press review on your iPhone or become a fan on Facebook. Some articles from today’s French press review: LE PARISIEN: French family taken hostage in Cameroon SLATE: War in Mali understood through satellite images LE FIGARO: France to unfreeze aid to Mali LIBERATION: Socialists and the austerity taboo All shows: http://www.france24.com/en/list/emission/18006 FRANCE 24 INTERNATIONAL NEWS 24/7 http://www.france24.com

55 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7430_06_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BIkoA/220x123-1j1.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7430-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7430_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:14:48">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xwxulq_jaime-watt-looks-at-what-issues-canadians-are-talking-about-this-week-including-the-conflict-in-mali_news</link><title>Jaime Watt Looks at What Issues Canadians Are Talking About This Week, Including the Conflict in Mali, the Idle No More Movement and US President Barack Obama's Gun Control Proposal</title><description>Jaime Watt Looks at What Issues Canadians Are Talking About This Week, Including the Conflict in Mali, the Idle No More Movement and US President Barack Obama's Gun Control Proposal

Toegevoegd door tvnportal vorig jaar

Jaime Watt takes a weekly look at how issues making waves in Ottawa resonate with Canadians on CBC's Power &amp; Politics. This week: Obama's gun-control measures and First Nations protests.Powered by NewsLook.com Producer : CBC

41 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7430_07_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BERXz/220x123-LTV.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7430-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7430_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:15:08">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xwt4q8_un-warns-mali-conflict-will-cause-humanitarian-crisis_news</link><title>UN warns Mali conflict will cause humanitarian crisis</title><description>UN warns Mali conflict will cause humanitarian crisis

Toegevoegd door euronews-en vorig jaar

Refugees who have managed to flee northern Mali are receiving food aid which has been arriving in the capital Bamako.The situation in the north is too dangerous for non-governmental organisations to operate.The UN believes armed Islamist groups have been preventing thousands from fleeing areas affected by their recent offensive. It has warned of a humanitarian crisis....http://www.euronews.net/

32 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7430_08_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/BDuQA/220x123-ahh.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7430-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7430_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:15:37">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xw42ni_french-envoy-to-un-discusses-mali-conflict_news</link><title>French envoy to UN discusses Mali conflict</title><description>French envoy to UN discusses Mali conflict

Toegevoegd door Al Jazeera English vorig jaar

The UN Security Council has unanimously approved plans for an African-led military intervention in Mali aimed at reunifying the embattled North African state. The resolution, approved in New York on Thursday afternoon, calls for political reconciliation, elections and the training of the country's security forces before any operation is launched to reclaim Mali's northern areas. Geraud Araud, the French Ambassador to the United Nations, talks to Al Jazeera about the conflict in Mali.

42 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7430_09_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/AxWMb/220x123-dNc.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7430-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7430_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:15:55">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xwuf30_french-ambassador-on-mali-france-s-ambassador-to-canada-philippe-zeller-discusses-the-developing-sit_news</link><title>French Ambassador on Mali France's Ambassador to Canada, Philippe Zeller Discusses the Developing Situation on the Ground in Both the Mali Conflict and the Hostage Taking in Algeria.</title><description>French Ambassador on Mali France's Ambassador to Canada, Philippe Zeller Discusses the Developing Situation on the Ground in Both the Mali Conflict and the Hostage Taking in Algeria.

Toegevoegd door tvnportal vorig jaar

Islamist militants have told a Mauritanian news outlet that Algerian military helicopters strafed the gas complex where they are holding hostages, killing 35 of the foreigners and 15 kidnappers.Powered by NewsLook.com Producer : CBC

35 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7430_10_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BD6Ak/220x123-0Nb.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>