<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7439">make crown</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:49:11" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7439-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7439_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:49:12">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xg3hko_how-to-make-a-braided-flower-princess-crown_news</link><title>How to Make a Braided Flower Princess Crown</title><description>How to Make a Braided Flower Princess Crown

Toegevoegd door Lifestyle 3 jaren geleden

Delight the heart of any girl with a braided flower crown you create yourself using her favorite posies.

1 231 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7439_01_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/xlbg/220x123-mLM.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7439-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7439_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:49:28">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x18wh5n_how-to-make-a-crown-for-your-american-girl-barbie-or-monster-high-doll_creation</link><title>How to make a crown for your American girl, Barbie or Monster High doll</title><description>How to make a crown for your American girl, Barbie or Monster High doll

Toegevoegd door SimpleKidsCrafts laatste december

In this episode we show you how to make a crown for your American girl, Barbie or Monster High doll [Ep:679]

369 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7439_02_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/DVaB0/220x123-OFd.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7439-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7439_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:49:55">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x19urn4_how-to-make-crowns-and-tiaras-for-your-doll_creation</link><title>How to make crowns and tiaras for your doll</title><description>How to make crowns and tiaras for your doll

Toegevoegd door SimpleKidsCrafts laatste januari

In this video we show you how to make crowns and tiaras for your doll [Ep:697]

230 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7439_03_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DbYpj/220x123-UVl.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7439-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7439_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:50:21">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xe2go5_how-to-make-a-balloon-crown-balloon_news</link><title>How to make a Balloon Crown- Balloon San Diego series</title><description>How to make a Balloon Crown- Balloon San Diego series

Toegevoegd door sandiballoon 3 jaren geleden

http://www.balloonutopia- How to instructions on making a balloon crown by Sandi Masori of Balloon Utopia. Visit our website for more awesome balloon designs.

622 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7439_04_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/AMvw4/220x123-stH.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7439-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7439_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:50:47">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xuod5e_crown-capital-eco-management-human-thirst-makes-earth-quake_news</link><title>Crown Capital Eco Management - Human Thirst Makes Earth Quake</title><description>Crown Capital Eco Management - Human Thirst Makes Earth Quake

Toegevoegd door Charles Crown vorig jaar

As we all know earthquake is a catastrophic natural disaster. Most earthquake-related deaths are caused by the collapse of structures and the construction practices play a tremendous role in the death toll of an earthquake. In southern Italy in 1909 more than 100,000 people perished in an earthquake that struck the region. Almost half of the people living in the region of Messina were killed due to the easily collapsible structures that dominated the villages of the region. Though there are some ways to prevent this from happening, it can never be considered as risk avoidance.A larger earthquake that struck San Francisco three years earlier had killed fewer people (about 700) because building construction practices were different type (predominantly wood). Survival rates in the San Francisco earthquake was about 98%, that in the Messina earthquake was between 33% and 45%) (Zebrowski, 1997). Even a moderate rupture beneath a city with structures unprepared for shaking can produce tens of thousands of casualties. Due to this fact, Crown Eco Management determined that safety measures for this could not be compared to fraud prevention.Although probably the most important that we should know, direct shaking effects are not the only hazard associated with earthquakes, other effects such as landslides, liquefaction, and tsunamis have also played important part in destruction produced by earthquakes.According to the Crown researchers, some earthquakes are not natural. Human beings can actually cause them.That’s the case with an earthquake in Lorca, Spain, last May. The quake measured 5.1 on the Richter scale and killed nine people. According to an analysis published in Crown Eco Management, the Lorca quake was caused by the extraction of groundwater from an aquifer near the fault that slipped. In circumstance, it does not take much to trigger an earthquake. Oil and gas wells, rock quarries, even the added pressure of a reservoir lake behind a new dam can cause the ground to rumble. But we do not know what pressure levels are safe, nor is it clear whether man-made quakes are unique or just the early arrival of temblors that would have occurred naturally. In the Lorca quake, the shaking itself was much stronger than might be expected from the removed water pressure.And so with this, we may be able to start earthquakes but we cannot predict their size as just like what we can do to some renewable energy scam. If we could, we might be able to relieve stress on schedule and without loss of property- or life.

13 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7439_05_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/AUed-/220x123-15C.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7439-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7439_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:51:05">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x14vtkh_how-to-make-a-fondant-crown-cake-fondant_lifestyle</link><title>How to Make a Fondant Crown | Cake Fondant</title><description>How to Make a Fondant Crown | Cake Fondant

Toegevoegd door Lifestyle laatste september

Learn how to make a fondant crown for a princess cake from pastry chef Angela Cuervo, winner of Food Network's Sweet Genius, in this Howcast video.

233 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7439_06_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/Cb2Ma/220x123-ipe.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7439-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7439_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:51:19">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x14gac6_origami-how-to-make-an-easy-crown_fun</link><title>Origami - How to make an easy crown</title><description>Origami - How to make an easy crown

Toegevoegd door Shinyorigami laatste september

Here are the origami instructions for the crown --------------------------------------------------------------- Como hacer una corona de papel (papiroflexia)En este tutorial os enseñare a hacer esta corona de papel, es realmente sencilla.

186 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7439_07_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/EeNeL/220x123-TTQ.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7439-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7439_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:51:43">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xfwxy0_how-to-make-roasted-tomato-crowns_news</link><title>How to Make Roasted Tomato Crowns</title><description>How to Make Roasted Tomato Crowns

Toegevoegd door Monkey See 3 jaren geleden

In this video, Chef Bryan Davis shows you how to make a great roasted tomato appetizer.

125 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7439_08_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/fso8/220x123-lOq.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7439-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7439_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:52:00">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xsdbga_libya-s-crown-prince-makes-appeal_news</link><title>Libya's 'crown prince' makes appeal</title><description>Libya's 'crown prince' makes appeal

Toegevoegd door Al Jazeera English vorig jaar

Muhammad al-Senussi, who would be Libya's crown prince if the country still had a monarchy, has spoken out about the ongoing violence in the country from London.Libya was a monarchy until Muammar Gaddafi took power in a military coup in 1969 and the exiled King Idris has long since died.In this interview with Al Jazeera's Barnaby Phillips, al-Senussi asks the international community to help remove Gaddafi from power and stop the ongoing "massacre".

17 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7439_09_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/AHSCb/220x123-CB6.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7439-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7439_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 10:52:21">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xdjdv4_balloon-artist-san-diego-how-to-mak_news</link><title>Balloon Artist San Diego- How to make a balloon crown</title><description>Balloon Artist San Diego- How to make a balloon crown

Toegevoegd door sandiballoon 3 jaren geleden

http://www.balloonutopia.com - Balloon Artist San Diego - step by step instructions on how to make a balloon crown. For more information on all things balloon, visit our website.

120 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7439_10_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/S_Pf/220x123-F1I.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>