<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7458">rice recipe</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:03:15" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7458-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7458_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:03:16">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1f7yvu_veg-fried-rice-how-to-make-fried-rice-simple-and-easy-rice-recipe-by-ruchi-bharani_lifestyle</link><title>Veg Fried Rice - How To Make Fried Rice - Simple and Easy Rice Recipe By Ruchi Bharani</title><description>Veg Fried Rice - How To Make Fried Rice - Simple and Easy Rice Recipe By Ruchi Bharani

Toegevoegd door RajshriFood laatste maart

Ingredients: Oil 1/4 capsicum (finely chopped) 3 garlic (finely chopped) 1 green chilli (deseeded &amp; finely chopped) 1/4 cup french beans 1/4 cup carrots Black pepper 1 tsp white vinegar 1 tsp soya sauce 1 tbsp green chilli sauce 2 cups Boiled Rice Method: - Heat oil in a pan - Add capsicum, garlic, green chilli, french beans, carrots and saute and stir fry the vegetables - Add black pepper, white vinegar, soya sauce, green chilli sauce and mix everything well - Add the boiled rice and toss everything together. - Add salt, spring onions to it and mix well everything well - Serve hot Director: Neha Sarkar Camera: Vaibhav Dhandha Kawaldeep Singh Jangwal) Editing: Ravi Varma Creative Head: Kavya Krishnaswamy Producer: Rajjat A. Barjatya Copyrights: Rajshri Entertainment Private Limited.

5 588 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7458_01_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/D1H2L/220x123-Myh.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7458-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7458_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:03:37">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xzg77m_hyderabadi-veg-biryani-indian-rice-recipe-by-ruchi-bharani-hd_lifestyle</link><title>Hyderabadi Veg Biryani - Indian Rice Recipe by Ruchi Bharani [HD]</title><description>Hyderabadi Veg Biryani - Indian Rice Recipe by Ruchi Bharani [HD]

Toegevoegd door RajshriFood laatste april

Quick Veg Biryani - Indian Rice Recipe by Ruchi Bharani [HD] INGREDIENTS- 2 &amp; 1/2 cups boiled rice 1/2 green capsicum cut lengthwise 1 onion cut lengthwise 1/2 tomato deseeded and chopped 1 cup boiled vegetables coriander leaves 1 tbsp. curd/ yogurt 1 tsp. biryani masala 1 tbsp. butter 1 tsp. garlic paste 1/2 tsp. sugar salt 1 tsp. kashmiri red chilli powder 1 piece cinnamon 2 cloves 1 bay leaf cottage cheese (paneer) for garnishing (optional) METHOD- - Heat 1 tbsp. butter in a pan. Add onions, cinnamon stick, cloves and bay leaf. Cook till onions turn brown. - Add garlic paste, capsicum and tomatoes. Cook well for 1-2 min. - In a bowl, mix 1 tbsp. curd, 1 tsp. biryani masala and 1 tsp. kashmiri red chilli powder. - Add the curd mixture to the onions. Cook for a minute. Throw in some coriander leaves. Add sugar and mix well. - Add the boiled rice and vegetables (french beans, carrots, cauliflower, green peas and potatoes) Mix well. - Add salt as per taste and 2-3 tbsp. water. - Cover and let it simmer for 2-3 min. - Garnish with grated paneer (cottage cheese) &amp; coriander leaves. Serve hot.

5 435 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7458_02_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BaVsa/220x123-3IW.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7458-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7458_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:04:00">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xzxqfo_chicken-fried-rice-recipe_lifestyle</link><title>Chicken Fried Rice Recipe</title><description>Chicken Fried Rice Recipe

Toegevoegd door RebeccaBrandRecipes laatste mei

Rebecca Brand shows how to make a Chicken Fried Rice the classic Asian way. Chinese Chicken Fried Rice is easy to make following this Fried Rice recipe. Start with cold white rice add some chicken and you're on your way to this quick dinner favorite. Great for leftover chicken, leftover turkey, and vegetables you have in your refrigerator or freezer, the base to this is the classic Asian flavor for the most delicious of Fried Rice recipes.

1 599 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7458_03_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/Bf9mw/220x123-9NR.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7458-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7458_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:04:23">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x15xopp_kashmiri-pulav-kashmiri-rice-rich-in-fruits-recipe-special-occasion-rice-recipe-by-ruchi-bharani_lifestyle</link><title>Kashmiri Pulav - Kashmiri Rice Rich In Fruits Recipe - Special Occasion Rice Recipe by Ruchi Bharani</title><description>Kashmiri Pulav - Kashmiri Rice Rich In Fruits Recipe - Special Occasion Rice Recipe by Ruchi Bharani

Toegevoegd door RajshriFood laatste oktober

In this episode, Chef Ruchi Bharani brings to you a special occasion rice recipe from the north Indian state of Kashmir. Kashmiri Pulav is aromatic, mild and sweet. This rice is famous for using a huge assortment of fruits and dry fruits. Ingredients: 1 Tbsp. Ghee Peppercorn Cinnamon 2-3 Cloves 3 Cardamoms 1 Tsp. Fennel Seeds Onions 2 Tbsp. Milk Saffron Strands 2 and 1/2 cup of Boiled Rice Salt 1 Tbsp. Sugar 2 Tbsp. Cashewnuts 2 Tbsp. Raisins 1 Tbsp. Walnuts 1/2 Cup Apple 1/2 Cup Grapes Method: - Heat a tbsp. of ghee and add peppercorn, cinnamon, 2-3 Cloves, 3 Cardamoms, 1 Tsp. fennel seeds and the onions cut lengthwise. - Cook the onions till they are brown. - In 2 tbsp. of warm milk, soak few saffron strands. - Add 2 and 1/2 cup of boiled rice in the cooked onions, season it with salt and add the saffron soaked in milk to it. - Add 1 tbsp. of sugar to rice, mix it well and get the rice out of flame. - In 1 tbsp of ghee, add 2 tbsp. of cashewnuts, 2 tbsp. of raisins and 1 tbsp. of walnuts and cook them till the cashewnuts get a colour. - Then add 1/2 cup chopped apple pieces along with 1/2 cup chopped grapes and toss them. - Add the cooked fruits to the cooked rice and toss them together. - Garnish it with a few pomegranate seeds. - The Kashmiri Pulav is ready to be served.

1 461 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7458_04_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/Coa7W/220x123-iJ5.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7458-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7458_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:04:55">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x152dcb_mars-bar-rice-krispies-cakes-recipe_lifestyle</link><title>Mars Bar Rice Krispies Cakes Recipe</title><description>Mars Bar Rice Krispies Cakes Recipe

Toegevoegd door VideojugFoodandDrink laatste september

In this episode of Keep Calm And Bake Caroline MiLi Artiss shows you how to make Mars Bars Rice Krispies cakes.

992 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7458_05_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/Cdk2c/220x123-L3N.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7458-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7458_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:05:10">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1hzc9t_tawa-pulao-indian-rice-variety-spicy-maincourse-rice-recipe-by-ruchi-bharani_lifestyle</link><title>Tawa Pulao - Indian Rice Variety - Spicy Maincourse Rice Recipe By Ruchi Bharani</title><description>Tawa Pulao - Indian Rice Variety - Spicy Maincourse Rice Recipe By Ruchi Bharani

Toegevoegd door RajshriFood laatste maart

Ingredients: 2 tbsp butter 2 onions (cut lengthwise) 1.5 tbsp ginger garlic paste 1.5 green bell pepper 4 tomatoes (finely chopped) Coriander leaves (chopped) 2 tbsp pav bhaji masala Salt 2 green chillies (finely chopped) 1 tbsp water 1 cup boiled green peas 2 boiled potatoes (diced) 3 cups boiled rice Method: - Melt butter in a heated tava and add the onions. - Let the onions fry till its translucent and not brown. - Add ginger garlic paste and cook it - Add capsicum to it and saute them a bit - Add the tomatoes, coriander, pav bhaji masala, salt, green chillies, mix everything well and cook it till the tomatoes are absolutely soft - Add water and again mix well everything - Add green peas, potatoes and mix everything well - Add rice, coriander leaves, salt to the mixture and mix everything well and its ready to served hot. Director: Neha Sarkar Camera: Jay Nayak, Vaibhav Dhandha Editing: Ravi Varma Creative Head: Kavya Krishnaswamy Producer: Rajjat A. Barjatya Copyrights: Rajshri Entertainment Private Limited.

634 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7458_06_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/D7Kxd/220x123-Iuf.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7458-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7458_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:05:40">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xy89wu_masala-khichdi-indian-rice-recipe-by-ruchi-bharani-vegetarian-hd_lifestyle</link><title>Masala Khichdi - Indian Rice Recipe by Ruchi Bharani - Vegetarian [HD]</title><description>Masala Khichdi - Indian Rice Recipe by Ruchi Bharani - Vegetarian [HD]

Toegevoegd door RajshriFood vorig jaar

Masala Khichdi - Indian Rice Recipe by Ruchi Bharani - Vegatarian [HD] INGREDIENTS- 1/2 cup of moong daal 1/2 cup of rice 1 tomato finely chopped 1 onion finely chopped coriander leaves 1 cup mixed vegetables (potatoes, green peas, french beans) 2 tablespoons clarified butter (ghee) 1 teaspoon garlic paste 1 teaspoon red chilli powder 1/4 teaspoon turmeric powder 1 teaspoon garam masala 1/2 teaspoon black salt salt to taste dry red chilli 2 pieces of cloves 2 pieces of cinnamon 1 teaspoon cumin seeds METHOD- - Mix 1/2 cup of rice and 1/2 cup of moong dal together with 2 cups of water and 1/4 teaspoon of turmeric powder. Pressure cook it for 3-4 whistles. - Heat 1 and 1/2 tablespoons of clarified butter (ghee) in a round bottom pan. Once its hot, add cumin seeds, cinnamon, cloves and dry red chilli. After few seconds, add onions, coriander leaves, chopped tomatoes. Add all the spices - garam masala, red chilli powder. Add 1/2 teaspoon black salt and regular salt as per taste. Cook this till the tomatoes turn soft. - Add the pressure cooked rice and daal mixture. Add water and mix it well. Add all the mixed boiled vegetables. - Add water as required. Cover the pan and let the khichdi simmer for 5 minutes. - Garnish with coriander leaves. Serve hot with roasted papad and mango pickle.

2 214 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7458_07_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BOr5m/220x123-8ca.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7458-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7458_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:06:04">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x15ngq1_kheer-sweet-rice-pudding-navratri-special-indian-dessert-recipe-by-ruchi-bharani-hd_lifestyle</link><title>Kheer - Sweet Rice Pudding - Navratri Special Indian Dessert Recipe By Ruchi Bharani [HD]</title><description>Kheer - Sweet Rice Pudding - Navratri Special Indian Dessert Recipe By Ruchi Bharani [HD]

Toegevoegd door RajshriFood laatste oktober

Rice Kheer or Kheer is a very popular Indian recipe made on holy auspicious occasions. Serve your guests with this sweet rice pudding as a dessert. Learn how to make this simple and easy to make homemade quick rice kheer recipe.. Ingredients: 1 Ltr Milk 4 tbsp Rice 3/4 cup Sugar 2 tbsp Milk Masala Powder Method: - Heat the Milk in a pan till the water from the milk is removed. - Add the rice and cook it by stirring occasionally - Once the rice is cooked, add the sugar and milk masala powder. - Boil the whole mixture till it reduces a bit more. - The Rice kheer is ready to be served chilled by garnishing a bit with chopped almonds and cardamom powder.

1 491 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7458_08_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/Ckhvm/220x123-vFB.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7458-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7458_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:06:31">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x15n8ub_indian-food-recipe-ven-pongal-or-ghee-rice-online-cooking-india_lifestyle</link><title>Indian food recipe - Ven Pongal or Ghee Rice Online cooking India</title><description>Indian food recipe - Ven Pongal or Ghee Rice Online cooking India

Toegevoegd door IndianVideo laatste oktober

Ingredients Raw rice – 1 cup (175 grams) Green gram dhal – ½ cup (75 grams) Ghee – 3 tablespoons Refined oil – 3 tablespoons Cashew nuts – 10 grams Ginger – 1/4 inch piece (finely grated) Mustard seeds – 1 tea spoon Black gram – 1 tea spoon Cumin seed (jeera) – 1 teaspoon Black pepper – 1 teaspoon Curry leaves – 1 sprig Salt to taste For more details: http://www.indiavideo.org/tamil/cuisine/learn-cooking-ven-pongal-6357.php

760 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7458_09_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/CkdtU/220x123-_Ri.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7458-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7458_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 12:06:51">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x11ngx8_mangalorean-rice-bhakri-indian-roti-vegetarian-recipe-by-annuradha-toshniwal-hd_lifestyle</link><title>Mangalorean Rice Bhakri - Indian Roti - Vegetarian Recipe by Annuradha Toshniwal [HD]</title><description>Mangalorean Rice Bhakri - Indian Roti - Vegetarian Recipe by Annuradha Toshniwal [HD]

Toegevoegd door RajshriFood laatste juli

In this episode learn how to make Mangalorean Rice Bhakri, a traditional Indian Roti but not made out of wheat, instead it is made out of rice and which is quite popular in Southern India. Ingredients: 1 Cup Boiled Rice 1/2 Cup Grated Coconut 2 tbsp of Coriander 2 Chopped Green Chilies Oil Salt Method: - In a mixture churn the ingredients, rice, coconut, coriander, green chilies, salt and little water to make a dough. - Pour the mixture in a plate. - Grease banana leaves with oil . - Make balls out of the dough and place it on the banana leaves with the grease side up. - With a rolling fill gently roll it. Keep It little thick. - On a heated pan, place the whole thing on the pan and let it cook. - Turn the roti when one side of it is cooked well. - Plate it when both the side have been cooked and the bhakri is ready to be consumed. There is an alternative way to cook it as well: - After mixing all the ingredients and making a dough out of it. - Oil your hand and make a smaller ball out of the whole dough. - Gently press the rice mixture in between your hands to give it a thick yet nice round shape to it. - Put it on a heated pan and add some oil and cook it till light golden brown - Flip it and cook the other side as well by putting some more oil to it. - The Bhakri is ready to be served

1 126 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7458_10_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CB5Tc/220x123-xJG.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>