<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7477">china bird flu</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:16:36" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7477-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7477_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:16:37">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1aq8jd_china-bird-flu-leads-to-chicken-ban_news</link><title>China Bird Flu Leads To Chicken Ban</title><description>China Bird Flu Leads To Chicken Ban

Toegevoegd door Segment News laatste januari

The sale of live birds has been banned for three weeks in Hong Kong to stave off a wider spread of a new strain of bird flu. The strain, known as H7N9, was found in a Guangdong supplier. Poultry sellers expected large sales for Friday’s Lunar New Year and are now upset over the ban. http://dailyglobe.com/47697/bird-flu-concerns-leads-poultry-ban/

2 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7477_01_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/DfpXo/220x123-_HC.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7477-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7477_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:16:59">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1iaw0v_0319-cr-m04-china-reports-two-more-bird-flu-cases_news</link><title>(0319 CR M04) CHINA REPORTS TWO MORE BIRD FLU CASES</title><description>(0319 CR M04) CHINA REPORTS TWO MORE BIRD FLU CASES

Toegevoegd door tvnportal laatste maart

no descriptionVideo provided by Xinhua News Agency Producer : Xinhua News Agency

15 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7477_02_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/D7zE9/220x123-4y0.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7477-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7477_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:17:31">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1b9ew1_china-warns-of-deadly-new-mutant-bird-flu-strain_news</link><title>China warns of deadly new mutant bird flu strain</title><description>China warns of deadly new mutant bird flu strain

Toegevoegd door euronews-en laatste februari

China has issued a warning over a deadly new strain of bird flu that has claimed the life of one woman.The new virus, called H10N8, has so far infected two people – a fatal case in a 73-year-old and another in a woman who’s critically ill in hospital.Chen Ze, a researcher at Shanghai Institute of Biological Products said: “the virus can survive in low temperatures and therefore we need to increase our monitoring of poultry farms.”The fact that it has jumped from birds to humans is of great concern to researchers. Investigators say the dead woman had been at a live poultry market but no virus samples were found so the source of the infection remains unknown.Chinese scientists writing in The Lancet medical journal who conducted a genetic analysis on samples of the H10N8 virus from the woman who died said it was a new genetic reassortment of other strains of bird flu viruses, including one called H9N2that is relatively well known in poultry in China.

36 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7477_03_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DheQY/220x123-YiG.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7477-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7477_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:17:56">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1hrkwa_h10n8-bird-flu-virus-chinese-scientists-decipher-genetic-composition-of-new-strain_news</link><title>H10N8 bird flu virus: Chinese scientists decipher genetic composition of new strain</title><description>H10N8 bird flu virus: Chinese scientists decipher genetic composition of new strain

Toegevoegd door NMAtv laatste maart

Originally published on February 12, 2014------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------Chinese scientists released a report in the medical journal Lancet detailing the genetic composition of a new kind of H10N8 bird flu virus, a novel reassortant of previously reported H10N8 viruses.To date, two human cases of the new kind of H10N8 virus have been discovered in Nanchang, China. A 73-year-old woman died nine days after exhibiting influenza symptoms in December last year. The other patient, a woman aged 55, is now in stable condition. H10N8, just like other influenza viruses, consists of hemagglutinin protein, neuraminidase protein and internal genes. In the report published in Lancet", the research team discovered that the haemagglutinin gene of H10N8 virus, which allows the virus to latch onto a host cell, is most closely related to H10N3 virus, which was found in ducks in Hunan Province, China. H10N8's neuraminidase proteins, which enables the virus to leave the host cell and attack other cells, are highly similar to those of an H10N8 virus isolated from a mallard in Korea, and an H3N8 virus, which was detected among birds in Japan.The research showed that all six internal genes of the H10N8 virus closely resemble the H9N2 viruses that are circulating in poultry in China. The genes also carry PB2 proteins, which make adaptation to mammalian hosts easier.Though no evidence of human-to-human transmission has been found so far, scientists warn that its pandemic potential should not be underestimated.------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------Welcome to TomoNews, where we animate the most entertaining news on the internets. Come here for an animated look at viral headlines, US news, celebrity gossip, salacious scandals, dumb criminals and much more! Subscribe now for daily news animations that will knock your socks off. Check out our official website: http://us.tomonews.net/ For news that's fun and never boring, visit our channel:https://www.youtube.com/user/TomoNewsUSSubscribe to stay updated on all the top stories:http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=TomoNewsUSStay connected with us here:Facebook http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSTwitter @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSGoogle+ http://gplus.to/TomoNewsUSInstagram @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus

4 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7477_04_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/D6oUI/220x123-7Ou.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7477-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7477_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:18:13">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1f92xw_0307-cr-m05-t-wo-more-bird-flu-cases-in-s-china_news</link><title>(0307 CR M05)T WO MORE BIRD FLU CASES IN S CHINA</title><description>(0307 CR M05)T WO MORE BIRD FLU CASES IN S CHINA

Toegevoegd door tvnportal laatste maart

no descriptionVideo provided by Xinhua News Agency Producer : Xinhua News Agency

1 view</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7477_05_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/D1Mq4/220x123-d-c.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7477-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7477_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:18:34">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1a8h6w_china-reports-six-new-bird-flu-cases-live-poultry-trading-halted_news</link><title>China Reports Six New Bird Flu Cases Live Poultry Trading Halted</title><description>China Reports Six New Bird Flu Cases Live Poultry Trading Halted

Toegevoegd door tvnportal laatste januari

Video provided by Xinhua News Agency Producer : Xinhua News Agency

16 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7477_06_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DdPXn/220x123-yyr.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7477-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7477_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:18:53">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1oecpz_china-reports-first-human-case-of-h10n8-bird-flu_news</link><title>China reports first human case of H10N8 bird flu</title><description>China reports first human case of H10N8 bird flu

Toegevoegd door NMAtv een week geleden

Chinese health authorities on Wednesday confirmed the first human case of H10N8, a new strain of bird flu, in a previously unreported case involving an elderly woman in Jiangxi province who contracted H10N8 and died earlier this month.The 73-year-old woman had a history of visiting a local live poultry market in Jiangxi Province. She was admitted to a hospital on Nov. 30 with severe pneumonia and died of respiratory failure on Dec 6.People who had been in close contact with her are being temporarily monitored and so far are symptom-free.--------------------------------------------------------TomoNews is your daily source for top animated news. We've combined animation and video footage with a snarky personality to bring you the biggest and best stories from around the world. Check out our official website: http://us.tomonews.net/ For news that's fun and never boring, visit our channel:https://www.youtube.com/user/TomoNewsUS Subscribe to stay updated on all the top stories:http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=TomoNewsUS Stay connected with us here:Facebook http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSTwitter @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSGoogle+ http://gplus.to/TomoNewsUS

1 view</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7477_07_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/EOW1n/220x123-sd_.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7477-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7477_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:19:22">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1ai9fo_bird-flu-fears-in-china-lead-to-ban-on-poultry-trading_news</link><title>Bird flu fears in China lead to ban on poultry trading</title><description>Bird flu fears in China lead to ban on poultry trading

Toegevoegd door euronews-en laatste januari

A slaughter is underway in Hong Kong. Over 20,000 birds mostly chickens have been destroyed in a bid to stamp out the spread of the H7N9 strain of bird flu.Its is the first time the virus has been discovered in imported poultry in Hong Kong. Imports from the mainland have been banned and all live chicken sales suspended. The island’s wholesale market will remain closed for 21 days.Twenty people have died from the virus in mainland China this year and two in Hong Kong. The government order comes into effect two days before celebrations for the Chinese New Year. “It is contagious. It is very scary especially with the New Year approaching. The virus is no small matter,” said one shopper.Poultry sales in other regions of China have also been banned in advance of the New Year celebrations when millions travel to reunite with family. Many often carry live poultry on crowded trains and buses.The virus is highly contagious between birds but health officials say it cannot be transmitted human-to-human.

16 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7477_08_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/Dephu/220x123-lKN.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7477-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7477_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:19:37">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xz51ov_china-bird-flu-patient-recovers_news</link><title>China bird flu patient recovers</title><description>China bird flu patient recovers

Toegevoegd door reuters vorig jaar

Sixty-six-year old Yang leaves a Shanghai hospital in good health after recovering from a new strain of bird flu. The virus, known as H7N9 has claimed 17 lives in China, but this patient appears to have made a full recovery. He says he was coughing and sick when he went to hospital but feels much better after the treatment. The first two detected H7N9 patients in Beijing have also left hospital. Authorities have slaughtered thousands of birds and closed some live poultry markets to slow the rate of human infection. But many aspects of this new variety of bird flu remain a mystery, particularly whether the new strain is being transmitted between people. The World Health Organisation has said that a number of patients who have tested positive for H7N9 had no history of contact with poultry. China has warned that the number of infections - so far at 82 - could rise.

15 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7477_09_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/BXXuC/220x123-Jny.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7477-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7477_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:20:13">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xzg2bh_as-bird-flu-spreads-death-toll-rises-in-china_news</link><title>As Bird Flu Spreads, Death Toll Rises in China</title><description>As Bird Flu Spreads, Death Toll Rises in China

Toegevoegd door tvnportal laatste april

The virus' death toll stands at 24, with more than 100 infections.Powered by NewsLook.com Producer : Newsy

6 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7477_10_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BaTDU/220x123-mGZ.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>