<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7483">facebook paying?</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:38:55" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7483-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7483_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:38:56">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xwil3b_paying-for-facebook-posts-and-charlie-reveals-all-kiss-breakfast-takeaway_music</link><title>Paying for Facebook posts and Charlie reveals all - Kiss Breakfast Takeaway</title><description>Paying for Facebook posts and Charlie reveals all - Kiss Breakfast Takeaway

Toegevoegd door KissFMUK vorig jaar

On today's Kiss Breakfast Takeaway, we're talking large-scale pranks, Rickie's using Facebook for evil and Charlie makes an announcement! Plus there's your chance to win a brand new Blackberry Curve 9320http://www.facebook.com/kissfmuk

82 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7483_01_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BBQfq/220x123-MAS.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7483-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7483_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:39:12">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xtlchn_get-paid-online-by-using-facebook-100-true-legit-paying_webcam</link><title>Get PAID ONLINE by USING FACEBOOK, 100% TRUE LEGIT PAYING</title><description>Get PAID ONLINE by USING FACEBOOK, 100% TRUE LEGIT PAYING

Toegevoegd door Marjun Yara vorig jaar

Contact us on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/swaccompanyJoin our group: http://www.facebook.com/groups/SWACGLOBALGROUP/After this video and you want to JOIN:Join here--&gt; http://generalkuya.swaultimate.com/

990 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7483_02_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/AQEqZ/220x123-_hr.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7483-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7483_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:39:37">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xqvtz6_gm-says-it-will-stop-paying-for-ads-on-facebook_news</link><title>GM Says It Will Stop Paying for Ads on Facebook</title><description>GM Says It Will Stop Paying for Ads on Facebook

Toegevoegd door associatedpress vorig jaar

General Motors said it would abandon Facebook ads after concluding they were ineffective. The announcement comes as the social network said it would add 84 million shares, worth up to $3.2 billion, to the company's IPO. (May 16)Copyright 2012 The Associated Press

7 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7483_03_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/AVY-n/220x123-KK_.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7483-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7483_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:39:55">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xqees6_searching-for-work-from-home-positions-or-employment-consider-high-paying-facebook-or-twitter-jobs_lifestyle</link><title>Searching for work from home positions or employment? Consider high paying Facebook or Twitter jobs!</title><description>Searching for work from home positions or employment? Consider high paying Facebook or Twitter jobs!

Toegevoegd door greatwebinfo vorig jaar

http://yupurl.com/socialmediajobsAre you looking for work from home positions or work from home employment? You should consider going for high paying Facebook or Twitter jobs.Companies are presently hiring people worldwide for a wide range of Facebook and Twitter jobs, so if you would like to get paid to spend time on Facebook and Twitter hurry and sign up now! Most of these jobs don’t require any prior experience and the only skills you need are a good knowledge of how to use Facebook or Twitter. Positions are filling fast. Click the link below to get started:http://yupurl.com/socialmediajobs

27 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7483_04_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/ATKDm/220x123-UP8.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7483-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7483_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:40:16">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xqfjy5_looking-for-social-media-careers-or-social-networking-jobs-go-for-high-paying-facebook-or-twitter-jo_lifestyle</link><title>Looking for social media careers or social networking jobs? Go for high paying Facebook or Twitter jobs!</title><description>Looking for social media careers or social networking jobs? Go for high paying Facebook or Twitter jobs!

Toegevoegd door greatwebinfo vorig jaar

http://yupurl.com/socialmediajobsAre you looking for social media careers or social networking jobs? Looking for social media marketing jobs? You should consider going for high paying Facebook or Twitter jobs instead.Companies are presently hiring people around the world for a wide range of Facebook and Twitter jobs, as such if you would like to get paid to spend time on Facebook and Twitter hurry and sign up now. Most of these jobs don’t require any prior experience. The only skills you need are a good knowledge of how to use Facebook or Twitter. Positions are filling fast. Click the link below to get started:http://yupurl.com/socialmediajobs

15 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7483_05_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/ARV_G/220x123-uIP.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7483-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7483_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:40:40">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xmtdot_why-paying-for-facebook-likes-to-drive-traffic-is-a-bad-idea_news</link><title>Why Paying for Facebook Likes to Drive Traffic is a Bad Idea</title><description>Why Paying for Facebook Likes to Drive Traffic is a Bad Idea

Toegevoegd door Tonya 2 jaren geleden

http://savvybizbuilder.com/2011/11/why-paying-for-facebook-likes-drive-traffic-bad-idea.html5 Reasons why paying cash for Facebook “Likes” will not continuously drive trafficFollow me on Twitter:http://twitter.com/savvybizbuilderFind me on Facebook:http://www.facebook.com/SavvyBizBuilder

27 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7483_06_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/s7ps/220x123-4Cj.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7483-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7483_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:40:58">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xjgqzc_are-you-tired-of-paying-for-facebook-credits_lifestyle</link><title>Are You Tired Of Paying For Facebook Credits?</title><description>Are You Tired Of Paying For Facebook Credits?

Toegevoegd door getfreething 2 jaren geleden

http://howtogetfreefacebookcredits.info Are you tired of paying for facebook credits and looking for ways to get free facebook credits? Most importantly, are you wondering how to get free facebook credits legally but easily? Recently, I've found a way! It suits all the criteria above and it's 100% legitimate. Visit my website to learn more!

103 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7483_07_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/AEWHX/220x123-Xol.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7483-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7483_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:41:24">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1cqhko_facebook-to-pay-19-billion-for-whatsapp_news</link><title>Facebook to Pay $19 Billion for WhatsApp</title><description>Facebook to Pay $19 Billion for WhatsApp

Toegevoegd door WSJ Live laatste februari

Facebook's $19 billion purchase of the WhatsApp mobile messaging service ranks as the largest-ever purchase of a company backed by venture capital. WSJ's Reed Albergotti reports. (Photo: AP) Copyright 2014, Dow Jones &amp; Company, Inc.

246 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7483_08_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DrxLB/220x123-FxP.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7483-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7483_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:41:49">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1k1i24_minnesota-school-pays-student-70k-after-facebook-incident_travel</link><title>Minnesota School Pays Student $70K after Facebook Incident</title><description>Minnesota School Pays Student $70K after Facebook Incident

Toegevoegd door Geo Beats 4 weken geleden

A school in Minnesota has agreed to pay one of its students 70 thousand dollars after forcing her to surrender her Facebook password. A school in Minnesota has agreed to pay one of its students 70 thousand dollars after forcing her to surrender her Facebook password.The incident happened in 2011, when Riley Stratton was 13 and in the 6th grade. It started after she made a disparaging comment about a hall monitor on the social media site and was called to the principal’s office and suspended. Soon after, she got back on Facebook and tried to find who had told on her, as she had made the comment while off of the school’s grounds. She was again called to the office, but this time there was also a deputy sheriff in the room. It was demanded that she grant them access to her Facebook page immediately.The ACLU took on the matter, and recently they and the school reached the agreement. Said the newly appointed superintendent of the school, “We'll be certainly much more cautious about punishing people for things they say off-campus outside of school time.”

253 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7483_09_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/EA1Kg/220x123-n-2.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7483-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7483_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:42:13">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1exqjr_facebook-will-pay-200-000-for-a-public-police-officer_travel</link><title>Facebook Will Pay $200,000 for a Public Police Officer</title><description>Facebook Will Pay $200,000 for a Public Police Officer

Toegevoegd door Geo Beats laatste maart

It was recently announced that Facebook will soon be funding the addition of a beat cop who will work near the company’s headquarters in Menlo Park. It was recently announced that Facebook will soon be funding the addition of a beat cop who will work near the company’s headquarters in Menlo Park. In doing so, Facebook will become the very first private company in the US to pay for a 40 hour per week officer. Many people are happy about the decision and think the move will create a new model for corporate community involvement. However there are others in a different camp who aren’t in favor of Facebook hiring a publicly paid official. Despite the conflicting opinions, Facebook’s offer to fund an additional police officer for the neighborhood where its headquarters is located was approved. The Menlo Park City Council approved the company’s offer of 200 grand a year for what they call a ‘community safety police officer’. The beat cop will work out of a nearby substation and have numerous duties including planning security measures and safety drills for nearby school campuses. He or she will also be responsible for gathering information on gangs and drugs. Last year, two Facebook employees went to the police department and offered to pay for an officer after learning the city was having problems with crime and needed additional help.Menlo Park Police Commander Dave Bertini commented ‘They are bending over backwards to be good neighbors. There is no quid pro quo here.’

107 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7483_10_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/D0fat/220x123-yKs.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>