<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7484">earthquake</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:42:36" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7484-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7484_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:42:36">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1r71d2_earthquake-in-various-cities-of-punjab_news</link><title>Earthquake in various cities of Punjab</title><description>Earthquake in various cities of Punjab

Toegevoegd door Abb Takk gisteren

Abbtakk.tv delivers the latest headlines news and information on the latest top stories from Pakistan and around the world on weather, business, entertainment, politics, sports and more.For in-depth analysis on news visit website OR watch abbtakk at live.abbtakk.tv

44 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7484_01_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/EcNPO/220x123-UEb.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7484-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7484_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:42:53">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1pezol_powerful-earthquake-rattles-mexico-shakes-buildings_news</link><title>Powerful earthquake rattles Mexico, shakes buildings</title><description>Powerful earthquake rattles Mexico, shakes buildings

Toegevoegd door reuters een week geleden

ROUGH CUT (NO REPORTER NARRATION) A powerful earthquake struck Mexico on Friday (April 18), shaking buildings in the capital and sending people running out into the street, although there were no early reports of major damage. The magnitude 7.2 quake was centered in the southwestern state of Guerrero, close to the Pacific beach resort of Acapulco, the U.S. Geological Survey (USGS) said. Some residents of the capital ran outdoors in their pajamas after the quake. Electricity was cut off in parts of the city and some residents said paintings fell off the walls and small parts of masonry crumbled inside apartment buildings. The Mexican government's emergency services said there were no immediate reports of damage and the U.S. Pacific Warning Center said it did not expect the quake to trigger a destructive tsunami. Nevertheless, residents of the capital were shaken by the quake, one of the biggest to hit Mexico in several years. The USGS said the quake w

850 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7484_02_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/ESwXi/220x123-AU4.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7484-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7484_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:43:15">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1pgy0f_powerful-earthquake-rattles-mexico-shakes-buildings_news</link><title>Powerful earthquake rattles Mexico, shakes buildings</title><description>Powerful earthquake rattles Mexico, shakes buildings

Toegevoegd door reuters een week geleden

This Mexican news station was in the middle of a live broadcast on Friday when a powerful earthquake hit. The 7.2 magnitude quake rattled buildings in the capitol Mexico City, sending people running into the streets. (SOUNDBITE) (Spanish) CALL CENTER EMPLOYEE, DAMIANA DURAN SAYING: "It felt horrible. I waited a while to see if the earthquake would pass, but it didn't. I work in a call center and we have pipes above us and they were moving like crazy. We all thought the building was going to collapse." The relatively shallow quake was centered in the southwestern state of Guerrero, close to the Pacific beach resort of Acapulco. Electricity was cut off in parts of the capitol but there were no early reports of major damage. Still, residents of the capital were shaken. A devastating 8.1-magnitude earthquake in 1985 killed thousands of people in Mexico City. Friday's relatively shallow quake was one of the biggest tremblers to hit the country

271 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7484_03_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/ETBdF/220x123-30W.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7484-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7484_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:43:32">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1prsxe_earthquake-strikes-off-papua-new-guinea_news</link><title>Earthquake Strikes Off Papua New Guinea</title><description>Earthquake Strikes Off Papua New Guinea

Toegevoegd door wochit vorig zaterdag

The U.S. Geological Survey says an earthquake struck late Saturday off Papua New Guinea's eastern coast with a preliminary magnitude of 7.5.The quake struck at 11:27 p.m. local time, 9:27 a.m. eastern and occurred at a depth of 19 miles.It was centered 47 miles southwest of Panguna, Papua New Guinea.After the quake, the Pacific Tsunami Warning Center issued a tsunami warning for Papua New Guinea and the Solomon Islands, but then canceled it.

21 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7484_04_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/EUVP8/220x123-irr.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7484-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7484_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:43:51">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1pg6qj_timelapse-video-7-2-earthquake-rattles-mexico-city_news</link><title>Timelapse Video: 7.2 Earthquake Rattles Mexico City</title><description>Timelapse Video: 7.2 Earthquake Rattles Mexico City

Toegevoegd door WSJ Live een week geleden

Buildings were evacuated in Mexico City on Friday following a magnitude 7.2 earthquake. In this timelapse video, the Monumento de Revolucion is rattled by the tremors. (Photo/Video: YouTube / WebcamsdeMexico) Copyright 2014, Dow Jones &amp; Company, Inc.

30 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7484_05_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/ES6dx/220x123-mSt.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7484-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7484_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:44:21">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1pnavq_0419-wn-m01-mexico-earthquake_news</link><title>(0419 WN M01) MEXICO EARTHQUAKE</title><description>(0419 WN M01) MEXICO EARTHQUAKE

Toegevoegd door tvnportal een week geleden

no descriptionVideo provided by Xinhua News Agency Producer : Xinhua News Agency

27 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7484_06_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/ETzlP/220x123-N7t.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7484-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7484_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:44:41">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1pmn6n_magnitude-7-2-earthquake-shakes-mexican-capital_news</link><title>Magnitude-7.2 Earthquake Shakes Mexican Capital</title><description>Magnitude-7.2 Earthquake Shakes Mexican Capital

Toegevoegd door wochit een week geleden

A powerful magnitude-7.2 earthquake shook central and southern Mexico on Friday, sending panicked people into the streets. Some walls cracked and fell, but there were no reports of major damage or casualties. The U.S. Geological Survey said the quake was centered on a long-dormant fault line northwest of the Pacific resort of Acapulco, where many Mexicans are vacationing for the Easter holiday.

3 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7484_07_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/ETreX/220x123-BtF.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7484-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7484_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:45:13">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1qleic_protesters-in-city-of-lquique-urge-govt-to-move-camps-set-up-after-earthquake_news</link><title>Protesters in city of lquique urge govt. to move camps set up after earthquake</title><description>Protesters in city of lquique urge govt. to move camps set up after earthquake

Toegevoegd door PressTV vorig dinsdag

Residents in a northern Chilean city take to the streets to protest against emergency camps set up by the government to house those affected by an earthquake. The protesters in the coastal city of lquique blocked one of the main roads with burning barricades. They called on the government to move the camps which they say pose health risks. Protesters say the camps have been installed without their prior approval or consultations. A powerful 8-point-2 magnitude quake and aftershocks hit the coastal city in early April, causing widespread damage to thousands of homes. Authorities say they need months before they can help the local population with reconstruction.

4 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7484_08_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/EYOR-/220x123-n4E.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7484-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7484_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:45:44">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1pfont_7-5-magnitude-earthquake-strikes-in-mexico_news</link><title>7.5-Magnitude Earthquake Strikes In Mexico</title><description>7.5-Magnitude Earthquake Strikes In Mexico

Toegevoegd door wochit een week geleden

A powerful 7.5-magnitude earthquake struck Mexico Friday morning. There was no immediate information on damage or injuries. The quake struck around 10:28 a.m. ET, 39 kilometers east of Petatlan, Mexico, in Guerrero state, north of the resort city Acapulco, the United States Geological Survey said. It was strong enough to shake central and southern Mexico.

8 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7484_09_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/ES3KS/220x123-M40.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7484-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7484_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 13:46:04">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1oa8lm_6-1-magnitude-earthquake-strikes-nicaragua_news</link><title>6.1 Magnitude Earthquake Strikes Nicaragua</title><description>6.1 Magnitude Earthquake Strikes Nicaragua

Toegevoegd door NewsyVideos een week geleden

Another earthquake has hit a country along the Pacific Rim. This time, in Nicaragua — where a strong, 6.1 magnitude earthquake hit Thursday.

40 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7484_10_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/EN_wx/220x123-Nyl.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>