<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7498">syria chemical weapons</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:33:23" name="Dailymotion" id="FW14-e021"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e021-7498-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7498_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:33:24">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xyct74_obama-warns-syria-over-chemical-weapons_news</link><title>Obama warns Syria over chemical weapons</title><description>Obama warns Syria over chemical weapons

Toegevoegd door Euronews vorig jaar

Barack Obama says the United States is investigating whether chemical weapons have been used in Syria - and has warned that the regime will be held responsible if they have....http://www.euronews.net/

57 383 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7498_01_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/BP3D6/220x123-Svs.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7498-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7498_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:33:40">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x15fnq5_team-arrives-in-syria-to-dismantle-chemical-weapons_news</link><title>Team Arrives in Syria to Dismantle Chemical Weapons</title><description>Team Arrives in Syria to Dismantle Chemical Weapons

Toegevoegd door NewsyVideos laatste oktober

The first step in disarming some of Syria's chemical weapons began Tuesday, as a team of engineers and researchers arrived in Damascus.

15 705 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7498_02_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/CiEcC/220x123-3qc.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7498-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7498_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:33:55">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x16nam8_syria-meets-deadline-to-destroy-chemical-weapons-equipment_news</link><title>Syria meets deadline to destroy chemical weapons equipment</title><description>Syria meets deadline to destroy chemical weapons equipment

Toegevoegd door reuters laatste oktober

The Organisation for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons says Syria has destroyed all of its declared equipment for producing chemical weapons. Spokesman Michael Luhan: SOUNDBITE: Michael Luhan, Spokesman, Organisation for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons "The Syrian government has completed what we call the 'functional destruction' of its entire chemical weapons-making apparatus and water mixing filling equipment for use for sarin gas, so it no longer has the capacity to manufacture new chemical weapons agents," The organization said its teams had inspected 21 out of 23 chemical weapons sites across the war-torn country. The other two were too dangerous to reach - but - reportedly - the chemical equipment had been moved to other sites already. Inspectors were sent to Syria after allegations the government used chemical weapons on its people - and the U.S. threatened to retaliate with force. Reaching this milestone means Syria has reached a

532 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7498_03_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/Cwm0i/220x123-jfH.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7498-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7498_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:34:14">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xzgsw1_obama-evidence-chemical-weapons-used-in-syria-a-game_news</link><title>Obama: Evidence chemical weapons used in Syria a 'game...</title><description>Obama: Evidence chemical weapons used in Syria a 'game...

Toegevoegd door Euronews laatste april

President Barack Obama has confirmed evidence of chemical weapons being used in Syria. However, questions remain over their exact usage.During a briefing for reporters, the US leader reiterated his position to not make any hasty decisions without being absolutely sure of the facts....http://www.euronews.net/

1 816 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7498_04_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/Bae5M/220x123-Hac.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7498-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7498_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:34:32">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xybmi3_syria-accusations-fly-over-chemical-weapons-attack_news</link><title>Syria: accusations fly over 'chemical weapons' attack</title><description>Syria: accusations fly over 'chemical weapons' attack

Toegevoegd door Euronews vorig jaar

Accusations are flying in Syria over whether a chemical weapon has been used and who is to blame.The government of President Bashar al-Assad says rebel forces fired a rocket loaded with chemical agents in Aleppo province, killing at least 26 people and injuring dozens more. State television later raised the death toll to 25 people....http://www.euronews.net/

1 482 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7498_05_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/BPiRI/220x123-_EE.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7498-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7498_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:34:49">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1435qy_evidence-syrian-rebels-used-chemical-weapons_news</link><title>Evidence_ Syrian Rebels used Chemical Weapons</title><description>Evidence_ Syrian Rebels used Chemical Weapons

Toegevoegd door Awaz Today laatste september

699 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7498_06_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/CVpB8/220x123-oO9.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7498-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7498_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:35:12">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x13gzfj_chemical-weapons-expert-comments-on-syria-gas-attack_news</link><title>Chemical weapons expert comments on Syria gas attack</title><description>Chemical weapons expert comments on Syria gas attack

Toegevoegd door Zoomin.TV Canada laatste augustus

Activist videos claiming to show the effects of a chemical weapons attack in Syria on Wednesday appear to show people with symptoms "consistent with some kind of trauma to the nervous system", a British expert has said.

741 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7498_07_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/CRSs0/220x123-bdO.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7498-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7498_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:35:27">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x1qm7va_fears-of-chemical-weapons-attacks-in-syria_news</link><title>Fears of chemical weapons attacks in Syria</title><description>Fears of chemical weapons attacks in Syria

Toegevoegd door reuters vorig dinsdag

\--STORY CONTAINS GRAPHIC IMAGES -- A man gasping for his breath seeks help amid reports that chemical weapons have been unleashed in Syria again. The video, which can not be independently verified by Reuters, appears to show children among the wounded in Idlib province, in a war that has already cost the lives of more than 150,000 people. Swathes of Idlib province are in the hands of various rebel groups and attacks in rebel-held areas are blamed on President Bashar al-Assad's forces by the opposition. The U.S. says there are indications a toxic chemical, probably chlorine, was used in a rebel-held area in Hama province mid-April shown here. That incident was reported both by Syrian rebels and the government -- with each side blaming the other. If proven, Chlorine gas attacks expose a major loophole in an international deal which promised to remove chemical weapons from Syria. It also suggests chemical warfare could persist after the removal operatio

152 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7498_08_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/EYVvt/220x123-yOl.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7498-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7498_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:35:49">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x18dkxa_syrian-chemical-weapons-disposal-plan_news</link><title>Syrian Chemical Weapons Disposal Plan</title><description>Syrian Chemical Weapons Disposal Plan

Toegevoegd door tvnportal laatste december

no descriptionPowered by NewsLook.com Producer : Xinhua News Agency

247 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7498_09_thumb.jpg">http://s2.dmcdn.net/DN3eI/220x123-Z_x.jpg</thumb></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e021-7498-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7498_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-26 14:36:17">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x19cwcc_syria-ships-out-first-batch-of-chemical-weapons-materials_news</link><title>Syria ships out first batch of chemical weapons materials</title><description>Syria ships out first batch of chemical weapons materials

Toegevoegd door reuters laatste januari

These ships are part of the flotilla that's been waiting to remove chemical weapons from Syria. On Tuesday, the United Nations announced the first batch of the most deadly toxins -- nine containers in all -- was moved out of the country for destruction. (SOUNDBITE) (English) FARHAN HAQ, ACTING DEPUTY SPOKESPERSON FOR SECRETARY-GENERAL, SAYING: "An initial quantity of priority chemical materials was moved from two sites to the port of Lattakia in Syria for verification and was then loaded onto a Danish cargo ship... This movement initiates the process of transfer of chemical materials from Syria to locations outside its territory for destruction." Their transfer comes two weeks before planned peace talks in Geneva over Syria's 21/2 year long civil war. Also on Tuesday, Syria's Information Minister said Damascus insisted that any agreement allows President Bashar al-Assad to remain in power. (SOUNDBITE) (Arabic) SYRIAN INFORMATION MINISTER, OMRAN ZOABI

124 views</description><thumb cache="FW14-topics-docs/e021/7498_10_thumb.jpg">http://s1.dmcdn.net/DY3hg/220x123-k8L.jpg</thumb></snippet></snippets></search_results>