<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7014">Asian culture</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:47:59" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7014-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7014_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:47:59">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=698987#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Hwangbo turns ambassador after North Korea escape</title><description>in North Korea. The country's gymnastics team was banned from the 2012 London Olympics for age falsification, but North Korean gymnasts are a major part of the local culture. Thousands perform in complex routines at the annual Arirang Festival. The intricate routines pay tribute to Korean history while functioning as an over-the-top homage to the supreme leaders. It appeared Young might have a future...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7014-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7014_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:49:15">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=538322#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>2010-11 Asia League regular season underway</title><description>and cohesive group of import players, combined with a smattering of high-skill native Korean talent and supplemented by a hard-working group of Korean role players. In assembling its foreign contingent, the club identified former North American professional players who would be willing to fit in with the Korean culture while bringing their skills to the club for more than one season. The approach has worked...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7014-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7014_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:52:51">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=520432#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Plante stands tall as Rochester Americans blank Toronto Marlies 1-0</title><description>to preserve the win and the shutout. Notes: The Marlies celebrated South Asian Culture Night at the game. ... Rochester is undefeated against Toronto this season. ... The teams combined for 11 minor penalties in the second period. ... The two teams will meet three more times this season....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7014-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7014_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:53:32">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=436499#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Japanese hockey says goodbye to most famous team</title><description>In most of Japan, hockey is a minor sport. Although many of the game's strategies and traditions seem tailor-made to Japanese culture, hockey has only really taken off on the northernmost island of Hokkaido. Nevertheless Japanese hockey has a much longer tradition than most Westerners realize. Several modern-day professional teams trace their origins back 60 or even 80-plus years. The recently...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7014-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7014_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 22:57:31">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=377919#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>CBC targets Chinese hockey fans with Mandarin broadcasts of NHL playoffs</title><description>it's no easy task. "Especially in hockey, where Chinese culture doesn't have a context for it, so I have to translate a lot of the terms, all the penalty calls, and sometimes I have to borrow from other sports," says Wang, sitting in the small recording booth at the CBC building in Vancouver where he calls the games while watching them on a large TV. "I have an entire list of penalty translations...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7014-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7014_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:01:08">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=371001#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Former NHLers find hockey adventure in Japan</title><description>, Hokkaido. The clubs, which derive their names from the companies that own and sponsor them, have lengthy hockey histories. In most of Japan, hockey is a minor sport. Although many of the game's strategies and traditions seem tailor-made to Japanese culture, hockey trails far behind baseball and soccer in popularity. Japanese hockey reflects the culture of the country, which has worked to the advantage...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>