<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7024">reinforcement learning</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:38:42" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7024-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7024_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:38:43">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=629429#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>MacLean has transformed Senators in first season</title><description>In his first season as coach of the Ottawa Senators, Paul MacLean developed a reputation as a player's coach, someone who preferred positive reinforcement over constant criticism. But through the first 10 days of the Stanley Cup Playoffs, MacLean was showing his stern, more serious side in dealing with the media. He kept his answers short and wasn't eager to divulge information on his players...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7024-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7024_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:43:16">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=414241#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Pacific: Nabokov returns, plays like his old self</title><description>." Getting some reinforcement back this week sure wouldn't hurt. Getting a good look -- Defenseman Dmitri Kalinin was among the players obtained by Phoenix GM Don Maloney in his deadline-day trades. The Coyotes are making sure they take a good look at the 28-year-old impending free agent in the final weeks of the season. Kalinin, who came from the New York Rangers with forwards Nigel Dawes and Petr...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7024-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7024_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:47:42">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=370474#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Dazzling Schremp works to make his game complete</title><description>Ever since he first put a puck on a string, second-year Springfield forward Rob Schremp’s skills have cried out for attention. Like most players, he loved it when the reinforcement was positive, which it almost always was. The real sign of Schremp’s evolution as a prospect, however, is coming this season as he smiles in the face of harsher assessment. He nods his head when Edmonton points out...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7024-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7024_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-19 23:48:26">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=369394#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Nash aims to take his game to the next level</title><description>by five losses." Consistency is often a young player’s bugaboo. But Nash, now 23, showed down the stretch that he was becoming more mentally tough. Though Nash has tasted the bad aspects — losses, frustration and injuries — at points in each of his first four NHL seasons, last season was more of a learning experience than any of the others. "It was sort of defined by two parts — since Ken Hitchcock...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>