<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7031">Thomas test</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:21:33" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7031-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7031_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:21:34">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=714559#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>NHL Capsules</title><description>NEWARK, N.J. - Martin Brodeur made 16 saves in what might have been his last start in a 20-year career with the Devils, and New Jersey beat Boston 3-2 on Sunday as the Bruins rested many of their stars in preparation for the playoffs. The soon-to-be 42-year-old Brodeur is in the final year of his contract and is likely to test the free-agent market now that he has become the backup to Cory...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7031-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7031_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:23:29">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=27976#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Kings a win away from clinching playoff spot</title><description>. We're in a month where we want to prepare ourselves and work on our game to get ready for the playoffs. I don't think there's any better test when a desperate team comes in [and] fights for the playoffs. For us, we've got to be ready for that intensity and that emotion they're going to bring. I'm sure it's going to be a fun game." The Coyotes, who lost 2-1 in a shootout to the Winnipeg Jets...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7031-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7031_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:26:14">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=27822#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Coyotes' Smith to be re-evaluated next week</title><description>GLENDALE, Ariz. -- Phoenix Coyotes goalie Mike Smith won't be on the ice to test his lower-body injury until at least the end of next week, but coach Dave Tippett is hoping he will be able to return to the lineup before the end of the regular season. Smith, who was injured late in a 4-3 overtime loss to the New York Rangers on Monday, is back to working out off the ice and will have his injury...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7031-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7031_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:27:07">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=27144#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>In need of win, Lightning expect test from Panthers</title><description>Horachek will start Dan Ellis in goal. Ellis, acquired in a trade for Tim Thomas, will make his first start with the Panthers. "There are back-to-back games and Roberto Luongo is not going to play every game," Horachek said. "There is a home game [Friday], so maybe it was a good place for [Ellis] to go back in. He's going to play some games down the stretch, so we have to pick some games...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7031-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7031_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:29:26">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=27035#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Young D-men thrust into Bruins-Canadiens rivalry</title><description>that they were impressed with him out of camp, but they felt he needed some more time. So they sent him down to Hamilton of the American Hockey League. Now they've recalled him and he's looking really good. He'll get a big test from the division rival Bruins. His arrival couldn't have come at a better time now that another Canadiens defenseman, Josh Gorges, is out until the end of the regular season...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7031-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7031_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:33:19">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=708058#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Canadiens make bold move trading for Vanek</title><description>Wednesday, forward Thomas Vanek from the New York Islanders, in a trade for forward prospect Sebastian Collberg and a conditional second-round pick in the 2014 NHL Draft. The Islanders announced they get the second-round pick only if the Canadiens make the Stanley Cup Playoffs this season, in which case New York's fifth-round pick in 2014 will go to Montreal. "For me, it's a message that Marc gives...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7031-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7031_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:37:50">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=707409#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Islanders' pair understands likelihood of trade</title><description>MacDonald and left wing Thomas Vanek before the deadline. MacDonald has 24 points (four goals, 20 assists) in 63 games this season and is averaging 25:25 of ice time per game, tops on the club. "This is the only organization that I've been with," said MacDonald, who was drafted in the sixth round (No. 160) by the Islanders in 2006 and worked his way up from the ECHL. "I've actually had Jack every year...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7031-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7031_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:41:23">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=26616#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Capitals' Green, Grabovski in; Johansson uncertain</title><description>at it on a bad day." For Olympic and Capitals teammate Nicklas Backstrom, the game against Florida represents an opportunity to put behind a disappointing finish in Sochi. Backstrom missed the gold-medal game against Canada because of a failed doping-control test, which he said was the result of taking allergy medicine. "Everything has been said," Backstrom said Thursday. "Right now, I'm just looking forward...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7031-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7031_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:42:04">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=706225#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Rivalry Night Faceoff: Smith vs. Hodgson</title><description>goals and 19 assists while playing all 48 games. A rough start to the 2013-14 season has led to many changes in Buffalo, including a new team president, general manager and coach. Talented forward Thomas Vanek was traded to the New York Islanders in October and Ted Nolan was hired on an interim basis to replace Ron Rolston as coach in November. Hodgson, though, has taken all of the changes in stride...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7031-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7031_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 00:43:00">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=25626#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Visnovsky back for Isles; Nabokov to dress</title><description>. He's ready to go. Obviously it's about the pace of the game and the big bodies Boston has. He's going to see right away. But there's no better time than now. He's been waiting, he’s been working hard, and no matter who we're playing against it's going to be a little bit of a test for him." Visnovsky said he is eager to get back and provide some help to a team that's scrambling to get back...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>