<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7044">song of ice and fire</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:07:17" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7044-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7044_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:07:18">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=696567#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Zac Brown Band leads Winter Classic entertainment</title><description>; the announcement of the rosters for the 2014 U.S. Olympic men's and women's ice hockey teams; a flyover of North American Aerospace Defense Command (NORAD) CF-18 fighter jets and a Canada-United States color guard; and appearances by Ann Arbor and Detroit-area youth hockey players. The entertainment for the 2014 Bridgestone NHL Winter Classic®, 2014 Coors Light NHL Stadium Series™ and 2014 Tim Hortons NHL...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7044-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7044_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:12:12">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=585458#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Summer with Stanley 2011 blog: First 10 days</title><description>for allowing us to share with them their day with the Cup. Truly a wonderful experience. To see all videos of for the European Tour be sure to check out NHL.com. \-- Paul Vinciguerra Four hours later, Savonlinna celebrates with Rask 07.24.2011 / 12:20 PM ET After four hours on the road and a switch in cars (from a bus to a Chevy Impala), we finally arrived at the Savonlinna Ice Rink in Tuukka Rask...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7044-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7044_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:14:26">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=585197#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Summer with Stanley 2011 blog</title><description>and a switch in cars (from a bus to a Chevy Impala), we finally arrived at the Savonlinna Ice Rink in Tuukka Rask's hometown. Upon arrival, Rask is greeted warmly by several hundred people that have been waiting for him and the Stanley Cup. Rask is scheduled to spend around an hour here before his private party with his family starts. More later... \-- Paul Vinciguerra Cup arrives in Finland, Rask's day...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7044-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7044_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:17:42">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=559733#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Boston vs. Montreal live blog</title><description>Gomez, set up Gionta for a gimme as both D for Boston were out of position. First period starts 7:06 p.m. We are just a few minutes from faceoff now. Both teams are on the ice and the pregame video is done. by the way, it is the third AC/DC song of the night, Thunderstruck. Thanks to PR guru John Dellapina, who made a dinner run for me, I am now fully fortified to document the game. The scratches...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7044-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7044_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:22:24">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=534054#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Stanley Cup tour blog</title><description>and handed it back. Buffett then handed Kane a tambourine and the Hawks' 21-year-old star played along with the band while dancing around the stage and kicking beach balls into the crowd.  Kane said it "was just a huge rush being on stage. The crowd was on fire." When the song ended, Kane raised the Cup one more time and the crowd erupted for a full minute before Kane finally left the stage. He watched...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7044-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7044_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:24:51">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=535976#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Thanks to Kane, Stanley's visit to Buffalo resonates</title><description>BUFFALO, N.Y. -- Moments after the puck fluttered off his stick and Patrick Kane started acting like the only crazed lunatic on the ice, there was an elderly man sitting in his customary spot inside his South Buffalo home who in that moment, that split second on June 9, 2010, may have been the only other person in the world to know why No. 88 in white was whooping it up. Even with 83-year...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7044-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7044_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:26:08">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=530178#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Cup Final blog: Blackhawks-Flyers</title><description>:09 a.m. ET Celebrating a championship on the Wachovia Center ice is nothing new for Patrick Sharp and Ben Eager. "I've won two championships and they've both been on this ice," said Sharp. Before last night, he and Eager won the 2005 Calder Cup, beating a team from Chicago – the Wolves, the Atlanta Thrashers' AHL team – in the finals. "I owe the Flyers a lot," said Sharp. "They've done a heck...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7044-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7044_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:28:35">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=527614#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Bruins vs. Flyers blog</title><description>for it and be excited for it. Nobody knows what's going to happen tonight, but the one thing I know is I just want to leave it all out on the ice." The Flyers did that in Games 4, 5 and 6, which is exactly why there will be a decisive game here at TD Garden tonight. If Philadelphia finds a way again, it will be the first team since the New York Islanders in 1975 to win a series after losing the first three games...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7044-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7044_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:30:02">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=516426#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>How will elite teams counter Devils' deal for Kovy?</title><description>skater, a great shot. So, there's no doubt that he's going to make this team better. I talked a lot about having one line that is a threat when they're on the ice, but I think we'll be able to get two, which is good, like many other teams." Lemaire's grin is in contrast to some of the scowls around the NHL as teams revamped their plans for wheeling and dealing with the biggest name in the rumor mill...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7044-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7044_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 01:34:23">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=511743#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>U.S. teams to be honored at Fenway</title><description>Bruins and the Philadelphia Flyers, gold medal-winning 1960 U.S. Olympic hockey team members Bob Cleary, Bill Cleary, Dick Rodenhiser  and coach Jack Riley will take the field. Fellow gold medalists Jim Craig, Dave Silk and Jack O'Callahan of the 1980 U.S. Olympic "Miracle on Ice" team also will take part in the tribute to U.S. hockey's two most successful Olympic squads.  Prior to the start...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>