<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7057">web of science</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:24:54" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7057-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7057_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:24:55">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=499020#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>National Academy of Neuropsychology (NAN) and National Athletic Trainers' Association (NATA) team up on campaign to raise concussion awareness</title><description>on affiliated Web sites, including www.nanonline.org, www.nata.org, www.nhl.com and www.nhpla.com and also available, upon request, at a cost of $10 at www.nata.org/brochures.  (VIEW THE VIDEO HERE) "Given the recent advancements in concussion research, education among coaches, parents, athletes, the media, and other influencers is critical," said athletic trainer Kevin Guskiewicz, PhD, ATC, professor...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7057-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7057_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:27:31">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=386711#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Bertuzzi paying immediate dividends for Flames</title><description>to make some changes, tried to work on a few things," Bertuzzi said. "I think the changes we had worked. It's not rocket science. You've got to get it back to our shooters. I tried to crash the net and get the rebounds. We got a couple of them tonight." It's only been 3 games, but Flames coach Mike Keenan has been thrilled with what Bertuzzi has brought to the club -- on and off the ice. "I thought...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7057-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7057_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:32:35">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=383325#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Canada loonie for Habs, Lidstrom gets cut</title><description>eye with a shot puck. He suffered a cut on his face, and was taken to the hospital for X-rays, which revealed a broken nose. The Wings announced the six-time Norris Trophy winner would miss at least the next three preseason games. "He's got a broken nose, but everything is fine," Wings coach Mike Babcock told the team's Web site. "He got hit in the head with a puck, so he wasn't feeling fine and he...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7057-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7057_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 02:37:28">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=370091#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>On-site weather station keeps AMP Energy NHL Winter Classic informed</title><description>ORCHARD PARK, N.Y. -- Matt Becker has set up a weather station in the Italian Alps. He spent a year working at NASA’s Goddard Space Flight Center, once setting up a weather station in the Rio Grande to measure ground water pollution. This week, though, he has brought his science to a whole different stage. This week, Becker, an Associate Professor of Geology at the University at Buffalo...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>