<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7083">I'm on the road again</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:10:13" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7083-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7083_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:10:13">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=714798#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Islanders finish strong, but fail to make 2nd straight trip to playoffs</title><description>to Brooklyn. Brock Nelson, who had 14 goals and 26 points in his first NHL season, will likely have a larger role then and in the future, along with fellow rookie centre Anders Lee. "These kids have played extremely hard," Capuano said Sunday after the Islanders' season-ending win at Buffalo. "I'm proud of what they've done not only in the last month and a half but these last three games on this road trip." ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7083-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7083_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:12:56">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=714075#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Tapped In: Rookie Krug finding Boston to his liking</title><description>. I asked a lot of questions as well. You don’t find that with a lot of locker rooms around the League, especially late and in the playoffs. It was an amazing experience. The entire playoffs went too fast for me, so I’m looking forward to getting it going again this year. KT: You have your first full season under your belt this year. You’ve seen every team. Who is the hardest player to play...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7083-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7083_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:16:07">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=28278#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Sharks' Hertl set to rejoin lineup vs. Avalanche</title><description>and 10 assists in 35 games before being injured. "I'm very excited because it's four months not playing hockey," Hertl said after the Sharks' morning skate. "I'm very happy. I hope it's all good, the knee is OK. I hope I'm ready to play and ready to play in the playoffs." Hertl, 20, has been practicing with the team for weeks and reportedly was cleared by two independent doctors, including...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7083-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7083_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:18:12">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=713602#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Penguins defenseman Letang returning to lineup</title><description>back. Kris has been bugging me for a little while here to return to play. I talked to him on the road trip, talked to him again [Tuesday]. He feels real good on and off the ice, so he'll be back playing this evening. "I'm excited for him because I think the main thing is health-wise he feels good, and everything is trending in the right direction for him short term and long term." Shero said it had...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7083-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7083_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:19:52">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=713100#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Varlamov matches Roy's single-season win mark; tempers flare as Avalanche blank Blues 4-0</title><description>has something to say after every game," coach Ken Hitchcock said of Roy. "So you guys pick up what he wants. I'm worried about my team and the way we played, OK?" Hitchcock did, however, suggest that forward Patrick Bordealeau left his feet on the check that hurt Shattenkirk when his stick was jammed into his face. Hitchcock also mused that he probably should have given rugged Ryan Reaves more ice...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7083-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7083_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:23:21">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=27996#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Martin back in Penguins lineup against Jets</title><description>in the season with a broken tibia and has played 33 games this season. He has two goals and 10 assists. "The doctors said that it was up to me," said Martin, who resumed practicing with his teammates this week. "I said I'm ready." With Martin back in the lineup, the Penguins begin a three-game road trip when they will face the Minnesota Wild on Saturday before playing the Colorado Avalanche on Sunday...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7083-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7083_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:25:45">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=712458#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Gardiner, Maple Leafs hope they can bring their best against Bruins</title><description>TORONTO - In the Boston Bruins, Jake Gardiner sees one of the best teams in the NHL but also one he and the Toronto Maple Leafs should be excited to face with their playoff hopes on the line again. "We think we match up well against Boston," Gardiner said. "I'm just going back from last year in the playoffs. Obviously it didn't end well, but I think we all elevate our game against them. We know...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7083-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7083_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:27:20">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=27878#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Devils' Larsson recalled following injuries on defense</title><description>looking forward to this." Devils coach Peter DeBoer will likely have Larsson paired with former Albany partner Eric Gelinas to open the game. DeBoer will also insert center Jacob Josefson into the lineup for the injured Stephen Gionta (lower body). Gelinas is looking forward to playing alongside Larsson once again. "We were matched up [Monday] in the morning skate so I'm really happy for him...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7083-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7083_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:28:47">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=711498#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Snider Foundation grows game in Philadelphia</title><description>storyteller. Now, though, caught in the part between her graduation from high school and her college years, her train of thought stalls as a flash of realization crosses her face. "I'm just … I'm just noticing now how much effort it took not to give up," she said. Reyes, 21, is tall, lithe and dressed athlete-casual in a West Chester Dri-FIT shirt, thermal black Nike tights, and running shoes. She has...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7083-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7083_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:34:13">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=27811#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Selanne ready for potential final game in Edmonton</title><description>. But at the same time, I'm very happy and thankful that I'm able to play all these years and I have all these memories. It means a lot." Goaltender Jonas Hiller will start for the Ducks against Edmonton. Goalie Ben Scrivens will start for the Oilers. Here are the projected lineups for the Ducks and Oilers: DUCKS Nick Bonino - Ryan Getzlaf - Corey Perry Patrick Maroon - Mathieu Perreault – Teemu Selanne...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>