<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7085">Adam rogers music</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:36:39" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7085-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7085_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:36:39">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=614377#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Elliott's surprising showing leads to All-Star berth</title><description>and may not be ready when the Canes resume Tuesday. Returning -- Dallas' Jamie Benn (appendectomy) took part in All-Star Weekend and will be back in the Stars' lineup when they resume play on Wednesday. … Chicago expects forward Patrick Sharp (wrist) to return to the lineup this week during the Hawks' trip through Western Canada. … New Jersey's Adam Larsson (wrist) and Adam Henrique (groin), both...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7085-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7085_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:38:57">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=564686#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Reading List: Taking a breather</title><description>With Rogers Arena switching for hockey to music for a couple of days (Supertramp on Thursday; Bruno Mars on Friday), the Canucks and Bruins had the first of two days of practice and rest before the Stanley Cup Final resumes Saturday night (8 p.m. ET; NBC, CBC, RDS). Both teams worked out at the University of British Columbia, undoubtedly trying to find ways to generate more goals without...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7085-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7085_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:39:48">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=500748#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Blog: Face-Off Saturday</title><description>1980s hair band will be featured during the first stoppage of the Wings-Blues game. It's like Stockholm is living in 1988. And I'm not making fun. I think it's great. Poison, Warrant, Def Leppard. I think we can all agree that music peaked then, so I'm on board with Sweden wanting to live in the past. It's why I keep all my Little League trophies at my desk at work. 3:13 -- The Canucks get some...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>