<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7091">don't listen to a word i say</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:47:18" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7091-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7091_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:47:19">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=712403#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Over the Boards: Boudreau reflects on historic rally</title><description>way, and when they put their mind to it, they're a good team if they play the way they're capable of playing. The first 35 minutes was a combination of: A) Being as bad as we can play; and B) Boy, was Winnipeg skating? They were really good, quite frankly. The last 25 minutes was: A) When we're physical, look at how much better we are; and B) When we don't turn pucks over, look at how much better we...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7091-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7091_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:50:29">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=651845#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Historic storm produced history for Devils in '87</title><description>to the hockey game on the radio. I go up and down the radio dial and can't find the game anywhere. I don't get to the rink until just before 9 o'clock. The Calgary Flames are there and the players from the home team aren’t. So we waited." Doug Sulliman, Devils forward, game's First Star "What I wasn't ready for was all the abandoned cars that were stuck. I couldn't get on the ramp to go two miles...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7091-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7091_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:54:21">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=690092#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Tapped In: Martin on hitting, TV hosting and fashion</title><description>party. KT: Nice! What did you sing? MM: I can't remember. Something girlie. KT: Must have been a good rookie party then? MM: (laughs) It was. Absolutely. KT: Needless to say we won't be seeing any karaoke videos of you pop up on You Tube anytime soon? MM: No, every time I always start singing, everyone gets mad at me, telling me to shut up. No one really likes my voice too much, so I don't think I...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7091-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7091_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:55:13">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=680158#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Oilers coach Eakins defined by total commitment</title><description>and finishing in Leadville, Colo., Eakins began a journey that would test his body, his mind and his resolve. He finished in just over 11 hours, holding his daughter Emerson's hand as she ran beside his bike for the final few feet to the finish line. "There are so many times when you start negotiating with yourself, like, 'What am I doing? I'm just going to quit,'" Eakins told NHL.com. "But you don't quit...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7091-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7091_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 03:57:57">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=679139#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Over the Boards: Ryan embracing new lifestyle</title><description>, had four straight 30-goal seasons with the Ducks and should get first dibs at playing right wing alongside center Jason Spezza. "My role might change a little, but I don't think my job is going to change a whole lot," Ryan said. "I've been fortunate to play with a playmaking center for a long time, and that seems to be what they have in mind for me again in Ottawa. My role on the ice...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7091-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7091_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:01:23">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=657813#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>What they're saying about the Blackhawks</title><description>in the picture that leads to winning hockey." NBC Sports Network analyst (former Blackhawks forward) Jeremy Roenick: "There is just so much. "I think it's their whole team effort, the way that they work as a group, line after line. They roll four lines and they have constant pressure with four lines for mostly 60 minutes. It's an onslaught. You can even listen to coach [Joel] Quenneville [say], 'Our fourth...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7091-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7091_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:06:35">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=645167#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Emrick to share booth with mentor for ECHL game</title><description>and color man Robbie Irons for the broadcast. According to The News-Sentinel, Emrick and Chase did work a broadcast together in 2000, but never from the same booth while the game was going on. "I don't know what my obligations will be. It may just be spontaneous and that's fine," Emrick said. "Whatever it is will be fun for me. I'm not driving the bus -- I'm just sitting behind the driver." Chase...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7091-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7091_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:10:18">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=618878#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Deadline Diner: Nash deal could be delayed</title><description>television interview, Flames GM Jay Feaster softened his stance a bit during a press conference. That doesn't mean he isn't still looking for deals to be made, though. "I don't want to say we're buyers or sellers. We're looking at all of our options," Feaster told Randy Sportak of the Calgary Sun. "It's about improving our team both short-term and long-term. Right now, as I'm talking to other GMs...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7091-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7091_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:14:04">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=588981#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Capitals back in spotlight with 'Hockey Diaries'</title><description>.mediachameleon.tumblr.com. "It is safe to say we have hundreds of hours of material," Nelson said. "There are the diary recordings, the general media scrums that we record, and then also don't forget that for any game that we feature we go back and listen to all the television play-by-play calls and all the radio play-by-plays calls and log that information to find the best way to paint that picture. We have just piles...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7091-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7091_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:18:35">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=554919#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Binnington benefitting from Stajcer relationship</title><description>Stajcer has been on the sideline. He had surgery on the hip in December and is just starting to get back on the ice. "When you're in the stands as long as I've been you see certain tendencies or certain things, and I'll say something and help him out," Stajcer said. "Jordan and my relationship is really good. If I said anything (critical), I don't think he'd take it the wrong way." Reeds has seen...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>