<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7098">tour moscow</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:47:09" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7098-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7098_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:47:10">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=712816#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Trip by two Canucks lifted curtain to Russia</title><description>winding down, they unexpectedly got to enjoy an infusion of Western culture when musician Billy Joel came to Moscow as part of a historic six-date tour of the Soviet Union. McIlhargey got to attend one of Joel's three Moscow concerts. "It was very unique. They hadn't had a lot of concerts there," McIlhargey said. "When people were starting to stand up and dance, the soldiers were in the aisles making...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7098-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7098_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:51:48">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=648219#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Barkov looks to shine for Finland at World Juniors</title><description>-pound center made history when he connected for the decisive goal in an 8-5 victory against Slovakia in the tournament's quarterfinal round. "It was a great experience and it was nice to score a goal against Slovakia," Barkov told NHL.com. "The best hockey experience ever was that tournament." In his second tour of duty for Finland at the 2013 WJC in Ufa, Russia, Barkov will certainly be a marked...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7098-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7098_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:56:26">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=11058#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>McCoshen enjoying time on and off ice in Russia</title><description>forwards close together, either looking for a quick shot or a drop-pass for a one-timer, and it was a little tough because we didn't want to have two of our defensemen playing so close together. The Russian team also seemed to look for that long stretch quite often. The day before our game, we had practice and then a chance to go sightseeing. It was a four-hour bus tour around Moscow. Our guide spoke...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7098-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7098_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 04:57:18">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=637783#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Malkin bringing trainer back to Moscow</title><description>game, a yacht tour on the Moscow River, and to plenty of exceptional and expensive dinners. "And when I wasn't with them, I was walking around trying to learn things on my own," Kadar said. "I didn't know anything outside of the 'Rocky' movie. It was definitely something a lot different than what I thought it was. It's a beautiful place with so much culture and history." It's also home...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7098-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7098_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:00:27">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=10505#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Voynov, Loktionov take Cup to Russia</title><description>The Stanley Cup began its tour of the world Wednesday, with Los Angeles Kings defenseman Slava Voynov and forward Andrei Loktionov taking the Cup through several Russian cities. Loktionov played just two games during the playoffs and none after the first round. Meanwhile, Voynov's emergence after the Kings dealt Jack Johnson to the Blue Jackets for Jeff Carter was a major reason for Los Angeles...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7098-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7098_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:01:20">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=633778#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Yakupov visits Edmonton for meeting with Oilers</title><description>of the Stanley Cup and other things, it's very interesting and it's great." Yakupov said he didn't bump into any current Oilers. During his visit, Yakupov was scheduled to receive a tour of the city, meet team owner Daryl Katz and the join several managerial members for a nice sit-down dinner. "Every team in the NHL is great, it doesn't matter what team is the team I am going to," Yakupov said. He...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7098-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7098_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:02:30">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=617120#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Outdoor game, shutouts highlight Oddset tourney</title><description>completed Oddset Hockey Games in Stockholm and Helsinki was the third of four segments of this season's Tour. The Karjala Cup Tournament was held in November in Helsinki and Örnsköldsvik, Sweden, with Team Russia finishing first. In December, the Swedes prevailed at the Channel One Cup, held in Moscow with one game in Chomutov, Czech Republic. The final competition, the Czech Hockey Games, will be held...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7098-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7098_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:04:02">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=598665#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Prospect Super Series rosters set</title><description>, the OHL won both games, 4-0 and 2-1, to improve to 16-0 all-time against Russia in the series.   Three OHL players eligible for the 2012 Draft will be participating at the game in Ottawa, including defensemen Cody Cedi (Ottawa 67s) and Slater Koekkoek (Peterborough Petes) and goaltender Andrew D'Agostini (Peterborough Petes).   Team WHL will face the Russians in the fifth and sixth games of the tour...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7098-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7098_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:05:24">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=559166#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>NHL overseas history</title><description>of the League's Original Six franchises, joined the Minnesota North Stars in the fall of 1990 in traveling to the Soviet Union for the "Friendship Tour '90". The Canadiens, who spent part of their training camp in Sweden, joined the North Stars in a similar tour to the 1989 odyssey undertaken by the Capitals and Flames. Again, games were played in Moscow, Leningrad, Kiev and Riga and again they were...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7098-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7098_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:08:21">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=537444#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Only the best draw invites to NHL Player Media Tour</title><description>NEW YORK -- For Henrik Lundqvist, the commute was a breeze. "I can see my balcony," Lundqvist told NHL.com Tuesday morning from the penthouse floor inside the swanky Hudson Hotel on West 58th Street. "So it's easy for me to get here." Physically speaking, yes, it was easy for the New York Rangers goalie to get to the host hotel for the 2010 NHL Player Media Tour, but in reality making...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>