<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7104">How to go from New York to Montreal</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:14:27" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7104-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7104_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:14:28">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=28519#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Plenty of intriguing storylines in first-round series</title><description>at the goals by Lars Eller and Tomas Plekanec for the Montreal Canadiens in their overtime win against the Tampa Bay Lightning. They challenged off the rush and made plays to score. I don't think all the forwards and defensemen were in sync. Overall, that was a theme for me in all of the games Wednesday. There are so many interesting subplots in the first-round series between the New York Rangers...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7104-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7104_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:17:07">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=28470#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Melrose Minute: First-round playoff predictions</title><description>struggled in the playoffs the last two years and that's what this series is all about. If Columbus can rattle him like the New York Islanders did last year, maybe steal a game in Pittsburgh, all of the sudden it's "here we go again." That's the series as far as I'm concerned. If Fleury can prove to his team that he's the goalie that won the Stanley Cup in 2009, Pittsburgh will win this series easily...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7104-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7104_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:18:57">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=714808#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>An NHL season of disappointment across Canada leaves just one playoff team</title><description>the final team eliminated. Change has already come for some clubs and more is on the way in other cities. Flames general manager Jay Feaster, Canucks GM Mike Gillis and Jets coach Claude Noel have already lost their jobs as part of this lost season. And already Vancouver hired Trevor Linden and Toronto hired Brendan Shanahan to oversee what comes next. So how did it all go so wrong? CALGARY FLAMES...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7104-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7104_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:20:58">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=714841#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Rangers' McDonagh healthy, ready to face Flyers</title><description>against the Montreal Canadiens last Saturday, but coach Alain Vigneault decided to rest him one more game in light of New York securing home-ice advantage in the first round. McDonagh skated the morning of the game and took wrist shots from 50 feet, but did not take part in contact drills. All restrictions will be lifted when the Rangers return to practice Tuesday and Wednesday. "These next two days...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7104-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7104_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:23:10">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=714798#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Islanders finish strong, but fail to make 2nd straight trip to playoffs</title><description>watching, but I'm looking forward to getting back to being 100 per cent." The trade of free-agent-to-be Moulson — Tavares' close friend — on Oct. 27 for Thomas Vanek cast a pall over the club. Vanek, also set to be a free agent, was then sent packing to Montreal at the March trade deadline. New York went into a 4-13-2 swoon in November and early December and fell out of contention. The Islanders...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7104-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7104_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:24:55">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=714657#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>The key matchups to watch in first round of 2014 Stanley Cup playoffs</title><description>him run away with the scoring title (and probably also MVP honours), Crosby will again have the weight of a city on his shoulders, especially with Evgeni Malkin coming back from injury. Prediction: Penguins in 5 \--- (2) New York Rangers (45-31-6, 96 points) vs. (3) Philadelphia Flyers (42-30-10) Flyers centre Claude Giroux vs. Rangers goaltender Henrik Lundqvist To get to Lundqvist, Giroux...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7104-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7104_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:26:21">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=713501#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Foundation pays dividends for Avalanche's Varlamov</title><description>DENVER -- Even new Colorado Avalanche coach Patrick Roy wasn't certain what to expect from goalie Semyon Varlamov this season. "There were a lot of question marks, and I think he responded to all the question marks," Roy said. "He worked so hard. He was really determined to turn things around and play with consistency, and that's what he's been doing. He was very determined to make a turn here...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7104-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7104_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:27:22">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=714484#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Lightning, Canadiens find little room for separation</title><description>mate Martin St. Louis in a trade to the New York Rangers affected Stamkos emotionally, which it clearly did, it had little impact on his offensive production. Stamkos finished with 25 goals in 37 games this season. There is perhaps no greater power-play weapon in the League than the Stamkos one-timer from the left faceoff circle, a shot that can change a game at any given moment. But the Lightning...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7104-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7104_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:29:23">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=713927#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>History makes Hershey a great hockey town</title><description>in the world. "The first thing you think of with Hershey is, this is the Montreal Canadiens or the New York Yankees of the American Hockey League," Bears coach Mike Haviland said. "All of the championships and the history and the players and the coaches, it is such an honor and a thrill to be part of that. Then you come here and you get into the community and see the passion and the loyalty of the fans...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7104-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7104_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 05:31:29">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=713981#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>An NHL season of disappointment across Canada leaves just one playoff team</title><description>the final team eliminated. Change has already come for some clubs and more is on the way in other cities. Flames general manager Jay Feaster, Canucks GM Mike Gillis and Jets coach Claude Noel have already lost their jobs as part of this lost season. And already Vancouver hired Trevor Linden and Toronto hired Brendan Shanahan to oversee what comes next. So how did it all go so wrong? CALGARY FLAMES...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>