<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7119">chocolate photo</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:20:00" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7119-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7119_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:20:01">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=713927#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>History makes Hershey a great hockey town</title><description>game. I don't even know what happened. It must have all been instinct, but Eric Fehr scored and the next thing I knew I was jumping on the pile with everyone down by the net. I've got that picture in my house, and I just thought it was a great moment for us. Walton: There is a great photo of Bruce jumping in the air, and I'm talking a full 2 inches off the ice. Fehr: I lost my helmet at the bottom...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7119-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7119_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:22:01">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=697698#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>New generation discovering joys of hockey outdoors</title><description>." That Minnesota tournament, the U.S. Pond Hockey Championships, has been at the forefront of a wave of outdoor tournaments popping up across the continent. "Someone had shown me a photo of this larger pond hockey tournament. I thought, wouldn't it be great to do something like that in Minnesota?" said Fred Haberman, founder of the U.S. Pond Hockey Championships, which is staged every January on Lake Nokomis...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7119-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7119_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:27:09">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=684499#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>NHL partners commence hockey season at 2013 Molson Canadian NHL Face-off in Montreal</title><description>to improve the quality of life of thousands of underprivileged children across the province of Quebec. NHL Network: Sports broadcast enthusiasts can visit the NHL Network Fan Zone, where they will get the chance to have their photo taken at the NHL Network™ broadcast desk. Oh Henry!: Hockey players of all skill levels who visit the Oh Henry! Hunger SHOT Challenge will have the opportunity to showcase...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7119-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7119_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:30:50">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=638810#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Brown enjoys busy day with Lord Stanley</title><description>cars. Jake and Mason, who gained fame for drinking chocolate milk out of the Cup when Brown had it for a stretch in Los Angeles, placed their miniature replica Stanley Cups inside the real one while clad in their Star Wars pajamas. Jake tried to climb into the Cup, something that was allowed in California but not allowed in Ithaca. Jake didn’t quite understand the change in protocol, but Brown...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7119-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7119_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:34:13">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=638834#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Brown uses Stanley Cup to help military families</title><description>ITHACA, N.Y. -- When Dustin Brown finally learned when he'd spend his official day with the Stanley Cup, his first thought wasn't about how he'd like to party with it at local bars. His first thought wasn't about how he'd love have his three sons, Jake, Mason and Cooper, drink chocolate milk from its top, like they did in Los Angeles. His first thought wasn't about all the places he would take...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7119-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7119_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:38:14">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=10778#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Brown brings Cup to honor fallen Marine</title><description>ITHACA, N.Y. -- When Dustin Brown finally learned when he'd spend his official day with the Stanley Cup, his first thought wasn't about how he'd like to party with it at local bars. His first thought wasn't about how he'd love have his three sons, Jake, Mason and Cooper, drink chocolate milk from its top, like they did in Los Angeles. His first thought wasn't about all the places he would take...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7119-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7119_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:41:59">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=634744#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Return of the Kings: Los Angeles' Stanley Cup champions celebrate with parade and rally</title><description>slammed him headfirst into the boards in Game 6, resulting in a five-minute power play in which the Kings scored three goals and essentially wrapped up the Cup. The Stanley Cup has already made an extensive tour of Los Angeles, starting at a Hermosa Beach pub just a few hours after the Kings claimed it. The Cup was in Brown's backyard Tuesday morning, where his two oldest sons drank chocolate milk out...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7119-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7119_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:45:36">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=634743#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>LA Kings celebrate Stanley Cup with parade, rally</title><description>slammed him headfirst into the boards in Game 6, resulting in a five-minute power play in which the Kings scored three goals and essentially wrapped up the Cup. The Stanley Cup has already made an extensive tour of Los Angeles, starting at a Hermosa Beach pub just a few hours after the Kings claimed it. The Cup was in Brown's backyard Tuesday morning, where his two oldest sons drank chocolate milk out...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7119-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7119_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:51:33">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=566690#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>The NHL Awards and Red Carpet Live-Blog</title><description>said, "Well, we hit the Spearmint Rhino two nights ago, but we took off early when I fought the bouncer. Totally wrecked him. After that, we gambled on high stakes monkey knife fights in an underground casino. Oh, we saw Seinfeld too. He's still got it." 6:05 -- Jeff Skinner's red carpet interview was about how thousands of teenage girls love him, how he was a model at a photo shoot, how he gets...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7119-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7119_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 06:55:04">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=506872#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Boston Baked Blog</title><description>into little boys as they took to the Fenway Park ice and reconnected with their inner child -- the one that played outdoor hockey until their toes tingled and their noses stung and the pull of hot chocolate and a roaring fire or a sizzling radiator became just too powerful. Skating on the Fenway ice myself is one of the biggest perks in a job that has its fair share of cool assignments. It is something I...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>