<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7123">raleigh bike</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:01:14" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7123-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7123_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:01:15">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=672981#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Eric Staal says progress slow but sure in knee rehab</title><description>In addition to modeling the new uniforms the Carolina Hurricanes unveiled Tuesday and will wear beginning next season, center Eric Staal also discussed with the media his knee injury that will require a few months to fully heal. "It's coming along -- a slower process than I thought and hoped," Staal, the team's captain, told the Raleigh News &amp; Observer. "Definitely progress from where it was. It...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7123-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7123_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:05:23">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=645859#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>NHL Network's Weekes a student of the game</title><description>for their two seasons of existence. “I loved playing in Greensboro,” he said. “That was my first introduction to the folks in North Carolina, and I still have friends in Greensboro and Raleigh to this day. The people treated me great.” The Best of Times On March 5, 2002, the Canes acquired Weekes from the Tampa Bay Lightning in exchange for forwards Shane Willis and Chris Dingman. Just over a week later...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7123-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7123_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:10:38">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=564787#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Chara has grown into his roles with Bruins</title><description>VANCOUVER -- As the abnormally large guy went past them on a bicycle, people walking along Causeway Street across from TD Garden in Boston craned their necks to follow the cyclist, then turned back to each other with a "Is that really ..." look. Yes, it was Boston Bruins captain Zdeno Chara riding home from practice on an off-day during the Eastern Conference Finals. His bike might have his No...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7123-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7123_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:12:37">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=536954#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Start to Finn-ish with Rosen</title><description>Monday night. Some of the players are riding the exercise bike while others are kicking a soccer ball around, playing that elimination game that I've only seen hockey players play. There is a lot of commotion around the rink today as some figure skaters are here and another junior hockey team. We've got another hour until practice begins. I'll check in later. Oh, and WAKE UP!!! Canes make it a red...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7123-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7123_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:14:35">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=383751#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Gagne returns to ice for Flyers</title><description>out of the Flyers’ first three exhibition games. Gagne said he felt good, but he knew there was only one way to find out just how healthy he really was. The great unknown is how he would respond the first time he took or delivered a hit. “I was feeling good all summer, but we play hockey, we don’t bike or run,” he said. “Until I was playing that first game it was tough to know.” He found out...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7123-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7123_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:16:43">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=381462#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Sign of the times: NHLers of all ages spend their summers training hard</title><description>draft. "We started running track when I was in bantam and started training after that. "Ever since then, all I've been stressed is: 'Try to get in good shape, you've got to be able to keep up with everybody.' I've been trying to do that ever since I was 15 years old." The training methods vary by individual. Brind'Amour likes to get up by 6 a.m. for a bike ride before hitting the gym or going...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>