<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7131">golf games</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:25:07" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7131-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7131_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:25:08">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=713626#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Krejci becomes focal point of Bruins' playoff attack</title><description>(23) during the Bruins run to the Stanley Cup championship. Two years later, Krejci's 17 assists and 26 points were the most among playoff scorers during a run for Boston which ended when the Bruins lost the Stanley Cup Final to the Chicago Blackhawks in six games. As the Bruins open their 2014 postseason, Krejci knows he's raised the bar for what the Bruins and observers expect this spring...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7131-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7131_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:30:09">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=714075#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Tapped In: Rookie Krug finding Boston to his liking</title><description>NHL fans may not have known the name Torey Krug prior to the Stanley Cup Playoffs last spring, but they certainly do now. The Boston Bruins defenseman made his mark after being called up from their American Hockey League team, the Providence Bruins, in the 2013 postseason, when Krug became the first rookie defenseman in the history of the NHL to score four goals in his first five playoff games...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7131-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7131_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:33:42">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=713699#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Prospector Files: Like father, like son for Reinharts</title><description>of my boys have understood that." Sam Reinhart, in his third full season with the Ice, had 36 goals and 105 points in 60 regular-season games this season. He scored 12 power-play goals and two shorthanded goals and finished with a plus-24 rating despite constant double-teams and shadows. Entering play Wednesday he was tied for second in playoff scoring with 17 points (five goals, 12 assists) in eight...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7131-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7131_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:34:50">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=710238#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Prospector Files: USHL draft-eligible All-Star team</title><description>.5, 200-pound versatile forward, No. 39 on NHL Central Scouting's midterm list of the top draft-eligible skaters in North America, has 14 goals, 35 points and a team-leading plus-18 rating in 45 games. Nick Schmaltz, F, Green Bay Gamblers It isn't by accident that Schmaltz has basically followed the same path as his older brother, Jordan Schmaltz. He played for the Under-16 Chicago Mission...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7131-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7131_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:36:02">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=710032#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Eberle scores twice, Fasth with 28 saves as Oilers down Predators 5-1</title><description>EDMONTON - Jordan Eberle had a pair of goals and an assist as the Edmonton Oilers continued to put crimps in other teams' playoff plans, coming away with a 5-1 victory over the Nashville Predators on Tuesday. Sam Gagner, Ryan Nugent-Hopkins and Taylor Hall also scored for the Oilers (25-36-9), who have won two in a row and gone 10-4-3 in their past 17 games, and at least temporarily moved past...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7131-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7131_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:37:29">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=709387#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Giroux in Hart discussion as NHL MVP for leading Flyers' turnaround</title><description>-clinching victory. "He's clutch like that," Flyers linemate Jakub Voracek said. "Not many players have that." Two years later, Giroux is in his second full season as Philadelphia's captain, and perhaps more than any other player in the league his success or lack of it drives his team. Going into this weekend's home-and-home series against the arch-rival Penguins, the Flyers are eight games under .500 when...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7131-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7131_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:38:09">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=708392#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Tapped In: Modano looks back at legacy</title><description>has the talent and is very consistent. We have some pretty good grudge matches. She doesn't give me any strokes, she's very competitive. I don't get any handouts. We love golf; we met on the golf course playing in Florida. It's something we both love doing, waking up, play a little golf, spend our day out there. KT: How is your game these days? MM: It's been really good since hockey got out...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7131-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7131_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:42:11">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=707810#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Prospector Files: OHL draft-eligible All-Star team</title><description>from the OHL eligible for the 2014 Draft: Michael Dal Colle, LW, Oshawa Generals In 63 regular season games as a rookie in 2012-13, the 6-foot-1.5, 179-pound left wing ranked sixth on the Generals with 48 points, including 15 goals, and fifth in plus-minus at plus-19. It was a season in which the versatile left-handed shot earned valuable experience on a line with captain Boone Jenner (Columbus...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7131-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7131_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:43:52">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=706060#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Selanne ends international career with memorable win</title><description>points in 95 games with Finland's senior national team. Selanne also left the rink Saturday night with the game puck, a gift that teammate Olli Jokinen made sure to give him before the Finns left the ice to meet the media. "You got a 43-year-old guy who scores two goals, the way he moves, who knows, maybe he'll be back in four years when he's 47," Jokinen said, laughing. "You never know." Selanne...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7131-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7131_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:46:42">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=704921#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Broten's hockey legacy far exceeds his public profile</title><description>in the winter I go out and feed the horses a little bit, come inside and have some coffee and relax a little bit and just kind of goof around the farm. I kind of just do what I want to do," Broten told NHL.com. "Summers are a lot of mowing and keeping the place looking halfway decent. Golf two or three days a week. That's about it." It's an anonymous existence for a Minnesota hockey legend. In a state...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>