<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7134">history of yoga</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:53:25" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7134-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7134_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:53:26">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=690428#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Super 16: Teams taking stock one month into season</title><description>as the season progresses, and while that might make it harder to win some nights, it also makes it easier to force overtime and collect at least one point later in the season. Points in the standings are important regardless of when a team accrues them. Recent history also suggests that a slow start can be overcome. If someone was looking for a couple of teams not currently in the Super 16 who still...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7134-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7134_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:56:41">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=659064#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>'Razor'-sharp Emery solidified Hawks' goaltending</title><description>by a goaltender to start a season in National Hockey League history, and Emery also holds the record for consecutive wins to start a career -- prevailing in nine straight starts to begin his career with the Ottawa Senators. Emery also improved his record as a Blackhawks goalie to an impressive 16-0-3 in games he's played at United Center. Good luck getting him to take the credit. "It's the team in front of me...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7134-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7134_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 07:59:14">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=621394#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Thomas ready for increased workload with Rask out</title><description>BOSTON -- The 25 straight games he started while flaunting Atlas-like strength in carrying the Boston Bruins to the Stanley Cup championship at the end of last season are an indelible part of team history.                 If Tim Thomas is going to duplicate that massive effort this season, it appears he's going to have to get used to a heavy workload a little earlier than he did before Boston...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7134-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7134_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:02:09">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=389713#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>For Lecavalier, less seems to be more</title><description>Canucks coach Alain Vigneault. "They're plunging. But history says that the stock market, sooner or later, comes back up -- and I have to believe the twins are the same way." King of the crease -- He doesn't take up as much space in goal, but Kings goaltender Jason LaBarbera is covering more of the net than in the past. While recovering from sports hernia surgery in Calgary last summer, the 28-year...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7134-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7134_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:03:49">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=387154#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Hitchcock thinks Sharks have League's best defense</title><description>\-- Kings power forward Dustin Brown has a 72-page manual he followed the last two seasons while training with team strength and conditioning coach Chad Smith. Pulling a weight sled, doing sprints on the track and yoga (yes, yoga) helped him go from 17 goals to 33 last season and could take him to the 40-goal mark this time around. ... Hurricanes GM Jim Rutherford recently remarked that he wants his...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7134-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7134_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:07:07">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=372152#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Despite ouster, reasons for Preds to be proud</title><description>-22-6, 2.90 GAA, .898 save percentage), since traded to St. Louis, struggled to gain his form from the outset, Ellis was there to seize the opportunity and took full advantage. The Saskatchewan native, who was signed from the Dallas Stars at the start of the season, was responsible for the fifth longest shutout streak (233:38) in League history, from the first period against Chicago on March 22 to 3...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>