<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7136">Soccer trick</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:09:58" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7136-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7136_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:09:59">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=701619#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Over the Boards: Sabres' Nolan keeps focus on today</title><description>percentage up to 48.6 after a relatively slow start in the circle. "He came to rookie camp and dominated and unfortunately got a concussion his last day of rookie camp," Tallon said. "He had a hat trick and got hurt the next day. Our goal was to get him healthy and get him down to San Antonio [of the American Hockey League] to get him some experience. But we played him a few games, about 10-12 minutes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7136-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7136_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:13:54">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=687755#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Crosby, MacKinnon making Cole Harbour proud</title><description>at Cole Harbour Place, a resplendent community center complete with an aquatic center featuring three pools and a roof-high slide, a library, areas to lift weights, play racquetball or put on a craft show and fields outside for soccer, baseball and other various sports. And there are the hockey rinks, Scotia 1 and Scotia 2, which are home to hundreds of kids on skates of all ages on a daily basis...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7136-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7136_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:17:34">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=672112#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Justin Williams, Jonathan Quick lead LA Kings past San Jose Sharks 2-1 in Game 7</title><description>it again 2:57 later, taking a cross-ice pass from Anze Kopitar and beating Niemi from short range with a one-timer. Williams had just two assists in the Kings' previous eight playoff games. Niemi kept the Sharks in it with two stunning saves, preventing a natural hat trick by Williams several minutes before stopping Brad Richardson's one-timer. But Quick matched every save, and the Kings preserved...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7136-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7136_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:21:45">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=645386#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Hall of Fame inductees discuss careers at Fan Forum</title><description>enjoy it and don't take the fun out of the game." Sundin, who is a first-time dad to a three-month old, said he thinks kids should be open to playing all kinds of sports and doing all kinds of activities with no restrictions as long as they're having fun. "Let them do what they want -- play soccer, hockey, basketball, whatever it may be," he said. "Enjoy all the different sports. Kids need...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7136-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7136_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:23:43">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=11862#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Quebec's Erne on a scoring rampage</title><description>For Quebec forward Adam Erne, it must feel like he's shooting at a soccer net these days. The Remparts left wing, who earned an A rating in NHL Central Scouting's preliminary rankings of players to watch for the 2013 NHL Draft, continued his hot play with a hat trick Friday in an 8-3 win at the Acadie Bathurst Titan. In his last four games, Erne has eight goals. After scoring six goals in his...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7136-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7136_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:28:16">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=11327#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Top prospect MacKinnon looks to improve even more</title><description>Scotia, the same hometown as Pittsburgh Penguins star center Sidney Crosby. He recently helped lead Team Canada to a gold medal after scoring a hat trick in the championship match against Finland at the Ivan Hlinka Memorial in Slovakia in August. He finished the Hlinka with five goals and six assists in five games. MacKinnon will be maintaining a blog on NHL.com all season leading up to the 2013 NHL...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7136-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7136_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:29:10">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=11113#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Baptiste recaps Sudbury victory over Denmark</title><description>in a circle trying to keep a soccer ball up in the air but your opponents [actually my teammates] try to knock you out of the game with bad passes. The game was outstanding. Toronto Maple Leafs draft pick, Josh Levio [@jleivo17] scored a third period hat trick to push us to a 7-2 victory over the Denmark Under-20 Team. After the game we took the bus to TGI Friday's for another North American style meal...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7136-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7136_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:29:58">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=562071#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Setoguchi beats Couture to the punch</title><description>Sharks forward Devin Setoguchi turned in one of the best offensive performances of the playoffs Wednesday night when he became the first player this postseason to tally a hat trick. The feat in and of itself is an impressive one, but this hat trick was sweeter than most, as the third goal came at 9:21 of overtime, giving the Sharks a 4-3 victory in Game 3 of their Western Conference Semifinal...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7136-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7136_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:32:49">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=541546#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Road to St. Paul blog</title><description>soccer stadium at the World Championships in Gelsenkirchen, Germany. If you're going to the game, you might want to pay special attention to three players who were named 'C Players' to watch in the CCHA by the NHL's Central Scouting Service. A 'C Rating' is designated to a player the Central Scouting is tracking as a potential late-round selection for the 2011 Entry Draft. Those players include...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7136-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7136_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 08:33:54">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=536953#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Taking Stock-holm with Lozo</title><description>," Wallin said. "That's probably the first diving call I had in my whole hockey and soccer careers. I don't know. It's part of the game and it happens. I've got the puck and I've got the advantage behind the net and I'm starting to skate straight up and he pushed my knee forward. If he calls that a dive, it's his call. But I thought it was funny." With each team having a game under their belts, expect...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>