<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7141">Cambridge must do</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:08:40" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7141-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7141_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:08:40">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=525417#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>8 games, 8 days blog</title><description>. Shawn will have all the details here in the 8 Cities in 8 Days Tour blog and will also provide updates on twitter: sroarke_nhl. Saying thank you04.22.10 /12:01 AM ET A change in fortunes04.21.10 / 8:20 PM ET It's amazing how fast things change in a playoff series.Finish line in slight04.21.10 / 4:33 PM ET I love sleep-in days. Who doesn't, right? Well, I must admit Wednesday wasn't a sleep-in day...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7141-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7141_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:12:14">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=508386#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>2010 Bridgestone NHL Winter Classic FAQ</title><description>Answers to frequently asked questions about the 2010 Bridgestone NHL Winter Classic at Boston's Fenway Park. What time will gates open on Jan. 1 for game day? Where are the gate locations and access points at Fenway Park? What is the parking situation on game day -- what lots will be open? How do I get to Fenway Park? Will Yawkey Way be open? What is the Bridgestone NHL Winter Classic ticket...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7141-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7141_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:15:07">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=420667#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Bruins-Hurricanes blog</title><description>goals in the playoffs and Jussi Jokinen is second with 6. "To be honest, it's been that way for a while," Cole told NHL.com. "Really, the longer it goes on, the easier it is to focus on the other things I can do well to make our team successful. For me, it's always been the case where if I'm doing the other things well, the opportunities come to me on the offensive side." Cole, in fact, hasn...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7141-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7141_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:17:05">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=371622#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>The Penalty Box: Playoff intensity from fans</title><description>. \--Melissa, Estes Park, CO Hey CTN, I must apologize for my last submission to the Penalty Box. You see I had a little chip on my shoulder over Avalanche coverage and in blind rage I took it out on you. That was wrong. Quite frankly, right about now, I wish people would stop talking about the Avs since every sentence having anything to do with them right now contains the word "sweep" or "demolition...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7141-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7141_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:21:03">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=371366#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>The Penalty Box: Playoff thoughts</title><description>games, but not a sweep. I know how die-hard the fans in Ottawa are and I must say even the fans in Pittsburgh are now die-hard. Do you think it's reasonable to think that the next series would go five or a full seven games? Consider also that the Penguins will be the most rested team for the next round. Will that hurt them or help them? Thanks for the input and keep it up with your music selections...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7141-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7141_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:23:28">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=370723#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>The Penalty Box: Is Brind'Amour from the future?</title><description>of the season, telling him why they needed to trade him. As fans, we figure someone must be insane for not wanting to win a Stanley Cup. But look at the way Sundin has been treated -- endless rumors in the media, enraged fans and certain hockey figures denouncing him as disloyal. All he wants to do is help his team. Even though the Leafs aren't going anywhere this season, let's not forget what he has done...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7141-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7141_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:25:07">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=370507#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>The Penalty Box: CTN takes some hits</title><description>inquiry by you. CTN must admit that he has only seen Boll play a few times this season. But the young man has left quite an impression upon each viewing. CTN would argue that Boll does not have the body of work to hold up against most of his competition on the Top 20 list. CTN thinks that if this list appears next year, Boll’s candidacy will have a lot more merit. Your 20 biggest hitters list...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7141-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7141_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:27:09">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=370362#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>The Penalty Box: No apples for this teacher</title><description>the last Penalty Box before the All-Star Game feast. And remember, you, too, can be a part of future Penalty Box segments. All you need to do is put your thoughts into an e-mail and fire it off to roarkeblog@nhl.com. Remember to include your name and hometown. CTN looks forward to hearing from you. Enjoy the All-Star Game and we’ll see you back here next week. Hey CTN, Last week’s report cards were...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7141-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7141_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 09:30:34">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=369706#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>The Penalty Box: Who's a Heel?</title><description>not see as much of “Probie” as Red Wings and Western Conference fans might have. For that reason, he did not beat out heavyweights like Clarke Gillies and Chris Nilan that CTN was much more familiar with. *** CTN, For as much as I can appreciate that you would include Nicklas (Lidstrom) on both sides of the ice, surely your current drugs must be failing you in that there is no Forsberg on either squad...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>