<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7165">vice president residence</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:33:41" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7165-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7165_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:33:41">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=585672#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Former Jack Adams winner Ted Nolan hired to coach Latvian national team</title><description>coaching stint with the New York Islanders ended in 2008. He most recently spent two years as vice-president of hockey operations with the AHL's Rochester Americans but longed to get back behind the bench. "I've been sending out resumes here for the last number of years and not getting a phone call back," said Nolan. "Then all of a sudden you get a call from a (national team), which was very humbling...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7165-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7165_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:35:30">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=498617#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Register for chance to buy 2010 Winter Classic tickets</title><description>, the Boston Bruins will give an exclusive first look and the opportunity to pre-order their 2010 Bridgestone/NHL Winter Classic jersey to those present at the annual "State of the Bruins" Town Hall Meeting.  Attending this year's State of the Bruins from the Bruins organization will be Owner Jeremy Jacobs, Executive Vice President Charlie Jacobs, General Manager Peter Chiarelli, Vice President Cam Neely...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7165-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7165_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 12:38:01">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=287614#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Edmonton Oilers president says team looking for new rink or rink upgrade</title><description>,000." Edmonton Northlands has commissioned a report from a U.S. architect on whether Rexall can realistically be upgraded to the size of modern NHL rinks. Andy Huntley, Northlands vice-president, said they expect to get the findings of the report next month and make them public. The feedback so far, he said, is that the lower-bowl sightlines are among the best in the business but that there's not nearly...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>