<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7174">seal team 6</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:59:41" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7174-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7174_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 13:59:42">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=714559#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>NHL Capsules</title><description>had two assists for the Red Wings, who earned the second wild-card spot in the Eastern Conference and will face Boston in the first round of the playoffs. HURRICANES 6, FLYERS 5, SO PHILADELPHIA (AP) — Eric Staal scored twice in regulation and had the only goal in the shootout to lead Carolina over Philadelphia in the regular-season finale. Jeff Skinner added a pair of goals for the Hurricanes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7174-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7174_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:03:00">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=706700#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>While Lundqvist rests, Rangers' Talbot beats Cup champion Chicago in 1st game after break</title><description>players in the crease weren't enough to push it across the line. A video review confirmed the puck never entered the net. In the second, Crawford briefly let a long shot trickle behind him before he quickly reached back to cover it. He then blocked a deflected shot by Nash early in the third to keep the Blackhawks' deficit at one goal, but Nash snapped his team-leading 19th goal past him late to seal...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7174-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7174_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:06:06">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=701691#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Kessel has 2 goals, Reimer stops 35 shots as Maple Leafs win 6th in a row, 5-2, over Avalanche</title><description>and scored again on MacKinnon's high wrist shot at 5:07. It was his 17th goal of the season. Colorado pulled Giguere for an extra skater with 2:56 remaining, but Jay McClement scored into the empty net to seal the win. "We played a decent enough of a hockey game to give ourselves a chance," Carlyle said. "The home team's going to come with a push and we withstood that." NOTES: Toronto RW Joffrey Lupul...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7174-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7174_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:06:52">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=701272#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Ice surface coming along despite high temps in L.A.</title><description>of white base paint and a quarter-inch of seal in the next step of the outdoor rink's installation. The ice markings will be put down Sunday -- with a non-paint product that doesn't bleed -- and the logo will be installed Monday. Behind the team benches, the NHL logo was painted in white on the grass in what normally is shallow center field. The stage planned for right field had not yet been erected...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7174-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7174_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:10:14">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=698403#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>NHL Capsules</title><description>but didn't return. Matt Niskanen cut it to 2-1 for Pittsburgh at 6:58 of the second off a pass from Sidney Crosby. DUCKS 6, SHARKS 3 ANAHEIM, Calif. (AP) — Ryan Getzlaf scored his 20th goal and added two assists, Francois Beauchemin got his first goal of the season, and Anaheim beat San Jose for its 11th victory in 12 games. Nick Bonino and Matt Beleskey each had a goal and an assist, and Jonas...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7174-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7174_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:13:20">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=698400#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>NHL Capsules</title><description>but didn't return. Matt Niskanen cut it to 2-1 for Pittsburgh at 6:58 of the second off a pass from Sidney Crosby. DUCKS 6, SHARKS 3 ANAHEIM, Calif. (AP) — Ryan Getzlaf scored his 20th goal and added two assists, Francois Beauchemin got his first goal of the season, and Anaheim beat San Jose for its 11th victory in 12 games. Nick Bonino and Matt Beleskey each had a goal and an assist, and Jonas...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7174-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7174_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:15:06">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=24504#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Petan scores twice as Canada rallies past Slovakia</title><description>There isn't a player in the Canadian Hockey League who can match the offensive prowess of Nicolas Petan of the Western Hockey League's Portland Winterhawks over the past two seasons. That success has certainly carried over into the 2014 IIHF World Junior Championship as a member of the Canadian National Junior Team. Petan, who has 186 points in the past 103 games to lead all scorers in the CHL...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7174-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7174_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:16:45">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=696428#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Pacioretty, Canadiens' special teams key to 3-1 victory over Coyotes</title><description>for the Canadiens in the final frame. "If you kill a penalty, score a couple of goals, you have a chance to win the game." Montreal's power play is by no means modest. The team entered the game sitting sixth in the league with a success rate of 21.5 per cent. But the Canadiens' special teams were slumping. They had only scored one power-play goal in their previous 21 opportunities. On Tuesday, Montreal (21...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7174-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7174_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:17:32">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=696419#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Max Pacioretty's two third-period goals lift Canadiens over Coyotes 3-1</title><description>. Pacioretty scored the winner for the Canadiens at 13:18 of the third, netting his 13th of the season by shooting the puck intro traffic in front of Smith's goal. The puck ricocheted off defenceman Michael Stone's skate and into the net. Phoenix hasn't won in Montreal since 1996. Boedker got the Coyotes on the board at 6:14 of the first period, banking his own rebound off his skate and into the net...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7174-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7174_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:20:43">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=691682#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Maple Leafs get plenty of chances, can't finish in loss to Sabres</title><description>Kadri, the depleted Leafs struggled against a Sabres team that was energized by wholesale organizational changes this week. This was the first game of the Pat LaFontaine era as president of hockey operations and the return of Ted Nolan, who last coached the Sabres in 1997. Buffalo didn't look like a playoff contender overnight, but there was a noticeable jump in the NHL's last-place team. Marcus...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>