<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7176"> weather in nyc</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:35:55" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7176-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7176_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:35:55">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=702130#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Messier helps bring huge Ice Center to NYC</title><description>with hockey." Today, Wollman Rink has the largest Learn to Skate program in the nation. The city has responded to the thirst for ice with four new seasonal rinks this winter, but due to the volatile weather conditions (it was 65 degrees for three days in mid-December, for example) outdoor ice can be spotty. "There are a lot of seasonals here," Butler said. "But seasonals, mostly outdoor, everything...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7176-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7176_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:38:36">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=627348#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Visitors to Cup fountain encouraged to try tap water</title><description>and the NYC Department of Environmental Protection at a ceremony to celebrate the beginning of the 2012 Stanley Cup Playoffs. On this occasion, the 35-pound Stanley Cup stood in front of the replica where fans will be able to drink. The water provided at the Stanley Cup fountain comes from the pristine Catskill Mountains 100 miles from NYC. NBC Sports, the NHL and NYC Water are providing reusable souvenir...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7176-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7176_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:41:36">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=505793#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Kovalchuk makes trip to NYC with Thrashers</title><description>Kovalchuk didn't accompany the team to New York, he said late Wednesday night that a weather delay before the flight changed the plan -- and that Kovalchuk, given more time to consider how he felt, was on the plane and will see if he feels well enough to play against the Rangers. Kovalchuk presumably will test his foot at the morning skate on Thursday, and perhaps in warm-ups before the game. He...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7176-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7176_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:43:20">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=418680#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Eastern Time Blog - Day 1</title><description>it into any of my copy off of tonight's game, a 4-3 victory in which the Rangers stole home-ice advantage away from the Capitals: MARKUS NASLUND On weathering the Capitals' surges: "Yeah, weather it and we have to do a better job of staying out of the box, myself especially. We can't let them have the seven power plays. That's going to be a big part of it. We know they have talented players and the less...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7176-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7176_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:46:17">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=396885#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Dellapina checks in from Chicago</title><description>beginning to thaw. (Note to my wife, Joy: The boots might not have gone with the business clothes, but they would have been a far better choice.) While the 12 degree Chicago weather was getting to me, Bobby Hull didn't seem to mind. We met him at the Taco Bell on the corner of Clark and Addison - don't worry, DiLo, I got a doggie bag. Upon taking my seat in the big rig (no biggie, since he's a forward...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7176-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7176_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:48:38">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=370598#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Props for Parise; Is Colorado-Detroit dead?</title><description>to the Pocono Mountains of Pennsylvania in 1990 (yes I still commute to NYC everyday). The area is inhabited by many transplants from N.Y., N.J. and Philadelphia. At first, hockey traditions came in with the new residents. Now, hockey interest is waning. We have a hockey club based around our school district boundaries. In spite of early successes (including a Lehigh Valley Scholastic Hockey League Varsity...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7176-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7176_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 14:50:19">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=370451#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>But wait! There's more!</title><description>with different locations and teams. \-- David Stephenson *** The next Winter Classic should be held in Calgary, between the Flames and an American team, such as Tampa Bay or Atlanta. The Calgary hockey market is huge, it has the resources (the football stadium for the CFL’s Calgary Stampeders) and weather to support such an excursion, and it would appeal to both Canadian and American fans, seeing teams from...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>