<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7207">earthquake</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:50:37" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7207-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7207_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:50:38">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=700923#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Sunday Long Read: Roots take hold in California</title><description>landscape revolved around the Lakers, Dodgers, USC football and UCLA basketball. The metaphorical earthquake happened Aug. 9, 1988, when Gretzky, the biggest name in hockey and the sport's most-prolific scorer, was traded to the Kings. "I was in my parents' house in Montreal," said Luc Robitaille, then a 22-year-old left wing and now Kings president of business operations. "My mom can never say no...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7207-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7207_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:52:07">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=604202#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>NHL Powered by Reebok Store 2012 Bridgestone NHL Winter Classic Tickets Sweepstakes Official Rules</title><description>for failure to supply any prize or any part thereof, by reason of any acts of God; any action(s), regulation(s), order(s), or request(s) by any governmental or quasi-governmental entity (whether or not proven to be invalid); equipment failure; terrorist acts; earthquake; war; fire; flood; explosion; unusually severe weather; hurricane; embargo; labor dispute or strike (whether legal or illegal); labor...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7207-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7207_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:56:04">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=599375#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Matt Frattin avoids earthquake after getting called up by Maple Leafs</title><description>TORONTO - Matt Frattin got out just in time. The rookie forward was recalled by the Toronto Maple Leafs on Monday afternoon and boarded a flight out of Oklahoma City a couple hours before his American Hockey League teammates experienced a 4.7-magnitude earthquake. They were quick to let him know what he missed out on. "I got a bunch of texts," Frattin said Tuesday before the Maple Leafs faced...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7207-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7207_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:56:41">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=596924#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Trio makes this golden era for California goalies</title><description>by dynamic team circumstances than their own individual talent -- that I've thrown the stat sheets into the proverbial trashcan. I was tempted to keep things calm and honor Swiss native Hiller by staying neutral and just calling it a tie. Instead, I'm going to honor the Golden State and trigger an opinion earthquake and declare Quick the California King. Why? Because Quick has something Hiller does not...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7207-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7207_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:58:23">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=589993#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Richards joins Rangers mix for season of promise</title><description>NEW YORK (AP) - Since Brad Richards relocated to New York with a big free-agent deal he has endured an earthquake and a hurricane. Those might turn out to be the calm days if he and the Rangers stumble this season. Richards was the big prize available when the NHL shopping season started July 1, and the Rangers landed him with a nine-year, $60 million contract that was reminiscent of their big...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7207-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7207_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 18:59:36">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=589990#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>With Richards in fold, Rangers hope big spending gets them back to Stanley Cup</title><description>NEW YORK, N.Y. - Since Brad Richards relocated to New York with a big free-agent deal, he has endured an earthquake and a hurricane. Those might turn out to be the calm days if he and the Rangers stumble this season. Richards was the big prize available when the NHL shopping season started on July 1, and the Rangers landed him with a nine-year, US$60 million contract that was reminiscent...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7207-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7207_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:03:03">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=589989#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Richards joins Rangers mix for season of promise</title><description>NEW YORK (AP) - Since Brad Richards relocated to New York with a big free-agent deal, he has endured an earthquake and a hurricane. Those might turn out to be the calm days if he and the Rangers stumble this season. Richards was the big prize available when the NHL shopping season started on July 1, and the Rangers landed him with a nine-year, $60 million contract that was reminiscent...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7207-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7207_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:03:43">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=589985#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Richards joins Rangers mix for season of promise</title><description>NEW YORK (AP) - Since Brad Richards relocated to New York with a big free-agent deal, he has endured an earthquake and a hurricane. Those might turn out to be the calm days if he and the Rangers stumble this season. Richards was the big prize available when the NHL shopping season started on July 1, and the Rangers landed him with a nine-year, $60 million contract that was reminiscent...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7207-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7207_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:04:29">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=589250#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Healthy Crosby, Malkin make Pens favorites in East</title><description>with confidence and it's a recipe for success -- a recipe for a championship. HRADEK'S EASTERN CONFERENCE CHAMP Pittsburgh Penguins How well are the Penguins built? They're built so well they were able to withstand the midseason injury losses of Sidney Crosby and Evgeni Malkin and still finish near the very top of the conference. That’s earthquake-proof, my friend! The Penguins were able to withstand those...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7207-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7207_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 19:08:37">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=587810#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Hockey world not immune to travel tragedy</title><description>to tragedies. Baseball Hall of Famer Roberto Clemente lost his life along with three other people Dec. 31, 1972, when his plane plunged into the Atlantic Ocean off the coast of Puerto Rico. Clemente was flying supplies to the victims of an earthquake in Nicaragua. New York Yankees star Thurman Munson died Aug. 2, 1979, when he crashed while practicing takeoffs and landings at an airport in Canton, Ohio...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>