<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7219">honda insight</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:17:18" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7219-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7219_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:17:19">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=713632#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Ducks' Selanne embraces playoffs curtain call</title><description>ANAHEIM – For a few lucky Anaheim Ducks fans, patience paid off after a recent game. More than an hour after Anaheim lost to the Toronto Maple Leafs at Honda Center on March 10, loyal Ducks fans milled about the north side of the building, hoping to get autographs from departing players. Teemu Selanne, the popular veteran forward, stopped and signed, parking close to the loading dock...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7219-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7219_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:21:08">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=702566#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Five Questions: Jets' Maurice finds fast success</title><description>NHL.com's weekly Q&amp;A feature called "Five Questions With ..." runs every Tuesday. We talk to key figures in the game today and ask them questions to gain insight into their lives, careers and the latest news. The latest edition features Winnipeg Jets coach Paul Maurice: He's seven games into his tenure as the coach of the Winnipeg Jets and so far it's been all good for Paul Maurice...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7219-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7219_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:24:27">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=701860#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>'NHL Revealed' packs punch in dramatic first episode</title><description>'s closest friends. They were there to celebrate the birthday of his oldest brother, Claude, but clearly something was missing. Denis Sr. passed away on Sept. 26, 2013. He was 82 years old. "We miss him," Brodeur said. "It's pretty fresh to us that he's gone only three months or so." Brodeur later offered insight into what it has been like for him individually dealing with the loss of his dad. "I still...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7219-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7219_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:25:57">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=25379#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Ducks' Bonino talks amazing home run on NHL Live</title><description>NHL Live with Bill Pidto and E.J. Hradek, at 5 p.m. ET Monday on NHL Network, sets up for a 10-game Tuesday with several special guests. The Anaheim Ducks put a 20-0-2 home record on the line against the Winnipeg Jets and forward Nick Bonino will join the show from the Arena Cam out at Honda Center to talk about their red-hot play. A rivalry renews in the Big Apple as the New York Rangers host...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7219-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7219_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:27:58">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=700499#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Five Questions: Ducks' Boudreau on team success</title><description>NHL.com's weekly Q&amp;A feature called "Five Questions With ..." runs every Tuesday. We talk to key figures in the game today and ask them questions to gain insight into their lives, careers and the latest news. The latest edition features Anaheim Ducks coach Bruce Boudreau: Bruce Boudreau may very well be the envy of the hockey coaching world right now. His Anaheim Ducks are the hottest team...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7219-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7219_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:29:24">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=550905#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>NHL Network has full lineup for All-Star Weekend</title><description>for insight into the picks and to handicap the weekend. Thanks to the new format for choosing sides for the 2011 NHL All-Star Game presented by Discover, it is possible members of the Chicago Blackhawks and Philadelphia Flyers will be teaming up at RBC Center in Raleigh, N.C., just months after battling for the Stanley Cup. NHL Network will have a special guest analyst for All-Star Weekend with plenty...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7219-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7219_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:30:49">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=550755#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Roenick part of NHL Network's All-Star coverage</title><description>. Captains Eric Staal and Nicklas Lidstrom will talk strategy before the draft and the alternate captains will be interviewed afterwards for insight into the picks and to handicap the weekend. NHL Network coverage on Saturday will include a three-hour pregame show leading up to the Honda SuperSkills with interviews from the NHL All-Star Red Carpet Show and Commissioner Gary Bettman’s State of the League...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7219-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7219_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:34:23">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=525403#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Devils vs. Flyers blog</title><description>goalie Martin Brodeur earned his ninth nomination as a Vezina Trophy finalist. I spoke to MSG Network hockey analyst and former goalie Chico Resch and got his insight into Brodeur's nomination. A story on Flyers coach Peter Laviolette and his coaching philosophy is also up on the site. "If I remember, before the Olympics, we were playing our best hockey," Flyers forward Simon Gagne said. "You could...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7219-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7219_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:37:48">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=515066#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>The Road to Vancouver - Part I</title><description>Canada GM Steve Yzerman this week and has some insight nto the status of all of Canada's injured players. \--Shawn P. Roarke Orpik thinks about the what ifs 01.25.2010 / 3:27 p.m. ET Brooks Orpik usually won't shy away from a hit, especially if it can be a game-changer in open ice. That's why Orpik is quietly hoping that in the Olympics, when the Americans are playing either the Russians...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7219-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7219_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-20 20:41:37">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=370522#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Red Wings host Ducks on NBC Sunday</title><description>Wings, 6-3, on Oct. 15 at the Honda Center. The Red Wings took 13 penalties in that game to Anaheim's 11. More recently, the Red Wings posted a hard-fought 2-1 victory Jan. 23 at the Honda Center. The Ducks took 11 penalties that night and the Red Wings had 10. For more insight on the game, NHL.com asked Hockey Hall of Famer Scotty Bowman to break down the two foes. In the interest of full...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>