<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7274">detroit riot</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:13:27" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7274-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7274_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:13:27">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=24119#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Senators preach consistency after being read riot act</title><description>OTTAWA -- Ottawa Senators general manager Bryan Murray read the riot act to his players Wednesday after a 5-2 road loss to the New Jersey Devils. Ottawa fell to 14-16-6 after following a 3-2 overtime win against the St. Louis Blues on Tuesday with the loss to the Devils. It was the seventh straight time the Senators failed to win consecutive games, dating to a season-high three-game winning...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7274-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7274_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:14:35">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=563916#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Sharks GM Wilson is proud -- and disappointed</title><description>the capabilities of doing that, that’s something you can’t have your coaching staff be the ones that to in and read the riot act all the time. There’s a time and place for that, ebbs and flows of a season. You understand that.  But even in playoff series, you have to understand the first game can be a very important game. Do I think we played great in the L.A. series? Not necessarily. Detroit, there’s a history...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7274-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7274_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:17:37">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=536039#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Getting excited about the upcoming season</title><description>) &amp; WSH (Washington Capitals) choke BabcocksFlyHair -- Mickey-isms (Detroit TV analyst Mickey Redmond). Datsyukian dekes. Everything. Reedkaufman -- Seeing how the new-look Hawks are, and the new look SE Hawks (Atlanta Thrashers) are in Georgia. Seeing how the Caps bounce back. Taylor (Hall) &amp; Tyler (Seguin). CrashtheCrease -- If Ovechkin tones his reckless play down any and if he doesn't will he...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7274-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7274_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:18:40">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=507837#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>How the 100-year-old Habs brought together a divided city</title><description>will occasionally drift in to divide the most united congregation. Recent Canadiens captain Saku Koivu drew scorn from local commentators for failing to learn French. Today, the near-total absence of Quebec players on the team is so lamented that even the trade of fourth-liner Guillaume Latendresse triggered polemical debates this week. Then there was the Richard riot. The events of March 17, 1955, are now...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7274-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7274_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:20:25">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=507796#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>How the 100-year-old Habs brought together a divided city</title><description>will occasionally drift in to divide the most united congregation. Recent Canadiens captain Saku Koivu drew scorn from local commentators for failing to learn French. Today, the near-total absence of Quebec players on the team is so lamented that even the trade of fourth-liner Guillaume Latendresse triggered polemical debates this week. Then there was the Richard riot. The events of March 17, 1955, are now...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7274-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7274_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:23:55">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=507795#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>How the 100-year-old Habs brought together a divided city</title><description>will occasionally drift in to divide the most united congregation. Recent Canadiens captain Saku Koivu drew scorn from local commentators for failing to learn French. Today, the near-total absence of Quebec players on the team is so lamented that even the trade of fourth-liner Guillaume Latendresse triggered polemical debates this week. Then there was the Richard riot. The events of March 17, 1955, are now...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7274-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7274_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:26:51">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=413660#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Flames find a way to top Wings</title><description>A few thoughts as we take a breather between hectic days on the NHL schedule and settle in for a pair of games tonight with playoff implications: New Flame lights lamp -- Olli Jokinen scored to open the scoring Thursday night against the Detroit Red Wings. He scored again in the middle of a late-game rally. And when that wasn't enough, one of the newest members of the Calgary Flames had some...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7274-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7274_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:28:40">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=393617#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Mahovlich recalls days of playing in Birmingham</title><description>Frank Mahovlich played for three of hockey's most storied franchises -- the Toronto Maple Leafs, where he was part of four Stanley Cup teams; the Detroit Red Wings, where he played left wing on a line that featured Alex Delvecchio and Gordie Howe, and in Montreal, where he was part of two Stanley Cup teams. But "The Big M" also was part of one of the oddest collections of players ever put...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7274-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7274_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:29:20">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=370795#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>The Penalty Box: Trophy disputes</title><description>the Rookie of the Year, the League MVP and two Norris Trophy-caliber defensemen at his beck and call. That is a lineup that would even make Detroit's Mike Babcock jealous. *** Hey, I just read your article on trophies in the NHL, and I think at least the mention of one potential Calder winner was missing. You mentioned three solid players, no doubt, but what about the rookie who's just been handed...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7274-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7274_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 01:31:53">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=370721#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>The Opening Faceoff: Trophy Tracker</title><description>– and each was based in raw emotion. London's Burning is a pitch perfect take on the bleakness of inner-city life at the time. Train in Vain is catchy country-ish song about the perils of love, London Calling captured despair on so many levels and White Riot was a short, intense call to end political apathy among whites in England. But CTN picked Should I Stay or Should I Go to lead off this week...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>