<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7294">assumption of mary</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:51:19" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7294-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7294_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:51:20">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=545053#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>HBO's '24/7' will change how fans view Crosby, Malkin</title><description>'t want to become the next Rex Ryan. Worse yet, he doesn't want Mary Beth to kick him to the couch.   "I hold my breath," Bylsma told NHL.com, laughing as he spoke in a phone interview from Pittsburgh. "Right now we have a swear jar in the coaches office and you have to put a dollar in there when you swear just to help us be more aware of our language in the meetings. I hate to say right now that I...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7294-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7294_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:55:37">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=410548#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Saturday's Grouped Hockey Results</title><description>St. 3 Trinity Conn. 2 Colby 6 St. Michael's 1 Colgate 2 RPI 1 Connecticut 4 Canisius 3 Connecticut Coll. 9 Mass.-Boston 1 Cornell 5 Union, N.Y. 2 Curry 7 Assumption 2 Fitchburg St. 6 Salve Regina 4 Geneseo St 6 Fredonia St. 5 (OT) Harvard 3 Clarkson 3 tie Hobart 1 Manhattanville 1 Massachusetts 4 Maine 3 Mass.-Dartmouth 4 Johnson &amp; Wales, R.I. 2 Mass.-Lowell 1 Vermont 0 Middlebury 5...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7294-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7294_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 02:59:42">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=408382#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Saturday's Minor and Junior Hockey Results</title><description>Bowdoin 3 (OT) Assumption 3 Stonehill 0 Babson 6 New England Coll. 0 Bentley 4 Holy Cross 1 Brockport 8 Potsdam 6 Buffalo St. 3 Fredonia St. 3 Canisius 2 Army 2 tie Castleton St. 2 S. Maine 0 Clarkson 3 St. Lawrence 1 Colgate 3 Quinnipiac 2 (OT) Connecticut Coll. 5 Wesleyan, Conn. 2 Cortland St. 6 Morrisville 1 Hamilton 3 Colby 1 Hobart 3 Elmira 2 Maine 1 New Hampshire 0 Manhattanville 5...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7294-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7294_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:01:43">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=408381#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Saturday's Minor and Junior Hockey Results</title><description>Bowdoin 3 (OT) Assumption 3 Stonehill 0 Babson 6 New England Coll. 0 Bentley 4 Holy Cross 1 Brockport 8 Potsdam 6 Buffalo St. 3 Fredonia St. 3 Canisius 2 Army 2 tie Castleton St. 2 S. Maine 0 Clarkson 3 St. Lawrence 1 Colgate 3 Quinnipiac 2 (OT) Connecticut Coll. 5 Wesleyan, Conn. 2 Cortland St. 6 Morrisville 1 Hamilton 3 Colby 1 Hobart 3 Elmira 2 Maine 1 New Hampshire 0 Manhattanville 5...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7294-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7294_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:03:54">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=405107#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Weekend Grouped Hockey Results</title><description>American International 1 St. Lawrence 2 Yale 2 Salem St. 1 Amherst 0 S. New Hamsphire 5 Fitchburg St. 4 Trinity Conn. 4 St. Anselm 2 Union, N.Y. 6 Colgate 3 Vermont 4 Northeastern 2 Wentworth Tech 4 Assumption 0 Midwest Adrian 11 Minn.-Crookston 1 Colorado College 4 Wisconsin 3 Concordia Moor. 4 Bethel, Minn. 1 Gustavus 3 St. Thomas, Minn. 2 Lawrence 6 Concordia, Wisc. 3 Marian, Wisc. 6...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7294-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7294_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 03:05:47">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=392582#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Friday's Grouped Hockey Results</title><description>. Lawrence 3 (OT) Elmira 3 Neumann 1 Franklin Pierce 6 Assumption 2 Geneseo St. 7 Potsdam 2 Harvard 5 Clarkson 1 Hobart 4 Lebanon Valley 1 Maine 3 Providence 2 Massachusetts 5 Boston U. 1 Mass.-Lowell 8 New Hampshire 3 Morrisville 5 Oswego St. 5 Northeastern 5 Vermont 3 Plattsburgh 5 Brockport 0 Princeton 4 RPI 1 Quinnipiac 6 Union, N.Y. 3 Ohio St. 4 Robert Morris 0 Midwest Adrian 6...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>