<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7348">map of the united states</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:12:13" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7348-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7348_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:12:14">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=711003#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Choices abound for Central Scouting's No. 1 ranking</title><description>the OHL, WHL, Quebec Major Junior Hockey League, USA-West and USA-East regions, which include all U.S. colleges, prep schools and high schools, and the Canadian junior and midget leagues. Prospects from the United States Hockey League, which includes the United States National Team Development Program, will be included in the USA-West ranks. "The NHL projection factor is always the key component...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7348-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7348_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:14:20">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=705743#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Blackhawks go from afterthoughts to Chicago's kings</title><description>. Soldier Field opened eight years later and is the oldest in the National Football League. Soldier Field recently underwent major renovations, but the building that hosted a fight between Jack Dempsey and Gene Tunney, the 1926 Army-Navy game, and the first Special Olympics Summer Games still stands. United States soccer coach Jurgen Klinsmann scored in three matches for Germany at Soldier Field during...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7348-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7348_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:17:51">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=26100#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Fantasy Spin: Players with value to gain in Sochi</title><description>spike in certain league types as a result. Ryan Callahan (RW, New York Rangers/United States) Yahoo ownership: 42 percent Considering how reliable Callahan has been for category coverage (points, shots, hits, power-play points) in the past, it's alarming to see his fantasy ownership plummet to this degree. Set to be an unrestricted free agent this summer, Callahan has missed 17 games this season due...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7348-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7348_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:20:22">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=703692#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Karlsson confident in Swedes' hopes for gold at Sochi</title><description>one of them," Karlsson said. "We have a lot of guys that have been around for a while and even won in the past. We have some younger guys that have been playing really good lately and we've got solid goaltending, and we should expect nothing else than to go to the gold-medal game." Sweden joins gold-medal favorites Canada, Russia and the United States as those with the most pressure to win...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7348-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7348_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:23:08">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=700923#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Sunday Long Read: Roots take hold in California</title><description>Martin and put on roller-hockey skates at the YMCA in his hometown of Long Beach, Calif. It proved not to be a fleeting interest. He transitioned to ice hockey, made the highly regarded prep team at Shattuck-St. Mary's in Faribault, Minn., and then played for the United States National Team Development Program. He became a 61-goal scorer in the Western Hockey League and made his NHL debut...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7348-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7348_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:26:54">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=693680#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Sunday Long Read: '96 World Cup an American dream</title><description>The clock was ticking and turning into the enemy again as the United States appeared to be moving closer to another would've, could've, maybe should've moment against Canada in a major international event. 3:24, 3:23 … Canada's Claude Lemieux wired the puck around the boards. It went untouched until it reached American Brian Leetch at the left point. 3:22, 3:21 … Leetch settled it and wound...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7348-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7348_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:30:01">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=692557#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Hurricanes' Karmanos a true hockey builder</title><description>the Stanley Cup was also a great moment." What allows Karmanos to appear like an impervious shield at times is his relentless desire to succeed and defy the odds in the toughest of times. It's his astute business acumen and determination that enabled him to build a hockey empire at all levels of the game in the United States for over five decades. "He's a passionate guy and when he decides to do something...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7348-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7348_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:32:46">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=689995#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Heaney was a trailblazer for women's hockey</title><description>. The Goal The world came calling for Geraldine Heaney in 1990 when Ottawa hosted the first IIHF Women's World Hockey Championship. And it was in the championship game against the United States that Heaney scored what forever will be known in the women's game simply as "The Goal." Joining the rush with a world title on the line against the Americans, Heaney made a quick move around the opposing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7348-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7348_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:34:48">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=22167#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Fantasy Spin: Denmark's talent suddenly on the map</title><description>It's no surprise when countries like Canada, the United States, Russia, Sweden, Finland, the Czech Republic and Slovakia produce NHL players that pay dividends in fantasy hockey leagues. But the first month of the 2013-14 season has seen Denmark emerge as a new source of fantasy assets. Coming into this season, no goalie from Denmark had ever played in an NHL game. The country's career points...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7348-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7348_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 10:36:27">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=672859#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Bruins' Bartkowski back in Pittsburgh as pioneer</title><description>competed on a Taibi-coached squad representing Pittsburgh at the heralded Chicago Showcase tournament. Team Pittsburgh won the tournament and put Western Pennsylvania on the hockey map. "We beat Team Minnesota that year. He scored the game-winning goal. Team Minnesota never lost in this thing. Every scout from the [United States Hockey League] was at that game," Taibi said. "Matt was named MVP...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>