<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7402">little johnny</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:38:52" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7402-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7402_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:38:53">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=715381#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Steen gets winner 26 seconds into third OT, Blues knock off Blackhawks 4-3</title><description>in front of a drive by Kris Versteeg with less than two minutes remaining. "Guys like me take pride in blocking shots and doing little details," Lapierre said. Tarasenko was among the best players coming off a 15-game absence because of a broken thumb, tying for the team lead with seven shots. Cracknell tapped in a rebound early in the first to end a scoring drought of 148 minutes, 39 seconds...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7402-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7402_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:41:59">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=28493#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Blackhawks' Kane getting accustomed to knee brace</title><description>," said forward Bryan Bickell, who wears braces on each of his knees. "That's the thing you want to do when you have a knee brace, get used to it and make it part of your own. It [stinks] the first time, but you get used to it." Kane compared getting used to the knee brace to breaking in a new pair of skates or gloves, or adjusting to a new stick. "Obviously you feel it a little bit when you first...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7402-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7402_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:44:50">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=714597#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Cup contenders Blues, Blackhawks clash early</title><description>with seven goals and 41 points. Keith and Seabrook are one of the best tandems in the League, but the second pairing is a separator among the elite for the Blackhawks. Swedish countrymen Niklas Hjalmarsson and Johnny Oduya give Quenneville another shutdown pairing he can employ against opposing top lines. They also get involved offensively by moving the puck, pinching into the offensive zone at times...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7402-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7402_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:47:19">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=714559#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>NHL Capsules</title><description>saves for his first victory with the Canucks. The result of a game that meant very little was overshadowed by a nasty incident late in the second period when Sedin was checked in the numbers by Calgary's Paul Byron and stayed down before being taken off on a stretcher. Byron was assessed a major penalty for boarding and was ejected. The Canucks said in a statement that Sedin was taken in stable...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7402-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7402_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:49:17">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=714553#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Daniel Sedin scores two, leaves on a stretcher as Canucks down Flames in finale</title><description>with the Canucks. The result of a game that meant very little was overshadowed by a nasty incident late in the second period when Daniel Sedin was checked in the numbers by Calgary's Paul Byron and stayed down before being stretchered off. Sedin appeared to be moving his fingers, but there was no immediate update on his status. Byron was assessed a five-minute penalty for boarding and a game misconduct...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7402-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7402_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:50:28">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=714452#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Daniel Sedin scores two, leaves on a stretcher as Canucks down Flames in finale</title><description>with the Canucks. The result of a game that meant very little was overshadowed by a nasty incident late in the second period when Daniel Sedin was checked in the numbers by Calgary's Paul Byron and stayed down before being stretchered off. Sedin appeared to be moving his fingers, but there was no immediate update on his status. Byron was assessed a five-minute penalty for boarding and a game misconduct...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7402-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7402_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:53:33">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=28335#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Boston College duo set to make Flames debut</title><description>." As for expectations, Hartley tried to downplay them, but admitted they are hard to avoid with a nickname like "Johnny Hockey," and having a private jet waiting after the Hobey Baker Award ceremony to hurry Gaudreau and Arnold back to Calgary will do little do quiet it. Craig Conroy, the Flames special assistant to the GM who signed the duo, went over Calgary's systems on the flight from Philadelphia. Hartley had...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7402-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7402_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:55:08">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=714159#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Rookie Hutchinson looking like an NHL goalie as Jets beat Flames 5-3</title><description>Brodie in the chest and caromed past unsuspecting Flames goalie Karri Ramo. The second goal was much nicer. Bryan Little left a nifty drop pass for Kane, who ripped a wrist shot from the top of the face-off circle into the top corner. Ramo had 22 stops to see his record fall to 17-14-4. Notes: Rookie Jets D Jacob Trouba left the game halfway through the first period after a shot from Paul Byron hit...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7402-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7402_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 19:58:45">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=714158#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Paul Postma's first goal of season lifts Winnipeg over Calgary 5-3</title><description>Brodie in the chest and caromed past unsuspecting Flames goalie Karri Ramo. The second goal was much nicer. Bryan Little left a nifty drop pass for Kane, who ripped a wrist shot from the top of the face-off circle into the top corner. Ramo had 22 stops to see his record fall to 17-14-4. Notes: Rookie Jets D Jacob Trouba left the game halfway through the first period after a shot from Paul Byron hit...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7402-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7402_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:01:02">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=713997#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>New power Union, traditional contender Minnesota play for hockey championship</title><description>gave them a 2-1 win over North Dakota. The title game is a classic little guy vs. powerhouse. Union (31-6-4), a small, liberal arts college of 2,220 students, offers no athletic scholarships. Minnesota (28-6-6), one of the country's largest universities with more than 50,000 undergrads, hands out the maximum for hockey of 18. The Dutchmen have never made a final. The Gophers have played in 11...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>