<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7404">kobe bryant</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:03:38" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7404-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7404_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:03:39">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=713927#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>History makes Hershey a great hockey town</title><description>in basketball and wrestling. Wrestler Kurt Angle won the heavyweight state title there in 1987. Los Angeles Lakers star Kobe Bryant won a state title in the building in 1996. Across the parking lot is Hersheypark Stadium, which has hosted the Big 33 Football Classic, a high school all-star game that pits the best players from Pennsylvania against the top talent from another state. At least one player...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7404-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7404_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:06:47">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=11687#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>L.A. Lakers meet the Stanley Cup</title><description>The Stanley Cup was back at the Staples Center on Sunday -- this time for a visit with one of the champion Los Angeles Kings' co-tenants. A number of the NBA's Los Angeles Lakers got up close and personal with the Cup following their preseason loss to Sacramento. Star center Dwight Howard took pictures with the Cup after making his debut with the Lakers. Kobe Bryant merely glanced...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7404-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7404_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:09:21">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=631314#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Coyotes, Kings set for first playoff meeting in West Final</title><description>– including a record five in a row to begin its Conference Quarterfinal vs. Chicago. The Coyotes were outshot in all six games against Chicago and in three of five vs. Nashville. The Stars are Out: Winning has brought out the glitterati in Los Angeles, where Tom Hanks, Matthew Perry, Alyssa Milano, Rachel McAdams, Kurt Russell, Kevin Connolly, Kobe Bryant, David Beckham and Landon Donovan have all shown up...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7404-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7404_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:11:14">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=630876#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Brown, Quick lead LA Kings' sweep of St. Louis with 3-1 win, on to conference finals</title><description>after beating up Nolan in a first-period fight. ... Kobe Bryant, Landon Donovan, Matt Kemp and Andre Ethier all appeared on scoreboard videos pumping up the crowd and urging on the Kings. Bryant, who attended a Kings game late in the season with his daughters, wore a white Kings jersey. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7404-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7404_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:12:21">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=630789#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Brown, Quick lead LA Kings' sweep of St. Louis with 3-1 win, on to conference finals</title><description>before Kopitar slid into the crease and knocked the puck underneath Quick. NOTES: Los Angeles' power play is in a 1-for-37 slump, but the Kings also held St. Louis scoreless on 17 power plays in the series. ... St. Louis' Chris Stewart held his finger to his lips to shush the crowd after beating up Nolan in a first-period fight. ... Kobe Bryant, Landon Donovan, Matt Kemp and Andre Ethier all appeared...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>