<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7405">light therapy</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:14:31" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7405-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7405_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:14:32">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=659057#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Despite long odds, Pronger hopes to play again</title><description>by the stick of the Maple Leafs' Mikhail Grabovski. The injury damaged Pronger's eyesight and both his ocular and vestibular systems, and is one of the causes of his concussion symptoms. "I don't think the eyesight part will [come back]," he said. "The peripheral vision has not come back. My eye is not functioning. … And that makes me dizzy when I do a lot of different things. I get light-headed. That...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7405-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7405_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:15:44">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=590924#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Sobering trip sees Sabres visit wounded veterans</title><description>," Goodrich said as the players moved on to the next room. In a sea of bated breath and misty eyes, there were some light moments shared between the players, the patients and the care providers. Sgt. Paul Zuendel, from Broome County, N.Y., served as a guide for one of the three groups. During one of the first stops, Zuendel made an innocent observation. "I guess hockey players aren't the physical...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7405-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7405_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:17:31">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=552903#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Parise eager to get back into the lineup</title><description>that if it's not where he wants it to be he'll have to shut me down for the season, and that was tough to hear," Parise said. "But we've been doing a lot of good physical therapy and I'm confident that when I do go see him we'll get the green light. But  who knows. I'm not a surgeon." Parise said his drive to play again this season stems from his desire to play in the NHL. It's his job, he loves it and he...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7405-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7405_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:18:09">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=397632#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Central: Hudler becoming more reliable offensively</title><description>, but he told the Post-Dispatch that he's doing light off-ice workouts. He had 2 goals and 13 assists in 11 games, but he hasn't played since Nov. 5. The injury bug struck the Blues again this week when Manny Legace went out with a concussion after being kneed in the head by Anaheim's Ryan Carter. Legace was put on injured reserve Thursday and will sit at least a week. Rookie report -- Sticking...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7405-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7405_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:18:57">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=371090#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>The Penalty Box: Music, Masterton and more</title><description>your favor and how hard it had to fight for its spot. Here are a few suggestions from my list. Feel free to make further suggestions. Queen/Brian May -- Back to Light (for teams like Boston) Dream Theater -- The Silent Men (for teams like Calgary or maybe Nashville) Queen -- Princess of the Universe (for Anaheim, as Cup Defender) Paradise Lost -- Hallowed Land (for the NY Rangers. I like the "You...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>