<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7408">tom cruise</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:24:27" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7408-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7408_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:24:28">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=703814#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Prospector Files: MacKinnon advises 2014 draft class</title><description>of Wall Street" Actor: Tom Cruise Website: Twitter and YouTube Music: "Hakan Hellstrom and Swedish hip-hop." Three you would invite to dinner: LeBron James, Floyd Mayweather, Leonardo DiCaprio Sport (other than hockey): Soccer and skateboarding Breakfast food: "Cereal with milk, a sandwich and O'boy [chocolate drink]. Life's so good when I got that." Superhero: Mr. Incredible \-- Mike G...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7408-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7408_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:25:30">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=672830#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Voynov scores, Quick stops 19 shots as Kings beat Blackhawks 3-1 to trim series deficit to 2-1</title><description>. ... Tom Cruise and Jim Belushi attended the game. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7408-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7408_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:27:24">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=672828#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Kings counter: Voynov, Quick lead LA Kings past Chicago 3-1 in Game 3 of conference finals</title><description>to the Kings lineup after sitting out in favour of Alec Martinez in Game 2. ... Carter went to the dressing room for repairs after Keith's high stick. Chicago RW Patrick Sharp went to the dressing room late in the second period after a big hit from Brown, but he returned to the bench for the third period. ... Tom Cruise and Jim Belushi attended the game. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7408-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7408_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:29:57">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=672112#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Justin Williams, Jonathan Quick lead LA Kings past San Jose Sharks 2-1 in Game 7</title><description>hit in Game 1 by Sharks F Raffi Torres, who was suspended for the rest of the series. Stoll is Los Angeles' third-line centre and a key contributor on penalty-killing and faceoffs. ... The Kings hadn't hosted a Game 7 since Wayne Gretzky had a hat trick to beat the Edmonton Oilers in 1989 at the Forum. ... David and Victoria Beckham attended the game with their children, sitting behind Tom Cruise...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7408-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7408_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:32:41">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=671854#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Quick shuts out Sharks again, and LA Kings surge ahead in series with gritty 3-0 win in Game 5</title><description>injured forwards Marty Havlat and Adam Burish. ... Los Angeles dressed the same lineup as in Game 4, although coach Darryl Sutter shuffled his lines. ... Tom Cruise and producer Jerry Bruckheimer watched the game from seats on the glass. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7408-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7408_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:36:08">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=671671#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Quick shuts out Sharks again, and LA Kings surge ahead in series with gritty 3-0 win in Game 5</title><description>, normally a defenceman, usually played forward. The Sharks are playing without injured forwards Marty Havlat and Adam Burish. ... Los Angeles dressed the same lineup as in Game 4, although coach Darryl Sutter shuffled his lines. ... Tom Cruise and producer Jerry Bruckheimer watched the game from seats on the glass. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7408-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7408_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:37:36">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=569723#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Summer with Stanley 2011 blog</title><description>school has a huge impact on their life, and this is part of my development. The people at the high school, specifically (former hockey coach) Tom Barrow, had a huge impact on the way my career turned out. He would take me to men's league games at 7 o'clock on Sunday mornings. He was trying to teach me patience, not to go so far out of my crease. I think he somewhat failed at that...but he was a great...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>