<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7415">most anticipated games of 2013</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:50:03" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7415-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7415_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:50:04">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=708641#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>After four-year wait, Kuznetsov joins Capitals</title><description>ARLINGTON, Va. -- Ever since the Washington Capitals selected forward Evgeny Kuznetsov at No. 26 in the 2010 NHL Draft, the 21-year-old has taken on an almost mythical aura. As Kuznetsov dazzled in the KHL and at various World Junior Championships, highlights of his most sensational goals and performances were passed around Washington's fan base as if they were folk tales, his burgeoning legend...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7415-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7415_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:52:51">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=704675#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Sweden's hopes lifted with Lundqvist's resurgence</title><description>them on solid footing in the Stanley Cup Playoff race. Now it's Sweden's turn to reap the rewards, starting Wednesday when the long-awaited and highly-anticipated Olympic tournament finally opens with the four teams in Group C scheduled to play. Lundqvist will be in net for Sweden against Jaromir Jagr and his Czech Republic teammates at Bolshoy Ice Dome (noon ET, USA); at the same time Switzerland...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7415-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7415_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:53:52">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=704251#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Group A: U.S., Russia to battle for top spot</title><description>Two gold-medal contenders will battle for an automatic trip to the quarterfinal round with one of the surprise contenders from four years ago and a national team making its first trip to the Olympics in Group A. The United States and Russia will play one of the most anticipated games in the preliminary round of the 2014 Sochi Olympics men's ice hockey tournament Saturday. The Americans open...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7415-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7415_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:55:04">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=702130#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Messier helps bring huge Ice Center to NYC</title><description>On Dec. 10, 2013, the New York City Council approved plans for the Kingsbridge National Ice Center (KNIC) to occupy the Kingsbridge Armory space in the Bronx. The complex, as proposed, will be, upon completion in 2017, the world's largest indoor ice center. The nearly unanimous vote capped three years of efforts by KNIC Partners, led by Kevin Parker, former global head of asset management...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7415-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7415_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:57:16">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=702006#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>CeeLo Green headlines entertainment lineup for 2014 Coors Light NHL Stadium Series at Yankee Stadium</title><description>NEW YORK -- Five-time Grammy Award-winning singer-songwriter-producer CeeLo Green will take the stage at Yankee Stadium during the much-anticipated 2014 Coors Light NHL Stadium Series™ in New York, the National Hockey League announced today. Grammy Award-winning singer-songwriter and actress Michelle Williams, the cast of the Tony and Grammy Award-winning Broadway hit Jersey Boys, Southside...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7415-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7415_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 20:59:09">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=701835#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Prospector Files: Twin engines power Salisbury</title><description>and keeps his game with the puck safe and simple. He moves the puck around effectively in all zones, has a good understanding with positioning and knows to play within his limits." The 6-1, 190-pound right-handed shot anticipated well and moved the puck effectively when on the ice for his team. He has eight goals, 28 points and a plus-19 rating in 43 games as a rookie for the Oil Kings this season...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7415-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7415_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:02:25">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=701501#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>NHL to create fan zone inside Yankee Stadium during 2014 Coors Light NHL Stadium Series</title><description>NEW YORK – The National Hockey League (NHL®) will celebrate the much-anticipated 2014 Coors Light NHL Stadium Series™ outdoor games in New York with a variety of hockey-themed fan attractions within the Great Hall and Concourse of Yankee Stadium when the New York Rangers face off against the New Jersey Devils at 12:30 p.m. ET on Sunday, Jan. 26 and the New York Islanders at 7:30 p.m. ET...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7415-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7415_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:04:38">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=697698#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>New generation discovering joys of hockey outdoors</title><description>among the most anticipated in sports. In the 2013-14 season, the League has given fans more opportunities than ever to participate in these outdoor spectacles. The 2014 Bridgestone NHL Winter Classic between the Toronto Maple Leafs and Red Wings at Michigan Stadium could set a new hockey attendance record. But the outdoor events won't end at the Big House. The Vancouver Canucks will host the Ottawa...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7415-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7415_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:06:28">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=694593#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Super 16: Can Lundqvist remain 'The King'?</title><description>[http://www.anaheimcalling.com/2013/12/3/5165160/takeaways-a-one-line-team-again]. 8\. Pittsburgh Penguins (19-9-1) LW: 10 As the final month of Olympic audition season nears, there are a few players who clearly are generating the most discussion about their worthiness for inclusion on the Canadian entry for the 2014 Sochi Games. On defense, the lightning rod at this point clearly is P.K. Subban...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7415-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7415_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 21:07:25">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=692817#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Sunday Long Read: Sid vs. Ovi has defined generation</title><description>. The following year Crosby scored one of the biggest goals in his Canada's history to secure the gold medal at the 2010 Vancouver Olympics, just a few days removed from his team routing Ovechkin's Russia in stunning fashion in the quarterfinals. In the two years that followed the 2009 postseason showdown, Capitals-Penguins was the most-anticipated rivalry in the League with Crosby and Ovechkin as the dueling...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>