<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7445">marathon training</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:40:55" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7445-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7445_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:40:56">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=705873#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Calgary Flames look to pick up where they left off before Olympic break</title><description>-ice conditioning session. "Today it was quite a marathon," said coach Bob Hartley, who ramped up the pace following a lighter practice Wednesday. "Yesterday was tough. Today was tougher. Tomorrow's going to be tougher but with no gym. We try to obviously get back to our habits, to our details, to our system but at the same time, we know that we were all basically on vacation." After Calgary lost 2-1 at home...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7445-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7445_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:42:45">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=688921#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Rangers return home ready to dig out of early hole</title><description>-to-bottom renovation, the Rangers were forced to contend with a six-week trip that began with training camp in Banff, Alberta, and proceeded through a 3-6-0 start to the season. It's the kind of marathon trip most players go their entire careers without seeing. "The first 10-day trip, we did that four times out west. That we're used to," said forward Derek Dorsett, who experienced the occasional lengthy trip while...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7445-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7445_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:43:37">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=687400#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Sunday Long Read: Tough decision, NHL or juniors</title><description>in 2001. Billington followed a far different developmental path than Sakic after being selected in the 1984 draft by the New Jersey Devils at No. 23. Following training camp in the fall of 1984, Billington was returned to the Belleville Bulls of the Ontario Hockey League. He would join the Devils full-time in 1985-86 as a 19-year-old. The year before joining the Devils, Billington was the most...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7445-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7445_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:46:09">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=20210#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Baertschi hoping to find stride at Flames camp</title><description>a watchful eye on the team's emerging young players in training camp. "The race, the marathon, it's still a short marathon, a few weeks, but the marathon is just starting," Hartley said. "I'm too old to get excited after one day or getting disappointed after one day. It's every day I'm rating the players. I'm looking for consistency, I'm looking for courage, I'm looking for toughness, I'm looking...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7445-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7445_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:49:07">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=680440#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Ian Laperriere completes Ironman competition</title><description>Philadelphia Flyers development coach Ian Laperriere wasn't sure what would happen Sunday, but it ended up being one of the most fulfilling days of his life. The 39-year-old recovered from a fall two weeks ago during training that left him with what felt like a recurrence of the same concussion symptoms that had ended his 16-season NHL playing career to finish his first Ironman, completing...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7445-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7445_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:52:06">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=679139#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Over the Boards: Ryan embracing new lifestyle</title><description>Bobby Ryan recently experienced what life for a star hockey player in Ottawa is all about during a half-day marathon of media commitments, fitness assessments and a youth hockey camp. It was a small sample of what's in store for the newest scoring right wing of the Ottawa Senators, acquired in a trade with the Anaheim Ducks on July 5. "That it has a lot of passion for the game," Ryan told NHL...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7445-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7445_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:53:03">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=672228#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Lucic's improvement has keyed Bruins' run</title><description>WILMINGTON, Mass. -- The Pittsburgh Penguins were in the midst of winning 23 of their last 27 regular-season games and riding a five-game winning streak when they arrived in Boston for a game scheduled for April 19. That contest was postponed a day because of the manhunt for the at-large suspect in the Boston Marathon bombings. It was the end of a trying week in the history of the capital city...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7445-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7445_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:54:38">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=668365#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Canadiens set to begin playoff rivalry with Senators after bounce-back season</title><description>'s tough when you finish in 15th place," defenceman P.K. Subban said Monday. "Some guys are going home right now and some are going to the world championship. "Some are going to start training in another week and a half. We're still playing hockey. We're privileged to do that, but we worked hard to put ourselves in that position and now we'll work hard to keep playing. We know what the ultimate goal is...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7445-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7445_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:55:29">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=650341#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>1994-95 numbers provides some context for '12-13</title><description>The race for the Stanley Cup is going to be a sprint instead of the usual marathon, with teams preparing for a 48-game season instead of the typical 82 games. Since 1941-42, the only other time the season has been this short was 1994-95, when teams also played a 48-game schedule following the end of a work stoppage. With the shorter schedule and teams playing entirely within their conference...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7445-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7445_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:56:22">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=649646#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>GMs prepare for whirlwind start to NHL season</title><description>at different levels of conditioning," Poile said. "That's a little bit of a wild card for not just the Predators but for every team. It is going to be a shortened training camp, and coaches are going to want to do what normally takes about three weeks. It is going to be a sprint versus a marathon this year." McPhee said, "Probably the biggest issue is not having any preseason games. It is one thing to skate...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>