<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7447">running shoes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:58:13" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7447-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7447_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:58:13">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=711498#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Snider Foundation grows game in Philadelphia</title><description>storyteller. Now, though, caught in the part between her graduation from high school and her college years, her train of thought stalls as a flash of realization crosses her face. "I'm just … I'm just noticing now how much effort it took not to give up," she said. Reyes, 21, is tall, lithe and dressed athlete-casual in a West Chester Dri-FIT shirt, thermal black Nike tights, and running shoes. She has...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7447-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7447_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 22:59:21">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=700996#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>He might look fearsome on the ice, but Blue Jackets' Nathan Horton is happy and humble off it</title><description>COLUMBUS, Ohio - It's three hours until the puck drops for the game between the Tampa Bay Lightning and Columbus Blue Jackets. And there, all by himself in the massive arena, is Nathan Horton in a dark T-shirt, shorts and black cross-training shoes, sliding around on the ice and slapping pucks back and forth off the side boards. "I enjoy coming to the rink," he explained later. When the game...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7447-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7447_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:01:41">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=692223#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Tapped In: Thompson talks finding success in Tampa</title><description>: Growing up in Alaska, what were some of the activities you participated in outside of hockey? Nate Thompson: In Alaska, fishing was the big thing. If I wasn’t a hockey player I’d be a fly fisherman. In the winter I actually skied and snowboarded. We also played hockey outside. I really enjoyed playing football. I was a running back and loved playing the game. I did so right up until I left to play...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7447-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7447_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:03:22">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=642006#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Part 2: Rhéaume arrives at Lightning training camp</title><description>to see her and she gave me a pair of shorts, except she was probably a size 0 and I wasn't a size 0. They were jean shorts and I could barely fit in them, they were skin tight on me. And they had T-shirts made for the team that said 'Real men wear black.' So now I'm wearing a 'Real men wear black' T-shirt and skin-tight jean shorts showing up with dress shoes because I didn't have my running shoes...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7447-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7447_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:04:03">http://www.nhl.com/ice/blogpost.htm?id=10175#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Special location for ball-hockey game</title><description>of footwear. Mikhail Grigorenko wore black dress shoes, while Nail Yakupov wore flip flops. "Guys didn't know it was casual," Alex Galchenyuk said. "Mikhail was trying to look good and Yaki [Yakupov] just came from the showers. Guess they didn't know they were playing hockey." There also was the usual good-natured ribbing. Jacob Trouba started the game on the bench, and when the Pittsburgh Ice team...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7447-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7447_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:07:10">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=564170#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>McGuire's 'teammates' remember him fondly</title><description>weather in Saskatchewan," Edwards said, laughing. "He was in dress shoes and dress clothes and his suit jacket. He used to call that thing his horse blanket and he carried that bag that must have weighed 80 pounds. He had everything he owned in that thing, but he never would leave without it." Peter Sullivan, one of Central Scouting's Western Hockey League scouts, said running Central Scouting was like...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7447-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7447_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:09:53">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=549617#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Briere's hot streak leads Flyers to top in the East</title><description>Chris Pronger resumed practice on Friday and could be ready to get back in the lineup as early as Tuesday. Out -- Detroit is running out of goalies. Starter Jimmy Howard went down Friday night after taking a shot in the knee, and backup Chris Osgood is recuperating after undergoing sports hernia surgery earlier in the week. The Wings dressed their AHL goaltenders, Joey MacDonald and Thomas McCollum...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7447-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7447_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:10:35">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=544483#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Thanksgiving Day Special: Players worth thanking</title><description>\-- Price used to drive fantasy owners crazy with talks about his potential every season. We can finally be grateful of taking a flyer on the Habs' netminder this year. Kris Letang, Pittsburgh Penguins -- If not for Byfuglien, Letang would be the talk of the blue line this season. Regardless, Letang, and not Alex Goligoski, has filled Sergei Gonchar's shoes with ease in Pittsburgh. James Neal, Dallas...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7447-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7447_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:11:45">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=536946#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Czech-ing In with Roarke</title><description>. Phoenix's other two scratches will likely be Kyle Turris and Paul Bissonnette. Running with the Tartan Army 10.08.2010 / 6:29 AM ET "Among the Thugs," a definitive look at soccer hooligan culture in England, is one of my favorite books. My personal copy is dog-eared after being read several times. I love anything at all to do with European soccer culture, especially its over-the-top fans. I...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7447-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7447_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:14:26">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=536611#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Traktor Chelyabinsk honors memory of Tertyshny</title><description>remember him as a real quality person and someone who you could tell right away was going to make it in the NHL," recalled former teammate Chris Therien. Tertyshny was dogged in his commitment to earning an NHL job. When the team conducted its preseason fitness testing, he was unaware of what was going on. That morning, wearing no socks and shoes that weren't meant for long-distance running, he followed...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>