<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7448">running shoes boston</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:14:58" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7448-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7448_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:14:59">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=711498#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Snider Foundation grows game in Philadelphia</title><description>storyteller. Now, though, caught in the part between her graduation from high school and her college years, her train of thought stalls as a flash of realization crosses her face. "I'm just … I'm just noticing now how much effort it took not to give up," she said. Reyes, 21, is tall, lithe and dressed athlete-casual in a West Chester Dri-FIT shirt, thermal black Nike tights, and running shoes. She has...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7448-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7448_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:17:10">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=700996#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>He might look fearsome on the ice, but Blue Jackets' Nathan Horton is happy and humble off it</title><description>handles himself," coach Todd Richards said. "You can learn a lot from asking him questions: What was Boston's approach? What did they do?" Far from crazy or greedy, Horton believes he's in a perfect place at a perfect time. "We've got all the right people running this team and the right people in the room. It's going to break out," he said. "That's the fun part. It's a great place to live, a great...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7448-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7448_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:19:34">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=692223#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Tapped In: Thompson talks finding success in Tampa</title><description>: Growing up in Alaska, what were some of the activities you participated in outside of hockey? Nate Thompson: In Alaska, fishing was the big thing. If I wasn’t a hockey player I’d be a fly fisherman. In the winter I actually skied and snowboarded. We also played hockey outside. I really enjoyed playing football. I was a running back and loved playing the game. I did so right up until I left to play...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7448-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7448_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:21:51">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=549617#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Briere's hot streak leads Flyers to top in the East</title><description>points in his last four games. Jordan Staal -- Staal looks like he's finally rounding into form after missing the first three months of the season with injuries. He has 5 points in Pittsburgh's last two games and was the best player on the ice in Saturday's 3-2 win at Boston. Patrice Bergeron -- It was a big week for Boston's leading scorer. He had his first NHL hat trick on Tuesday and put up 7...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7448-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7448_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:24:41">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=544483#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Thanksgiving Day Special: Players worth thanking</title><description>\-- Price used to drive fantasy owners crazy with talks about his potential every season. We can finally be grateful of taking a flyer on the Habs' netminder this year. Kris Letang, Pittsburgh Penguins -- If not for Byfuglien, Letang would be the talk of the blue line this season. Regardless, Letang, and not Alex Goligoski, has filled Sergei Gonchar's shoes with ease in Pittsburgh. James Neal, Dallas...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7448-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7448_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:28:03">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=536946#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Czech-ing In with Roarke</title><description>B's change it up 10.10.2010 / 10:15 AM ET After losing 5-2 Saturday in the first game of this 2010 Compuware NHL Premiere Game series in Prague, the Boston Bruins refused to stand pat. When coach Claude Julien was done tinkering, two different players were in Sunday's roster and several forwards were playing different roles. Goalie Tim Thomas, making his season debut and playing his first...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7448-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7448_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:31:06">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=420671#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Capitals-Penguins blog</title><description>forward. Can the Penguins maintain this emotional level in the next round? Can Crosby continue to play the same way against Boston or Carolina when he doesn't have Ovechkin to drive him? Can Sergei Gonchar's right knee hold up for another round? All those questions will get answered soon enough. We just witnessed some of the most amazing hockey any of us have seen in a very long time. Now...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7448-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7448_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:34:06">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=384725#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Gomez, Drury have taken control of Rangers</title><description>their leadership official at a team dinner Friday night, naming Drury the 26th captain in team history, and Gomez and free-agent signee Markus Naslund alternate captains. Drury shared the captaincy with the Buffalo Sabres prior to signing with the Rangers, and he also captained the Boston University Terriers when they won the 1995 NCAA championship, his high-school hockey team and the Trumbull, Conn., team...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7448-09"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7448_09.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:36:36">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=377416#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Sabres nearing elimination a year after winning regular-season title</title><description>AMHERST, N.Y. (AP) -Dressed in sweats and running shoes, Buffalo Sabres players were hardly noticed in working their way through the crowd of parents and children packing the hallways of a suburban ice rink complex before the team's brief workout Saturday. It was an unusual experience for anyone not to take a second look at a group of athletes who, only a year earlier, had captivated this hockey...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7448-10"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7448_10.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:38:58">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=358550#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Sabres nearing elimination a year after winning regular-season title</title><description>AMHERST, N.Y. (AP) -Dressed in sweats and running shoes, Buffalo Sabres players were hardly noticed in working their way through the crowd of parents and children packing the hallways of a suburban ice rink complex before the team's brief workout Saturday. It was an unusual experience for anyone not to take a second look at a group of athletes who, only a year earlier, had captivated this hockey...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>