<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7457">the music man lyrics</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:50:28" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7457-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7457_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:50:29">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=564011#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Tampa Bay vs. Boston Game 7 live blog</title><description>45 days or so. It is as inspiring today as it was the day I decided it would be my song fot the postseason journey. I know not everybody likes music as heavy as I do, so I thought I would just share some of the lyrics to this song for those of you that won't get around to checking it out. If you don't live for something, You'll die for nothing. Through the best and the worst The struggle...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7457-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7457_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:54:00">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=530619#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>'Chelsea Dagger' has become hit for Hawks' fans</title><description>,000 delirious Hawks fans become engrossed in the "Do, do, do ... do, do, do ..." chorus of a song called "Chelsea Dagger." It's sung by the Fratellis, a relatively obscure Scottish band whose popular song also gained fame for being used in a beer commercial. It's now become synonymous with the Blackhawks -- to the point where people in Chicago subconsciously hum the tune, players know the lyrics and even...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7457-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7457_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:56:46">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=498742#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Armstrong happy to have opportunity</title><description>At age 36, forward Derek Armstrong is at the stage where he can start appreciating some of the more refined things in life. Classical music is not among them. The symphony tune you hear when his cell phone rings is more nuisance than preference. "I don't know how to change it. I'm too old to change it around," he said. "It was on the phone when I got it. I'm 36, man. The young guys on the team...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7457-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7457_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:58:57">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=398672#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Surveying the scene in Toronto</title><description>that serves as background music. The game is at 7 p.m. tonight and I plan to leave in an hour or so to be on hand. I'll check back with you then with all the early news and some more observations. Friday - 10:40AM Well, it appears the weather man was spot on this time. Toronto is getting blasted with a pretty good snowstorm right now. Visibility outside my fourth-floor balcony is only about 500 yards...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7457-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7457_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-21 23:59:53">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=371435#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>The Penalty Box: Disagreeing with CTN</title><description>you Joffrey Lupul).  Keep up the great work! \-- Rob, Gagetown, NB Rob, let CTN first say that CTN loved the compliment. And as far as the switch to country lyrics, CTN is always game to go a little country. As long-time readers will attest, CTN has quite the country bent when it comes to music. So CTN is comfortable in that element, as well. As for your contention that the first round delivered...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7457-06"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7457_06.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:01:10">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=371267#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>The Penalty Box: CTN a global sensation</title><description>, CTN is not the only one. Martin Brodeur, among others, have made this same argument, only far more eloquently. Before CTN departs, though, CTN would be remiss not to issue a shutout for framing your letter in the lyrics from Black Sabbath’s War Pigs, one of the best songs ever recorded. Good work, my man!   The Breakaway...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7457-07"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7457_07.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:02:03">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=370721#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>The Opening Faceoff: Trophy Tracker</title><description>years after they burst on the music scene. In Should I Stay or Should I Go, The Clash perfectly capture the indecision that plague so many people involved in difficult romantic relationships. The lyrics, especially the Spanish-language backing vocals, may have had an element of pithiness, but the plaintiveness of the question remains overwhelming. The Clash had better songs, if not more popular ones...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7457-08"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7457_08.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:03:38">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=369648#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>The Opening Faceoff: Shinny with the stars, Part 2</title><description>around Maybe I'll break hearts And be as fast as you \-- Fast As You, Dwight Yoakam Country music’s Dwight Yoakum clearly knows a little about heartbreak. Fast as You is a look into the heart of a man that has been wronged one too many times by the fairer sex. Yet, it is also a sneak peek into the heart of a hockey fan. A stretch, you say. CTN says think again. Sports are about rooting for someone...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>