<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7459">little johnny jokes</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:06:37" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7459-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7459_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:06:38">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=630630#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>P.J. Stock, Isabelle Brasseur willing to take hits for Depend adult diapers ads</title><description>.S. version of the campaign stars soap actress Lisa Rinna and NFLers DeMarcus Ware, Clay Matthews and Wes Welker). But they agree that most of the jokes are tolerable if it means people are speaking more openly about incontinence. "It's immaturity at the end of the day," Stock said. "Sticks and stones, right?... I have four young kids, how am I supposed to tell them, 'Oh, don't listen to what Johnny...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7459-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7459_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:07:43">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=536953#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Taking Stock-holm with Lozo</title><description>Do the same, but better 10.09.2010 / 9:57 AM ET Even with a 3-2 loss Friday, many of the Blue Jackets players found a lot of good things to take with them from their first game. They all repeated how they felt they had been the better team 5-on-5, and recounted their scoring chances against the Sharks. "It's the little things and bounces that then tipped it for them," said Anton Stralman. "We...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7459-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7459_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:10:39">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=425875#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Viva Las Vegas Awards blog</title><description>English the second time around, making jokes before going through the obligatory list of thank-yous. It was appropriate that one of the presenters was Mike Bossy -- a three-time winner in his own right during a Hall of Fame career, Datsyuk is only the second player to win the Lady Byng four times in a row. Frank Boucher of the Rangers did it from 1928-31, then won three more from 1933-35 -- the NHL...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7459-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7459_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:12:59">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=402156#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Robidas misses his big chance</title><description>blue lines and these hockey faithful kept cheering them on. It was quite a scene. \--Dan Rosen YoungStars speak of SuperSkills invasion plan Jan. 24, 6:16 PM Dan Rosen, NHL.com's Johnny-on-the-Spot, was on the YoungStars bus on the way to the rink this afternoon and he got some exclusive reaction from the YoungStars that are invading tonight's Dodge/NHL SuperSkills. Steven Stamkos is barging his...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7459-05"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7459_05.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:15:02">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=370575#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Dallas goalie Smith a Tragically Hip figure</title><description>ten times better and owns about seven guitars, and even has one that stays on the Stars' charter plane for extended road trips. His road roommate, left wing Brad Winchester, also plays guitar. Smith says the two enjoy jamming together on the road. Not at home, though, as the two need to be apart, Smith jokes. And throughout the years, Smith's love for The Hip has stayed strong. He caught the band...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>