<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<search_results><query id="7460">kobe bryant news</query><engine status="OK" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:17:01" name="NHL" id="FW14-e163"/><snippets><snippet id="FW14-e163-7460-01"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7460_01.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:17:02">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=630876#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Brown, Quick lead LA Kings' sweep of St. Louis with 3-1 win, on to conference finals</title><description>after beating up Nolan in a first-period fight. ... Kobe Bryant, Landon Donovan, Matt Kemp and Andre Ethier all appeared on scoreboard videos pumping up the crowd and urging on the Kings. Bryant, who attended a Kings game late in the season with his daughters, wore a white Kings jersey. ...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7460-02"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7460_02.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:19:21">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=630789#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Brown, Quick lead LA Kings' sweep of St. Louis with 3-1 win, on to conference finals</title><description>before Kopitar slid into the crease and knocked the puck underneath Quick. NOTES: Los Angeles' power play is in a 1-for-37 slump, but the Kings also held St. Louis scoreless on 17 power plays in the series. ... St. Louis' Chris Stewart held his finger to his lips to shush the crowd after beating up Nolan in a first-period fight. ... Kobe Bryant, Landon Donovan, Matt Kemp and Andre Ethier all appeared...</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7460-03"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7460_03.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:21:02">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=616478#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Carey Price, Habs embarrass Leafs with 5-0 win on Mats Sundin night</title><description>'s NHL career ... The Leafs had US$7.5 million in salary in the press box with Colby Armstrong and Mike Komisarek scratched. Both players are alternate captains for the team ... Kessel and Mikhail Grabovski each wore an "A" in their absence ... Travis Moen, Ryan White and Yannick Weber sat out for Montreal ... Los Angeles Lakers star Kobe Bryant was among the announced crowd of 19,685....</description></snippet><snippet id="FW14-e163-7460-04"><link cache="FW14-topics-docs/e163/7460_04.html" timestamp="2014-04-22 00:22:32">http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=567893#&amp;navid=nhl-search</link><title>Free Agent Opening Day Live Blog</title><description>Gretzky and Kobe Bryant selling the virtues of Los Angeles. Now that's bringing in the big guns. 7:45 p.m. The newly named Winnipeg Jets reportedly have made their second signing of the day. Multiple media reports say Tanner Glass will move from Vancouver to Winnipeg after he OK'd a one-year deal worth $750,000. 7:30 p.m. Great job by Shawn Roarke keeping you updated through one of the wildest days...</description></snippet></snippets></search_results>